<Blog>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
     
    
</post>


<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Writing this after teaching you how to extract email addresses from a text document. This gave me an idea about where you stand today and I will adjust my pace and content according to your current knowledge. From your side I would like to see complete dedication and passion to learn a programming language. It will take you atleast three months time to get started learning independantly. In these three months you will have to spend atleast ten hours thinking about programming. And three hours of time you should spend with computers everyday.    What is a function? In C programming language, everything is a function. You need to understand thoroughly about functions and what is involved in writing a function. A function is a set of statements that does a specific operation, something like adding two numbers, printing the values. A function can return a value. For example you can write a function to add two numbers and return the sum. The function for that will look like this ---------- int sum( int a, int b ) {    return a+b; } ----------   What is a function call?   Lets say you want to add 2 and 3. And you there is a function sum in your program. What you need to add 2 and 3 is to make a function call. Lets say this is my program  ---------- void main( void ) { 	sum(2,3); /* I'm making a function call here */ 	sum(5,6); /* etc.. you can call any number of times */ } ----------  Exercise:  Write a program to print sum of two numbers.    What is a function parameter?   Anything that is passed to a function is a function parameter. That is the values inside the brackets (...) are function parameters. In the above example 2,3,5,6 are function parameters.    Why does a function take a parameter?  Assume you want to write a function to print names with some decoration, something like printing *****Name*****.  ---------- void printName() {    printf("*****Dharma*****");	 } --------- Suppose if you want to print your name instead of dharma? How do you do it? How do you write a function that prints any name? For that you need function parameters. We can change printName function to look something like this  --------- void printName( char []name ) /* name is the function parameter */ {    printf("*****%s*****",name); } ---------   Why does a function return a value?    Try to answer this   How do I pass parameters to a function?    Its very simple. for the sum function we have written above, we have to just say sum(2,3); This will make a function call.  Exercise: How do you call printName? What is the function parameter you will be passing?    How do I get the return value from a function?   You get the return value by just assigning it to a variable.  x = sum(2,3);  The return value of the function sum will be in x.    Why do I need to call a function?    I guess you know the answer by yourself.    Misc exercises: ---------- int sum(int x, int y) {    return y; }  x = sum(3,4);  What is the value of x? Try to answer this without trying it on the computer  ---------- int sum( int x, int y ) {    return x - y; }   x = sum(3,4) + sum(5,5);  What is the value of x?  ----------   
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello World Program. This is the first program one wants to learn. But certainly most programmers didn't start it this way. And I believe the best way is to put your hands on the computer and start doing something with it. Read,read,read and try out everything that comes to your mind not the only stuff that are specified in a book. Thats the way to learn programming. Its like a fine art, you need to scribble a lot to get the line right.   Before getting into programming you might want to first familiarize using a computer.  Try to spend atleast three hours a day sitting in front of the computer. In this internet era, you might be captivated to browse the net. But I would strongly advise you to refrain from using internet during the first few weeks of learning. The first few things that you might want to try are browsing the directories, creating a directory,a file. And try to do all these from a command prompt. Learn the commands and learn how commands are executed. Learn about file extensions and the assoicated meanings.     Error Messages . Error messages are the one which teach you the basics. Pay attention to the error messages. Read them carefully and try to understand what you did wrong and understand the reasoning behind the error messages. If you have done something and the error messages went away try to recreate the error message and make sure you have understood the error messages properly. I used to remember all the error messages, when I started learning programming. I would say if you know the meaning of all the error messages then you are an expert. It might be a good idea to read up on all the error messages and understand it before hand, that would save some of your time and frustration.   The first program  -----------------  #include &lt;stdio.h&gt;  void main( void ) {   printf("Hello World!\n"); }  -----------------  When I saw this program for the first time, I was majorly dissatisfied with the number of lines i need to write to get Hello World printed out, as I have coded only in qbasic before. It looked so complex to me, that I could not understand why so many lines of code is required to get Hello World printed out. Understanding the above program to the byte level is not an easy task. My idea is to teach you as much as possible using this example.   You need to know a little bit about what a program and a control flow means. A program has statements one after another. Before start writing a program you should be able to understand the control flow. For now, assume the simplest linear control flow, statements will get executed one after another.     
    
</post>


<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       3.50 I am not in my usual moods today, and slowly this mood becomes my usual mood these days.Sometimes feel like lost the battle with the fate. But i never wanted to have a battle with it, as I always knew i am not strong enough to face it. All i was doing was proper planning and knew exactly how to evade fate and run away from it. But now i got trapped, it is standing in front of me with a huge weapon in hand and with a victorious smile of catching me. There is no way to run away now as i am already in the middle of a fight 4.01         I am writing here to find out ways to come out of the trap and win the fate. Let me elaborate a little bit more about the scenario to get you understand the scene at hand. Lets say life is a game about you reaching a destiny. You are given a life with a set of capabilities and you can gain and lose some of them in due course. Fate is like an unknown it takes any shape and fate cant directly achieve its destiny but it tries to achieve its destiny through other lives. It dictates other lives to follow a path and achieves the destiny it wants. 4.16         I didn't know when fate started playing the game but I know for sure when it started making the important moves. In fact if you look at it the initial dealings with fate are really good but slowly I am realising i am tending to reach a place where i never wanted to be. Its not under my will, infact i dont have any will, i have fully surrendered my will and blinding following the path dictated by my fate. To be specific, when i was a kid all i wanted to do was topping the class, slowly as i grew up i wanted to be a scientist doing some research. 4.27 When i was in 12th grade thats when fate started dictating my life,was focussed mainly on getting a seat in a good college. Fate showed that this is the way to earn money! Also I dont think i was left with any other choice. May be i should have taken up medicine, but i was very specific about earning a lot of money in a short time and made this conscious choice. That was the trap, I didn't give it a thought that money alone wont take me to my 4.52 destiny, its just a weapon. Four years of college, thought everything is in place and couldn't foresee any hurdle to the destiny, closed my eyes,brains,senses,everything you could think off and just waited for time to let me out. Those days turned out to be the sorrowful days of my life which let the fate make its own moves without my intervention. At the end of four years the fate has done its job well. Came out of the college, hard work is something i lost touch with, i slowly acquired the habbit of not listening, gradually stopped using my brain completely. For the past three years,I had the energy to fight against the fate to reach my destiny but with a scattered mind. Nothing succeeded.               Finally, I am lying fully wounded,with a bleeding body and with a mind resisting to think positively. Have no clue about my destiny. Shall i continue the path of fate? hoping that i have a good fate. Open a pencil manufacturing shop in madras? Run away to the village and teach the kids? Try again and reach for my old destiny?   5.33     
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      10:57 After an year long battle with the builders,brokers,bankers,even bus drivers, electricians, carpenters, more importantly vastu lovers i turned my weird imaginations of building a house into reality. Thanks a ton for all the people who hindered but still helped. I have been waiting for this day to come. Wanted to ride my bike on the mount road. Started the day like this, took my bike and my brother to sit and give me some company. Unfortunately my girl friend was not in town. To be honest i dont really know which town she is currently in :) ok, lets leave that topic, i dont want to digress too much and tell you all about my girl friend seeking stories. I was driving really safe and reached the life style at alwarpet. This used to be the meeting place with my architect, who actually turned my house from nothing to everything that is there today. Didn't have any plans of buying anything, generally spent some four hours trying out all the funky shirts that don't fit my personality. First tried one 11.11 no sleves shirt and looked into the mirror, hmm.. everything fit well except the big tummy.. if you are a girl reading this i am just kidding! for others beleive me the mirror reflection was flawed. I tried all kinds of weird dresses and finally came to a conclusion that its not the fault with the shirts that i am unable to choose but with my close friend dharma's structure. Went to the coffee shop qwiki's, inside the lifestype and had a caffe latte. Finally chose one sports pants and walked out.    Got a call from home. "Where are you? when are you coming back?" - `me at my friends place, would be coming in another one hour' - My parents are new to the city and have high confidence in me screwing up things when i go out alone. They are literally scared now. 11:21 Then went to my friends place and met my old college days roomates.    Parked my bike and went inside globus in T Nagar thinking of getting a shirt for my brother. Shopped a couple of things and got a bill for 2000 and a gift voucher free for 1000 rupees. I couldn't beleive what they were telling me. They said you can purchase gold for 1000 bucks for free. Went to the diamond shop and chose one for my girl friend. But couldn't buy it as i really dont know where she is! I'm getting senti :) Finally picked one ring for my mom and left the place. Its .15 carat diamond in white gold!   Now comes the most exciting part of the day. Came outside and i saw it raining! Raining in chennai is like seeing the diamond ring of solar eclipse. Convinced my brother and we went into the rain! This is my first drive in mountroad ever in a bike, it felt really awesome. I forgot all the worries i had. felt like being in heaven. felt the city. felt like a city guy for the first time, eventhough i spent four years in college here. In city you have enough things to do but it does cost a little too much. time just flies like anything. the days in my village are totally different. All i do is go to the balcony and watch the trees. When it gets close to evening, take my bicycle and go to the fields and watch the greenary more specifically trees,i like watching them, till the sun sets in dark. 11.39    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        10:28  Managed to get a ticket and watch the movie on the second day in a good theatre. But it costed a bit high though, 150 bucks! more or less a carpenter's daily wage.   I wouldn't say its an awesome movie, neither i would say its just yet another kollywood film, not because there were awesome guys like Mani Rathnam, A R Rehman, Sujatha backing the film. 10.34    The movie starts like this, a not so serious car chase and an unexpected shooting scene. This is supposed to be the scene where all the three characters in the movie meet for the first time. I liked the way the director has chosen to tell the story. Then he takes us one month back and tells what happens in each one of those three guys life. First comes madhavan, an amorous*,brawny,sternheaded,little psychopathic rowdy who does anything that makes sense at the moment. He has a beautiful wife,meera jasmin, i dont know what made her marry this guy, and  for some unknown reasons she has very strong liking for this guy, eventhough often/almost always beaten up by this guy everyday. There are handful of scenes which shows their love, i wouldn't call it as love, may be lust, better this way love in meera jasmin's and lust in madhavan's heart. I think mani has little overdone in showing madhavan's amorousness pissing off some orthodox audience like me ;) The scenes where madhavan lifts her and walks slowy is something touching your heart. And the rest is all some usual stuff and finally madhavan takes the job of killing surya.     Next episode is about surya. surya is a brilliant omnipotent young guy who instigates the college kids to jump into politics and try to reform the country. There is this villain bharathi raja, who often meets surya for some cooked up reasons. There is a girl from delhi who has again a strong love for surya. Their love doesn't go well with the story, its just made for compensating the lack of comedy track and to introduce some song sequences. madhavan meets surya while surya teaching his friends how to do the soda bottle throw-hit game. You got to throw one bottle and hit it in air with another one. Its nice actually, they took it much more realistic. Surya is supposed to be some geekish guy, its funny that he is so geekish he talks about the equations which try to explain the mysteries of universe with his fellow college students in a lock-up, and talks about gene sequences with his mom during dinner. I couldn't understand any of those, i'm sure its sujatha who is talking from behind the scene. Then there are some usual stuff showing the power of the students, etc. Finally surya gets shot by madhavan near Napier bridge.    Next episode is for the freaky,funky,city teens. Siddarth comes as an young, funky engineering student. A typical SRM/SVCE dude. Claims 42 and a half have fallen in love with him before. This episode didn't meet my expectations, didn't have the surge of youthfullness in it. Looks like there was not much attention paid in depicting this part of the story. I liked the scene where siddarth's younger brother switches off the TV when he gets scolding from his father. Just to tell something about siddarth, he is a college grad who wants to go to USA and settle down there. Then there is some usual masala about how girls go behind him and how trisha falls in love with him. Finally sidarth meets surya accidentally just before he was shot by madhavan.     The rest is the story that you might want to watch in the theatre, i am not writing it here.     The last few minutes touched my heart. Felt like the whole movie was made just to give meaning and life to the last few minutes. Some more addons. Places where madhavan just shoots people without hesitation is something gory to watch. definitely deserving an A certificate.The suspense of madhavan turning to be a good person, keeps the movie going. One more good thing about the movie is you could identify the locations in the movie and relate it to real life. Places like Napier bridge,Mayajal,where i watched this movie!,NIFT, guess trisha's hostel is NIFT, and the park hotel pub, i have been there! There are lots of humming,and really good humming,similar to the popular song in Kaka kaka. may be kaka kaka effect. 11.43     Overall i would say if you are an adult city guy/girl and not a brahmin girl* (not hinting at someone i know for the past 8 years) brought up in a really orthodox way you may want to watch it! Others, it a big NO!     11.56      
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Living objects are objects that are able to react to more than one universe.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "For heaven's sake I dont want to meet you again"  - This is what I heard last from my friend. Girls are one of my fascinations may be the biggest driving force behind all my actions. But, there are only a handful of girls whom I liked and surprising they all have some common traits. Its 1986, I was in second grade, and I found my first crush, Vijay Priya. She was from delhi, extremely cute and intelligent. I never talked a word to her. Art, its actually a skill i have by birth but i never had any strong desire or passion to pursue it fulltime. It was when I was in third grade I remember doing my first sketch, a ship. Science, its the magnets and the paper arrows that always filled my thoughts those days. When I was in third, I wanted to build a flying paper arrow with a sand engine! These are the three channels of thoughts all my mind is made up of.     Its Nirmala, she joined my class in fourth grade. Not all that smart but was number four in our class. She was little short and very friendly and I talked to her a lot. I used to ask her to come to school on holidays and played with her. It was a little mature friendship, we used to participate in competitions together and win prizes. I became a full time artist when I was in fifth grade. Made a lot of sketches, and used to give it to friends. Used to take photos of my friends in paper camera and give them a sketch of their face. Started using water colours and found some cool techniques to do it well. Cartoons were my favourite. Maths became my favourite subject and I started putting a lot of enthu in it.     Ambika was my class topper in fifth standard. I started getting weird from here on. Looks funny, I wanted to marry her. I did so many things to talk to her. But dont remember any serious conversation with her. Went to hindi classes as she was going, and I was desperate to talk with her. Put fight and participated in a play with her. She was an angel and I was a shepherd! Sadly, I had only one scene acting with her. I moved to a different school the next year. Hoped to meet her in some interschool competitions but couldn't. One fine day, I heard that she is going around with a friend of mine and she finally got married to him in 1996, early marriage. Everyone knows about my paintings these days. Tried my first self portrait in sixth grade, but found it hard to draw it small, I drew it as big as I saw it in the mirror. Used to do a lot of simple experiments at home, mainly involving light, mirrors and lens.    I met vanitha in a hindi class. she was in seventh grade and i was in nineth. The very first day I met her, she came straight to me and started talking incessantly. She is also from delhi, little taller than me, fat and intelligent. We started talking and we talked everyday some four hours and it continued for four years. She was one girl who liked me a lot, and talked about me with her friends. I did lots of paintings for her, but never gave one to her. Its all still with me. She used to write poems and she even wrote a poem about me once and gave it to me. I kept it with me till my final year in college, but finally decided to lose it, I put it inside a library book and returned the book. Its nice, I used to threaten her that I wont come to hindi classes anymore and she used to tell me that she was coming only to talk with me. She convinced me to continue the classes. We were very competitive, she came once zonal first and I was second. I liked her and wanted to propose, scheduled a time with her and I called her out and said  'don't talk to me' . She was shocked, i was also shocked as this is not what I wanted to tell her and I couldn't tell her that I liked her. After few months we were once caught up in a rain alone, I went and talked with her, she blasted me and wrote the poem about me the next day. Obviously the poem was about what she didn't like about me. In the few months i didn't talk with her, i did a painting and gave her a copy of it through her friend. On the last exam day,actually the last few days i was in touch with her, she got the painting and showed it to me that she still had it with her. I had to stop going to the hindi classes that means stopped meeting her too. Soon, became a good portraiter. I did a portrait of my hindi teacher and gave it to him. That was my first small portrait in water colour. Astronomy got somehow into my mind. Designed a telescope to view moon in three dimension, but it didn't work out. Later, I joined the college in Madras and wrote her a big letter. Days gone, weeks gone, no reply from her. I fell sick and took a month break. When I returned, I got a reply from her ending with  "your loving sister, vanitha" .      
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        kuppan.dharma@g*.com would be my new email address. Thanks a lot to Anand Swaminathan, my junior in college and work. To be honest we are not all that close in college or work. We maintained only a gentle relationship of sharing hi's and going out in groups. Never had any serious friendship. But Anand put me in an elated state today by gifting a gmail account to me. Thanks a lot Anand! 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am not a homo economicus who tries to put everything under a common denominator, neither an ardent fan or follower of economic principles. In fact I was terribly scared about the economic courses i took in my school. Still remember the day i went and begged for marks from my economics teacher, I got something like 6 out of 25 and was last but one in the class. I was really scared about failing the course but something magical happened and everyone in the class passed including myself. This is purely accidental that i got hold of this book and started reading.    But this book has changed the way i looked at the world. Clarified some of my confusions and has given me a complete idea of a well defined framework which i could use to make decisions as a human in a society. Helped me understand my role and responsibility as an individual in the society    I had some strange ideas about bringing up my kid. I always felt like I am a generation behind compared to my fellow friends as I am a quasi-villager. So, decided that i will feel* like a rich dad's kid and live a life like one. I started thinking all my luxuries as necessities, thinking that it will cut down the generation gap. If you are an old friend of mine you might have wondered why I abandoned my cycle, slippers and old clothes and got suddenly a most expensive bike, a new wardrobe of TShirts and Jeans, etc. At the same time I always dream about becoming part of the village where I started my life and teach them all the things I learnt. But I could never connect my both thoughts as they are apparently contradicting. I was following a mix of them, but one fine day I dropped my dream and started following the materialistic thought. He claims that in this materialistic world, luxuries of one generation becoming necessities of the next generation is a sure way of depleting the resources faster and could be totally avoided. Through a series of essays he convinced me that i should follow up on my dream.    I have never worried about the human race in my day to day life! Have you ever? I never thought i am part of a society which digs its own graveyard. He takes the simple resource, the land resource and beautifully portrays the threat of depletion of land resource which could potentially wipe out living beings from earth. Human beings are the only one who work against the nature while other animals seem to go well with nature. What do we do wrong? I dont have an answer. After having read this chapter, everytime I go in a plane and see a city from top, I feel the devastating effect done by humans to the surface of earth.    Rest he talks about Nuclear Energy,Intermediate Technology, Unemployment problem in India, Socialism, Ownership, Buddhist economy and so on. All of them are interesting. Its a must read for everyone who aspires to understand and make some meaningful contribution to the society he lives in.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Is it the end of everything? Trying hard to not accept the reality. I know god is with me, and I beleive he knows exactly what to give and what to take from me. But I dont understand why he took you away from my life. I was like a dead tree before meeting you. After few days of in touch with you I saw some leaves coming out of my dry bark. Now, its withering off. Did you leave me for ever?      
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyday I see this sign board on my way to office and laugh at it. "Way to NIMHANS",thats what it reads. Finally decided to go to NIMHANS and consult with a doctor, hmm, is it bad to tell it open that i am slightly mad? But these days i was confused about whether i am totally mad or slightly mad. Its the degree i wasn't sure of, and wanted to check it up. Thought they will have some psycometric tests to judge my degree of madness. It was just a short meeting, she, yea the doctor was a girl, she asked me questions like, "do you feel shy talking with girls?", I said "not these days". And she asked some typical questions like "do you smoke,drink?" etc,etc. I was trying hard to make her understand that i am seriously mad, but nothing convinced her that i am mad. She finally said I just have some problem of expressing the feelings and asked me to speak out things with people. She finally said I'm totally NORMAL!   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I started like this, went to an ATM and took two thousand rupees. Made up my mind that i am going to do it whatever I might end up with. Parked the bike at the Brigade road-Residency road junction, and started walking straight to the shopping mall at the end of Brigade road. My heart started beating little overspeed than normal and started rethinking about whether i should do it or not,i had only a very little time left to decide. Finally decided that i am going to do it anyway. By this time I have crossed the road and reached the mall. This is all I wanted to tell the shopkeeper "I want to dye my hair brown".   Entered the mall and to my disappointment, I could read only "Dockers" in the place where the saloon was there. Looks like he ran out of business, Bad time I need to find a different saloon to get my hair dyed. Walked into the brigade road looking for a saloon. Found a men's beauty parlour hoarding in fifth Avenue shopping complex entrance. Went inside and started searching for the shop hoping to find a decent one. A shop in one of the corners in the third floor read XYZ men's parlour, fully air conditioned. Went in and told "I want to dye my hair brown". He gave me a catalog of hair colors and I chose a dark brown color. He told me politely "It would cost you one thousand and fifty rupees sir", I said "its ok" and the process started. After two hours I came out and looked exactly like this!       
     
    
</post>


</Blog>