<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         It's going to be a beautiful Memorial Day....spent driving the bev-cart. Blah. I always end up working the damn holidays. That place is going to miss me when I quit. And that won't be too much longer I tell ya. Anyhow, I guess when I get off work, around 5, Jeff and I are going to go over to Rick and Diems for some BBQ. Diem makes good food too so I'm all about it. Yesterday Jeff and I went over to a party in DeLand that my cousin was having with some of his friends. I wouldn't really call it a party. There were like 10 of them at the most and they were cooking and drinking. You had to sit outside b/c it was cooler outside than it was in their house. No kidding! I couldn't live in a place like that. Their landlord won't install an air conditioner for them. I'd move. I only went to the party b/c Bryan has been inviting me to hang out for a while now, and I'd always have some kind of excuse not too, but this time I had nothing. We stayed for a couple hours. It wasn't too bad. I ended up knowing one of the girls. Her name is Laura Ray but she goes by her middle name now, Lane. Well I'm rambling and I'm going to stop so I can get dressed for work. Yay. I hope everyone has a great Memorial Day!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thinking about going to the beach today, but having to think really hard about whether or not I want to fight all those people for a parking spot. It's going to be insanely crowded, I'm sure of it. Probably just getting to the beach will take me forever! Maybe I should just wait until next weekend and lay out by the pool instead. Yeah. I forgot this was Memorial Day Weekend until yesterday. I have to work it anyways. Back in the day I used to go to Juniper Spring with my best friend and her family. It's a 7 mile canoe run. We used to have a blast. Ahh...the good ol' days. They probably still go, but I haven't hung out with Emily in  FOREVER.  I miss her. Well I have nothing exciting to write about today. I think I'm going to just hang out by the pool and enjoy the nice weather. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jeff's been working a LOT these past couple of days. Looks like the whole month of June will be the same way. This is a great thing though. He started his own business back in January. He builds fences for a living. He just landed a 26,000 foot job, which is what he'll be doing for all of June. He'll make great money with that job too, even though he's got practically all of it spent already. He just bought a new truck and tractor, and now he wants a new trailer and 4-wheeler. Go figure. I should be understading and stuff about how he works ALL day out in the hot sun and comes home just to eat and go to bed and do it all over again. But, I'm getting kind of frustrated. I don't know. It's like we don't ever get to do anything fun anymore b/c he's either too tired or we don't need to spend the money on stuff like that right now. I know he's trying real hard to make all this money so that we can build a nice life together.....but..... I guess what I'm trying to say is that I'm 23 and I feel like I'm 40. I'm kinda getting resentful of all the time he spends at work. I want  me  time. Or I at least want him to aknowledge me. Like bring me flowers once in a blue moon or  something!  Sigh. I feel like I'm trying to express my feelings but I'm not making any kind of sense. Am I being selfish? Am I making sense?
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cheerleading. Probably makes you think of the movie Bring it On, huh? Lol. Actually it's not too far off. We would start try-outs for the different squads at the end of the year. We would teach a chant, a cheer, a dance, and then you would have to show some sort of gymnastics ability along with your russian jump   There would be judges and everything and they would rate you on all the categories and then the next morning the scores would be posted on the main office door and it would tell you who made varisty and who made junior varsity. Practices would be after school everyday for about 2 or 3 hours. We would have to run around the track, stretch out, and then we would go over our cheers and chants. We perform them at football games and basketball games. Football was a lot more fun than basketball. We even put together a competition squad which was a lot of hard work but we ended up going to Nationals in Tampa and placed 1st in our division. If you've ever seen Bring it On it looks a lot like that at a competition. People think it's easy to do but it's one of the hardest things I've ever done. I had to learn how to do a round-off back-handspring in a week. That was nerve-wracking....As far as like stereo-typing, you have some of the girls who only try to join the sqaud to be popular, but they usually end up quiting b/c they find out it's a lot more work than they thought(for example you sweat a lot and have to have a lot of coordination and flexibility and strength. You don't just put on a cute outfit, say a little chant and call it a day. Lol. I miss it a lot though. Good times. MTV does some specials every now and then on cheerleading. Those are usually pretty good and gives a real feel for what it's like. My senior year I was given the opportunity to try out for the UCA Coaching team but I never did. I regret that now. But life goes on! I'm not sure I covered what you really wanted to know in this blog, lol, but I hope so!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I was going to sleep in, wake up, drink coffee, and then maybe go to the beach or something. Well that went all to hell. About 8 o'clock I hear my nextel beep and then Jeff's voice yelling, "Baby! Rise and shine!" Not how I wanted to wake up. I drag myself out of bed and answer the phone. Turns out him and Ryan are at a job in Sanford and he's just gotten his truck  stuck.  Now he needs me to drive Ryan's truck all the way to the job so that they can use it to pull Jeff's truck out. I  reluctantly  agree. I put in my contacts,throw some clothes on and proceed to drive Ryan's truck to Sanford.  Note:  Ryan's truck is a big ol' F-350 Powerstroke 6 speed with huge tires. I'm about 5'7 and 110 pounds. This truck swallows me! None-the-less I get it there and they pull Jeff out and we begin to drive home when Jeff realizes he's lost his phone. So now we have to turn around and go back to the job to find his phone. I end up finding it after about half an hour later and by this time Jeff is behind schedule and getting  very  short tempered so he's driving home like a maniac and almosts rear ends a guy. His only reply is, "Well that'll teach the mother- BEEP er to get the hell out of my way next time." Lol.  Boys.  I'm finally home now and in one piece. I have my coffee so all is right the world. The beach thing is out of the question though so I think instead I'm going to go to the park with my sister and kick the soccer ball around. (Remind you I was a cheerleader and dancer in high school. When it comes to soccer I have no idea what the hell is going on. So this should be interesting.) Hope everyone has a great day.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just finished watching American Idol. There was nothing else on. Fantasia has the contest in the bag. I like her though, even with her big ol' Steven Tyler mouth. She's got the whole Macy Grey sound going on.... Anyways, I feel like poop. Like you really wanted to know that. Lol. I just feel drained of all energy. I need to start working out again. I think that's part of my problem. Plus since dance is done for the summer the only workout I ever get is prying poor turtles from Tanks mouth. He's like a turtle feind. Everytime I let him out to go to the bathroom he finds another turtle hole and has to harrass the darn thing. And these are the endangered ones!! Silly dog. Luckily he's never hurt one. Just scared the crap out of it. Well this post is dangerously boring so I'll say adios and post tomorrow. Adios.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Growing up sucks. You have all these responsibilities and there's so much pressure on you to decide what career path you want to take. Well how in the hell are you supposed to know that? I've been in college, on and off now, for about 4 years. I still have no clue what I want to do. I wasn't one of those kids who ate the age of 12 was able to tell everyone, "I want to be a fireman/doctor/bus driver when I grow up." My head has always been in the clouds too which sometimes makes things worse. For instance if someone asked me today what would I be if I could be anything in the whole wide world I'd say the next lead singer in the Dixie Chicks band. That's right. But let's face it, I'm 23 and not getting any younger, I don't happen to live in Nashville, and I'm not the best singer in the world. (Shocking, but true.) So this leaves me where? I once thought I wanted to be a elem. school teacher. Then I started taking classes and volunteering and found out what it was all about. No thanks. Did you know that if a kid shows signs of suicide and actually commits suicide, they can blame it on a teacher for not seeing the signs? Stupid, stupid, stupid. Parents are ruining the whole teaching thing. They blame everything on the school system. So I x-ed that career. My friend Megan just graduated from USF and has moved to Syracuse, NY to get an advertising job. My other friend Kelly graduated from UF and has since went on to graduate school in Boston for criminal justice. Kristy became a nurse. Andrea works for an eye doctor. Jill's one year away from being a dental hygienist. Claire's graduated and can now get a job as a high school physics teacher. Leslie has a graphic art design degree....Must I go on? And what am I doing? Working part time at a golf course still twiddling my thumbs saying, "What do I want to be?" (Sigh) Jeff's mom told me I should get into real estate. It's only a 2 week course and then you take a test. I think I'll take the classes through the community college. At least then I'll have a real job. Maybe I can take night classes too once I get into real estate. Maybe by then I'll have figured out what I want to be.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My life could be a soap-opera. (I'm sure a lot of people think that about their lives too.) A couple months ago Jeff and I decided it was time to try and move out of here (here being my grandpa's house) and find a place to call our own. You see, about 2 years ago I moved back here b/c my grandpa said that he was going to get an apartment in Daytona, since that's where he works, that way he wouldn't have to drive as far. He would only come back to the house every Wednesday to do laundry and check up on things (i.e. bitch about the yard not being mowed or the gutters needing cleaning, etc.). He told me that if I could find someone to live with me and rent out one of the bedrooms, then we could have the house to ourselves. So I asked my friend Amy if she would like to live with me since she was living in a situation that wasn't good for her at the time. She said yes and moved in. We got settled in here, adopted a dog (Tank), and everything was cool. Next thing I know, my sister (who was going to Jacksonville University at the time) decided that she wasn't happy at JU and wanted to move back home. So Erin packed her stuff up and moved back home with me and Amy. Erin then decided she wanted a dog since Amy and I had one. She then adopted her dog, Diesel. Couple months go by and Jeff and I started to date and it turned into a serious relationship, so eventually he moved in with me. Amy and him didn't get along very well b/c she had a crush on him and was jealous of our relationship and he got annoyed with her all the time. Things got bad, Amy moved out, and things we're ok again. Time goes by and Dad calls. He lost his job in Tennessee and him and his girlfriend we're no longer doing well together. He then wants to know if we would mind if he moved in with us "temporarily" until he found a job down here and was able to get on his feet again. Erin and I said sure and he moved in with us this past January. Took him about 2 months to find a job but he finally got one. He agreed when he moved down here that he would pay Gramps 100 a month for rent and I don't think Gramps has seen a dime. He was only supposed to be here for about a month or two. It's been 5. We have a no smoking rule in the house which he seems to think doesn't apply to him b/c he sits in his bedroom and smoke about a pack a day and uses empty cans for his ash tray. I guess he thinks we can't smell or something. I hate cigarettes. I'm about to put a sign on his door that says No Smoking. He can march his happy ass outside like everyone else. He's also a slob, doesn't help out around the house, and comes home drunk all the time. I told him I don't like him when he's drunk so he tries to hide that too. Disgusting. So anyways, this is where we're at today. I have to get out of this house. My mom seems to think she might be moving back down here too so of course she would come here. I'm just ready to be out on my own and not have to put up with everyone's drama. If all goes well we will be in our own house by the end of June! YAY!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The other day I wrote about my friend Diem and I going to Cassadega to get those candles. Well I think one of them worked! I went to work yesterday and we were having an event. Each person in this event had tickets for a free drink off the bev-cart. Well to make a long story short, my boss forgot to tell me that I had to write everything down that they got with the free tickets. So end of story- I made  way  more money in tips than I should have. But my boss was so cool about it. He was like, "Well you deserve it anyhow. Next time we'll know how to do it the right way." Now most of you out there would say that it was just a misunderstanding that led to my extra cash, but no. It was the money candle.   After work tonight Jeff and I are going over to Slade's house to watch a Nascar race. I'm not into it personally but Jeff and just about everyone we hang out with is. So I guess I'm going to suck it up and just make myself get into it. I'll just find the cutest guy and root for him. Well I have to get ready for another exciting day at the golf course.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I was scheduled to be on the bev. cart at work. Normally we come in at 9am and work until 5pm. Now, in order for me to get to work at 9 I have to get up at 7. I have to feed and walk the dogs, and I  have  to have my morning coffee or else the rest of the day is going to be a bad day. So when I got to work this morning I find out that there's only an outing for the day and it doesn't start until 1pm. This means that I didn't have to be there until 12 which also means that  I didn't need to get up at 7 am!  Ya think someone could have  called  me and let me know!....  Stupid people.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was out with Diem today and we had to go over to her friend Susan's. She's an older lady with three kids, but very cool. I know her from when I used to work at Asahi's. Her family eats there at least once a week. We were there to talk about some things and you know how girls are- we get off the subject and just start gabbing away. Well we got onto the subject of the psychics in Cassadega. Now for those of you not familiar with Cassadega it's a very small section in Lake Helen where all the psychics congregate, so to speak. They have everything there from pet psychics to tarot to palm reading to whatever. It's crazy. There's an old hotel there that's supposed to be haunted too. Well anyways, Susan was telling us how she goes there every so often to talk with a psychic and then Diem piped up and said she goes too. I would tell you the story that Susan told us but I think it might be personal to her, so I won't. It gave me goosebumps. Then Susan showed us some candles that she bought while over there. One of them was labeled money I think and she said that after she got it her husband got a raise. So after we left, Diem and I decided to go into Cassadega to get some of our own. I figure if they don't work, then at least they smell nice. Diem bought 2 and I bought 3. Mine are Good Health, Abundance, and Money. Good Health says, "I believe in the healing powers of the universe and its ability to restore health. May these powers guide me to a state of complete well-being." Abundance says, "May an abundance of goodness flow freely into my life. Allow me to be receptive to the treasures that present themselves, enriching my life's journey." Finally, the money one says, "May prosperity flow freely through my life. I sense a natural attraction to wealth and its comforts. Let me embrace prosperity in all forms." Hey, I could embrace winning the lottery. That would be cool. Now the candles also have an interesting little note on the sides. It talks about "charging your candle". You have to, like, sit outside and will the energy of the magical white light of the universe to protect you. Then you have to say,"Manifest a Miracle! I will it so...So be it!" ...... right . I think I'll just light them and cross my fingers. I'll let you know if they work.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every morning between 6 and 8 I get awoken by my sisters dog, Diesel. She is so annoying. Jeff leaves for work around 6 and around that time my sister lets her dog out of her room. Well as soon as Jeff leaves, Diesel sits right in front of my bedroom door and whines. Not only does she whine but she seriously, like, tries to beat my door down. I kid you not! She bangs into the door and then she takes her paws and drags them down the door leaving scratch marks all over it. Yeah. This is how every morning goes. I try and ignore it until I can't take it anymore. And don't think I don't yell at her and tell her to stop. She'll just look at me wagging her tail and as soon as I shut the door she's at it again.  Every  morning. Anyways.  Did anyone catch the season finale of Smallville last night?(That Tom is such a hottie!) If Chloe is dead I'm going to be  VERY  upset. I hate season finales. They're so nerve-wracking. Now I have to wait, what,  3 months  until I get to know what happened? Torture.     
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, my first blog and I'm... speechless.  It's like stage fright. You have this whole speech/monologue prepared, you walk to center stage, you look out into the blinding lights and you stall. Figures.  I guess I could start with telling you a little about me. My name is Jessie. I'm 23, a scorpio and I think Jessica Simpson is hilarious. I also blast Britney Spears in my truck, have an addiction to Diet Coke, and wouldn't trade my flip-flops for Monolos, even if you paid me. Ok... maybe  if you paid me.   Well I guess that's a good enough start. I promise to try and make all future posts much more interesting!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing exciting going on at the moment. Went and saw the new Harry Potter movie last night with my sister and some of her friends. It was pretty good. Nothing beats reading the books though.... It's been raining a lot lately. That's why I'm home early today from work. Well I might write more later. It's thundering outside and I think I should get off the computer.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gramps is going to sell us his house!! I'm  so  excited! I talked to my mom yesterday and we finally came to an agreement about the house, so she talked to Bill (gramps) and he said ok! As soon as I'm done drinking my morning coffee I have to go over to Jeff's mom's work so that we can write up a contract before anyone changes their minds. I'm so happy. This house needs some fixing up, which won't be cheap, but it's going to be well worth it. The only downfall is that we have to write in the contract that my mom can live here with us for as long as she needs to without having to pay rent and that if Bill ever gets to where he can't take care of himself then he gets to come live with us too. I don't mind those things. I did want to have my  own  place, but I surely don't mind sharing. Another bad thing too is that if and when mom comes down here to live, I have to tell Dad he's got to go. But he needs to go regardless anyhow. I love him but I don't like living with him.  On to something else- I saw this little questionaire thing on some persons blog and I thought it was cute so I want to do it too.  1.Spell your name backwards: EISSEJ 2.Where do you live? Home of the happiest place on earth- Disney World! 3.Describe yourself in 3 words: Dreamer, friendly, loving 4.Who is your worst enemy? I am my own worst enemy 5.If you could have any animal for a pet, what would it be? Black Panther 6.What is the latest you've ever stayed up? 8am  Describe Your: 7.Wallet: It's pink and beige from American Eagle 8:Brush: green with sparkles 9.Toothbrush: Hot pink 10:Jewelry worn daily: Hoop earrings that Jeff bought me for Christmas and a gold necklace with a pearl and diamond pendant 11.Pillow cover: boring ol' tan 12:Blanket: It's a down blanket and it's soooo comfy 13:Coffee Cup: It's a halloween coffee cup with pumpkins on it 14:Sunglasses: I lost mine but they were Oakley Teaspoons. They were silver with blue-like lenses. I miss them. 15:Undies: Right now they are red with a moose on the butt. They're from Abercrombie and Fitch. Love that store. 16:Shoes: FLIP FLOPS!  17:Handbag: It's light blue. It's one of the new ones from the Gap. 18:Fave top: Umm...Tank tops 19:Fave pants: Cetines from Express. They make my butt look cute. 20:Perfume: Ralph by Ralph Lauren 21:CD in stereo right now: The new Avril Lavigne 22:Tatoos: None. I'm anti-tatoo. 23:Piercings: In my ears. I used to have a belly-button ring but it got infected and had to be taken out. 24:Hair: Brown, straight, little past my shoulders. Thinking about getting highlights since it's summer.  What/Who/Is/Are 25:In my mouth: the occassional gulp of coffee at the moment 26:In my head: ........... 27:wishing: to be a famous country singer or to win the lotto 28:talking to: No one's home but me and the dogs. Well Erin's home but she doesn't come alive until after noon. 29:eating: nothing. I don't do breakfast. 30:Do you like candles? Yes. I love candles, especially the ones from Yankee Candle. 31:Do you like hot wax? Silly question. I guess I do stick my fingers in it from time to time. 32:Do you like incense? No. Yuck. 33:Do you like the taste of blood? Hell no! I can't even stomach looking at it. 34:Person you wish you could be with right now? My granny. 35:What/Who is next to you? Tank, Diesel, and Dozer- my dogs. They follow me  everywhere.  36:Things that scare you: Clowns and carnies, tornados, and war.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday my friend Kristina called me to see if I would like to come over to her house to join her and Gage (her 1 year old) in their new pool. It's so cute, their pool. It's about a 5x5 foot circular blow-up pool and its about a foot and a half deep. It's blue with little fishies all over the bottom. Too cute. Gage just thinks it's the best thing in the world too. Kristina is currently pregnant with her second child. She's due in late August. Another boy. Her and Jon have been married for a couple years now, I think, and they want to have a big family. She's my age- 23. She keeps asking me when Jeff and I are going to get married and start having kids. Lol. Not any time soon I can tell you that. I put up with 3 dogs right now and I can assure you- thats enough! I know that eventually I do want to get married and settled down, but I feel so young still. I don't want to do all that until I'm like 28. Maybe to some that's a long time away, but not to me. Plus I can see what everyone else has to go through so that by the time I get to that stage in my life, I'll have had a lot of experience. I was asking what Kristina and Jon wanted to name their baby and they have some awful (I pray she never reads this) names. See Jon wants his kids to have names that no one else has b/c his name is Jon and their are  tons  of Jons everywhere. So they have come up with Briar, Gunner, and Tuff. Terrible. Briar reminds me of that Disney thing- Briar Fox- or something, and Gunner is something I would name a hunting dog, and Tuff- well that's just silly. Everyone will say Tuff ain't so Tough is he? (Or something equally as dumb) But how do you tell someone that the names they're thinking about are...well....wierd. I'm all about originality, but I think you should carefully go over what terrible things could be associated with their names. Bullies can be mean. Did you hear *read* what Gywneth Paltrow named their new baby girl?!? APPLE. C'mon! Are the next ones going to be Peach and Pear? Maybe apple holds some kind of romantic meaning to them or whatever, but if that's the case then I think you should save something like that for the  middle  name. Anyways.....  My friend Megan recently moved up to Syracuse, NY with her boyfriend and Memorial Day was her b-day but I have no address or telephone number to get in touch with her, so I didn't get to tell her Happy Birthday. Maybe I could call her parents. I'm sure they know a number I could reach.  Today I am   finally   going to go to the beach. My sister and some of her friends are going to Blue Springs and asked me to come, but I really want to go to the beach. I need a new beach pass anyhow. Plus I like to go to New Smyrna Beach and look at some of the surf shops they have. Well, nothing else exciting to write about at the moment. I'm going to get my bathing suit on and head out. Have a great day!!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Before my dad moved in with us in January he had called to say that when he got here he had something very important to tell me and my sister. I thought nothing of it at the time. About 2 weeks after he had moved in he finally sat us both down in the kitchen and said, "You two have another sister." I just stared back at him while the thought registered in my head. He then went on to tell us the story of how she came about and why he hadn't told us sooner. Something about her mother made him sign all his rights away to her when she was 3 and he thought that since he had done that, that he wasn't supposed to say anything about her anymore. He didn't want to cause trouble. (A little far-fetched if you ask me, but I didn't pursue it.) So apparently Ashlee (that's her) has known about Erin and me since she was born. As she's been getting older, she's been trying to get in touch with us. That's why Dad finally told us about her. He basically had to. So Ashlee is 15 now. 15 years have gone by that I can't get back. See I wasn't mad that he had had another child with another woman. That's his business. He's a grown man and can do whatever he wants as long as he still does his "Dad" duties for Erin and I. I was just upset that this had been held from us. Like we didn't deserve to know. Well shortly after he told us about her, he went up to Georgia to visit her. He brought back pictures of her and stuff. I got her email address and I've emailed her a couple times, but it's not the same. She feels like a distant friend rather than my sister. And for that I am resentful. A bond with a sister is something that no one can replace. Lord knows Erin and I have our moments when we get on eachothers last nerve (which is normal), but having her in my life makes everything better. She's the one I could talk to about anything, for we've been through everything together. And I wish that Ashlee could have been a part of that too. But I'm hoping that maybe this summer she will get to come down and visit and we can kind of get to know one another. It will be strange but I think it will be cool at the same time. I'm not really sure how I got on this topic, but I feel much better typing out all my thoughts about the whole thing. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>