<Blog>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      here are some jokes, not really that funny, but i like em.  1.Yo mama's so fat; when she stepped on the dog's tail we had to change his name to Beaver. 2.How are the New York Jets defense and yo mama alike? You give them a quarter and they'll let you score!  3.Yo mama's so fat, when the cops see her on a street corner they yell, "Hey you guys, break it up!" 4.Yo mama's so fat, even Richard Simmons laughs at her! 5.Yo daddy is so bald, when he wears a turtleneck he looks like a broken condom. 6.Yo mama's so fat she makes Godzilla look like an action figure. 7.Yo mama is so bald I can see what she's thinking. 8.Yo mama is so dirty she has to creep up on the bathwater. 9.Yo' mama like a Big Mac -- full of fat and only worth a buck! 10.The only difference between your mama and a washing machine is, after you drop a load in the washing machine, it doesn't follow you around! 11.Yo' mama's lips so big, she can whisper in her own ear. 12.Yo' mama so dumb, she waited at a STOP sign until it said GO! 13.Yo mama's so big, fat and clumsy, when she tried to get to Wal-Mart, she stumbled over K-Mart and landed right on Target. 14.Your mama cooks so bad, your family prays after they eat! 15.What is the difference between yo' mama and a winding road? The winding road has curves you can get used to! 16.Yo' mama a saint...a St. Bernard! 17.Yo mama is so ugly that when she worked at the bakery they dipped her face in the batter to make animal cookies. 18.Yo' mama's breath is so nasty, when she burps her teeth have to duck. 19.Yo' mama's breath stinks so bad, people look forward to her farts! 20.Yo mama's so fat, she uses a semi-trailer as a couch. 21.Yo mama's feet are so scaly that they filmed Crocodile Dundee in her footbath. 22.Yo mama's so dirty, plants grow off her ass. 23.Yo mama's glasses are so thick that when she looks on a map, she sees people waving 24.Yo mama's so fat, when she farted pluto's ice caps melted. 25.Yo Mama's so ugly, she had to trick-or-treat over the phone. 26.Yo mama's house is so small, I threw a rock in the window and hit everyone inside. 27.Yo mama's house is so dusty the roaches ride around in dune buggies. 28.Yo mama is like a brick -- she is always getting laid. 29.Yo Mama's like the Pilsbury Doughboy. Everybody wants to poke her. 30.Yo' mama's lips so big, she doesn't use chapstick -- she uses Mop 'n' Glo! 31.Yo Mama's breath is so bad, she could clear a chat room. 32.Yo Mama is so poor, she told your little siser that Santa Claus was dead. 33.Yo' mama so dumb, that the Psychic Friends only charge her half price to read her mind! 34.Yo' mama got such bad dandruff, the principal declared a snow day! 35.Yo mama is so bald that she has to use rice for rollers. 36.Yo mama's so bald that when you rub her head you can see into the future. 37.Yo mama is so bald that when she takes a shower she gets brainwashed! 38.Yo' mama so country, she thought an elevator was a mobile home! 39.Yo mama's so dirty, the U.S. Army wants to use her bath water as a biological weapon. 40.Yo mama is so disgusting that every time she bends over to tie her shoes, she's gotta fart! 41.Yo' mama so dumb, she failed a pregnancy test! 42.Yo mama's so dumb, she thought masturbation was a karate teacher. 43.Your mama's so dumb, she had to have a cook help her make ramen noodles. 44.Yo mama's so dumb she thought Subway made trains 45.Yo mama's so dumb she thought Master P was a special restroom. 46.Yo mama's so dumb she sat on the TV and watched the couch 47.Yo mama's so dumb, when god was giving out brains she thought they were milkshakes and asked for extra thick. 48.Yo' mama so dumb, she bought a solar powered flash light! 49.Yo mama's so dumb, she thought that the the International Dateline was a global dating service. 50.Yo mama's so dumb, she stuck the phone up her ass and thought she was makin' a booty call. 51.Yo Mama's so dumb, she went to a movie that said ''under 18 not admitted,'' so she left to go get 17 of her friends. 52.Yo mama is so dumb that she was on her way to the airport and saw a sign that said “airport left.” So she turned around and went home. 53.Yo mama is so dumb she stuck a battery up her butt and said, "I got energy!" 54.Yo' mama so dumb that if brains were dynamite she couldn't blow her nose! 55.Your mama is so dumb, she sold her car for gas money! 56.Your mama is so dumb when she was pulled over for drunk driving and they asked her to walked the line she said, ''Which one?'' 57.Yo mama's so dumb, she tried to drown her pet fish. 58.Yo mama is so dumb, it took her an hour to cook minute rice. 59.Yo' mama so dumb, when she filled out her job application and it said ‘sex,’ she wrote “not lately.” 60.Yo mama is so dumb that she got locked in the bathroom and peed her pants. 61.Yo mama's so dumb, she thought menopause was a button on the VCR. 62.Yo mama is so dumb, she thought a ribbed condom was soul food. 63.Yo mama so stupid, when you were born she saw the umbilical cord and said, “Hey it comes with cable!” 64.Yo' mama so fat, the tag on her dress reads: "Made In Hungary, Turkey, China, U.S.A., Algeria, Japan, Indonesia..." 65.Yo' mama so fat, she falls out of bed on both sides! 66.Yo' mama so fat, she has to make a long distance call to talk to herself! 67.Yo' mama so fat, her doctor said she had a flesh-eating disease and told her she had 13 years to live! 68.Yo' mama so fat, I take a lap around her for exercise! 69.Yo' mama so fat, when she needs to wipe her butt, she sends out a search party! 70.Yo' mama so fat, she got more rolls than a bakery! 71.Yo' mama so fat, when she goes to a stadium, she sits next to everybody! 72.Yo' mama so fat, she has to sleep in shifts! 73.Yo' mama so fat, all the restaurants have signs that say "Max. Occupancy 240 OR Yo' Mama." 74.Yo' mama so fat, she uses transport trucks as rollerskates! 75.Yo' mama so fat, they showed her a picture of her feet and she couldn't identify them! 76.Yo' mama so fat, people exercise by doing laps 'round her! 77.Yo' mama so fat, when fighter pilots see her they say, "Bogie at 11, 12, 1, 2, and 3 o'clock." 78.Yo' mama so fat, when she dances, the band skips! 79.Yo mama is so fat, when you slap her leg, you can ride the waves. 80.Yo' mama so fat, she fell in love and broke it! 81.Yo' mama so fat, when she inspected the Sears Tower they had to rebuild it! 82.Yo' mama so fat, she fell asleep at a new gas station and when she woke up she was painted orange with a 76 on her and was stuck at the top of a pole! 83.Yo' mama so fat, she can stand over the homeless and give them a home! 84.Yo' mama so fat, she's the reason there's night and day! 85.Yo' mama so fat, she has an echo in her belly button! 86.Yo' mama so fat, fat is a compliment! 87.Yo' mama so fat, she has to play pool with the planets! 88.Yo' mama so fat, she has to use a telephone pole as a tampon! 89.Yo' mama so fat, the president declared her the 51st state! 90.Yo' mama so fat, that in order to kiss her, your dad has to hit her in the stomach and ride the third wave in! 91.Yo' mama so fat, she fell through a black hole and got stuck! 92.Yo' mama so fat, they had to take aerial shots for her senior pictures! 93.Yo mama is so fat, she's on both sides of the family. 94.Yo' mama so fat, if she were one of the three little pigs, she'd say 'Not by the hair on my 26 chins!' 95.Yo' mama so fat, the photographer charged her for a family photo! 96.Yo' mama so fat, when she goes to the movies, she sits next to everyone. 97.Yo' mama so fat she has to walk on the street instead of hogging the sidewalk 98.Yo' mama so fat she went on an airplane and turned it into a boat. 99.Yo' mama so fat, her beeper goes off and people think she's backing up! 100.Yo' mama so fat, that when she wears a yellow rain jacket, people think she's a taxi cab. 101.Yo' mama so fat, when she jumps off the high dive, she shows up on radar! 102.Yo' mama so fat, I had to take two trains to get on her good side! 103.Yo' mama so fat, when did the splits, she gave the road a hickey 104.Yo' mama so fat, she was alone on a corner and the cop arrested her for loitering 105.Yo' mama so fat, that when you tell her to haul ass, she has to make 2 trips! 106.Yo' mama so fat she has to call Sherwin-Williams to paint her toenails 107.Yo' mama so fat, that when she sits around the house, she really sits around the house! 108.Yo' mama so fat, you use her thong as a hammock! 109.Yo mama's so fat, when she ran away they had to use all four sides of the milk carton 110.Yo' mama's so fat, she broke the stairway to heaven! 111.Yo mama's so fat that she went into 7-11 and didn't come out until 11:07 112.Yo mama is so fat, the last time she saw 90210 was on the bathroom scale 113.Yo mama's so fat a parachute wouldn't cover her. 114.Yo mama's so fat, she got busted in the airport for having 200 pounds of crack. 115.Yo' mama is so fat, when she joined the army and the soldier said head for the trenches, they all jumped in her butt crack 116.Yo mama is so fat that she keeps a pack of bacon for dental floss. 117.Yo Mama is so fat that she got baptized at Sea World! 118.Yo mama's so fat, first she filled the bathtub, then she turned on the water. 119.Yo Mama's so fat, when she goes to get out of the bath you have to call the Coast Guard. 120.Yo' mama so fat, when she goes to the beach, the tide comes in! 121.Yo mama's so fat, she goes to the beach to sell shade 122.Yo' mama so fat, she goes to the beach and she's the only one who gets a tan! 123.Yo mama's so fat, she has to put her belt on with a boomerang 124.Yo mama's so fat that when she bends over, we go into daylight savings time 125.Yo mama is so fat that when she took a vacation to New York City, she wore a black dress and everyone thought there was a power outage 126.Yo mama's so fat, her blood type is Ragu 127.The difference between yo mama and a blue whale? About ten lbs 128.Yo' mama so fat, when she was born her mom said, ''Great, triplets.” 129.Yo' mama so fat, she broke the family tree 130.Yo mama is so fat that when I took her to a buffet, she pulled up a chair 131.Yo mama is so fat that, when she was bungee jumping, she took the whole bridge with her 132.Your mama is so fat, a bus drove by and she said, ''Stop that Twinkie!'' 133.Yo Mama is so fat, her ass has it's own congressman 134.Your mama is so fat, people use her butt cheeks as a ski slope. 135.Yo' mama so fat, when she puts on BVD's it spells out boulevard  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      he's guatemalan, a little bit on the short side, but he's beautiful inside and out.  i met him at walmart, weird place to meet someon right? i was with my friend (now ex-friend)  keyona at the time shopping with her mom for bras.  i saw him with his friend checking out a shirt, and i knew i liked his style at that moment.  he was lovely, divine... god i loved that secound.  i smiled at him when he passed the sunglasses stand... he smiled back, and came to me.  he asked me my name, and i told him, then he told me his... we exchanged phone #s and it was over.  that night he called me and we talked.  he had a gorgeous voice, which i was instantly in love with, and he told me he wanted to go to the movies with me (cinemax was actually the word he used, since his english was really limited, but i understood after a few minutes)  this was about 7 months ago and now i'd die for him.  doesnt matter how physically attractive someone is... its the love  the love that i feel at this moment
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      k, so ill say something to all you ppl who think your life sux: its NOTHING compared to mine, ok so maybe im exaggerating a bit, but my life is pretty gay. read on:  i live with a paranoid bitch, my mother.  she believes that im plotting against her no matter what i do.  if im nice, she freaks, if im bad, she screams... *sighs*  i go to Classical high.  basically the worst mother fuckin school you can imagine.  the kids are afraid of me mostly.  they spread rumors, and call me, "goth"  i hate labeling so you can imagine how much that pisses me off  i have a bf, well more like a ball-and-chain. his names julio, doesnt matter what happens he'll always say im cheating on him.    i have the worst little bratty bitch-of-a-sister in the universe.  she snitches, she kicks, and oh yeah... she bites.  well, i got a load off my mind now... think ill play online a little
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      w00t!!! so now i have a blog... crazy man, just fuckin crazy... im not really sure what to say, so i think ill stop talking, er typing now.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>