<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      tt i promised or kinda promised in the previous previous post...there are lots...as i expected...but i too lazy to say now..so i shall just tell u tt i am a forgiving person who do not take to heart such insignificant imbecile-ic wrongdoings against me...haha...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haha i nv tot i will ever say tt...(but i alr said frisbee is fun,so anything is possible...hahah)but it is...my we had like totally last minute training,izzat and peiqi trying to get some strategy thingy into our brains...haha oh well at least we got the catching part..haha and it was great...it was fun...haha...and i havnt run liddat for a very long time alr...haha but my leg still pain from tt day in choir...how lame rite?haha then i nearly scored...but then got touched then skidded...so got cut...haha then somehow i fell...got skinned rather badly...oh when i scored,i think i overexerted my leg muscles...very pain...then now put tiger balm medicated plster...haha...not too bad...at least its working...now i cant cross my legs...cuz one side knee injured,then otherside muscles pain...haha then cut my palm...u know,those type of super irritatingly small but super pain ones...haha irritating the hell out of me la...haha oh then after i fell,gotta go get first aid rte,then royston brig me all ard the place la...haha then when finally found it,it doesnt have antiseptic or plasters...haha crap...so in the end i just have to wash my wounds w water...then royston send sherri in to find me...then she came in,asked me whether i'm alrite then started telling me abt this gamma gal who got injured...then i was like,it's me...haha ridiculous..haha i banged into this other gal too...her forehead hit my shoulder...then now my shoulder got big lebam...so pain..haha... oh then shit and winnie waited for me to go for dinner at suntec!!(although i dint know at tt time) then i dint feel like gg cuz leg pain and all...but feel a bit bad la...cuz they wqaited so long and in e end i dint go...haha so we went...rather fun la...haha then when we came back(me and denise),we saw chong yew and ze ming...our nemesis from 15/03 in capt's ball...haha  oh ya i dint say tt my team,gamma 2,got into finals and got 2nd!!!haha...not too bad...we won all our matches except the last one...tt's y we 2nd...sob...but it was still damn zai!!!haha okla...enough abt it...i must go nurse my palm and legs...haha not to mention my knee and elbow and shoulder too...wah really multiple injury man... its a rough game...but still fun nonetheles... hhaha  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haha i am so proud of us today!!!woohooo...we rock man!!haha we made it so far!!!yeah!!!haha it was such a great achievement!!!haha ok i am still rather excited abt it...and we trashed 07 and 13!!!haha and the girls rock man...haha we played all the matches continuously...and god knows we are tired...but we made it thru...so far...haha oh my i said it and i'm gg to say it again!!we rock!!haha i had such a wonderful time playing with u guys today...haha and we played as best we could and we did it man!!we got into interhouse and trashed kiu's class...haha... for idols today,i so think tt cliffy shd get in...haha he was sooooo cute!!!and tim cmi la...not full monty...haha...so sad for him...haiz... oh well tt's all for today...ta..wait for reports abt my touch rugby tmr...haha i think there'll be a lot of gossips...hahaha 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      those two are nike adverts too...just in case u wondering why i suddenly onz abt adverts is cuz i happen to flip thru a few magazine on mon,...haha i only read mags for the adverts...totally love them...haha oh well this nike ones are rather cool...so decided to put them here...still got somemore...its promoting their new line of nikewomen clothes...supposedly after u wear it and exercise,u will feel the energy,courage and chaste and a whole load of other stuff i dun rmb...hahaha...lame though it is...still think it's rather cool...haha and the description is adidas ad...rather cool too... oh and the have this new series of clinique ads also damn cool...haha i suddenly feel like starting a collection or something...crazy?it's called passion...hahah joking...gonna slp early... thank god vu came back early then i dun havta do tonight's phone duty for her...hehe...can go slp now...
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The ENERGY of after  Seriously. You could jump over that car. You're jet-propelled. You have a firecracker heart. You are a champion. You don't need anything. Food? Sleep? Never! (Cue King Kong chest-pounding effect.) Coursing through you is a raging river after a thaw. We have a winner! You're electromagnetic. You are nikebeautiful.  The COURAGE of after  You are not tepid. Youe are steadfast; a knight in featherweight, form-fitting armor. Compromises will never again be made by you. Never! Distractions and substitutes lose their cheap shine. Your inner resources are an embarassment of riches. Lucky girl! Lion heart! You are nikebeautiful.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      HOT NEWS:psf likes khx and yi jian likes cookie monster!! oh my...haha i manage to find those out within 12 hours...it was information overload...haha got headache out of it...i dint even know tt yi jian knows cookie monster la...haha then turned out they dated for a while somemore!!!haha and i just realise she rather plump?haha... today me and mak pon sch...hilarious man...hahah last nite she was like bugging me to go for breakfast,end up i woke up earlier than her la...hahah sleep like a pig liddat...hhaha..then we ate breakfast in her room...everything was going well...spending a relaxing day...until lunch tt is...haha...she got no more instant noodles so gotta go out to eat la...so go feng shan...she went down first la...then while i was bounding down the stairs,and i really meant it as literaly bounding,i met mdm tan...such luck!!haha then i have to immediately like look sickly and tired...haha stupid la...every monday got roomcheck...then they were like saying mon is not a good day to pon...and end up i dun meet her during roomchecks but when gg out for lunch!!so ridiculous...haha just realised tt ppl in hostel though in a community,leads such separate lifes...recently talked to duck and talked to jul last nite until 12.30am!!haha it's such fun to be able to like i dunno...bond with them again?it's been such a long time...kinda missed their company...jan too...oh he's coming back soon!!!haha cant wait to see him...haha i can alr imagine him like so much fatter and much more insane...then the other day,rite before concert,he msged me...hmmm did i say this b4?anw,just in case i din...i tot he was back...was so happy...haha but turned out it was global sms...stupid baboon still happily in phillipines...haha  hmmm and i really think i'm very stressed...haha well kinda cried for no apparent reason again...today...twice somemore...i think i'm gg crazy...SATs and jct coming so fast...ugh...stress stress STRESS!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      just had this hostel barbeque thingy...and guess where we had it?in the AH parking lot!!!haha just a great place dun u think?haha but tt's not e point the thing is tt i got to finally like talk to the second intakers in tp...rather cutesy pple...pecklyn is cute...she really brings the art of acting cute to a new level...winnie:learn fr her...hui wen too...hahah just joking...but rather ok la...act innocent to... and then we were sitting down there talking crap,then profound came along and sat down next to us and started telling us about medical checkup procedure for the guys...and how they check for hernia...ahem*cough cough*...haha... but the thing is,we dint wanna know...and mak and me sorta cringed with every gesture she made...oh and she uses rather picturistic(no idea if there's such a word)gestures...kinda leaves nothing to the imagination...haha..anw,then smart alec yi jian come along and sat down...and we are all like...dotz?haha...then smart pig went and asked him about it...ugh...ok...i shall not say anymore...dun wanna relive the conversation...haha oh well...my legs really cannot make it alr...haha overexertion during choir photo taking...dun let me stand behind,so i gotta bend down...and down cuz behind cant see...and then when i'm like in a sitting position(on an imaginary chair,of course) then have to stay there for like forever and ever(amen!) while they click away with the 17 thousand cameras there...haiz...really hurts..haha  oh well...they were like talking abt churhes...then were trying to decide which church to go tmr...then mak wanted to go blc(peng siang's) then yi jian said he's gg for this cavalry aog(peng li's)...the i was like wondering y the hell the churches they wanna go to tmr are like my classmates?haha rather ridiculous thought...but i think they going this lighthouse or something...i dunno la...haha not a christian anyway... i just realise my blog so far is rather crappy...and wat do u mean by it's a big blob???haha i cant or rather i dunno how to do anything to this horrible template...though i absolutely love the dots...haha and i dun think im gonna lose steam anytime soon...but i maybe forced to cuz have to start studying!!ugh...haha i totally am not in the mood at all...have been lagging like forever and ever(i'm not gonna say amen,although i think i shd...so here goes:amen!)...if mrs goh sees my tut she'll know i havnt been doing my work not cuz i dint do my tuts(cuz i never do them anyway) but cuz i have stopped copying the ans!!ugh!wats worng with me...and i cant believe it's alr the last week of sch...darn...everything is happening so fast... i have to say tt blogging is good for the soul(again)..haha cuz it gives me a space for the outpouring of my soul...haha al the crude things i'll never say in front of evrybody or u for tt matter...so if i have insulted u here,dun take it to mind...cuz i have to get rid of the urge to kill u sometimes...so better here than in reality rite?but if u really wanna die,tell me...it'll be a pleasure...hahah(joking!!!) hmmm i think i think too much...turned out tt pig is younger than me!!no fair..and eunice can drive...sob...i am of age and i havnt even taken my undang(law:have to take this exam to make sure tt u know wat is or not against the law while driving) yet...horrible...ugh...i'm so gonna go back and get my license...hmph!!ok..obviously thinking toomuch since i managed to think myself into depression...isn't tt great?i mean i must be like totally talented to be able to do tt la...i mean come on, how many ppl u know can do tt?great accomplishment dun u think?haha i think...ok i shant think anymore..but i cant help it...so i think tt even for a starter,i am blogging too much...did anybody ever told u tt blogging is addictive?like i said,i still beats writing a diary... 1. takes much less energy 2. u have to be in front of the computer...which means u can't study and blog at the same time... 3. the computer room is air-coned... 4. i can just crap my heart out and dun care abt how u feel to read this...muahahahaha 5. i'll think of something and tell u next yr... ok since i am not supposed to think anymore,i shall just tell u 5 now... 5. ok havnt think of anything yet...tell u another time... i just realise i alsways use first person when i blog...or when i write gp essays,for tt matter...sorry mr chin,dint mean to not listen to wat u say...but bad habits die hard...and u can't fail me anymore...muahahah... i am evil...i admit tt...haha i love being evil...like i said a very long time ago,i have perfected the art of executing evil deeds...it creeps behind ur back...u will never guess tt its coming until it is all over u...haha and even if u think u are prepared,u will always be caught unawares...muahaha...i think i shd change my blog add...then u all cant read my evil thoughts...hahaha....then i can maintain a nice, good girl image...haha never knew i had this capability in me,eh?hehehehe(evil laughter)... stay tuned for the next episode on monday(comp rm not open on sundays):)
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haiz...last performance..i mean this is rather anti-climax la...haha so sad...all the picture taking...and i dint have my camera with me...sad...but took pics with kiu,ai,salty and fart...haha the rest are just too many to mention(sorry!!)haha...then *sob* *sniff* i cried...again!!haha i think i really break record this time la...its like in this year,or rather 6 mths,i have cried more times tha i did in any one year...and i think there will be more to come...haha so ridiculous...i hate crying..haha and cliffy looked so sad just now...sigh...and i will miss the practices..haha not tt they are like fun or anything...but its a time to gather...and i'll miss being forced to be ard ppl like desmond and chion...hahah and cute justin..hahah of course not to mention my lovers like eudora and les-mate kiu kiu...and the forever blur queens sheep killer and ngian xin...haha and e hot babe izzati...haha and tree...principal of the sch of clowns...haha upgraded to university alr..hahaha...leslie sweetheart and charles dear(eudorable's)haha...and the act cute Max...grins*...haha never ever ask him to smile...u'll be blinded by the reflection of light fr his teeth...haha crazy banana chocolate... and not to forget my surrounding pple like jain hao on the left and cliffy on the right...haha will miss e crappy jokes tt we cracked while standing in the back row...and also the not so friendly glares tt i share with choppy...can't do it to anyone but her...haha oh she irritates me soo...but tt is not the point.. ok i have to go again...kena chase out again...sigh 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haha called my mum just now...and i just realised...no,cant say tt...but she resurfaced something tt i dint exactly wanna think about...my future... i mean if i cant change wat is going to happen,then wat e hell am i working for?hmmm this can lead to the oh so overdiscussed topic... if God has est everything and everything is predestined...then wat difference does our choices make?or did he arranged the different types of choices we make?y live when even if u dun make an effort,ur life will still turn out the way God wanted it...am i sitting here typing all this because God made it so?so its like i am predestined to ask these qns and whoever reading this is going to have to think about it whether u want it or not because God made it so?hahaha i love confusing pple...ok maybe tt's cuz im confusing myself...haha oh well life suckz...as usual...but love life,live life...haha...kiu asked me something a very long time ago...she asked,wat is life?we always say other pple have no life,but do we have a life?haha wats is life?eating,slepping,talking,playing,go sch,go out...such repetition...isn't it these kinda repetition tt got us to say tt other's lifes are boring and hence they have no life?haha does going out more often gives us 'life'?haha no wonder my econ suck...haha end up no where...ha...as foo wld say:biting ur own tail...haha  ugh i hate this..totally pathetic...feeling super lethargic...although im starting to recover from this post concert syndrome as winnie calls it...haha rather worn out...dun feel like hitting the books...this is even worst than last year la...i am so gonna die...and i have no more time alr!!!see the thing is,i know very well tt if i dun start studying soon,i really wont cut it this time...but my body refuses to listen and the body and brain wants to wage a war...but i am just too tired to let them..haha tt's really a whole bunch of crap...but tt's wat i 'm feeling rite now...totally shittified and crappified... and y does everybody wanna go out next friday?two pple's b'dae and both wanna go out on friday...kel is the best...she wants me to go with her to go with her frento go out with her frens godsis...wat kinda outing is this? and i can't make it for shit's chamber concert...so sad...sorry...winnie is gg back on tt day itself...and i got nobody to go with...and SAT is on the 5th...ugh...i was really looking forward to it...i wanna see the double bassist...hmmm sob sob...and i wanna see the shit play...haha... oh ya explaining y two posts today...cuz i came back just now and it was so hot...so i went into e com room la...then got nothing to do...haha then we have this allocation thingy...so in the afternoon is the sec kids' timeslot...so this big fat guy,came along,sat next to me,then chased me out of the comp room..hahaha i make him sound rather bad...but unfortunately he has the right to do tt...darn...hahah  'SHE MOVED THROUGH THE FAIR' My young love said to me "My mother won't mind And my father won't slight you for your lack of kind" And she stepped away from me and this she did say, "It will not be long, love, till our wedding day"  She stepped away from me, and she went thro' the fair. And fondly I watched her move here and move there. And then she went homeward with one star awake, As the swan in the evening moves over the lake.  Last night she came to me, she came softly in, So softly she came that her feet made no din. And she laid her hand on me, and this she did say "It will not be long love, till our wedding day"  such a beautiful song...lyrics are a bit weird but e song is still nice..haha hmm 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      this is totally crappified.ive been trying to modify this thing but to no avail...oh well poor winnie is doing her chem prac now and amy is slacking ard waiting for her temasek idol and chamber pract...me,i am back alr...haha obviously...just bored... i think humans are weird creatures...sometimes,they can be such caring people and yet, they can do such horrible things at the same time...is this the epitome of hypocrisy?ugh...ok i dunno how to spell tt..haha too lazy to check...think its rite though..ha and sometimes they just go against their principle just to gain enjoyment for a short while(and i mean a really short while)...hmmm and if they feel a certain way,y dun they just admit it?i mean so wat if it doesnt look cool or something,hey,if u wanna do it,just go ahead...nobody's stopping u... ok when i say those stuff doesn't mean i m like a saint and dun commit them too...kinda like the poverty thing tt ms lim made us do yesterday...the poor have their principles too,but talking about them does not mean living by them...everybody have their ideals...and i am entitled to my opinion...haha this morning,i was sitting on my bed and i just happen to look up(my bed is rite opposite the window)...i saw the sun rise...it was rather cloudy...then this huge red globe right under the clouds,so it was like grey at the top half and pink at the bottom half...very beatiful...and just then,a plane soared into the skies,just above the clouds...its nothing much really...but at tt point in time,i just felt as if i am watching something magical...it just kinda struck me...u might think tt i am very free,sitting down there looking out of my window(even if u didn't,mun yin did),but it all just happened in a split second...no tt's too fast...but it was just for a while,cuz e plane flew away and the sun got covered by the clouds... oh well such simple things in life doesn't take a long while to enjoy...hmmm sounding like ms lim...haha but it isn't like im grateful tt the sunrise today...but i will always remember the scene...;P hmmm ben said something last nite tt kinda got me thinking...he asked whether i am not planning to get a bf...haha then it kinda got me to think,even if i plan to,wat am i to do?go ard looking for potential bfs?haha funny image just came upon my mind...haha kinda like fishing...haha even for fishing,there is no absolute certainty...u just have to wait...maybe u can put in more bait to attract more or bigger fishes,but ultimately,it all comes down to fate..and luck of course..haha  such ridiculous stuff...haiz...hmmm funny how a simple thing can trigger such events...hmmm no linking...gg a little nuts again...ok this is definitely not a good sign...yup...and i emphasize,it spells disaster!!scary thing is,i think it kinda reciprocates...darn...argh...help me...hahaha like i said in my previous posting,it doesn't matter if nobody understds as long as i do... yup...kena chase out...haiz cuz its e sec time now...hahah  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok this is totally crappified.msn just got hanged...horrible!!and i was half way thru opening the Josh Groban song tt winnie sent me!!!arghhh!!sad...more like irritating.now i can't even close e msg box...just taking up space...haiz doesn't anybody teach courtesy in her country?i was in my room,waiting for dinner,then after the bell rang,i sorta just did my own stuff la...waitin for her to come and call me...then i waited for like rather long,then i just went down la...she has alr finished her dinner,happily talking to some guy...wth...do unto others wat u want others to do unto u...please...it's just polite to knock on my door on your way out since u have to pass my room!and its obvious im back since my shoes are outside!please la...i have half a mind to just stop being kind or wateva u call it...ugh so not gonna help if u need me to do anything for u...u can jump down and die for all i care...ugh... ok tt was a little strong...i will care if u die,cuz i will have to comfort my roommate and try not to laugh at the same time...ha hmmm tt was evil...haha but if i dun voice it out it might find an outlet thru my action,rite?haha so this is good for the soul...ha such misguided thoughts..haha today,we trained for the capt's ball thingy again...haha started damn early like abt 2 liddat...then all the way until 4 plus liddat...so tiring..haha my muscles were dormant for so long...now suffering the aftermath of such vigorous training...haha played frisbee first...it is actually rather fun...haha and we(never played frisbee before) actually managed to score a few times...haha and peng siang and xuan yu are damn good la...its rather crazy...all the screaming and running...haha and jimmy rather poor thing...always kena chase after the frisbee...haha  oh gossip time...haha tg wanted to go to tampines to meet up with her jjc frens...then she insists tt she doesn't wanna go alone cuz whoever tt she is meeting will most probably bring frens as he is traveling all the way from jurong east...so ah hem...haha she managed to convince somebody to go with her...or rather shd i say force...as this person is definitely not happy bout it...hahaha and shit i just realised tt their gp ppl also know about this and they also find it rather amusing...so ah hem whoever this person is...watch out...hahahah if u still dunno who i'm talking abt,ask me...haha... hmmm...i realised tt digging e dirt out allows for the cleansing of the soul...haha totally crappy...as hui wen would say:shingy's logic...haha muakz tribute to u...haha k la...run out of grit to pick...haha should really go do my econ hw...haha oh ben,my buddy...oh well kinda miss his crappiness..haha haiz...hope he is doing well in sa...haha ok really shd go...oc starting soon...haha
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hmmm i just realised tt i'm rather incoherent...oh well dun care...haha it doesn't matter whether anybody understands...as long as i do...haha
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      oh well....just spent like a lot of time tryin to improve the looks of this thingy...haha hope it looks better...argh physics test tmr...i totally forgotten about it until huong asked me y i not studying(cuz i stupidly said tt i got nothing to do)haha...oh ya vuvu's another uncle just passed away...it's sad la...cuz the first uncle tt passed away was her close uncle...then now less then a month apart she hav to face another blow again...haiz i also dunno wat to do la...very bad at this kinda comforting stuff...but at least this time she got over it faster...now nearly back to normal alr...but still a bit zonked out...hmmm scared... ha havnt done my econ rem hw yet...die...foo so gonna skin alive and hang me up to dry...:P hmm they wanna 'train' for captain's ball tmr again...haha i think there is no need...since they are all alr like so pro...and e guys are like rather good la...but run ard too much...i too lazy to chase them down to mark them...haha  oh darn physics test...die die die!!! and SATs coming up...my future is going down the drain...hahaha...exaggeration...:P hmmm still a bit loose above the neck...haha quote from kiu... and stupid mr ng...he made us all come down to meet him just so tt he could read out to us how many times each rooms forgotten to switch off the lights...and my room dint even kena la...stupid...then last time he called me into the office then started reprimanding me abt lights off and how we always forget to switch it off...then when he flipped open his file,there is like only one entry of it...stupid idiot...but he still trying to prop his stand so he said:improve alr...but if u do tt again then i'll take away both ur light tubes...stupid man...he take away e room lights still got our table lamp and our own various lamps which are all very bright...arghhh...just hate him...haha dhana said he'll lend me the six episodes of oc...haha and cuz of some error he cant burn me the love actually vcd...so sad...haha reminds me of the song last christmas by wham! that i always get stuck in my head..haha hmmm lova tt movie...oh ya watched troy on sunday..haha sponsored by my mum...haha good movie...although e plot kinda falls apart occasionally...hahaha and i'm gonna treat my couz to watch shrek2 as her b'dae prez..haha can't think of anything to buy for her anw...hahah can't wait...hmmm wanna watch laws of atttraction...think it's coming out tmr...at least tt's wat e newspaper says...hahah oh well so sad can't go out with carol cuz she got training day and nite...in the national canoeing team...rep s'pore...and she's so busy...now tt she moved over to ghim moh practically can't meet up with her until the hols when she move back to tanah merah...oh well sad...haha hmm i just realised whoever reads this blog won't know half the things i'm talking abt...cuz it involves so many groups of ppl...frm my sec life to choir to class...haha and even winnie and shit(who i can say know e most) doesn't know wat i'm talking bout when it comes to carol and mr ng...haha hmmm i'll try to fill in as much as possible...but not today...extremely late alr...they are closing soon...haha oh kiu on phone duty today...then she just sat there typing away while the phone rings away...hahah then when she finally realised tt she's supposed to ans it,it stopped ringing...haiz...tt gurl ah...hahaha... and beetsma keeps mixing me up with ching chui...even when me and chui are side by side...crappy senile old thing...haha but she rather cute la...haha hmmm starting to slip into crazy mode again... must go study study...
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Suddenly inspired to start blogging...beats writing a diary anyways...haha it's crazy!!!been a crazy year so far...just had a crzy week and gg to have more craziness as jct comes!!!arghhh...lastly, i AM crazy...wow...feeling the healing effect now...haha after admitting tt...but then makes not much of a diff since i say tt everyday...ha...ok gg crazy again... and it's so damn cold in here...bloody...its so hot out there...hmmm like i said to winnie jjust now,e greater e diff in temp, the greater e change in temp experienced...ok so am i crazy or wat? established fact:i am crazy...ok now tt i can continue...let's see today was...i dunno... lost?haha better type faster b4 my craziness sets in again...erm better start w yest... my mom came to s'pore to watch my choir concert...so far so good...then yest,she was leaving...then complicated stuff abt selling the house came up...my aunt's hse...then got even more complicated cuz i got like tonnes to do and skipped sch on mon...then at first it was like me,mom and kel go our diff ways,then it got complicated cuz my aunt asked my mom to see kel back home...so my mom,who was alr super late cuz this bunch of nana taitais came to see the hse,had to follow us to bishan when she had to meet her frens in tiong bahru...so to make it easier for her i volunteered to bring kel home since i got time anw.then she insisted to bring her back...which in e process of arguing which way is e best,she scolded me and made herself later... and complicated things even more...then we got in e cab and argued some more...scolded me, us more like it,then i cried then when we got to bishan e stupid taxi driver got lost... so conclusion bad day...might have been happier had i went to sch...at least can slack during foo's period... oh well to day is just weird...but i can sleep again!!!haha recently cant sleep well..tired but just cant seem to go to slp...oh abt e slping thing...i slept through the whole of physics lecture...it felt good...haha...oh well feelin kinda bone tired...haiz...sleep sleep sleep...  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      original plan for yesterday:go midvalley watch some jap film fest movie with sis' frens...everything going according to plan...went earlier to do some shopping...when it was time to meet up with her frens,mom called and told us we are gg to genting immediately!going for Annie the Musical... synopsis:the candid and touching adventures of the world's favourite orphan comes to life on stage.and the orphan is named(drum roll....)...Annie(duh!)! my mum got six free tix...and it was vip seats...it was RM160 each... it was rather cute...funny la...the little girls playing the orphans were soooo cute...so hyper...reminds me of crystal...haha...and one of the female leads looked like the actress in love actually(hugh grant's natalie)and the 'old man' who adopted her looked like the granpa in gilmore girls..so basically it was an entertaining nite...haha not too bad after we hauled our butts out of the cold...managed to actually enjoyed it a bit..haha as i was too busy catching up with my mum,i dint do anything else...ugh...and same for today... did nothing...made my sis ferry me ard to buy sandals...hahathen got stuck in traffic jam...at least we bought one in the end...haha i was like trying to do everything today...as if i'll never get a chance to do them again...haha... ugh...gg back tmr(dread dread dread)...haiz... oh well,my father is into this fruit craze...haha bought a lot of fruits back just for me...hahahahahaha  gg to eat now...ta...must as well enjoy a bit more before i go to my doom tmr...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i am blogging too much...and i cant work the stupid scanner..ugh...irritating...today,i din't do anything at all...i mean anything tt will save me...haha crappy...spend too much time slacking...i am so totally distracted..i mean...ugh  WTH AM I STILL DOING HERE?  dun worry...it's called stress relieving..haha but i am still sooo dead... *rips self away from keyboard..ouch*    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i have a great brother...he is simple indescribable...he is so smart,tt he managed to crack the connection from the cpu to the monitor so we cant even start the com..i mean who else can achieve tt?if my sis dint have to get her documents immediately,i would still be disconnected from the rest of the world...okla tt was a bit too much...but everytime i come back on hols,my bro crashes the com...last hols it was breaking the keyboard and the mouse...last last hols it was blocking the internet...somehow...i dunno how he did it but he definitely managed tt...and last last LAST hols he destroyed the monitor...i mean JUST LEAVE THE BLOODY COM ALONE!!!! ok done with tt,i must say a few last words,and invite all of u to my funeral...my life might end anytime...depending on when my mum finds out tt i have my jct(she doesn't know its a major exams)right after hols and tt i havnt studied...if i managed to get back to s'pore in one piece,it can happen when my heart just stops from the anxiety and stress when i finally get it in my brain tt i have a lot to study...or if i live thru the preps,i might still die when i see the paper on the desk in the exam hall...or if i am lucky(or should i say unlucky)enough to live thru all those,there is still a chance my life will end in mrs goh's hands(and all the rest of my tutors) when she knows my results...and if i still managed to hang on to my miserable life,i wil just kill myself before i tell my mom my results... see i'm SOOOOO dead...nite
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ms Heng is getting maried!!and it's tmr!!!confirmed by cieh shuang and mdm cheah...muahaha..and rach actually smsed the old senile wrinkled thing...haha oh and she sends her love to all the moor house gals...haha this is rather crazy... ok must really go now...haha
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      my post last nite wasn't published!!!haiz...irritating man,write a long one and then com hanged!!haiz..haha oh well...i shall try to rewrite it..if i rmb...haha hmmm watched harry potter yesterday with my sisters and bro...was disappointing...the 3rd bok is like the best so far and the movie is just a total let down...i mean it's not bad la...but no climax le..if u dint read the book,it just suck la(sis opinion)..haha oh then after tt we ate at this hong kong restaurant..kim gary...very nice restaurant...it has super cool mirror thingys as one part of the wall..and while  was eating,i realised tt a lot of the staff are like short..ad i mean rahter short...they have this counter where they serve the dish and the waiters collect to serve to the ppl...those who are short ractically cant even see over the counter la..she had to tiptoe to stick the straw into the drink she was serving..rather funny..haha then the guy who served our beef steak with spaghetti and twin sauce...was crying when e served...he came along,put it down,sniffed and sobbed and told us tt the plate is hot...not to touch it...haha rather cute...he look so por thing...haha... then we went shopping..haha was great fun..mb tt's cuz i havnt done tt in a very long time..haha she wanted to buy sandals..and i made her walk ard in stillettoes!!muahahaha oh and i was clicking ard,then i found my pri sch frens in freindster..haha for once,friendster is useful..haha oh ym it's been such a long time...wonder if they still rmb me?hmmm... A Voice Within    Young girl, don't cry I'll be right here when your world starts to fall Young girl, it's all right Your tears will dry, you'll soon be free to fly     When you're safe inside your room you tend to dream  Of a place where nothing's harder than it seems No one ever wants or bothers to explain Of the heartache life can bring and what it means     When there's no one else Look inside yourself Like your oldest friend Just trust the voice within Then you'll find the strength That will guide your way If you will learn to begin  To trust the voice within     Young girl, don't hide You'll never change if you just run away Young girl, just hold tight And soon you're gonna see your brighter day     Now in a world where innocence is quickly claimed It's so hard to stand your ground when you're so afraid No one reaches out a hand for you to hold When you're lost outside look inside to your soul    When there's no one else Look inside yourself Like your oldest friend Just trust the voice within Then you'll find the strength That will guide your way If you will learn to begin  To trust the voice within   Yeah... Life is a journey  It can take you anywhere you choose to go As long as you're learning You'll find all you'll ever need to know     You'll make it You'll make it Just don't go forsaking yourself No one can stop you You know that I'm talking to you     When there's no one else Look inside yourself Like your oldest friend Just trust the voice within Then you'll find the strength That will guide your way If you will learn to begin  To trust the voice within   Young girl don't cry I'll be right here when your world starts to fall    my big sis brought back a taiwanese series today...and it's like got this little bo in it...so cute!!!haha got super rosy cheeks...totally cute man...haha i gg a bit off alr... haiz..must go study...haha as if i will...
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i cant think of a title and i just cant stand it when i dun have a title and the whole first lie of my post get stuc there...clogging up the whole place la...haha oh ya...i was gg to say tt i have to cut down on my hahas...there are just too much everywhere!! oh well...my sis' fren gave an extended invitation to the raleigh ppl to go street lugging!i mean how cool is tt??but of al ppl,she goes like...it's too dangerous,u cant go...and i mean just cuz she's scared does mean some accident will befall me...i dun even know how to spel it.. oh well...everything is so slow moving here...i mean i love the slacking ard...though it is definitely not helping much with my studying...ugh...overexposure to tv...hmmm never tot the greatest thing in my life rite now is discovering a new disease..haha and it is highly contagious too...since i caught it fr my bro...and i havnt even seen him for like 24/7 yet...ad he broke the tap in the kitchen...now hae to use the tap in the back kitchen(this weird hse has like two kitchen...one wet and one dry)...not tt i dun like staying at home or aything...its just tt they moved when i was in s'pore when i was in sec1...and i just like never stayed long enough to know it...i mean i feel like a bloody guest in my ow hse...just tt i gotta do the chores too...ha i mean wat a sad life...nomadic or wat?i mean i stayed at hostels longer than i stayed at home...and my bro is alr like taller than me...just a bit la... oh and i am reading way too much...i'm like done till the last few pages...just kinda saving it just to prove tt i havnt finish the book yet...hence,not reading too much...i mean who can i fool?ha...i am seriously gg crazy...losing my mind...ugh...u know,i shouldn't publish this...  bah! i'm to lazy to write another one... 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      haha finally it's home sweet home..haha i cant rmb the last time i'm so happy to e home..haha last nite was an interesting trip back..haha cuz i tumpang this time,so i brought a lot of stuff...then i realise tt i cant get it tiong bahru myself and i wil have to take cab...but had no cash..haha so i asked jul...amazingly he agreed...oh wel yu chii wet home the nite before..and mak wet ack on thurs..then chui owe me money but she wet back a day before me...hence the brokeness..haha..oh well...then both of us looked like dunno come from where one..haha each carrying like three bags..haha then we tok mrt somemore...rather funny sight..i think...haha  then my mum asked me to e at the hotel by ard 530 liddat...so i tot leaving at tt time la...then their meeting ended at 630...and then after tt,they had this discussion thingy...continuation of meeting in the lounge..until 8!haha then only we could leave... it was a rather nice trip in all cuz i slept like all the way...had dinner at 930...then slpt all the way again...then got horrible traffic jam from muar to seremban...took an hour to get thru tt stretch which usually taes like wat?20 mins?haha...oh well...they tot it was sukma...but i have no idea...so we took e old route back..meaning thru seremban to kajang...haha the road twists so much and it is pitch black la...cannot see a thing lo..hahathe when we got to this part where they started building a highway,its like on a roller coaster...it climbs all the way up,then comes all the way down..haha wat a ride...got back home at like 2am?haha i positively wasted this whole day...haha watched tv,played piano,read a book(i bought yesterday while waiting for my mum...went to tiong bahru plaza to walk ard...ooh it's titled 'the devil wears Prada'..such an absolutely cutesy trashy book),and listening to music...now watching mvp qing ren...haiz... i shd start mugging soon..yest,when i was packing,i realise tt there's a bloody lot i have to do...ugh!!die die die... go away while i kill myself...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i do believe i just redefined the meaning of study...haha ever since the 28th of may(frog's b'dae),i have been going out every single day...and tt is my studying...let's see...i covered it until tuesday...oh ya wat did i do on wednesday?i went cycling...with eunice,mak and jul...biked all e way to ecp...and how long did it take us?ONE HOUR!!haha is tt pro or wat?haha i can't believe it man...and on the way back,i banged into this man who happily walked into my path...i mean he was walking along the side of the pavement...so i had space to cycle past him...then he walked rite in front of me...i tried to avoid hitting him...which led me to fall off my bike(i mean the bike i borrowed fr ching mien)and into the drain...i mean i had no great injury...just a tiny cut...but the front brake came off...so me and jul exchanged bike...haha rather poorthing...then we decided to cycle to feng shan to fix the bike but for gotten it's public hols so shop closed...in the end just had our dinner there cuz somebody dint pack for us...haha... so we had to go down the next day to fix the bike la...then me and jul cycled...then when we reached tanamera,it started to rain...so we seeked shelter at the bus stop...haha then got stuck in the hdb...it's all interconnected la...then after wat seemed like hours..we cycled to the bike shop...the uncle there look and said huh??like tt only ma...then he took the brake and just put them together...and both of us were just staring at it...haha and then started laughing...oh my wat a day...haha so time wasting la...i mean how dumb can it get...after all the trouble we had getting wet and all...ugh!! oh then we played table tennis...me,jul and chui...haha kena trashed by chui...haha then i was there to like pick up balls...haha and i saw this notice board they have...then i think there is this pic of sherri(11/04) really young..mb sec1?haha rather skinny and cute...nv know she in ahs tt...haha then i went to my aunt's place...for those ignorant,my aunt migrated to perth alr...but couz st here...so occasionally she stays there... oh then i went to buy her dinner at parkway...then i met tiang lim,yuen leng,walmond and si wei there..haha they were like,bf leh?then pretend to look ard..haha then when i was gg to leave pp,i met carol!!haha in front of mph...and both of us were like...i wanted to call u out but my phone died...haha rather interesting..haha so i dragged her to go back wif me...oh ya i impromtu decided to go over cuz it's kel's b'dae and she alone there like so poor thing..then met tiang ilm they all again..and they were like bf leh?then i pointed to carol...haha oh on the way to pp i met joan fr indon on the bus...i havnt met her like for 4 yrs,after she left ri and ij...oh my...brings back many many memories...haha we were so young then...oh well..haha turned out she went to bedok to swim and her relatives stay op pp..haha then we went back and gaved kel her dinner...and then she dint wanna go out any more...so me and chan went out again...haha went to eat ice cream waffles at gelare..oh did i mention tt i ate mud pie at coffe club with pee on sat?it was super delicious!!haha had hershey choc syrup all over it!!haha...back to gelare waffles...then we went to play pool at e place beside pp...it looked very scary...cuz its old la...then got trashed by chan...haha but it was very fun!!haha then went back at like 11...haha..and the tiramisu cake tt i bought for kel melted...it was like all watery when i woke up this morning...haiz...oh well...haha but all in all it was interesting..haha oh and then i finished my batteries and i had this sudden urge to go ikea!!haha mb cuz i read the sales page today...haha oh well...gg crazy la...haha so i went all the way there with ching chui...basically just wasted all my time...(although i brought my sat book along)pei her go buy train tix at tanjong pagar...then studied at anchorpoint...in delifrance...and i met juliana!!!haha i turned ard and suddenly she was like sitting behind me...haha so qiao...haha she in sajc hockey..haha kinda unbelievable...although i wasn't like really close to her in ij but still nice to see her..and her sis is so darn tal...i think taller than me..and skinnier than me too...haha  oh then on the train back saw this jap girl...she looked like she jumped out fr some comic book la...just several inches shorter and wider...haha and her skirt was so bloody short she must as well just have wore a fbt shorts...haha but she got muscular thighs...haha a bit freaky..oh well...doesn't do justice to the nice comics tt we see...haha ok la...crapping too much... it's shit's chamber concert today!!!ugh!!!i wanna go!!!haha but sadly i can't...supposed to study...as if i have done much studying...haiz...so sad...then i wanna call mak to go somewhere wif me also cannot...cuz she went home yesterday...sigh...oh well at least i'll be home soon...haha going back the day after tmr..yay!! hmmm chel's anderson sec drama teach was featured in newspaper today...something abt geps...oh and chan din't know abt my uncle!and she said it's like so incredulous...actually it's just the same case abt her being a national canoeist la...haha both are like so out of this world..haha
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yay!!it's finally here...not tt i anticipated it a lot kinda thing..haha but too much freedom...i have been going out everysingle day since friday...now,is tt crazy or wat?haha fri went with carol,sat with perpetua,sunday went to st mary's church at bukit batok(it was featured in Life!...super good architecture...very beautiful place...)mon went bishan,watched confessions of a teenage drama queen with kel(and then we got a free ticket after we watched the movie)...and today went to orchard with mak and jul...haha but today wasn't a very fun outing cuz it rained on the way back...and jul's shoes can't kena water..so we had to sneak into east meadows(teresa's condo) for shelter...but in the end it was no use cuz the rain dint subside and we came back freezing cuz the wind was very cold and strong...haha oh and on friday,i changed my watch strap!!!haha so hapy...now in place of the yellowy transparent strap,its now a white base one with very beautiful butterfly motifs on it..hahaso nice..haha then it gave my fren the idea to buy a watch with ugly strap then change it to a nicer one...haha crappy...oh and on fri i watched the day after tmr with chan and we met so many ppl in cine la... saw benjamin tan yeong ming(he's so far the first person i found with the same yeong..haha)he's doing much better now...at least he look like it...haha i hope he is happier now...haha  then on sat, went with pee...my, tt gal has grown,man..haha love tt crazy gal from the top of her crazy hairdo to the tips of her 3-inched feet...haha just as siao as i am happy to find her..haha i never knew she was nj's harmonica band conductor!!haha...can anyone believe tt she can conduct?haha interesting images flashing across my mind...haha haha just now the tampines directs came back from ps(plaza singapura)..haha and got me this badge which says "WHAT THE HELL?"haha cuz when they saw it,it reminded them of me...haha so sweet of them..haha rather heart warming... and i borrowed love actualy soundtrack today!!!haha so happy!!and it's very nice la...haha got a few songs stuck in my head alr...hahahah thank god it's hols...or shit and poo will start getting these superbly beautiful songs stuck in their heads too...muahahaha haiz...so sad,winnie leaving on thurs now..haha actually it's not like anybody dying..so oh well...haha... going to watch wedding planner now...ta...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      then it was shop shop and shop till u fall..(for me,it's literal) thurs day was the first day...was supposed to watch spidey with the class...then the girls dint wanna go,so it was my gang and the guys..but they wanted to watch in tm cuz timo wanted them to play soccer at tampines..so we ap-ed them and went to lido to watch...it was damn good!!haha and there were so many ppl i met...long lost ppl i havnt seen for yrs!heh...there was steph c,rainna,eileen lim,yi fen,cheryl lam,dian,cherie and grace koh(both are now half brunettes)and not to mention the tjcians tt we saw...basically just a lot la... then fri day went pooling..with eric,huong,julian,chii,and jo..chii and jo's class outing also in parkway...so halfway thru they went to join their class...it was fun then i pei-ed huong cut hair in century square for 20 bucks!and she still dare say i spend unnecessarily...hmph!then eric they all went to lido first to buy tix for ard e world in 80 days...but by e time huong is done with her hair cut,i was too tired and lazy to drag myself to lido and back again...dun think i cld have stayed awake aniways..ahha saturday was shopping day with ppt and licia and denise(my ij gang..haha) sunday i went to chijmes...the 150th anniversary thing...it was rather boring..but i cant believe it's alr five yrs past...i still rmb our 145th...when i was a wee little thing being on stage for the first time in sec1...then saw selvam..her husband is cute!haha then tan aye leng suddenly walked up to me and huong and started talking to us...freaky!!then i saw jen chu..she sends her regards to my parents...saw tan kheng hua(the pck actress)she has such a cute daughter.. later on i met up with clara koh..she went to sydney for the hols and we were reminiscing abt the crazy time we had there and all our crazy antics..i rmb walking into the pub to watch football while we were walking back to the hotel..haha then kena scolded like shit.. anw,then we went shopping!haha then i bought a top... in the evening i met up with vu and wen wen in ps..then i bought my bag...finally!!!...and i finally bought chan's b'dae prezzy..haha bought this"wash away your sins" lip balm from topshop...cute!.. haha  to be continued...  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      pretend it's back to 19th of june...... argh if i added up e amt tt i have studied,i wld only have done a quarter of wat i'm supposedd to have finish by now...so die...die die die.. then i met up with chan...studied with her on sunday nite...i think,or was it monday...anw,the week flew past very fast...cuz i practically spent everyday in changi studying!!can u imagine tt?me!studying!...achievement.... then by fri day:i am very proud to announce tt i have finished three subjects!!hahahaha...tt will of course,not include econs...haha...so proud of myself...and e award for making the best miracle goes to....(drum roll)....Shing Yeong!!!yay but tt was all i cld do...after tt,i just cant bring myself to study econs...haha then,monday came,chem was traumatising...i was just so totally frozen there...then maths was ok...but still rather shittifed cuz i dun even know wth i was doing!!gp was crap...i was rather zonked out alr...then econs came and went...i got very stressed and the paper was so shit tt i am rendered speechless...physics was better than econs...but if huong thinks its hard,imagine wat  it was lke for me...so at the end of the day,econs won the award for suckiest paper...hooray...(i hope foo is reading this..ha!) and then,as fast as it came,it was over!!!!!tt called for major celebrations...(now tt i'm looking back on it,it seems pretty fast.but when it was there and not budging,it was torture!!) 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>