<Blog>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Not much to say today.  Just getting started.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was having a bad day or maybe a bad week.  Josh I know it is just a house.  The house is more of a metaphor for a bigger deal.  Dana, we are trying to rent it we will see what happens.  If we can do that we won't lose money as fast.  Brandon, thanks for your words especially about leadership, I needed to hear that.  Karla and I are going to try and make your wedding. We will see what happens.  If Dana is going to be there we may sneak in and sneak out.  (just kidding we won't come at all, really just kidding we will come even if Dana is there.)  Today is a new day.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Not that I am any great source of wisdom, or that I can convey my simple thoughts very accurately via the written word, but I need some help.  I feel sort of abandoned.  I have complete faith that God is in control, I also have complete understanding of the fact that I don't really have to know the Lord's reasoning for things.  But recently I have felt abandoned by Him.  I know that leaving camp was something I needed to do.  Jacob needed better care and he has received it.  I have confidence that my current situation is a stepping stone for other things.  It is a good firm stepping stone, one I will be on a while.  However, in the last year I have never felt more ignored by our Lord.  We have had our house on the market in TX for almost 18 months and I still own it.  Was I not supposed to leave?  Can all the positives here that I thank God for out weigh my departure.  I had complete faith that God would take care of the house and so far I remain disappointed.  It's not like it's been 3 months and I am begging for an answer.  It's not that I am angry or telling God do it now.  What is happening is a detachment that I can not describe.  I can't let the past go and face the future and so I remain in limbo.  Sooner or later I am just not going to care anymore.  I know all that God has to say but nothing seems to help.  How can I share God's love and His desire to have a relationship when mine is currently disfunctional.  This is the one thing that "Time" doesn't take care of.  Time only makes it worse.  For instance when someone dies we rely on God and over time we learn to function with the loss.  Time here continues to make the void grow larger.  Time in this instance is like gas to a fire.  I really don't think I can give it to God anymore than I have.  Each day I pray and I put it in God's hands and when tomorrow comes I wonder and so I pray and put it in God hands and the cycle goes on.  I continue to ask for God's will to be done.  So is this really His will?  With each passing day I feel more and more like I am making a mistake.  So God says "his grace is sufficient for me."  So now I am a numb forgiven child of God.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>