<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wsup,  BRUIN BHANGRA tonight, yes i am going and i am going to see MANDEEP!! damn, i cant believe we pulled it off... "unstoppable"  imma see him next weekend too! wOoT!  summer school @ reseda's gonna be hella tight.  damn, today.. i havent heard our phone ring that many times. =) felt good.  my aunt's here from india and she brought all these cool things with her! God she is so awesome. shes so FUN, u knooo !!  anyway, today is tha day man, imma give mandeep his letter and that poem i wrote fo him.  dang, things have totally changed around here in the past week. hella crazy.  crazy in love? mandeep?? nahh....  (; *wink* i lovVEEeEEE yOUUUuUUUu. fa showness  almost 4:00pm. its sunday man. tomorra got a day off to spend wit mah aunt.  things are going well. *knocks on wood*  so yeaa..someones talkin shit but whatever i dont care. who cares?? right mandeep??  shoutOUT to HOMeGURl: arTi. comin in 10 days. soo excited, i love her man.  English Sonnet about King LEar?? PeicE of Cake. imma ace this final.  " realize all the things i don't need,  all the things i dont deserve/   so i try to live simply,  in a complicated world... "  member?? May 1st homie.  damn all those old conversations make me crack up cause like... "us" jus happened u knoo.  coo coo  today imma wear YeLLoW. =) stand out so that MANDeEP will be able to recognize me.  damn. today better be fun.  better be?? it WILL be. me and mandeep?? togetheR?? how can it NOT be fUN? =)  woohoo, im so happy.  aight well, i gotta take shower #2.  ill check ya'll lata.  NOOr-i 
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wat up.  today, chillen in computer class and its a Minimum DaY, 12:26pm today baby.  haa, yesterday, talked to MaNDeeP fo a long time yesterday but its never long enough. damn, babe i love you.  JuNe 2nd, is a tuesday, you gotta get that ForM seNt today homie. PLEaSe. i hope this works  Magnet Dinner tonight. Have fun.  volunteering?? no. i dont wanna.  hha, you like ThA BaBe, huh..said it yessterday..sounded nice. its not weird. ur my babe, only mine.  JUNE 5th, im comin fa show, history teacher is plannin a trip to Disneyland that same day and shes makin us go, right after tha SAT testing, lets see..id be going to Reseda at like 11 in the morning and comin back at 11:30 at night, if i am able to go to disneyland.   damn.   anyway, mandeep read ur comment yesterday, i LOoOOooVvVvVeEEEe yOUUuU. damn, those comments jus make my day.  STAY IN CHEMISTRY young man. I want you to do well.  fck that Julie chick, tell her to stop messin with my man. if she fcks up another grade fo you, tell her to meet me at reseda high 3:30 on tha pe field afterschool on a thursday. she's jus jealous.  tell her Jealousy aint gonna get her no where in life, so let her kno that she needs ta get over herself.  =)  didnt that go well? haa..  if i go to the mall today, imma fa show get mandeep something.   gotta find tha money. =)   Jeramiah is tha homie. tell Toby shes missin out on what a great person you are. (;  what else is there to write...  today moms not coming home til like 8:00pm. damn thas a long time, so ish jus gonna be me and mah dad...  hmm, wonder how thatll be. ( =/ )  so hungry already dude, dont know what to do.  took a quiz in math, aced that sht fo reall man.  NOTEBOOK CHECK in spaNisH, gotta write down all tha tarea, but w/e  didnt do tha classwork yesterday, o well. gonna get in trouble. damn it.   MoOd: jus happy thinkin bout mandeep's smile.  mandeep you gotta show me how all this stuff works man, like all this makin beats and recording... the WhOle SyStem. i wanna learn. but, only from YOU.  =)  You HAVE to go to resedas summer school, please im begging you, and God, let this happen. let this work. if i cant see you this summer or after June 5th, imma be crying. 10 weeks MaN? without seeing you, ill try to live, you said you might not be able to even talk on the phone, i dont know what im gonna do. Praying.  aight well tha bell's gonna ring, so ill cheCk You later.  love, noor
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wsup,  today Balraj asked me if i want to go to Canada with him on June 20, but hes going alone and we both have friends in the same area, and he has an extra ticket cuz his sister decided she doesnt wanna go anymore.  how sweet, he asked me, but tha Mama isnt gonna be cool, so i had to turn down tha offer.  but thanks nanu, =)  damn, if mandeep can go to summer school @ reseda, my summer will me MADE. i wouldnt need anything more, today at nutrition i gotta pick up tha form fa show.  damn, computer research. how gaY is that?  wanna go to india so bad, jus got a letter from nani there, i wanna go see her before i loose the chance.  put in earrings today after like...3 months. =)  so supposedly, in my computer class..we are supposed to be researching sites, and pick a destination..where we wanna go. She told me Montreal, Canada...and i have to book a trip there, and write down a bunch of crap. sOo boring.  Oh! so the "bonding" with my ma.. it was aight, felt good to be able to talk to her about my day at school. =) was coo..  im so hungry, ate cereal in tha morning but im still hungrayy.... =/  anyway, i think imma leave it here fo now, ill come back when i reach home.    NOTE: tomorra- minimum day 12:20pm. goin to tha mall probably, gonna introduce Raman to a few homies. Volunteering?? who knows.  latee  nOoR
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wsup,   its 9:31pm. updatin now while parents are gone fo a walk. i wrote my 2 Extended Metaphor Poems:   Poetry   Like the writing in a lover’s journal Like the dance of dreams   on dew dropped petals   in the early morning’s light Like the optical illusions   and unspoken lies   that slides away a mask   and finds another hidden disguise Poetry Like the love misguided    from an innocent heart Like the scriptures in holy books Poetry Like the silence in me   that is stronger than words    My Vision of You  My vision of you   is like the sea shells washed up ashore like the footprints in the sand   that lead my heart to yours My vision of you   is like my mute eyes staring into yours in twilight   like a feeling of purity   like a person who is blissful The vision I have of you   is like the sweet dew drops on a rose petal My vision of you    is one that is heavenly   yeaa..damn it i hate when i sign on and someone i.m.s you and you say that youll be right back and then when you sign back on theyre not there, its like wtf..  anyways, talked to MandEep today!! jus now again, damn i love him.  im gonna make it on June 5th fa show. Dont trip, but how long you want me to stay?    GOoD LuCK manDeeP on ur SpaNisH FinAl. i love you.  but damn..ur dad sounded Pissssed. i love you!! i always seep to get you in trouble, im so sorry. damn, our bad luck. Sucks. =/  ARTI emailed finally, today!! i miss her like WHoA, cant wait til she comes.  Bruin Bhangra, yeaa not going. Sucks ass cuz i really wanted to see mandeep.  rAnjod, man you got to get on tha liNe cuz man you GoT iT baD, and wHAAT bout next SundaY? i gotta get THAt gift. cau' damn man, why you gotta leave when i said id be right back??  gotta practice mah singin, might actually have enough money to get a teacher this summer. i need a coach, im not lettin go of this dream no mo'  i gOtta stop hittin my legs wit that cane, gotta get these moves right. i can sing it, do tha routine, tha cane movements are all that's left.  mandeep, babe, go to summer skool @ reseda! you gotta go wit tha plan i said on tha phone today.  homie, MehEk, her rhyme:  yo wsup mah name is Mehek and when i saw yo face i was like what-the-heck haa..shes catchin on tha RaP gAME fa show.  balraj, good lookin' out man, thanks fo lightin me up today, so glad i got u at schoo. dont kno what id do without ya. u got mah back i got ur back, its all good.  parents are walkin, when they come back, im goin back out wit mah ma and we gonna "bond"..tell you how that goes, tomorra in second period.  played bball at nutrition fo like 10 mins. but i scored 10 points. =) coo coo  RubEl, are u sure i dont need an invitation to ReSeDa's graduation? cuz i HAVE to come.  no magnet dinner next year? oh well. =/..short 8 ppl, if i had money and had the chance to go with mandeep, i sOO would. trust me on that one.  aight well, rent gotta be comin home soon, and i gotta get out. cHeck ya'll lata.  PeACe -thA wOmAn. 
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wsup,  i wrote another transformation poem but i dont think i did it right cuz tha task was: --> Write a poem describing a worker becoming a part, a tool, or a product of his or her work.  This requires your intimate knowledge of the particular work process and the attitudes, responsibilities, and language connected to the work. (NOTE: Do not use any form of the following words: become, change, tranform.  Instead, make us exerience the transformation.)  instead i made an object (the room) transform or change into something else:  The Room  I feel that the room around me is fading The walls are shrinking Narrower and Narrower as my heart gives more and more to you 1 sq. foot, 2 sq. feet smaller The walls are closing in  quickly fading... The shadows on this heart of mine are disappearing Where is all of this going? The walls are melting down The doors to this heart are opening   My heart,   the room,  in which all my love for you,   is stored.  yeaa..i think imma change it around to fit tha Task tho..  MANDEEP! i was reading your comments and someone moved past me to get to another seat in the class and i clicked the mouse and i clicked and accidently deleted one of your comments.  damn, im so mad!  yes i called you babe, hahaa.. =)  I loved the song you played for me that your two homies spit on, i loved it. wow, im so impressed..i cant sing that well haha, i suck compared to D'ana.  =/, oh well, imma keep practicing..get better.  so whas new, im sittin here, so bored in computer class..damn, does she ever shut up? she is scared of me..imma make that bxtch shut up one day.  MAndeEp, June 5th..Dont know anymore, but ill let you know.  Dad said to tell the "sophmore class" that i wont be able to make it, but im workin on it, reall hard...i wanna see you so bad, you dont even know..when my dad told me that yesterday, i felt like screaming, i took my pillow and started crying. i dont kno..if ill be able to make it there, but tha surprise party?? WhAT date is that? Time? Address?  WhERe WhEN HoW?? u know, tha information. im so sorry, even tho my dad started talkin to me, hes still pissed and not lettin me go anywhere, but tha party ill ask my mom when mah aunt comes and she HAS to let me go, ill be like..shes/hes turning 16 and they really want me to go, and blah a bunch of bs.  stupid shit man, i swear.  mandeep i love you so much, you dont even know man, i'd fckin die, jus tell me tha time and day, i'll do it.  stupid research project in a fckin Computers Elective?? how gaY is that. damn..  got a 93% on my chemistry test last week.  dont kno bout math yet, but im makin up a test today at lunch. math teach is bein a bitch lately. whatever tho its coo..  Ranjod's birthday is next SUndaY!!!!!!! gotta get a gift, find some money..  JUNE 9th- ArTi is ReAcHin AmErIca, wOoT. i am so happy, cant wait to see her..we gonna take drivers ed togethaaa.. eY mandeep, lemme kno if you wanna take classes too, we can see each other there yea?  summer school @ reseda? hows that lookin?  will it happen?  only in my best dream..  Registration is on July 1st 8-12:30pm. be there if Mommy says yeaah. *praying*  aight well, i gotta do some work fo this stupid research project, damn shes so stupid.  ill check you later.  NoOR   
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Honor Court Election? haa, didnt even know about it..  this friday is Magnet Dinner, $25 at Sportsman Lodge, but i cant go obviously..sucks. i wouldve gone with Mandeep. our first dance =)  so wsup.  feelin a little lighter day by day becuz ma said she loves me and kissed me befo i went on tha bus today. she be coo....for now. haa..  lakers lost = sucks.  we still gonna make it  started Matrices in math yesterday..damn multiplying them are confusing but whatever i get it.  cant chill wit Tom no more cuz she thinks we talk too much, hahaa, reading the board?? no i dont think so.  mandeep, i wanna call fa show but ur mommy man, id hate to get on tha bad side of her. i keep thinking that i see you in school..my heart stops for a second. skipped a beat...  all i can think about is seeing you next and wishing that you were with me, wanna give you a BIG HUG. liike HUGE babe.  Harry Potter comes out on June 4th! wOot, my and didi are gonna try to gO to the premiere, if its at UCLA. really wanna go to Bruin Bhangra still, and imma ask bout "my friend's" Surprise Party. haha, MandEep!!  mammiji brought a suit for me from india, it fits! im so happy, she brought so many cool things for me i love her man she cracks me up. went there for dinner yesterday and since i finished my hw, i got to watch Dilwale..with her, that movie is all time favorite for both of us.  Mandeep i am so proud of you, you Won on Friday and i never really got to express to you how proud of i am of you.  i will always be proud of you in anything that you do, always be right by your side.  i love you and remember that. i'll only watch that dvd with you, dont want to watch it alone, i wanna be with you..  June 5th- fa show imma tell my mom its a Sophmore Class Activity. what time you want me to be there?  i wrote a 'transformation poem for English class last night, wanna see??  here it is: The Writer  While writing, the writer embraces her thoughts Spills them on her blank pages She writes and writes about her beloved With ink all over her hands, she smudges her paper Thoughts scatter everywhere Making imprints where they belong Feeling rough and empty While he is full and vibrant She is lost Yet he is found She looks out upon him A lost page of his imagination She looks down to find that There is nothing there but a torn out page  i dont know if that makes sense to anyone, but it does to me in some way. yeaa..  ahh, today i have piano, i wanna hear whatever my teacher has to say..  shiet, i forgot to ask my mom if i can stay afterschool to help out with magnet dinner decorations!! ill call her at nutrition/lunch.  so hungry...half an hour til nutrition. coo coo..  anyway, what else is new? lets think...  watched Holes in history, that was a coo movie, i liked it...i was picturing whatever i read in the book..everyone did a reall good job in acting it out.  mandeep, i say that me and you jus go to Puerto Rico right now..no?? i mean theres not that much time and..damn we got shelves to fill hOmie. yeaa?? aight coo..we'll book two 1st class seats. =)  aight well, im gonna go..gotta pay attention, i think shes looking at me right now.  latee.  NoOR-i
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wsup?  WAS chillen wit Tom until he had to switch seats. stupid teacher thinks that when hes reading to me whats on the board that we're jus wasting time. dumb bitch.  dad still hasnt looked at me once.  today is Day 4 of wishing i was dead.  last night i went over to Rekha auntie's (my god-mom) house and told her everything that happened on friday and she talked to me.  its so sad, she knows me better than my mom.  talked to mandeep on the phone yesterday,  i tried not to cry on the phone but i couldnt help it.  i am so glad he has been with me all the way.    yes im still going to try to go to UCLA Bruin Bhangra but i doubt it very much. still trying.  talked to balraj this morning and told him bout Ramandeep, so on friday Rekha auntie, mehek, manny, raman, his mom, and mammiji might go hang out at the mall. and balraj and raman will be able to meet for the first time.    raman has finished 11th grade, he says "whats the point of going to skool for one more year...im jus going to work at uncle's subway in seattle anyway.." i really want him to finish at reseda and go to college with me, he'll be much better off. i never thought we would meet after those 3 summers and here he is..right across the street from me. haa..coo.  parents have me on check 24/7 and i dont know what to do. i dont want to eat dinner with them because all i hear is the sound of my spoon hitting my plate.   yesterday was by far the worst piano recital i have ever had.    friday- i thought nothing could go wrong and everything went wrong that day. i couldnt see the 1 person that makes me feel alive, who makes me feel like im a gem..like im the best. who makes me feel sane, makes me feel good about myself mandeep im so sorry.  i feel like i cant breathe at home, feel suffocated.  today a few friends asked..."how was it on friday?!!" i just shook my head. i didnt know what to say, i felt like crying but i was able to hold it in.  summer school with mandeep would have been awesome, i cant even imagine what my parents reaction would be if i ask again.   'Everytime I try to fly I fall without my wings I feel so small'  What happened to the Angel of the Battlefield?? she's gone.  peace.     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      feel so numb  had my piano recital today and i messed up so bad, i couldnt even focus, i jus kept shaking and on top of that i was crying so yeaa didnt help at all.  my piano teacher still clapped and many said "good job", stupid liars.  i didnt hear a single word from my parents. my dad hasnt looked at me for 2 days  i havent stopped shaking since friday, every move i make seems to be a mistake to them  i hope i get to talk to mandeep today becuz hes the one person that makes me feel like im at the top of the world, and i jus..i feel so bad. i always mess things up  my parents are dead for me. no more..  i love you mandeep.  noor
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello  felt so lifeless and so helpless yesterday, didnt know what to do, what to think  Mandeep, i owe you the biggest apology, i got grounded yesterday. parents found out that i have had a bf before and they said they couldnt trust me to go. i need to talk to you on the phone, im really really sorry mandeep. i was looking forward to yesterday so much and it all crashed the minute i stepped in the car afterschool.    i wrote a poem for the rents:  All those thank yous I owe you All those times you said you want the best for me All those times you told me you loved me  Now   That you have given up, I don't have the chance to say a      simple Thank you All I wanted to hear was a "I'm proud of you " but I've lost the chance I screwed it up for myself    and now... what's the point in trying? I'll never be trusted, never be considered good for anything  The memories of you, I am throwing away for when I replay them, all I shed are tears There is no love inside of you left for me No space in your heart, now I give up too and sit in remorse    and discontent thinking of what to do The memories of you fade as I lose my heart and no...   there is nothing I can do.  Back from the SAT, it is 5:13 pm.  Cried all of yesterday, all of today, cant stop. dont know when it will.  I cant pick up the phone and call anyone or else a beating occurs.  I dont know what else to do with myself.  suicide is the cowardly escape.   Day 2 of wishing I was dead.  out. 
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wsup  chillen with Tom in 2nd period.  he's tha HomIE!  so...goin to GranaDa HiLlS ChArTer HiGh SchOoL today, :)  cool song:  HOOBASTANK- the Reason  I'm not a perfect person As many things I wish I didn't do But I continue learning I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you  I'm sorry that I hurt you It's something I must live with everyday And all the pain I put you through I wish that I could take it all away And be the one who catches all your tears Thats why i need you to hear  I've found a resaon for me  yeaa..  tomorrow..12:00- 4:30 i'm takin tha New SAT AGAIN at csun at night- going to Ankur's house  i wish Mandeep was coming :(  damn, had a dream that i was drivin around yesterday..ever since i drove ive been havin those dreams where im driving, soo coOol.  got my New SAT Score- 1660 out of 2400 HAA..that is ridiculousy bad, but whatever i don't care. let's see how i do on Saturday  soo, gotta look good today cause today is a special day fo seeing a special someone hahaa, ish gonna be tight  BRUIN BHANGRA, tha homie Ayda got some extra tickets, imma buy one off of her and see if I can make it down there fa show. hopefully ill get to chill wit mah sis that day, damn i really hope that she can go.  gotta get Balraj 2 tickets too..i don't know what imma do..how imma get them.  ill figure something out.  "if God can't see us together then he must be Blind"  =)  9 days 'til my aunt comes from India fa show man, doin it Desi style, haha  damn today is going so slow...getting picked up from schoo today, so that i can practice piano and take a showa befo i hit tha road fo a 15 minute drive to Zelzah Avenue, aT gRanADa HiLls baby. not that far away  damn, i need a car.  i cant wait to give MANdeep his letterrrrr!  he's gonna fa show beat me in length but its cooo.  i want to see the expression on ur face!!!  Christina Milian- Dip it low    but Mario Winans is tha maaaann.  aight, ill check you all later  peace
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sup cool guy  its 10:12 and all i can think about is tomorrow and how it is going to be.  i wonder..  tomorrow i get my New SAT Score, wonder how i did...its out of 2400.  haa..probably got like a 900 or something, hahaa. oh well.  damnn.. : life goes on No matter if your life is tattered And you can't fix what went wrong Life goes on Your battered and your life is scattered You're a hook in your own theme song Life goes on You're a fighter but the grip is tighter And you know that you can't stand long Life goes on Yours only get brighter Life goes on Yours only get brighter Life goes on  - Pigeon John & Abstract Rude  ^ somethin that caught my attention  i cant wait to give MANdeep his letter tomorrow!! its reall long, but i think he's gonna end up beating me.   my letter got reall boring after a while..i'll be surprised if he's able to finish reading it without falling asleep.  i cant wait for Arti to come, JUNE 9TH baby..yeaa...  so it looks like a 95% chance that imma be on a plane to India in about 2 years.  it's gonna be a hard goodbye, big weight on my back rite now.  aight well, 10:17 now and i think i should get some sleep, i have 3 tests tomorra...studied, lets make it all worth it.  i hope i can pull up my grades and make a smile appear on my dads face at the 20-week.  all ive been wanting to see for the past 2 years.  a smile, and a "i'm proud of you" from him, but i haven't gotten that yet.   i'll keep trying. no doubt.  Bruin Bhangra  sucks major, was looking forward to meeting up with Mandeep.  mood: reall low  im out.  always, nOOR  
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1 day left.  wsup p.i.m.p.'s   sittin here with Tom, jus chillen. computer class is hella gaY homie.  Damn, nothing can go wrong tomorra, i am so excited to see ManDeEeeeP!!!!!! wOoT!   haa, talked to Jess yesterday = CoOlnEsS :0! hahaa, yeyaa  Got mah hat. LooKing good.  aight latee, bell is ringing as i type. ONe  A.O.T.B. 
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like the way you walk The way you talk The way you dress The way you smile I like the way you are The way you ain't I like your honesty, integrity, It levels me, so please don't ever change..  yeaa... wsup.  workin on composing a song..dunno how its gonna come out tho..piano's hard..  damn..    all prayers go out to Phil.  hes gon make it, hes strong fa show..he aint gon sell anyone out jus like that..don worry bout it, hes gonna be okay.  damn..  god fuks us over the most.  "I may be able to speak the languages of human beings and even of angels, but if I have no love, my speech is no more than a noisy gong or a clanging bell. I may have the gift of inspired preaching; I may have all knowledge and understand all secrets; I may have the faith needed to move mountains-but if I have no love, I am nothing. I may give away everything I have, and even give up my body to be burned-but if I have no love, this does me no good."  shit..  out.  thinking bout...  MAnDeEP!!!!  late.
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh my god.   yeaa mann..5 hours.  beat that.  i love it...   oh my god.. damn
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      babe..  You should’ve known better than to think I would leave  You should’ve known better than to doubt me  It don’t matter if you are up  matter if you are down Either way im gonna be around  You should’ve known that I would stay by your side  You should’ve known your girl was gonna ride or die  And it just don’t matter if ya rich or poor  Out or in doing 5 to 10  You should’ve known better  What makes you think that I would forget about you  Think about it who comes to see ya  Every Saturday and Monday I was on that receiver It’s me your girl your life your world  My family your friends they just don’t understand  They say I should just leave you lone But I say that they should just leave us lone  Don’t u get it    I Love You, I LOVE YOU.  I mean that to its fullest.   Im sorry about what I said, what I wrote, I think imma delete that..after this. I still feel like a really fcked things up, but imma think that until things get totally okay, which i hope is sometime soon.  It was the first time I felt like.. I  really  hurt someone, badly.. felt like..I lost you, felt like things would never make it now..felt like I jus Fcked Up.  I couldnt help but cry yesterday, I couldnt stop, felt like..I would never make things okay, like..I drowned.  But I Love You Babe. I love you.. Imma keep loving you for the rest of mah life.  I love you  more than anyone in this world. More than you love me I can garuntee that.  Damn, how much i love you..  i love you so much.  so  so so  much.  i miss thursday. i miss YOU.  God, how i love you..  man!!  i wanna see you right now, i wanna show you..jus my neerves get in the wayyy!!!!!! arrggg, otherwise wow, you'd know..  i love you mandeep.  god, im like crying..damn, i am so sorry for all this bullshit..i am so so so sorry.  damn, i love you..  i dont know what i would do without you, i would kill myself..the second i found out i couldnt be with you..i love you so much mandeep, so much..so damn much.  ...  damn..     i love you.      ......    noor.   
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      fcked up.  so my parents call reseda to find out my grades because they dont believe that my report card is gonna come by mail and they dont think it should take that long.   I AM SO MAD.  its like..id rather shoot myself, it'd be much less painful.  IM PISSED BECAUSE I DIDNT EVEN GET TO TALK TO MANDEEP BEFORE HIS LIKE..MOST IMPORTANT DATE IN HIS LIFE: COURT DATE. I WAS BASICALLY LOCKED UP IN MY ROOM FOR A LONG ASS TIME WITH NO PHONE NO NOTHING, NO NOTHING. NOTHING WHATSOEVER.  I cant even like..find words to express how sorry I am Mandeep. I am so sorry, so sorry, I wouldnt be surprised if you dont talk to me for a while.  I WAS SO PISSED. YOU DONT UNDERSTAND.  your mom hates me and my family but loves iishas?  hmm,  comforting.  How bad is my luck. The crappiest things always happen to me.  LIfes a bitch whats your excuse?  I need to get out of here, I cant take this shit anymore. The one person I thought I had, I think I just lost..yeaa, the one person that made me feel like I was the best. wow, how that can change in a matter of 1 day.  that phone call..its so hard to imagine whats going to happen next. i thought the worst.      make it work? how will we manage to do that.  im your life? so if i just died one day, you would be finished too?  I dont know anybody who could care more about you than me, not even your mom would or..could as a matter of fact.  gifts for me?? Theres NO point, YOU ARE MY GIFT. YOU. THATS IT.  May 21st = the day I fucked things up to the max. I dont think we were ever the same or ever will be.  this isnt working.  i dont want this life anymore. i wanna get out, i wanna jus..die.  no matter how hard i try, i will never ever be able to make up for how i fucked things up. never.  no matter how hard i try, i just cant make things okay. i cant, theres like no way..not possible.  people say it'll be okay, people say just be urself and everything will roll through jus fine..  HOW CAN I FUCKIN BE MYSELF WHEN I DONT KNOW HOW THE FUCK 'ME' IS?  HOW  TELL ME.  this is some fuckin bullshit, this life?? life is beautiful?? HAa..  LOVE is BeAutiful?? Love is pain. espeacially when people like me are fucking things over for everyone.  seems like im good at fucking up peoples lives. i mean..thats what it looks like to me.  i dont even know what to fucking do, i dont know what to fucking say..  theres no room for me in this life anymore..  no room.  out.  status? dead.  
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeaa..  ambiGOus PLAYaz (12:14:48 AM): dam.  ambiGOus PLAYaz (12:14:49 AM): u a soldier  memories.  Life goes on No matter if your life is tattered And you can't fix what went wrong Life goes on Your battered and your life is scattered You're a hook in your own theme song Life goes on You're a fighter but the grip is tighter And you know that you can't stand long Life goes on Yours only gets brighter Life goes on Yours only gets brighter Life goes on  - Pigeon John & Abstract Rude  yeaa..  hit me up when all tha frustration mellows down. for now, who knows whats going to happen.  i wanna see you but then i dont because then i will have to say bye for a while.  i dont know.    feel like im on auto-pilot.  out.  something close to how i feel:  The walls in this room are slowly closing in, like a slowly working punishment for an unspoken sin. I came to my bed at just after eleven, but last time I checked, it was almost seven. The sun is newly shining but it seems very late. Is there some reason I've been so cursed by fate? Every night I just wish that I could drift off to dream, waiting expectantly until the alarm starts to scream. I'm weak and exhausted but carry on nonetheless. It feels like it's killing me and it's hard, I confess. Every day I face a Battle, another total emotional drain. Constantly, I'm being criticized and told that I'm to blame. I'd give so much to sleep in peace even for just one night. Nobody seems to understand that every night is a harder fight.  peace.  
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sup.  feelings are coming back. feelings of..  i dont know.  thursday was reall fun.  it was a day where i had nothing to worry about. where i felt like i had everything. where..if someone were to kill me i'd die with a smile on my face..  yeaa..thats how i felt.  but im hurt too because i couldnt assure the person i was with that i would never leave them. they still walked away with the feeling of insecurity, the feeling of If. the feeling of "is she always gonna be with me?"..  i dont know.  they'll never know how much i care. never.  i dont know what to do.  out.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sup..  power is knowing you never have to prove shit to anyone you command your own destiny and your own decisions and life is your bitch.  yeaa..  woo, chemistry is over!!!!!!! thank god.  so wsup.  mandeep, i hope you are having fun! i commented on tha blog. chek it out when you get a chance.  haa, i am so proud of you man. you DID IT!  CONGRATULATIONS TO YOU AND PHIL.  im havin a party for you both! =)  aight well, spanish and history finals tomorra and then i am DONE!!!! wOo!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  im out.   studying.  latee, noOR
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sup.  taking tha computer final right now. this shit is long but its easy as fukkkk..  mandeep!!! i hope you are having a nicee time interning. sometimes you get to do cool things.. =). i miss you tho, a lot.  took my math final. haa, i had to stay in nutrition to finish it. and tha given time was 2 hours. damn, thats gotta be a bad sign.  dl: "night butterfly" Mental Sky good song.  so, wsup.  mandeep.  damn i cannot wait til you get your cell phone. i should get the same plan that you are, then it would like..always be free and out parents wouldnt have to get mad at us fo raisin up tha bill.  i got something for you. i still havent gone to pick up tha other gift, cuz its sittin in LA. but i call every 2 days to make sure its still there. ill give you what i got on thursday. something that you can keep with you all tha time. keepsake.  ^if thats how you spell it.  aight, almost done..wit tha final. shit man, this crap is Annoying.  i cant wait til thursday!!!!!!!!!  2 on 2 mandeep?? haha, i better start practicing like hell. i wanna be good. Page (  HOOBASTANK- The Reason. damn thats a good song.  Egyptian waR? in caRdS? lets piss off tha english sub today..hahaa, suzy.."Excuse me young lady, you are laughing too much, what seems to be the problem??" shiit, that was hilarious. we couldnt stop laughing after that. stupid subs..  lunch next!!! gotta brush up on that basketball. shiet..2 on 2 and i aint gonna embarass mahself.  haa, aight well im out.  ill post again later.  nOOR  
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn.  jus got off the phone with mandeep.  i thought my ma knew that it was him becuz i was like "..hes helping me with my chemistry" and she was like "....k" and i was like yeaa. but i guess she thought i said "she" and tha only other gurl ive been talking to on tha phone bout skool is Tina.  shit man. she just got done yelling the shit out of me. i agree, i shouldnt have called but i couldnt NOT call either.  this is so hard.  mandeep, dont be sorry. it wasnt your fault. YOU didnt get me in trouble. i got myself in trouble. maybe i shouldve called later when i was done.   damn, but i had to call.  shit happens, what are you gonna do.  shit i am never gonna tell my mom "a lie" or so she thought about whoever is on the phone again. i'd rather just say who it is straight up.  damn, i feel so bad. i mean, it wasnt that bad. but like, shit after she called me to her room and yelled. fck.       out.  noor  
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so wsup.  mandeep, i dont think i said what i wanted to say that clearly today..if you call tonight, maybe i will be able to tell you. i love you so much man.   i am so sorry i didnt call you back today, my mom was tripping like crazy. sucks. i mean, i kno what shes sayin but if i dont talk to you fo one day..damn, in my world...all hell brakes loose.  i hope you had fun tonight, bowling! =)   tell yo friend thanks fo lettin me call on tha celly. hahaa..  so wat new.  mandeep you are my saathiya fo life man. i love you so much.  me??  simply in love.  felt so good to be able to talk to you online fo like a whole hour un-interrupted.  ooh yeaa.. ;)!  talked to ranbir today, awesome guy.  i am proud of him.  sleepover mandeep?? fa show. we can kiK iT. =)!!!  me and you...alone...dancing in the sand..  we are gonna do that.  damn its like only 9:00pm.  i want it to be twelvE! so that i can talk to youuu!!  aight well, i should get back to studying..maybe if i keep studying, time will go faster yeaa?  aight then. i shall write again later.  latee,  NOOr
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn.  wsup.  how u doing.  just found out that I have to get 77/75 on mah math final to get a fckin A in tha class. dumb bitch. she said she wouldnt even round it fo 2 fckin points. ARGGGG. no no no!!!!  graduation- reminder- I gotta get the time so that I can tell mandeep.  MAnDeEP!!!!!!!!! YOU KNOW WHAT? YOU KNOW WHAT? KNOW WHAT? WHAT? HUH?? PUNK> KNOW WHAT?? I Love You. =0!!!!!! hahaa...I love you. Damn, I really love you.  I dont think I can say that enough.  Today you can call me, but I will most probably call you befo' you call me fa show. Unless you call me while you are at work.   *Next Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday are ALL Minimum Days!  I shall be home at 1:20p.m.   Damn, on Wednesday June 9th, 11 kids from our school got arrested for drug dealing. we have Narks at our school that go around, pickin out tha people that drug deal, or anything else. damn... ghettO aSs SkOol.  so..getting my nails done I dunno when, but mama can just do them.   I wore Kajol today after so long and everyone kept lookin cuz I havent been wearing makeup fo a long time. haa..  I have a chemistry test today that I didnt really study for..oh o.  FINAL REVIEW today in computer class. Ugh, I dont wanna do this.   So yesterday I come down at like 12:30am..gettin some water befo I go back to studying, and I see my parents downstairs in the family room watching their own wedding video.  So I watch a lil bit, my parents looked like they were teenagers who didnt know what they were doing.  They looked so much in love.   Even now, my parents....oh god....... my dad still asks my mom to the movies and my mom gets all ready befo goin' out wit my dad. I think thats hella nicee. =)  LAkErs- pshh..we gonna win tha next two games no doubt.  damn, I have so much sht to do before finals.  but as my babe says, "just stop...fo one second. dont do anythin.." i really need to stop. take a fckin break.  I think that I think too much. Even didi told me that..  I need an inhaler damn it. I cant even play at lunchtime or nothing because I dont have it. If I dont get that shit today in tha mail, Imma go to the doctor and get it. This crap, pisses teh shit out of me.  Mandeep I neeeeeed you rite now.   I cant wait to go to Venice man. Im gonna JUMP ON YOU!!!!!!!!!!  haa..I am so excited  Mandeep I care about you a lot a lot a lot a lot a lot a lot. =). haa, I confused you....  What else were you wondering about? ...  mood: well, thinkin about mandeep so how can I not be happy? duH. =) !!!!!!  mandeep, update your blog young man. I wanna comment tooooo. hahaa..  your comments are the best.   and, go out with your friends!!! I want you to have fun.   aight?  you hear me?? ...HAVE FUN.  aight well, I need to go. peace ouT.  nOor.  p.s. fuk life?? nah...jus fuk math.  
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sup.  got mah english final back. 90/100. I still ended up with a B in the class. ugh.  spanish..i dont know what I have. I think I gotta try hard on the Final. Math, oh God..help! Chemistry, I think I need a miracle.  AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH. *pulls hair*. I cant do this anymo'  mandeep! I started writing you another note. This one is going to get long until I see you next Saturday most probably. Damn I miss you.  Yesterday, I felt like my emotions could never be crushed. i-n-v-i-n-c-i-b-l-e.  I Love You.  aight well, I think I should get back to studying for finals.  I'll catch YoU laTER. or..should I say..JUMP yOU!!! :)!!  latee, noOr
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sup..  yesterday, one of the best conversations i have had in a long time.  shit man, i noticed this morning that my eyes change color, but only in the morning and only some days. shit thats soo weird.  i still dreamnt in black and white last night. but i cant remember my dreams.  haa, came to school today lookin like a bumb. =), damn, i really didnt wanna go to school today. i wanna go to mandeeeep.  mandeep i miss you so much. i wanna see you like right now.  felt so good talkin to you las night, im sorry i had to go..i didnt want to but..my terminator dad came. hahaa..  so yesterday Bobby i.m.'s me and send me tha link to UTT's website. haa, i was like "yeaa i saw already, i keep mahself updated, dont even tripp." and he like "coo..i made it myself"..i was like "coo, good job" damn, they need some self-confidence.  so i did my chem homework in math and didnt let her see it so she couldnt take it away...dumb bitch.  justin!! be confident in spanish. who gives a fuk, everyone wants to get to the fOoOOd!! ;).  mandeep, i lub you.  ranjod! congratulations: homie got tha liscence on monday!!! o and...HaPpY BiRtHdaY on SunDAy!!  wow ok..so my computer teach posted a pic of me on my yahoo!free-webpage.. wanna see? (THe wOrSt pic of MysElF that I Have ever sEen)  http://www.geocities.com/noorschool2004/mypage.html  yeaa...horrible pic.  damn mandeep...so yesterday i was lookin at an album and you gotta see my baby pictures..there this one where i'm doin like some kind of james bond pose, hahaa..  damn this class is so boring. jus until next friday! thats it.  today, math tutoring from 5pm-6pm.   trying to get a singin coach, but i dunno. gotta call around. im not letting go of this dream.  August 15th- wanna go to camp with Mandeep, Ranbir, Jessica, Preeti, etc. it sounds coo, thanks fo tellin be Ranbir.  yeaa..this weekend i dont think imma be allowed any phone calls, unless i jack my moms fone and talk at night. cuz its free weekends.  yeaa..  anyway, i think imma go. i dont feel so good. tummy hurts and crampinggg!  haa..  peace nOoR
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sup...  fuckin bitch math teacher, she fuckin knew that i was done with tha assignments fo this week and she still took away my fckin chemistry homework. thas fcked up, i WAS FCKIN DONE WITH THE WORK. fckin bitch.  talked to mandeep yesterday!!! so he's gonna be working... you bought me tha gift i always wanted.  i love.  but the best gift of all was to be somewhere in your heart. i love you so much mandeep.   yesterday when i picked up the phone to call, i put it back down cuz i thought your parents were gonna flip like crazy and blow up on you. haa, ur mom doesnt kno we are together. but tha papA is tight. i always liked ur dad man, he was so funny, like whenever it was my bday he would tease me to the MaXx. haha...i was watchin a bday video yesterday at like 10:30pm..haa...  damn i wanna be with you so bad right now, everytime i pass by that tree. damn..saturday comes back. yesterday..spent some alone time wit tha tree afterschool, worked on some hw..was coo.  yesterday was my spanish presentation and i was nervous as hell, so i stumbled on a few words..and she had to correct me in the beginning. i hope i still did ok atleast.  in chem, i dont have my fckin homework and no notes anymo, so i dont know how im gonna study fo tha test on friday..stupidest shit, i swear.  today are student body elections, voting fo amy fa show. i talked to amy yesterday!! she wasnt THAT mad that i said i didnt kno her that well, she said still come over and so imma see if i can kick it at her house over summer fo sho. =)  rESeDa GRaDuAtIoN- JuNe 17th. what time? i dunno yet. gotta see RubEL graduate! wOo! im so happy for you.  mandeep, check out YOUR blog, i commented that one day...but write in it!! or should i say...type. =)  have an english vocabulary test today, 5th period. damn my english teacher is a bitch.  shit my nails are getting long, imma grow them out fo graduation, so they can look nice....lol...wtf am i talking about? i dunno..  mandeep! wearing PINK today!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! =) yayayayayayayayyy! hahaa, yes my favorite color is PINK.  damn, 1 more day til arti is here. today is gonna go so slow.  its only tuesday and it feels like a thursday.   haa, ur mom cracks me up... "aRE YOu GOTH?" hahahahaa....ohh mann. that was great.  saw part of Tere Naam yesterday night..was a sad movie. shiiit..  Glamour shots in like 2 weeks. mandeep, imma give you a nice ass picture. =) if they come out good...  damn its cold today.  Abhaas thank you for helping me out yesterday. :)..  anyway, my mom and my massi are goin to UNIvErsAL StUDiOS today!! wow mann, i wanted to go..i hope they have fun together. both sisters..thaaaaaaasss coooo  aight well, im out.  love you mandeep.  ur girl, noor
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha.  sup.  mandeep, i am so sorry that i couldnt call yesterday. when i went downstairs after getting off the phone with you, my dad was like "is that all you do? jus talk on the PHONE?" and im like.. "that was like my 2nd fone call today.." and he was like "so?! thats enough." and im like.. =(.  shit. i felt so bad.  yesterday, i went to my god-mom's house in the evening jus to kik it..made a music video hahaa..jus fckin around yesterday.. it was coo.  made a music video to a fckin trance truntable remix. haha, it was coo.  i loved saturday. damn, to see him...to hold hands, to jus absorb the whole feeling of being complete..i love you mandeep.  yes! omg! first kiss fa show- JUNE 5th, 2004.  =) hahaa..  today, my english final is due. here it is..  In the dark I stand-alone in the rain You don't seem to notice all of my tears You could never understand all of my fears Uneasy, giving all of which you gain Good my lord, those who love "most" are insane Regretfully, time will cut through the years What one feels is not always what one hears Honestly, a soldier filled with disdain  You realized the error of your ways Alas, you felt my loving hand in yours With my soul depated, you found a way Come with me now, into heaven's bright maze Looking in your eyes, I see noble shores Our story, one to remember and say  shiit..i worked so hard on that, and it sounds like a peice of bs. thats like the biggest peice of shit i have ever written. hahaa..o well. i wonder what i'll get on it..  then today, i have my spanish presentation for tha FoOd project. haa, i cooked a dish and i have to present its ingredients and procedure on how to cook it, in spanish. woooooo, i hope i can pronounce all of that shit. i have butterflies in my stomach. shit..  mandeep! we didnt take pictures...o well. that day will come when i am going to take you away forever and we are gonna open up a studio along with our library. but that's after you become a professional rapper and i become something..hahaa, aight man, i gots lots of planning to do on this project.  haha, i jus thought of my dreammmmm when i ran back and jumped on you. !!!! hahahaaaaaa. god i love that dream.  i read your comments and damn, your comments flip tha script. i feel like ill never be down again when i read anything about you or think about you...anything with YOUUU.  we are going to be making our own webpages today.  shit, i didnt do my chemistry hw. uh o. =0!  yessss i got my eyebrows done. hahaha... 'grew back like all hell broke loose' =)  did you get my letter back? shit man, now that they found out bout..u kno, i dont know if your ever gonna get it back..i hope you can..someday..  shit man, waxing hurts like a bitch. got WaxEd yesterday and shiiiiiit, you did NOT wanna be there. i was like crying. lol  aight well im out, time to shut this bitch up.  latee  
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey  so yesterday, i saw mandeep!!!!!! one of the best days of my life, including BRUIN BHANGRA.  man.. mandeep, damn. yesterday was the best man, we could jus Kick It. withh no mo' worries.   =) !!  yeaa..then i had to come home to a working hell. i have so much work to do, its not even cool.  damn, so little time.  always concerned about the TIME. sucks.  aight well, enough breaking.  nOor
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sup cool guy  first things first: good morning babe. =)!  how u doing. i hope thA MAma didnt blow up too bad on you yesterday.   damn, we try soo hard. what more do we need to do?  we have tha worst luck.   finished TIMELINE is history yesterday- a kickass movie man.   yesterday, i was answering Trivia Questions so that I could maybe win a plasma TV on my friends celly! hahaa, was answering questions about cartoon shows.  Harry Potter today. so excited. Mandeep! I wont have my moms celly cuz shes not dropping me off, she has to work. but I'll try my best to call you from there. I love You.  This Saturday, indian party??   what I wanted to tell you was that...everyone knows that we are going out Ppl: Vishal, Ankur, Rohit, Rupal, and Payal  everyone knows. but you know what?? I DONT REALLY GIVE A FUCK. if they have a fckin problem then thats their shit that they need to deal with.  anyway, took math test today and I think I got a good grade. =)  damn, today I'll be leaving right after school and I won't have time to check if there are any comments on this thing. shit man, dang it!  Had another dream... I show up at a party, its an American party in LA at some club. (In this dream...MAndeep and I haven't met yet) so I walk in and sit down on a seat and watch my friends dance and have fun. Mandeep spots me and I spot him.. I go up to him and ask if he wants to get out of this place.. the answer is: yes  so..we get out and we stand outside fo a while and try to get to kno each other and discover that we were childhood friends that were separated. it was so cooool.  we chilled tha whole night..walked down to this park and chilled on tha swings. damn, it was night time and we were OuT. =) hahaa..  it was so.. dressy..yet so childhood like..i dont think i described it that well. but damn, it was a good dream.    Mandeep. Dont lose yourself. You can fix all this bullshit. there is NOTHING that you cant do. I have soo much faith in you, you dont even know. I Love You so much. I am here til tha very end babe...til tha very end..  'til next time..stay strong.  noOR.
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wsup,  first of all: good morning to my babe.   Graduation @ REseDa fa show. tomorra..seeing Harry Potter at 5:30pm in Westwood, wOo!  FINALS are coming up, and today I got a chem test, gotta study at nutrition. =/  I got a 9 out of 10 on mah math quiz, sucks cuz I made a careless mistake...cant wait to see what my dad has to say to that.  damn, I was looking forward to summer school at Reseda with Mandeep, but I dont think thats gonna happen no mo...tha due date fo tha form was ysterday and I Highly Doubt that his mom took him.  June 5th, is the last day I am going to see him.  I wont be able to see him all of summer, wont be able to hear his loving voice. write letters? i need your address Mandeep.  EVERYTHING is UpsiDedoWn. it sucks a lot..  slept with wet hair yesterday and now I think I'm getting sick, I sneezed like so many times las night. or maybe...someone was thinkin a lot bout me. =)  damn, I really need to get my eyebrows done...they grew back like all Hell broke loose. hahaa..  continued to watch TIMELINE in history and damn, that is a cOoOl movie. haha, Time travel is tha best..  so..my aunt knos how to knit and shes makin wool tops fo me and didi...=) cOo man, I'm excited to spend tha summer with her.  6 days = arti. wOO, i miss her so much.  damn. I really gotta start practicing my songs on tha piano, "its a big waste of money" if I dont.  Mandeep, you cant give up on yourself. You gotta stay wit me on tha field man..I miss you and I Love You, I will never lose faith in you...you are YOU and you have to keep rapping and keep your life the way YOU want it. If something is not right, lemme help you fix it. If you dont like something in your life..Ill help you fix it. Dont lose yourself.  "keep ya head up" remember?  cmon boy, you will never lose me, NEVER. I'm always gonna be here. WE can work together. If you need alone time to get these priorities of yours straight then do so. I'm gonna stick with you 'til tha very end.   Jus wanted you to know that no one can ever care more about you than I do.  Good Luck today in school. My prayers are with you all tha time.  still be prayin in tha mornings, fa show.  i LovEeEee YOuUUu.  Whenever you need me I am here Mandeep.  Down to ride 'til the very end, it's me and my boyfriend.  you mean so much to me.   peace niggaz,  n00r
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sup playas  had a dream last night. mandeEp!! ok, gotta tell you.  it started with my window and tha sun coming in my room, i was sleepin. but for some reason on a bigger bed. you are here. you come in and bump up, "WhAAAaAT YOUu WANT, uhh YOUuU KNoOooo I GOT IT, wOO.." i wake up, and start laughing, its summer time. and we got free time.  i get up.. one sock on, one off. collared shirt and big boxers..jus comfortable.  so i get up, wash up, go down stairs. and you are already downstairs waiting..writing... i sit next to you and we talk and spend time.   we decide to go out to venice...get in tha car.. im driving, stick shift, all gears in place, everythings coo.  got tha SummerTime CD and we jus BuMP.  we go to tha beach and play volleyball wit a bunch of homies that met us there.  so after a while..you come up behind me and pick me up and jus start walking..we both start laughing and damn it was jus soo much fun.  damn, reall nice dream.  so wsup.  started writing another letter...today was takin math notes and jus got bored..so i started writing.  mandeep!! i commented on ur blog. jus luckily i told myself that this wasnt my blog before i started, haha. =)  stupid papermate pens, damn blue ink gets all over tha place.  my Bhua is having a babbbyyy!!! i am so excited..found out that the baby shower in on june 26th.  summer school at reseda: Please.  how tha hell are people failing a fckin elective computer class?? gaY.  back on track today...yesterday watched part of TIMELINE in history, damn thas a freaky movie. Time Travel fa show.  HARRY POTTER ON FRIDAY, going to tha premiere at UCLA on friday, maybe..if mah sis can find out about it.  working on writing a song, started it yesterday..i dunno, jus messin around.  Song of tha Day (thanks to mandeep): "High Road" Swollen Members     damn i hope you and Phil make it through tha day. i LoVEEEE YouU.  aight well, im out.  lata  nOoR
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3:50pm  jus talked to mandeep. i feel goooood. i-n-v-i-n-c-i-b-l-e, yeaa babe.  BRUIN BHANGRA. best damn night of my life. there wit mah babe.  was tite.  i love youuu so much mandeep. tell ur mommy to take to to RESEDA RIGHT NOW YOUNG MAN. damn, june 5th?? will be the last day i see you? maybe.. my death day.  i just have to say thank you mandeep.  how i feel: "Thank You"- Dido Album: No Angel  My tea's gone cold, I'm wondering why I got out of bed at all the morning rain clouds up my window and I can't see at all And even if I could it'd all be grey, but your picture on my wall it reminds me that it's not so bad it's not so bad I drank too much last night, got bills to pay my head just feels in pain I missed the bus and there'll be hell today I'm late for work again and even if I'm there, they'll all imply that I might not last the day and then you call me and it's not so bad it's not so bad and I want to thank you for giving me the best day of my life Oh just to be with you is having the best day of my life Push the door, I'm home at last and I'm soaking through and through then you handed me a towel and all I see is you and even if my house falls down now, I wouldn't have a clue because you're near me and I want to thank you for giving me the best day of my life Oh just to be with you is having the best day of my life   i love you.  ur MY babe.  love ur soldier fa life, nOoR  
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn, last night was a night to remember.  i come home with a friend and she hasta work on homework, so im chillen on tha comp and i sign on AIM. mandeep was online already, and damn i couldnt stop smiling..i was so happy. so he i.m.s me like right when i sign on and says that hes gonna kik mah ex..Vishal's ass. and im like wtf.. so i call him and he reads the conversation to me and i cant believe what hes reading..and shit man, i was fuckin pissed off, i felt like fuckin screaming.  so then, he tells me that they both are gonna fight each other at reseda, 12:00pm on saturday. what tha fuk..this is horrible.  fuk man, im still so pissed.  this is my shit with vishal and shit man, all this shit hasta start. i thought all this shit was over.  why does he fuckin care if im going out with someone or not? why tha fuk does he care...move on, damn.  so then i call up vishal. and his fckin mom picks up tha phone so i hang up obviously, so i go back online and i.m. him askin him fo his cell number. and hes like "why do you want it" and im like "cuz we needa fuckin talk" and so he signs off on me after telling me.. "say what you wanna say here" and im like "hell fuckin no, i wanna TALK to you" and he signs off on me.   so i call him up and im like "bitch whyd tha fuk did you sign off on me, i didnt appreciate you fuckin signin off" so i start askin him all these questions about what jus went down wit mandeep and this foo flips tha script and tells me "i said like 10 good things about you and maybe one thing about me..and you think im the bad guy??" i was like "tightest guy vishal?? tightest guy? what tha fuk are you thinking?"   so this kid starts bullshitting me and thinks that i havent heard the conversation already. so then he hangs up on me. and i call back and im like "bitch why tha fuk did you hang up on me, you got tha decency to hang up on me?" and hes like "later late.." and hangs up again. so i go back online and start cussin and at this point im PISSED. and all he has to say is "my mom is here"..like you SWEAR i give a fuk.  and so i keep goin and hes like "youre the one always talkin shit about me..i never said shit about you" and im like "what tha fuk is there to say bitch, me and you went out?? we broke up?? now we rarely talk???" theres NOTHING TO SAY. yeaa sure, i was mad we broke up and yeaa i was pissed. but i shared my feelings with people i trust that wouldnt say anything, and they havent.  and on top of that he fuckin trusts Ankurs words over mine?? especially when that fag was talkin shit even while we were goin out, i bet he believed it then too. what a fckin idiot.  hes goes "i dont know why your blowin this up over a stupid question that i asked you...you wanted him to fight you" and i was like "i didnt even kno about this shit until now, i wasnt tha one that was fuckin talkin shit to mah boy" i mean what tha FUK? so this conversation lasts and lasts and let it all out, everything that i have been feeling for the past so many months. all my fckin anger about every little thing.   so then he says "you know who we should blame our life's problems on? ankur" and im like.."its sad you trusted that fagget" and IM like "later" and hes like "yo before you leave...nevermind, later" and im like "if you have fckin something to say then jus say it" and hes like "i didnt want things to go the way they did" and im like "yeaa well they did, we cant change the past...only change what happens in our futures" and hes like "yeaa we can only change the future" and hes like "jinx" and in my head im like (wtf...we arent like best buds after all this) and hes like "you kno we broke up cuz of distance, not cu we had beef, at tha time" and im like "ill see you around" and hes like "ill talk to you later peacE"  what tha fuck was that....  so then like 5 minutes later he i.m.s me again and is like "hey, if you thought i was a bitch why did you keep my utt shit in ur profile for so long" and im like "your homie bobby told me to put it in there and i said i would keep it in there for as long as he wanted me to and i dont break promises" and hes like "so you never thought differently of you and me" and i was like "well he was the one that asked me to put it in there not you" and hes like "cool cool" and hes like "i know youre still mad about the shit between you and me" and im like "no i jus think ur fucked up, straight out" and hes like "its coo, ur opinion" (or some shit)...  wtf man. yesterday i was crazy in anger.  the minute people start talking shit i cant take it, and how tha fuk are you gonna start saying shit about the past?? didnt you think it was over?? if you really thought it was over then you wouldnt bring up shit all over again.  move on.  oh and then i was like "dont even bother coming on saturday" and hes like "you want me to" and im like "i jus said dont bother"  and like, the whole reason why he was mad was because mah boy mandeep let him know that he has no future.. if he had any self esteem, any confidence he would let anyone's words affect him that much. yeah sure theres self respect but damn..  i dont know, shit is jus fucked up. i cant believe this.  how i feel?? fuckin exhausted. fuckin angry. fuckin pissed off. thats HOW I FUCKIN FEEL.  people need to learn how to fuckin shut up.   when i have shit with people, i take it to them and i regulate that shit.  i talk shit?? if i have somethin to fuckin say then i say it to their fuckin face. i aint no pussy who's gonna hide shit. imma be straight up.  everyone knows it.  yeah everyone tells their friends how they feel about different things but that is NOT the same as talking shit.  truth hurts.  mandeep, i truly feel that we are being dangerously stalked.  thanks fo still sticking with me through all of this bullshit. you mean so much to me and i cant see anything ever coming between us. love you, fa sho.  thanks fo yo comments, mean much to me and always leave me smiling. thank you.  aight well, imma go.  theres no more fuckin shit to say, if YOU HAVE A FUCKIN PROBLEM WITH ME OR IF YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY THEN SAY IT TO MY FUCKIN FACE BITCH.  noor
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       LET ME HOLD YOU    CARESS MY BODY    YOU GOT ME GOING CRAZY    YOU -TURN ME ON -TURN ME ON....    LET ME JAM YOU    WINE ALL AROUND ME    YOU GOT ME GOING CRAZY - YOU -TURN ME ON -TURN ME ON....      damn..      Kevin Lyttle- "turn me on"      yeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa         scroll down babe and read tha last entry toooo                                             i love you            aighh...                              look downnn....  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yeaaa baby.         tonight is the night i have the priveledge of meeting my one and only lover.      shit man, i am so excited to see you baby, damn i jus wanna...uhhhuh u know.         damnn/ i miss you so much. i love you so much and i cant wait to see you, damn...            cant wait to get ready with you, damn i love you so much, i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you...imma burn you that BRUIN CD..and i got this other cd imma burn you from Citywalk..some Chile/Colombia/Puetro Rico group that can play some stuff..theyre aight, but yeaa..all i thought about was uss..damn..i love youuu..      if i got time ill burn you another cd too..i love youuuuuu, omg i think imma go crazy in the next 4 hours or so...i gotta start getting ready now shit, but ill wait up fo you don worry...ill jus take a shower in tha mean time..hahaa..      i love youuuuuuuuuuuu            love you babe.         I JUST LOVE YOU OK.            damn, how i love you.         imma bring a pad and we can talk talk talk....dance dance...drink water (well me of course)..talk some more...dance/talk....go crazzy babe...damn i cant wait to see you, i developed tha picz from july 4th...ill brin 'em...ofcourse i llook ugly but you lood gOooOd......mmmmmmmmmmmmmmhMmm      aighh well immma out...         ill catch you later babe.                     "be easy"            love youuuu         aighh..latee         "oh yehh"....did i mention..............................                                                            I LOVE YOUUUU?????? nahhh...........i could remind you again.............i love youuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu               love you babe         love you.                  aighh??                     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I HATE your mom.   how the fuck is she jus gonna start hitting you like that, fuck..i fucking cant believe her..oh my fucking god, what the fuck man   i hate this..what the fuck is her problem, i fucking HATE her.   what the fucks her problem, oh my fucking god, damn, i wanna slap her a couple times..    &nbsp;  what the fuck happened.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  damnn...i am so pissed right now, fuck i cant even feel anything, i fucking hate this shit, i feel so god damn useless, i cant do anything, because that situation is my own, FUCK MAN..I HATE HER...damn, i fucking hate her..what a fucking bitch.    &nbsp;  yesterday- didnt end up going anywhere, didnt end up going to god-moms house, didnt do any shit whatsoever, i couldnt stop fucking crying after my dad got yelling at me. so fucked up, i hate living here, im starting to hate living..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  i feel like shit. i feel like i cant fucking do anything, i feel like i cant FUCKING BREATHE WITHOUT GETTING FUCKING PERMISSION I CANT BELIEVE THIS IS HAPPENING TO US.    &nbsp;  i just, dont know what i ever did wrong in my life.    &nbsp;  my dad doesnt even know me..    &nbsp;  fuck man..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  im out    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  too much fucking bullshit    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  life is fucking bullshit.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  damn..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  i hate this.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  i love you mandeep   love you   so    so    so much    &nbsp;  damn..how i love you.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  im so fucking sorry about everything....i cant even express to you, how sorry i am.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  damn..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  im so sorry.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;    &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Life lets you breathe, death doesn't   Life lets you explore, death doesn't   Life lets you make decisions, death doesn't   Life lets you love, death causes mourning    &nbsp;  Best thing bout life is..it lets you recieve love.    &nbsp;  yeaa..    &nbsp;  talked to mah babe @ nutrition.    &nbsp;  my broke-ass gots ta find some change fo tomorra..damn, i really needa start makin money, gotta find a way.    &nbsp;  so wsup.    &nbsp;  how was ur day off?    &nbsp;  damn, yea, i dont think we gon b able to make it fo the rehearsal on saturday fo august 7th, but im pretty sure now, im performing..but its probably not gon be new stuff, probably jus from the reseda show, cuz we don got enough time to prepare.    &nbsp;  gotta ask ayda if shes interested in doin tha dance. if not, it'll jus be me, harneet, and kareena.    &nbsp;  yeaaaaaa.....    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  i dont know what else..   ill update later.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  peace nigga    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yeaa..     &nbsp;   so today @ nutrition:    efrain: "so are you coming today..??"    me: "uhh...where?"    efrain: "didnt arti tell you...we're all going to the movies and out fo dinner.."    me: "oh no..uhmm..shes coming to my house maybe shes gon tell me then..and we'll jus leave from my house..if my mom says yeaa.."    efrain: "ohh aighh..cool. aight well i guess ill see you 'round"    me: "yeaa..peace.."     &nbsp;   so later..the bell rings and I go to second period...finish all my hw from English..and do the work in class and shit, hoping that if I finish all my work..I would be able to go out with Arti one last time before she leaves on Wednesday...     &nbsp;   so I get in the car, my mom picks me up..    mom: "Ritu auntie called today..asking if you could go to the movies with Arti.."    me: "ohh.."    mom: "yeaa..i told her no.."     &nbsp;   wtf.     &nbsp;   so..I'm not gonna see Arti for another year after tonight, and they wouldnt even let me kick it with her before she left. WOW...    this is some bullshit..I fucking hate living here.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   so yeaa. thats my story.     &nbsp;   then later on, when Arti leaves from my house after eating lunch..I go upstairs..start reading before I get in trouble for anything else I may have done.     &nbsp;   Then.    my dad comes upstairs.     &nbsp;   dad talks to me about how he thinks he should send me to India Spring semester so that I can get away from all my "too-close friends"     &nbsp;   so I break down, and I cant even talk.     &nbsp;   so turns out, I'm going to India for Medical College and there is not ifs/buts about it.     &nbsp;   This totally sucks, I cant even live my life the way I want to.     &nbsp;   As for the party on Saturday, I dont even know if I'm going to be allowed to go..you know..since I couldnt kick it with my best friend before she says bye for a whole year.     &nbsp;   damn..shoot me.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   so I'm getting a job next week, dont know my hours or schedule or anything yet, but I'll find out.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   This is my life's reality and I cant get away from it no matter how hard I try..they say.."Love is when you don't want to go to sleep.Because reality is better than a dream"...yeaa, but when your apart from your Love, then what do you do..     &nbsp;   damn, I gotta work harder, and try to make my life fit together, been thinking about this fo 2 weeks.     &nbsp;   situation with my rents: 2 months and 5 days now.     &nbsp;   damn, so much can happen in just 2 months..     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   I'm fucking torn, I dont even know what the fuck to feel, how to react, how to fucking handle the situation, I just need to get away, and find myself, and my ground.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   fuck man.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   damn..     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   I thought life was bad on May 21st.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   look at my life now, I got no college fund, I have to support myself, and put myself through school, save up money for Driver's Ed Classes and then Training, then I gotta go to work, get a Metro-Bus PAss, then...I dont know.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   fuck..I'm fucked.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   damn...I'm not gon be able to see my best friend fo 1 whole year..    being separated from Mandeep is enough..     &nbsp;   god damn, I really needa find friends..seems like I got none left.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   out like my lack of getting my life together.     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   damn..     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;     &nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Meet me at the altar   In your white dress   We ain't getting no younger   We might as well do it   Been feeling you all   The while girl   I must confess    Girl let's just get married   I just wanna get married&nbsp;   yeaaaaa..mann.&nbsp;haha, fa show, imma b the one to propose..shit.&nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;  jus thinkin bout friday and how i talked to you fo so long and i didnt even notice, haha, that was tha best mann..shit, i should eat a cookie everytime i talk to you..hahaa..   your supposed to get the ring niGGA  damn straight.  &nbsp;  "daAAMN bABY...i jus WAnnaA fUUCKK"  yeaa..    &nbsp;  damn man, home-stress is up to the max right now, i cant believe all this shit man, my head starts hurting when i think about it..everytime i see my dad, there a current in me that goes through me and reminds me of all the things that have happened..   looks like now ill never get over my fear..    &nbsp;  damn..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  life just sucks..   it just sucks, right now.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  peace.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;    &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ill meet you in heaven.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  NO YOU CANNOT CALL THE ABUSE NUMBER, THAT IS MY JOB AND YOU WILL NOT DO IT UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCE.    &nbsp;  Mandeep, I am serious, I swear on my life that I will die if you do that. I am not joking..JUST DONT DO IT.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  I know about the jagran, we were invited also, but my mom is having Preeti, Jessica (who cant come) over..and all these ppl from Punjab over, so that my Massi can meet them before she leaves in September.   I wont be able to come.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  Tomorrow I am hopefully..going to the hospital to volunteer, let me know if I can call you from there, I dont want more trouble to start if I cant call you.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  I love YOU.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  please..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        no words to express how sorry i am that all of this happened, i feel like..  this:  &nbsp;  Jeska2610 (4:40:09 PM): omg1Jeska2610 (4:40:11 PM): !Jeska2610 (4:40:26 PM): noor?indyangurl01 (4:40:35 PM): yeaa..i knowindyangurl01 (4:40:38 PM): i feel horribleJeska2610 (4:40:47 PM): dude u just missedJeska2610 (4:40:48 PM): himJeska2610 (4:40:52 PM): he left like 5 mins agoindyangurl01 (4:41:10 PM): i jus managed to fck up everyones livesJeska2610 (4:41:15 PM): dude its okJeska2610 (4:41:17 PM): it happens okJeska2610 (4:41:27 PM): just take it easy for rite nowindyangurl01 (4:41:28 PM): no its notJeska2610 (4:41:36 PM): did they do nehting to u?indyangurl01 (4:41:43 PM): my dad hit meJeska2610 (4:41:49 PM): a lot?indyangurl01 (4:42:02 PM): i have a bruise on my backJeska2610 (4:42:07 PM): o mgindyangurl01 (4:42:25 PM): its nothingJeska2610 (4:42:30 PM): noor...i feel like shit rite nowindyangurl01 (4:42:35 PM): its been happening a lot latelyJeska2610 (4:42:35 PM): its not ur faultindyangurl01 (4:42:39 PM): yeah it isJeska2610 (4:42:41 PM): u dont deserve that shitindyangurl01 (4:42:47 PM): its all my faultindyangurl01 (4:42:50 PM): ALL of itJeska2610 (4:42:52 PM): its none of ur guys' faultJeska2610 (4:42:52 PM): HOW?Jeska2610 (4:42:57 PM): u just wanted tot alk to him indyangurl01 (4:43:22 PM): iknow, but i..shouldve been more carefulindyangurl01 (4:43:27 PM): i think im losing himindyangurl01 (4:43:30 PM): because of my dadJeska2610 (4:43:37 PM): dudeJeska2610 (4:43:41 PM): he still loves the crap outa uJeska2610 (4:43:43 PM): u dont even knoJeska2610 (4:43:51 PM): hes still as crazy for u as he's ever beenJeska2610 (4:43:54 PM): dont think thatJeska2610 (4:43:59 PM): hes having a tough time tooJeska2610 (4:44:07 PM): i jus fixed him up a little bit Jeska2610 (4:44:11 PM): hopefully he'll remain like thatJeska2610 (4:44:18 PM): he said he feels sick in his stomacheJeska2610 (4:44:24 PM): bcuz he thinks its HIS faultindyangurl01 (4:44:24 PM): thats not a good thingindyangurl01 (4:44:31 PM): i wish i could justindyangurl01 (4:44:38 PM): erase everythingJeska2610 (4:44:40 PM): yeah but its ok..hes fine nowindyangurl01 (4:44:41 PM): i hate thisJeska2610 (4:44:42 PM): dude i knoindyangurl01 (4:44:46 PM): i feel like shooting myselfJeska2610 (4:44:48 PM): it sux so badindyangurl01 (4:44:49 PM): you dont understandJeska2610 (4:44:53 PM): its like...indyangurl01 (4:44:56 PM): how many times ive thought about thisJeska2610 (4:44:59 PM): u feel ur whole life is stainedindyangurl01 (4:45:02 PM): it isJeska2610 (4:45:06 PM): noor dont u dare do nething like thatindyangurl01 (4:45:12 PM): its never going to be the sameindyangurl01 (4:45:15 PM): after 18indyangurl01 (4:45:17 PM): im leavingindyangurl01 (4:45:20 PM): i have toJeska2610 (4:45:23 PM): ur parents need to understandindyangurl01 (4:45:25 PM): my dad doesnt want me anymoreindyangurl01 (4:45:30 PM): at 16indyangurl01 (4:45:34 PM): i have to get a jobJeska2610 (4:45:36 PM): that the more they breathe down ur neck the more instances like this wil occurindyangurl01 (4:45:37 PM): and start saving upindyangurl01 (4:45:40 PM): to support myselfJeska2610 (4:45:52 PM): dude noJeska2610 (4:45:54 PM): hes just madindyangurl01 (4:45:54 PM): i fucking dont know what to doJeska2610 (4:45:57 PM): ne fatehr would beJeska2610 (4:46:02 PM): imagine his position...indyangurl01 (4:46:06 PM): i feel likeJeska2610 (4:46:10 PM): but he needs to understand urs moreindyangurl01 (4:46:11 PM): i dont even know how to feelindyangurl01 (4:46:13 PM): or how i feelJeska2610 (4:46:17 PM): dude i kno exactly how u feelJeska2610 (4:46:21 PM): i really dont kno wut to sayJeska2610 (4:46:30 PM): it feels as if im the one in the situationindyangurl01 (4:46:30 PM): i havent stopped cryingindyangurl01 (4:46:38 PM): i feel like indyangurl01 (4:46:41 PM): it is my faultJeska2610 (4:46:42 PM): i kno..i could tell by the sound of ur voiceindyangurl01 (4:46:43 PM): which it isindyangurl01 (4:46:51 PM): i shouldnt've done thatindyangurl01 (4:46:59 PM): i shouldve been more carefulJeska2610 (4:47:02 PM): its a BIG BIG riskindyangurl01 (4:47:05 PM): its all my faultJeska2610 (4:47:09 PM): noor dont say thatindyangurl01 (4:47:10 PM): all my faultJeska2610 (4:47:12 PM): things happen for a reasonJeska2610 (4:47:16 PM): just sHUT THE HELL UPJeska2610 (4:47:19 PM): do u beleive in that?Jeska2610 (4:47:23 PM): cuz mandeep doesnt wut soeverindyangurl01 (4:47:31 PM): well he shouldindyangurl01 (4:47:33 PM): fckJeska2610 (4:47:34 PM): yeahJeska2610 (4:47:36 PM): thats wut im telling himindyangurl01 (4:47:37 PM): i always fck upJeska2610 (4:47:39 PM): dude noorindyangurl01 (4:47:43 PM): ALWAYSJeska2610 (4:47:44 PM): ive been thru sumpthing similarindyangurl01 (4:47:46 PM): no u dont understandJeska2610 (4:47:48 PM): many MANY timesindyangurl01 (4:47:50 PM): i always mess upindyangurl01 (4:47:59 PM): all the timeindyangurl01 (4:48:02 PM): fkcindyangurl01 (4:48:07 PM): i donteven know what to thinkJeska2610 (4:48:21 PM): shit dude....i feel like shit rite nowJeska2610 (4:48:30 PM): i wish i could get u out of ur situation rite nowJeska2610 (4:48:33 PM): id seriously do nethingindyangurl01 (4:48:37 PM): ive been feeling like that since that nightJeska2610 (4:48:41 PM): i&nbsp; kno its worse than helJeska2610 (4:48:42 PM): lJeska2610 (4:48:46 PM): doesur sister know?indyangurl01 (4:48:54 PM): no shes at schoolindyangurl01 (4:49:00 PM): uclaJeska2610 (4:49:04 PM): so she hasnt talked to ue ver since?Jeska2610 (4:49:10 PM): ur sayin she has no idea all thisshit happendindyangurl01 (4:49:22 PM): nopeindyangurl01 (4:49:23 PM): no ideaJeska2610 (4:50:07 PM): ok u need to do sumpthing about thisJeska2610 (4:50:26 PM): cuz this is gonna haunt u for the rest of ur lifeindyangurl01 (4:50:36 PM): yeaa i knowJeska2610 (4:50:36 PM): unless u dont do sumpthingindyangurl01 (4:50:37 PM): that muchindyangurl01 (4:50:43 PM): what am i supposed to doindyangurl01 (4:50:46 PM): runaway?Jeska2610 (4:50:51 PM): nOJeska2610 (4:50:57 PM): BAD BAD BAAAAAAADDDDDD IDEAJeska2610 (4:50:59 PM): DONT EVERJeska2610 (4:51:00 PM): EVER DO THATindyangurl01 (4:51:06 PM): i already have beforeJeska2610 (4:51:09 PM): thats hte worst thing sm1 could ever doindyangurl01 (4:51:12 PM): and i know its a bad ideaindyangurl01 (4:51:16 PM): but likeJeska2610 (4:51:18 PM): ok well dont do it againindyangurl01 (4:51:28 PM): jessica i just feel like killing myselfindyangurl01 (4:51:31 PM): its not even funnyJeska2610 (4:51:33 PM): noorindyangurl01 (4:51:35 PM): i dont kno what to doindyangurl01 (4:51:38 PM): i dont know what to doindyangurl01 (4:51:42 PM): i feel like screamingJeska2610 (4:51:44 PM): u arent the only one in this position rite nowJeska2610 (4:51:45 PM): I KNOWindyangurl01 (4:51:48 PM): i knowJeska2610 (4:51:49 PM): i kno exactly how u feelJeska2610 (4:51:50 PM): just Jeska2610 (4:51:51 PM): trust meindyangurl01 (4:51:54 PM): i just dont know how to deal with itJeska2610 (4:51:54 PM): calm downJeska2610 (4:51:58 PM): dudeindyangurl01 (4:51:59 PM): im so..indyangurl01 (4:52:00 PM): lostJeska2610 (4:52:03 PM): i dunno if u have the guts to do this..Jeska2610 (4:52:03 PM): but Jeska2610 (4:52:08 PM): when u feel the time is rite..Jeska2610 (4:52:17 PM): talk to ur parents..about this...just apologizeJeska2610 (4:52:23 PM): if u try toback urself upJeska2610 (4:52:25 PM): its never gonna work outindyangurl01 (4:52:25 PM): i already have triedJeska2610 (4:52:29 PM): i really think thats the only wayindyangurl01 (4:52:35 PM): i already triedJeska2610 (4:52:38 PM): and said wutindyangurl01 (4:52:39 PM): my dad just slapped meJeska2610 (4:52:52 PM): when did u tryJeska2610 (4:52:53 PM): today?indyangurl01 (4:53:02 PM): yesterdayJeska2610 (4:53:08 PM): wut happend today?indyangurl01 (4:53:33 PM): nothing, my mom picked me up from schoolindyangurl01 (4:53:37 PM): and i came homeJeska2610 (4:53:45 PM): is she mad at u too?indyangurl01 (4:53:46 PM): and there were no words between me and my dadindyangurl01 (4:53:50 PM): i couldnt even talkindyangurl01 (4:53:53 PM): i jus kept cryingJeska2610 (4:54:09 PM): did u even eat nething?indyangurl01 (4:54:14 PM): no  &nbsp;  i dont know wwhat to fucking do. i ruined my boyfriends life, i fucking fucked everything up in my house, i dont know what to do, my actions just keep getting better and better dont they..  this is ALL MY FAULT. all of it, i dont even know how to express how sorry i am mandeep, i am so sorry...so sorry..i will give my life to show you how sorry i am.  &nbsp;  i understand what i have done to you and i know i cannot erase...and for that i am sorry, i am so sorry mandeep..god i wish i could just say that to you right now, i cant stop crying and i cant even call you..i cant do anything, i cant even sit idle for one minute, i am supposed to be doing hw right now...for english but i cant i just cant do it...im trying my hardest to try and hang on..my best, but sometimes thats not enough, thats just not enough..  &nbsp;  i am REALLY REALLY sorry that all of this happened...and because of me..what a better person that ME to fck up your life..i am so sorry..  &nbsp;  i cant believe i would cause that big of a loss for you.  &nbsp;  damn..  im so fucking stupid.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  i know you are pissed as fuck..but i love you to death..i love everything about you...i love you so much, you cant even imagine, i love you mandeep..i just love you so much.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;   &nbsp;  &nbsp;       
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       damn..    &nbsp;  i am SO fucking done.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  suicidal tendencies: disconnect and self- distruct one bullet at a time.    &nbsp;  i mean yEAH man, thats how i fucking feel. shit, now it feels like this weekend was pure shit, like i fucking did something wrong.    &nbsp;  I dont try?? Fuck man, what else CAn I do?     &nbsp;  aight so this weekend, Amit's party, cant say no   cousin takes&nbsp;me out befo he goes back to SD, aight..my choice   saturday, i find someone to stay with while my parents go out and party, so i end up calling 5 different ppl and end up staying at my cousins   sunday, gurduwara in the morning..depika's birthday langar, wasnt my choice, and later, had to take my sister back to ucla, i cant stay home..    &nbsp;  so i went out this weekend, it doesnt mean i dont fuckin try fo you, every chance i get that my mom is in a good mood i ask her if i can go out with friends..and her response "beta, my answer is always your answer, because i know that you are doing what you have to do, the only thing is your dad has to know"..now if my dad is upset about something or he doesnt like me having a social life, then what can i do about it? what can i do other than what i did the other day over and over? i feel hopeless half the time..i feel like you think that i dont want to see you, i feel like you think its only one way, but lemme tell you..i fucking try, i do, and i wanna see you, and i wanna party with you and i fucking wanna spend time with you..   fuck   i mean   i wwanna spend the rest of my life with you..   so me not trying?    &nbsp;  thats like saying, this isnt even a fucking relationship   and that fuckin hurts, shit..i feel weird as fuck inside too sometimes    &nbsp;  no matter how much i try to explain to you how it is in my house, i cant show you because you dont live here, and thank god you dont.   i dont expect you to feel bad, but sometimes i just cant do things that i want to, as a matter a fact its like that most of the time, unless its something having to do with family.   i have gone out with a total of 2 ppl this summer other than family.   other friends want to kick it together too and i wanna kick it with them, but my first thing was always aight..gotta find a way to chill with mandeep first cuz i know im not gonna get that many chances later on..   so dont think i dont fucking try   i may not tell you everytime i do   but i do   and i need you to trust that   if you cant, then i dont know what else i can do    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  i feel like total shit, like i havent done anything in this relationship, like i havent fucking Tried..shit.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  I dont know how its going to be once we hit teh regular school year..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  out now jus like my lack of trying    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp; &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       aight bitches im back..    &nbsp;  we aint leavin fo another hour...so i got time.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  chek this    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  People are often unreasonable, illogical, and self-centered; Forgive them anyway  If you are kind, people may accuse you of selfish, ulterior motives; Be kind anyway  If you are successful, you will win some false friends and some true enemies; Succeed anyway  If you are honest and frank, people may cheat you; Be honest and frank anyway  What you spend years building, someone could destroy overnight; Build anyway  If you find serenity and happiness, they may be jealous; Be happy anyway  The good you do today, people will often forget tomorrow; Do good anyway  Give the world the best you have, and it may never be enough; Give the world the best you've got anyway  You see, in the final analysis, it is between you and God; It was never between you and them anyway-Mother Teresa    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  tight woman..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  shit...    &nbsp;  aight, befo my dad blasts me..im out, ill catch up later..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  wsup babe.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  jus gotta remind you that i love you..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  peace..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp; &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       wsup.    &nbsp;  YOU MET HOOBASTANK?? OH MY FUCKING GOD. YOU LUCKY-ASS. OH MY FUCKING...   WHAT A FUCKING PERFECT TIME TO TAKE A FUCKING SHOWER. OH MY...SHIT MAN!!! I HATE THIS....I SHOULDNT HAVE TAKEN A SHOWER. DAMN IT..    &nbsp;  so wait...you actually got to talk....oh my fucking god..   shit...thatsss SO COOL. like...you dont even know. omg.....shit..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  aight, so las night.   go to amit's party at Punjab Palace and kick it there fo a couple hours..then cousin picks me up and we roll down to LA (east). go to a party there, and my cousin's turning 20..so all these people arre atleast 3 years older than me...there are some chicks...some guys...HUGE HOUSE..haha, so we enter...and party is happenin'..."move ya body" -nina sky...is being "bumped" damn...so we walk in...and im like still dressed up becuz of amit's party..in american clothes thank god..so we're in...drinks...smoking...shit man, the works..EVERYTHING WAS AVAILABLE..but nah, not me..cousin?? maybe...everyone else?? maybe...but me?? nah, im straight..   so there was major dancing...a what me and my cousin like to call "make-out louge" and then...a fucking kick back upstairs..where we could play pool or watch movies...shit, this kid has a fucking theater in his house...how fuckin tight is that shit..damn, was hella tight until...   we stepped outside tha house...onto tha streets..so my cousin sees his gf kickin it wit other guys..so he goes up to say hello...and she starts stutterin like fuckkkk...and my cousin finds out that she be cheatin wit 3 other guys...damn, that was a scene...so my cousin is pissed as fuck..and shit, im ready to cuss that bitch out...i start but then..my friends and other ppl from tha party..say to jus leave...   so later on...we're all dancing..and getting high off nothing..so we're dancing..some ppl gettin nasty...some ppl tryin to make moves...some ppl jus havin major fun fucking around...and then there were tha ppl..who were jus havin a good time...so i get off tha floor to get punch..and knowing me..i didnt kno there was shit in tha punch..so i drink..and drink...and drink...and who do i see?? THE BITCH. my cousin's now ex girlfriend...damn..i hate that bitch now..fuckkk...so i tell my friend..to start playin stutter from joe..and i tell my cousin to go do his thing..so shes jus standin there like a stupid dumbfuck..and so he goes up..and "stutter" -joe is LOUD AS FUCk...he starts bustin out wit tha singin and movin to make her feel uncomfortable...and dumps her while singin tha song..and at tha end all i heard was.."damn bitch get tha hell on" damn...i was amazed..my cousin is usually not like that..hes usually nice..and dumps tha chick jus one on one..no matter how bad she turns out..   so she leaves and goes home fucking crying...but thas what you get when you fucking 4-time with 4 different guys...dumb bitch.    &nbsp;  so we kick it and now tha time is like..fucking..1 in tha morning...and we're all jus havin a good time..old friends...made new friends..and saw some ppl after a hella long time...shit, a HELLA LONG time..its fun to see how much some ppl change and to see where they were and where they are now..shit, ppl can change like wHOA.    &nbsp;  it was hella tight, and plus i got to kick it with my cousin, that was the best part..cuz when hes up at SD it sucks, he barely has any time to talk at all...and so, las night was our chance.    &nbsp;  shit, seems that i can tolerate alcohol considering it was in tha punch and considering i didnt even fuckin notice..damn..hahaa..oh well, shit happens..that was mah first time getting any alcohol into mah system.....was bound to happen one fuckin day..so las night was it..    &nbsp;  mood of las night: Dip it lowPick it up slowRoll it all aroundPoke it out like your back brokePop pop pop that thingIma show you how to make your man say "Ooo" ...   shit everyone was hitting on EVERYONE..was hella funny..    &nbsp;  i was like.."uh...no.." hahaa, mandeep...ohh man, i miss you like fuckkk..   i wish you were there with me..shit i would turn you tha fuck on and we could rock it on tha dance floor...fuckkkk, i miss you so much...i love you..could get nasty shit...everyone was..no one would even give a fuck...that was shit man, no one was concious...everyone was hitting on each other...everyone was doin their thang...turnin each other on..and fuckk..i wish you were there...fuckkk, we wouldve had such a good time..    &nbsp;  fuckk..best party ive been to in a while.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  yeaaa...fuckkkkkkk.....    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  "You getting boldHe growin' coldIt's just the symptoms of young loveGrowin' oldYou think it's timeAnd your thinking of leavingBut give it timeIt's late at nightHe's coming homeMeet him at the door with nothin' onTake him by the handLet him know what's onIf you understand meYall come on.."    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  fuckk, yeaa baby..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp; 213 concert tonite feat. snoop dogg...i'm gonna whoop some ass in the emcee battle before haand..&nbsp;fuuuck i hope i can spit some heat...that'll be crazy dope..get to be on stage with em' &nbsp; &nbsp;  damn..you will you will, shit im so glad you're having fun!!!!!!!!! fucking, thank god.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  "lets get married"-jagged edge    shit hell yeah..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  damn mandeep, i love you so much. fuck i cant wait til i see you next.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  i gotta let you know bout tha day we can go out, jus this weekend and next weekend is gonna be hella crazy with parties at home and parties outside and shit, but i will try my BEST I can assure you of that...damn, i wanna see you so bad baby..so fucking bad...    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  damn..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  i hope you're havin fun like whoa..    &nbsp;  aight well..im out, i gotta get ready,&nbsp;ill check you later.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  peace.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp; &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp; &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       aight..first day without talkin to mah babe...    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  shit i read that blog like 50 million times..damn. i miss him so much.    so   so   so   much.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  have fun in Vegas!!! you have to have fun, or atleast try for my sake..god I feel like I control how much fun you have or how much you go out. I dont wanna be the person who does that man...start chillen like you used to...please man..    &nbsp;  no call yesterday: damn, now I know how much you worried..I thought about tha craziest things..damn...    &nbsp;  I love you so much.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  shit, who am I kidding, I cant live without you for four days..   thats like...shit man, thas like bein punished fo nothing..shit I miss you so much.    &nbsp;   &nbsp; "i love you with all my heart and soul...i hold so much respect for you in every way..for how far you've come...for who you are...and respect you as a person, both physically and emotionally..." &nbsp;  damn, all I can say is thank you. thank you so so so much mandeep...so much...thank you for being with me and being in my life..shit I dont know where I would be without you..thank you so much..I owe you my fuckin everything, my fuckin life...thank you so god damn much..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  damn, I love you.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  shit...its time to go to tha doctors..I'll try t write again later..   doctors: jus check up..I think, unless my mom has something else up her sleeve like that day I got summoned..   shit, that was NOT funny...    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  aight,    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  mandeep,   I love You.    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  try to have fun, please...jus try atleast..I'm missing you....like wHoOa...damn...I love you sooOoooooo much..    &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp; &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          this is tha entry i couldnt publish...and when i tried...i couldnt see so....here i am tryin to publish it again..hahaa..  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  shit..mah babe told me to write more so im writin more  &nbsp;  damn..god-mom calls me and asks if i can sleep over...what a perfect day...cuz shes all alone today in tha house..and damn it..i dont wanna go..cuz i needa get tha cell phone baby...damn i gotta find some way i can either make up an excuse for takin tha phone..or i gotta....stay home...but i dont know what imma say to her... "no i wanna stay home" sounds kinda bitchy..u know...damnit..i needa think of something quick..  &nbsp;  thas tha update so far..  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  talked to mandeep:  shit, talks with him are so damn inspirational. i love him to death.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  damn, i really have the best guy in the world..  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  priviledged.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  damn, i gave you hell mandeep and i feel so fucking bad every fucking time..  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  its like..now that i stood up, i feel good..but then most of tha time..im still scared as hell that something is gonna happen....i thought that would go away after las night but i guess not....im still scared that every move i make is gonna cause another crisis...damn, i dont know what to do...  i feel like i failed myself..in a way..damn...i hate this feelin.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  but you helped me get rid of the stuff i needed to say and i thank you so much...so so so much. thank You.  thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you thank you..so so so much mandeep...omg you dont even know...shit thank you so much.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  i love you.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  i gotta go, dads comin up...shit man, i wish i could write more...ill my BEST to call you...my baby...damn, i wish i could jus live with you right now...i love you so much.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  i miss you like hell..remember to be up tomorra befo 10:00... =)  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  latee..    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeaa..wsup..  las night: screaming and yelling, i blew up on my dad after getting off the phone, oh how it felt like the walls were going to tear down...inside my walls were tearing apart..and so was my heart..  i cant believe i have such a bad relationship with my dad. i cant believe..after these 16 years of living with him...that he doesnt even know my likes and dislikes..  and everytime something happens at home, it cuts down time that i get to talk to mandeep....mandeep, i am so sorry, but please jus bear with me.. i love you so much.  god damn, i didnt sleep at all last night, it was like..my mom didnt even have to wake me up in tha morning cuz i was already awake..half crying half glad that it was time fo me to stepp out of this hellish place..  it was crazy....las night was crazy..   moving on: school was aight, still hella hott..100 degrees today..    awwwwshiitt..whas mah new name?? well according to mah lover its: Sonia. coooooo..hahaa..     damn. jus thinkin..        damn, richard i fucking saw you today after a fuckin week of summer skool hahaa.. feels like there are more ppl in summer skool than there are in tha regular year..      haa..found out today that i can still open my locker.."aww shit aww shit...watch out.." as tom would say   taking tha permit test in a week. gotta read that shit over again.                     damn thank you so much mandeep. thank you so fucking much for being with me. i dont think i can say that enough. yo niggaz, if you have any relation wit this kid...damn you're fuckin privileged, i hope you all fuckin realize that.. damn, dont take ppl fo granted, realize how fucking great they are right there and then.   damn.     yeaah..     damn nigga..imma get my tongue pierced. except im hella scared..haa, but damn i gotta get it...i jus don know when..    "damn..you fuckeerr..." hahaa...damn, i always crack up thinkin bout that. the way u said it that night..damn, that was greatt..    aight well, im out. i gots hw today.   "When someone really gets at you...takes away your self esteem and breaks down your ego piece by piece.  Correct me if i am wrong but it actually takes 32 muscles in your face to frown.On the other hand...it only takes 4 muscles to bitch slap that motherfucker across the face " - Grantham   damn nigga, some crazy ass shit went down las night. i went OFF.. feels good.           
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn i just talked to mah baby.   shiit, i cant believe you spit what i wrote. thas fuckin tight. that jus like hit me..shiit man, i feeel goooood.   i hope i get the phone today. *im prayin, prayin babe..   'Lets get MArried'- Jagged Edge hell yeaa nigga..    "i'm trying to ask it all provocatively...like sexy n shit...obviously that shit didn't work...and she's all like..."aiite then i won't i won't"  "  haa, im playin wit you nigga, but shit man...i was serious, you take it like a joke...on tha reall..i dont know how..    "hehe...man i can see you smilin' and doin that sexy ass thing you do when you look away....ahah"  i looke sexy when i do that?? damn..i should look away all tha time.      damn i jus wanna turn you tha fuck on.      damn u gon be needin a new fuckin car one day..1 time use. hahaa...  yeaaaa mann.     shit but that shit i told you today on tha phone, i didnt mean to scare the shit out of you i just had to tell you because...shit, i jus couldnt keep it from you..  i love you..     Unsteady In time's distance I catch up to you on a simple street, hold you in conversation a moment only. Turned from your purpose, you turn back again, the child round in you: it is, indeed,  late spring. I stand still, a prisoner of coincidence; you go  the way you must and I cannot follow you. Later, I come to your door, a stranger; the child  uncertain clings to you. There are only words  between us; I dwell on them, the silence in me stronger than words. My eyes grow mute in twilight, and I live in the sound of you. I imagine  the ballet of your fingers; they, too, are silent movers of thought. I have never seen you work your words. Somewhere I wait for words that flash in air. Unsteady at my post I watch at each new corner for you to turn again.    damn nigga, i remember tha evenin i showed you that shit..damn...i love everything about you. e v e r y t h i g .    damn, i love you so much.    this is how i feel..every single time..  Lately when I look into your eyes I realize You're the only one I need in my life Baby I just don't know how to describe How lovely you made me feel inside  You give me butterflyz Got me flying so high in the sky I can't control the butterflyz   hell yeaa baby alicia keys..butterflyz    and...   Can you rock with me (Aw, baby) Non-stop with me (Stop with me) Can you take it to the top with me.. I just wanna love you, baby (Love ya, babe) Always thinkin’ of you, baby (Love ya, babe)   Can you roll with me (Ooh, baby) All over me... (Over me) Can you take control of me.. I just wanna love you, baby (Love ya, babe) Always thinkin’ of you, baby    awwwwshittt...   hahaa....   "maybe i should just hospitalize myself. that way i can see you at least once a week.  damn...that mite not be a bad idea."   never in my life will i want you to do that just to see me. what are you?? CRAZY??? Never..do that...ok..neverr   ill try until i die.    know why??    cuz i love you.     "thats my wife...pink cheeks. so back the fuck up niggaz. "  damn..        ooh man, that bitch is gon get it from me next time i see her, you do not even wanna be within tha same 10-mile radius. i'll fukin....damn, i dont kno what imma do, but shitt..she pissed me off.. damn.....she dont wanna be seein me fo a long time..     "she's busy...she ain't here...sleepin'...shower...too early...too late...she's doin homework...she's studying...daAAAAAAAMNn nigGA "   where are you in that title?? where aRe YOU nigga..   shit i miss you like crazy right now, even tho i talked to you like 10 mins ago..shit i miss you like fuckkkkk.   i love you so much.    out..rent are here
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn.  nigga can flow 'my boy Havok can floww'   damn, las night: didnt sleep fo a second.  pulled an all-nighter all by myself, with him in my thoughts    seems like i manage to fuck up every single time, Every Fuckin Single Fuckin Time. damn, if i had just gone down to get the phone like 10 minutes earlier, i couldda had him.   damn and today...not even gon be home..baby shower at 12 in beverly hills, then we gotta drop my sis back.. she says she dont wanna go back at like 4 and wants to come home first.. my dad: "no im not driving all the way back..we'll figure something out." fuck, i dont know what the fuck to do.   know what's sad? i feel like im being monitored in my own fucking house. every move i make, every step i take.. "what are you doing?? did you do this? did you do that??..." its like..chill tha fuck out.         "Happiness and how to achieve it" damn, my grandpa was a fuckin writer.         i asked you. you told me. i said yes. your still asking. maybe i shouldnt.    haa..      "Whether you police or a thug on the streets Whether you look for beef ,or you living in peace Whether you back down  or you stand strong bold  Yo we never know what tommorow gon hold " "We can live today , but were not promised tommorow, We can pass away say goodbye to yesterday We can live today , but were not promised tommorow, We can pass away say goodbye to yesterday" - Non Phixion    yeaa...      i didnt wanna cry on the phone the other night, but damn..i had to. i fucked up so bad. so badd..        out    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      your not a distraction your an attraction.    When winter comes in summer When theres no more forever When lies become the truth Well you know then that's when I'll stop loving you And when this world doesn't turn anymore When the stars all decide to stop shining ‘Til then I'm gonna to be by your side Gonna be loving you forever Every day of my life..  never will i stop loving you.   shit..close to 6 hours homie yeaaaa mann, hahaa..   damn..went through some old stuff today and found some scary shit that i wrote..damn.  A little girl wrote a poem and titled it 'Love' And her teacher gave her an A And her mom hung it on the kitchen door And she kept writing about love And her dad tucked her in bed And she slept with her teddy bear Then the little girl wrote a poem and titled it 'Hurt' And her teacher gave her a C And told her to try harder And her mom didn't hang it on the kitchen door And she cried about her poem And her dad didn't tuck her in bed And she slept with her teddy bear Then the girl wrote a poem and titled it 'Pain' And school became difficult And her mom didn't hang the poem on the kitchen door Because they just painted it And she kept writing about her life And her dad no longer tucked her in bed because he went away And she lost her teddy bear And she cried about her life Then the young woman dropped out of school She decided it was too hard And she cried about her broken life Then she wrote a poem and titled it 'It's Hopeless' And she made deep red slashes on her wrists And she hung her poem on the bathroom door Because she couldn't make it to the kitchen   damn, that shit scared me when i started reading, who knows what the fuck i was thinking   everything in life nowadays is amazing me..like...everything that i never noticed before..sometimes i feel so blind..and sometimes i feel like i knew it all along but just ignored it...damn, life can point out some pretty important things    another, deck of cards.  cut the deck queen's left for dead soft and wet scarf tied to your bed jack's all tragic when he stands alone feelin demonic, harmonic in a no-go zone you look well suited like you came to win lust spite and malice your degrees of sin crusin for pity and lookin pretty as fuck ace take your chances queen wish your luck.   shit all my stories i wrote from when i was a little kid..i found them today, haha..they weren't even like my own idea because i included like..sesame street characters and..jasmine from aladdin...hahaa, theyre so weird..but anyway it was coo to find them and read them like..10 years later.         damn i cant stop thinking about mandeep.  its that feeling when you can't get a song out of your head.only this time..i can't get his name his voice his smile his e v e r y t h i n g..out of mine  yeaah.    damn i love you.  god, damn, how i love you.       damn.                    awwwshitttt.. If the sqeeky wheel's always gettin' the grease  I'm totally devoted to disturbing the peace  And I'll do it all again, when I get done  Until I become your number one  No method to the madness, and no means of escape  Gonna break every rule or bend them all outta shape  It ain't a question of "how", just a matter of when  You get the message that I'm tryin' to send  I'm under a spell, I'm in over my head  And you know I'm going all the way to the end  To stand out, above the crowd  Even if I gotta shout out loud  'Til mine is the only face you see  Gonna stand out ...  'Til ya notice me     yeaaa niggaaaa.      "Tis better to remain silent and be thought a fool than to open your mouth and remove all doubt."- Samuel Johnson  hehyeaa..   aight. im done.  one thing tho.. i love you mandeep.     peace tha fuk out.        
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How did we wind up like this Why weren't we able To see the signs that we missed And try to turn the tables Now the story's played out like this Just like a paperback novel Lets rewrite an ending that fits   yeaa..seems like no one gives a fuk anymore what really goes down..what really happens, what reall thoughts occur...assumptions are horrible.  "I don't want to talk to you anymore I'm afraid of what I might say I bite my tongue every time you come around Cause blood in my mouth beats blood on the ground"   judge me all you want but keep the verdict to yourself.   That's Rock Bottom - when this life makes you mad enough to kill That's Rock Bottom - when you want somethin’ bad enough to steal That's Rock Bottom - when you feel like you've had it up to here Cause you mad enough to scream but you sad enough to tear   One lonely raindrop falls from the sky. One lonely tear falls from my eye. There's a snake in the grass, And a wolf at my door. Love, or hate, Which one hurts more? Lonely is the road of life, It twines you like a polished knife. Values and virtues only to hurt,  Because it comes back always as curt. Friends, or lovers, is it for real?  They never give, but your love, they'll steal.  What do you look for in this world of strife, When all you feel is a miserable life?  One heart has stopped, the other one black, Everything for both, but still stabbed in the back. What can you do when it all seems downhill?  Happiness is the feeling farthest from real.  Sealed in a fortress is where love should be,  But some trust too much and let it go free.  What is this hatred, this thing called love?  Is it the heat of a fire, or the heart of a dove?  Or could it just be some stupid emotion,  That some just cannot feel?  That, I think, is the answer, for real.  It is something that some just cannot contain.  Like flames of a fire, put out by the rain.  One lonely raindrop falls from the sky.  One lonely tear falls from my eye.    or maybe love is..  Love is patient, love is kind. It does not envy, it does not boast... its is not rude, it is not self-seeking, it is not easily angered, it keeps no record of wrongs. Love does not delight in evil but rejoices with the truth. it always protects, always trust, always hopes, always perseveres. Love never fails.  But this is how i feel around you..  A reflection in calm waters Something so simple and true One can see their feelings mirrored In the deep pools of blue Through the distortion of the breeze And the interference of reality Happiness and sadness reveal their true nature Untouched in a world of insanity The darkness in my eyes and my heart Was washed away with a glance The beautiful light of friendship and love Has filled the shadows; I’ve taken the chance The outcome is certain Even as the next day is not You've given me more than words can say; Before you saved me I was lost Truth be told, the day will come When in some way we must part By death or life's troubles Still, you'll hold my heart As a friend you've been the best As my love, you've proved true And I’ll try my very hardest to ensure That you know how much I love you.   now: my head hurts cuz my heart aches cuz im not near you cuz im not with you cuz im not there to hug you cuz im not there to see your pretty face cuz im not there to take you in my arms cuz im not there..just not there baby and it hurts..it really really hurts.     Staring at the wastelands, Watch my life fly by, The hands of Fate have gripped me, I do naught but cry. Pain, my last companion, Has taken hold of me, Alone I trudge these mountains, My philosophy. I brave these constant dangers, Hoping that I'll find, The only thing I know of, That can free my mind. I search for the answers, To questions never asked, Freedom's thirst does hold me, But I can't find the flask. Voices always haunting, Showing my mistakes, Laughing at my peril, The choices that Fate makes. I am left to wonder, About the life I lead, I wander at Fate's forcing, Will my heart be freed? Still I find more questions, Than answers in my head, And yet this will continue, 'Till the day I'm dead.    well..im leaving now. "out like my emotions"  nightfall...the stars shine...the scene before me captures my gaze as i stare out my window observing the twinkles hoping to become lost in their hypnotizing dance.  The moon guides my eyes towards it as they are engulfed in its beauty......no...I snap out of my episode having my eyes glossed with emotions...emotions that slowly form a web, which grows as time passes.  The web holding in thoughts of happines, excitment, vexation, hurt, sorrow.  Everyday this maze we are held in, this maze which has no escape, no exit, grows thornier.  Only death is its exit....death is the exit to life, nothing else.  Bliss and purity are handed to u...with its imprisonment...taking all who are good for eternity..    peace.   oh and yea..blogs shouldnt be love letters now should they. i mean...fuck that..right..i mean no reason for that at all..shit..what were they thinking..  some people just dont know what the fuck they are doing  wow, what a day.   whenever some shit goes down like this bullshit..i always try to get away myself from it but in the end it always ends up soundin like im the one who fucked up reall bad.  so..with that..imma say this now: i fucked up.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God show me the way because the devil trying to break me down The only thing that I pray is that me feet don't fail me now   yeah, wuttup babe..  first things: baby i know you love me..and i Know you dont break promises, you've already proven so much, more than there is to prove..i love you and i always want you to know that..  You Will Never Lose Me.  Never..  I Vow that on my fukin Life.   haa...my sexy ass voice?? whoa.   hahaa YES!!! SCOREEEEE....i turn youu onn..=)  mission complete. hahaa..!   EY, BABE...WTF IS THIS?  aight well,  you mean much to me and if anything is up u kno tha numberrr.   latee homeboy  nOoR-i   you wanna know...ohh man.. im such a Dork.   i had to come back to you last night. i couldnt jus leave you hangin there after that phone call.   haa, i love your reaction "no way" "fucking"  hahaa..   Pink Cheeks.  hmm..its goes it goes...cuz its like: reflex.  ride or die chick..thas me.    ooh man..perfect verse to describe my reaction to my dad bout you..  Tell ya daddy stop his hating Cuz I be wearing braids and rockin jerseys daily But that dont mean im thuggin no He dont want me with ya But I aint tryna hear it though Not tryna hear it though  But I know that if he knew yah He would understand yah Know that your my man and He would never hurt me no Let me come and see you So that we can be alone, alone.. As long as you make sure that you safely get me home    shiitt..  "i promise you i ain't even goin look at other girls, let alone talk to em besides being friends."  i promise you tha same babe.  but lemme tell you..I Know your not gonna do any of that shit, you dont even have to tell me..  I trust you soo much, with my fukin life. My Life..  "ya beautiful face. ya bAnGIN' body... ya sExy voiCE... ya sOft hAir... ya enchanTing fRagrAnce... oooeeey...still thinkin bout ya sexy body"  ive never been complimented so many times..fuk whenever i hear your voice its a fukin compliment..  like i said..its a privilege to know you..  shit.. i totally forgot..  i dreamt in color last night. it was like we connected online..like thursday...  im sorry fo playin wit ya emotions, but babe lemme tell you now...that i love you with my all..my everything..sht, i could die right now if you told me to..i love you soo much.   no ur not a loser, ur jus a sweet guy who rocks a innocent gurl's socks..   yeaa..    aight well peace out nigggga i love you.  -ya gurl..  p.s. hahaaa..."there IS no secret nigga.." HAaa.. =)   
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dearest Mr. Mandeep Sethi:         :Your wife would like to inform you that she enjoyed her ride down the memory lane and would like to do it again sometime. She says to call whenever possible and she was asking if things are still heated, or if she can call you now.         :Your Butler.   wuddup babe..  damn, I jus read ur blog like..680349830092 times..hahaa..still reading it as im typing my own..  damn my emails..you must of been like "what tha fuk is this chick doing.." hahaa, i sound so re-re-re-retArded..lol  you are one of the few, that wwhen i talk to...i feel REAL. thanks for the feeling of sane-ness   yep.    sounded like i was stuttering..haa...probably was..     you know why i said 'whatever that is'..cuz i didnt wanna sound weird.. hahaa, guess i didnt...or did i?   damn..our names do look good together..  mr. & mrs. mandeep and noor sethi   yeaa..thas how we do.. hahaa..  B-LIZZZZZZLEEE    i Cant Stop...its like... : reflex   damn i lifted you with what i wrote in my blog? i wonder how thats gon b in person.. like Damn.  hold her tight in my arms,  and my problems are all healed/  she's the angel of the battlefield/  i stand among warriors,  and i don't need a shield/  she's my angel of the battlefield//  i was singin that in mah first period today..shit...haa..   im craaaazzzy about you..     in love babe..so much in love...   i wish i still had our emails..shitt, if my dad hadnt taken down mah passwords..i'd still have all of 'em from day one..every single one..  hotmail threatened me soo many times..cuz i wasnt buyin their extra storage..hahaa..   i love you so much..   'til next time. all my love, all my heart is with you.  -ya gurl.. 
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got this jones formin in my bones from a man who indeed took over my soul understand I couldn't breathe if he ever said he would leave get on my knees til they bloody red beggin please see I don't know if you get it yet just don't know he's like a lighter to my cigarette watch me smoke I never knew another human life didn' t know could have the power to take over mine so baby  Baby baby baby baby baby  baby I love you baby baby baby baby baby I love it when I hear your name got me sayin baby baby baby baby baby baby I love you baby baby baby baby baby  See I can never feel alone with you in my life I'll give up everything I own for you won't think twice almost ashamed how I'm mesmerised such a shame I lose my thought lookin in your eyes I know why because your kisses make my lips quiver... and that's real and when you touch me my whole body shivers.. I can feel now I can see how another life another life could have the power to take over mine cause you're my  Baby baby baby baby baby  baby I love you   ooh mann..  came home at 11..first thing, check out tha Blog..play Baby by ashanti.....since i got tha house to mahself....start singin like all hell is in one spot.. haa..   damn mandeep..  mah babe..    There ain't another Don't want no other lover I'll put nothing above ya' I'll kick up to the gutter You tried to shake me End up loving me crazy now Look at us lately And tell them whose your lady   I'll never thought you'll be the one Make me shine brighter than the sun There ain't no ups and downs No when and outs  you're here right now...   niggaa..  i miss you so much..  that smiling face...  shitt, no one can  beat that..  damn..   aight well imma go take a shower..but ill be back cuz today..  damn today..i gotta write like Whoa fo mah babe..   like..WhOA..   -nananananoor :) 
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got this jones formin in my bones from a man who indeed took over my soul understand I couldn't breathe if he ever said he would leave get on my knees til they bloody red beggin please see I don't know if you get it yet just don't know he's like a lighter to my cigarette watch me smoke I never knew another human life didn' t know could have the power to take over mine so baby  Baby baby baby baby baby  baby I love you baby baby baby baby baby I love it when I hear your name got me sayin baby baby baby baby baby baby I love you baby baby baby baby baby  See I can never feel alone with you in my life I'll give up everything I own for you won't think twice almost ashamed how I'm mesmerised such a shame I lose my thought lookin in your eyes I know why because your kisses make my lips quiver... and that's real and when you touch me my whole body shivers.. I can feel now I can see how another life another life could have the power to take over mine cause you're my  Baby baby baby baby baby  baby I love you   ooh mann..  came home at 11..first thing, check out tha Blog..play Baby by ashanti.....since i got tha house to mahself....start singin like all hell is in one spot.. haa..   damn mandeep..  mah babe..    There ain't another Don't want no other lover I'll put nothing above ya' I'll kick up to the gutter You tried to shake me End up loving me crazy now Look at us lately And tell them whose your lady   I'll never thought you'll be the one Make me shine brighter than the sun There ain't no ups and downs No when and outs  you're here right now...   niggaa..  i miss you so much..  that smiling face...  shitt, no one can  beat that..  damn..   aight well imma go take a shower..but ill be back cuz today..  damn today..i gotta write like Whoa fo mah babe..   like..WhOA..   -nananananoor :) 
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got this jones formin in my bones from a man who indeed took over my soul understand I couldn't breathe if he ever said he would leave get on my knees til they bloody red beggin please see I don't know if you get it yet just don't know he's like a lighter to my cigarette watch me smoke I never knew another human life didn' t know could have the power to take over mine so baby  Baby baby baby baby baby  baby I love you baby baby baby baby baby I love it when I hear your name got me sayin baby baby baby baby baby baby I love you baby baby baby baby baby  See I can never feel alone with you in my life I'll give up everything I own for you won't think twice almost ashamed how I'm mesmerised such a shame I lose my thought lookin in your eyes I know why because your kisses make my lips quiver... and that's real and when you touch me my whole body shivers.. I can feel now I can see how another life another life could have the power to take over mine cause you're my  Baby baby baby baby baby  baby I love you   ooh mann..  came home at 11..first thing, check out tha Blog..play Baby by ashanti.....since i got tha house to mahself....start singin like all hell is in one spot.. haa..   damn mandeep..  mah babe..    There ain't another Don't want no other lover I'll put nothing above ya' I'll kick up to the gutter You tried to shake me End up loving me crazy now Look at us lately And tell them whose your lady   I'll never thought you'll be the one Make me shine brighter than the sun There ain't no ups and downs No when and outs  you're here right now...   niggaa..  i miss you so much..  that smiling face...  shitt, no one can  beat that..  damn..   aight well imma go take a shower..but ill be back cuz today..  damn today..i gotta write like Whoa fo mah babe..   like..WhOA..   -nananananoor :) 
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got this jones formin in my bones from a man who indeed took over my soul understand I couldn't breathe if he ever said he would leave get on my knees til they bloody red beggin please see I don't know if you get it yet just don't know he's like a lighter to my cigarette watch me smoke I never knew another human life didn' t know could have the power to take over mine so baby  Baby baby baby baby baby  baby I love you baby baby baby baby baby I love it when I hear your name got me sayin baby baby baby baby baby baby I love you baby baby baby baby baby  See I can never feel alone with you in my life I'll give up everything I own for you won't think twice almost ashamed how I'm mesmerised such a shame I lose my thought lookin in your eyes I know why because your kisses make my lips quiver... and that's real and when you touch me my whole body shivers.. I can feel now I can see how another life another life could have the power to take over mine cause you're my  Baby baby baby baby baby  baby I love you   ooh mann..  came home at 11..first thing, check out tha Blog..play Baby by ashanti.....since i got tha house to mahself....start singin like all hell is in one spot.. haa..   damn mandeep..  mah babe..    There ain't another Don't want no other lover I'll put nothing above ya' I'll kick up to the gutter You tried to shake me End up loving me crazy now Look at us lately And tell them whose your lady   I'll never thought you'll be the one Make me shine brighter than the sun There ain't no ups and downs No when and outs  you're here right now...   niggaa..  i miss you so much..  that smiling face...  shitt, no one can  beat that..  damn..   aight well imma go take a shower..but ill be back cuz today..  damn today..i gotta write like Whoa fo mah babe..   like..WhOA..   -nananananoor :) 
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      jus talked to mah babe..   faintly i hear him cry shedding those tears shit i wish i could jus hold him my baby mah life as much as it hurts.. i feel so helpless  so unable so Conscious  im dangerously in love.. so in love babe..so in Love..  i love you babe, love you with my life, with my all, with everything i have to give with..jus all of Me.. shit, i love you so much it hurts  i have an unbelievable amount to show you man...i don know how else to say..i jus love you  shit i wanna be with you..i love you so much mandeep..you dont even knoww  what is it bout me.. ur mom...shit..  her words are like alcohol touchin an open cut..damn...she burns  i hear you all day..  im your angel..jus yours  jus yours babe...   there are those who abuse what they've been given there are those who struggle everyday jus to stay livin' a simple existence is what i shall seek and with that i'll always know that my life is complete  damn.    damn, they say life take ur dreams and turns them upside down  but with me..  one person..can change my everything     so who completes your life sweety aunty..       sorry, all i did was like your son.. all i did..      you feel cursed with me in your son's life..and your son feels blessed..what irony..   damn, im sorry aunty. im so sorry.     what am i gonna do.    how can i speak the thoughts of my mind..how can i convey the feelings inside..trying to console myself that one time there will be a chance for you and me..there have been times that weve been together..stolen moments that weve shared together..happiness yes but then thereafter questions rise up in my mind.. will all of these last forever? since you came in my life i have loved you and i have tried my best to understand you, though i know there are times.. it causes me pain deep inside..and i try to hide the tears i cried. but there are feelings that only our hearts can understand and  i dont know until when i can stay like this with you i cant assure myself of what lies ahead between me and you..what my heart knows is the past was already behind..the future is far beyond... and the present is the most important...because as of now my present lies with..my love for you..   i love you so so much..  damn..   my life. my love. my everything.  you, mandeep..Youu..   -ya gurl.. 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whoever fuckin wrote that comment better watch their fuckin back  dont even trip..U mah prey fo tha next few months..  fuk this bullshit..  i miss you mandeep and im reall sorry bout today..damn how i got beat.  we cant talk on tha phone fo a while now...or atleast wit our rents knowin bout it..   shit..   damn, i saw you today..i couldnt even breathe i was so happy..but terrified at the same time...  fuk.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       having faith in someone. having faith is being confident in a person, knowing that if they strive their hardest..that they can acheive anything that they want to pursue in life..being encouraging and supportive.      yeaa..      over here it seems we are living in the negative. everything is about how much wrong a person has done, how many sins they have committed, I dont understand..if having faith doesnt come from home first, then where else does it bloom?                                       well..         anyway,               jus a song..            Beauty queen of only eighteen   She had some trouble with herself   He was always there to help her   She always belonged to someone else   I drove for miles and miles   And wound up at your door   I've had you so many times but somehow   I want more   I don't mind spending everyday   Out on your corner in the pouring rain   Look for the girl with the broken smile   Ask her if she wants to stay awhile   And she will be loved   She will be loved   Tap on my window knock on my door   I want to make you feel beautiful   I know I tend to get insecure   It doesn't matter anymore   It's not always rainbows and butterflies   It's compromise that moves us along   My heart is full and my door's always open   You can come anytime you want   I don't mind spending everyday   Out on your corner in the pouring rain   Look for the girl with the broken smile   Ask her if she wants to stay awhile   And she will be loved   She will be loved   I know where you hide   Alone in your car   Know all of the things that make you who you are   I know that goodbye means nothing at all   Comes back and begs me to catch her every time she falls   ...        yeaa..wow. Maroon 5- "She will be loved" great song.    anyway, babe, I Love You. I am reall sorry about yesterday, after we had gotten off the phone I thought that we weren't going to be able to talk so I went to my godmom's house to say bye to her and then came back at 10:30..I'm so sorry, shit, I shouldve stayed home..damn, from what it sounded like on tha phone, I thought we werent gonna be able to talk fo a long time.    I dont know if it's ok to call today, but Imma call anyway cuz my cousins are coming over for dinner..and you said you were gonna drop your mom off at the airport at around 7 (??)..yeaa.    today, my dad went over my SAT with me, and I got some math problems wrong..that was the worst morning I have ever had. I dont think I have heard anyone say Stupid that many times. Its like..ok I'm sorry if I don't remember a formula or one thing...thats kind of why I'm practicing so that I can memorize more of what I need to so that I can do well on the SAT.    whatever.        tomorrow I'm going to the gurduwara from 6:30-9:30pm. my parents might be going to a banquet so me and my massi will go with Harneet. On Friday I'm not going to the hospital to volunteer because I have to practice again at the gurduwara from 6:30-9:30pm. so yeaa..Saturday is two days away, I cant wait to see youu. I LOVE YOU MANDEEP.        love you..                        aighh...weelll, im out..                    I lovE yOU.        love you..                                                                                                                                                             i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love youuuuuuu.....                                                                aighh..take care..                                     nOOrSeTHi.                           
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       no baby..      too long, toooo long 'til saturday. i cant wait that long man. i miss you like crazy..haa, today i got on to my 6th page..jus fo today's letter..plus 3 more from yesterday..damn, imma winnnn. hahaa..anyway, watup babe..how YOUU doin'..      so las night after i got off tha phone, i cried a lil and listened to yo demo all over again..damn man. you cant last 2 weeks?? you gon hit school and start gettin busy..imma be home fo another month. i miss you like crazzzzy..you dont even know..i miss your smile, that look you give me when i look stupid..lol...shit man, thaT cracks me upp..hahaa..i love you so much, damn..you dont even know..ohh man, imma show you..imma SHOW you....damnn..so how you doing, how was ur day, how are things at home??..hows tha MoM? tha DaAd?..jasdEeP?..grandMa?..i hope everyone is okay.      damn i miss you so much.      anyway, i gotta go.         ill catch you later, ill try to write more later..         aighh..               I LOVE YOU..                                                   noor..Sethi.....                                             yeaa..                                       
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yeaa..      wuttup babe.      oh man, las night..was tha hardest night of my life. i fuckin cried.   i want you here with me so bad mandeep. you dont even understand how i feel. damn i jus wish all the times i was with you could repeat all over again, saturday is too far away for me. i love you so much and i want you to never ever ever forget that. i love youuu.      news: my bhua had a son at 9:00pm las night. wooo! one more GUY cousin. haha...its coo its coo.      but yeaa, back to what i was saying..   damn mandeep. how i love you.      i miss you so much and i cant wait til saturday. we gon be hookin it up wit tha chapstick and all. you know..      damn i miss youuu. i feel like crying..   this is My Frustration.      i miss you so much so so so so so so so much.      come home sooon, i cant wait to talk to you. I LOVE YOU. i thought i would write long today but when i came home from school, i couldnt because i went to dJ Aman's house with Harneet to make our Cd since my mom wasnt coo wit ur house and so that took from like..uhh..lets see...12:40 to 3..i think, yeaa..3. and then we practiced until 6:30..and i jus got done with some of my hw, i still gotta work on SAT crap, dad said i needa get started on it again. but today during school, i wrote you letters...and i started practicing my signature of when im married.      you know, jus a head start. =)      noor sethi.      yeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.....hahaa..      i cant wait.         i love you so much mandeep. i love you SO much.      i jus wanna be in your arms and never leave. saturday was the best night of my life next to thursday june 17th. damn boy, august 17th..3 months.      we movin' and grooovin.         ey, i listened to yo demo...i LOVE tha new tracks. damn..you gon make tha big pages someday, i can garuntee you that. i love youuuu....then...after..i went back and listened to Track 7 on tha old one..      thas when i broke down..i love you so much.      damn, it amazes me how much we've been through and my love for you has only grown.      --> may 17th, the day i was admitted into heaven.      yeah.      damn..            it is a priviledge.                              it is a priviledge..            i love you mandeep.               love youu   so   so   so much.         i love you.                           aighh..im out befo mah pparents bust my ass...i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you i love you..            damn..i LOVE YOU.                                       -ya wife,   xoxoxo      noor sEthi       
    
</post>


</Blog>