<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is your full name? Susanna Elizabeth Crafton Nicknames? Suzy, Zannie, Floozy Single or taken? taken :) Sex? Girl Where do you live? K-Town Sex or ice cream? mmm icecream for now. lol What color underwear are you wearing right now? A really purdy blue! What are you doing right now? Trying to escape bordom What was the last thing you did? mmm had a b'day party 4 my big'D! What is right next to you? A closet If you were a toy, what would you be? A My little Pony Where do you want to go on your honeymoon? An exotic island Who do you want to spend the rest of your life with? Jody! How many people do you have on your buddy list? 197 How's the weather right now? It's nighttime. Last person you spoke to on the phone? mmm my mom? Last person who IMed you? James Last person you IMed? James What's your ring tone? Toxic What do you think a toblerone is? Swiss candy duh! haha anna... lol hair? In a clip What are you wearing right now? Black pants, pink shirt... Do you wear contacts? Nope What school do you attend? NCCS Do you own a vehicle? yes'm Have you ever won a special award?  haha... well this year, most improved for swimming and 3 letter award What are your futures plans? Go to UGA and be a Pediatric P.A. or Psychiatrist Fave day of the year? This year... SEPT 4!!! but i dunno... e'ry year is differant Are you too shy to ask anyone out? haha no... but i dont have to worry bout that now do i? ;) Have you ever been in love? Yes, deeply. Do you like scary or happy movies?? Happy most of the time Christmas or Easter? Christmas. Lust or love? Love. Kisses or hugs? Kissies. If you could change one thing, what would it be? I would change the minds of nonbelievers (of Jesus) What color are your pajamas? dadgum, i have LOTS of pajamas... so well... e'ry color! What color is your toothbrush? Blue.  Fave part of the opposite sex? hair What’s the first thing you think of when you wake up? Wut i g2 get up and do... Roller coaster: scary or exciting? Exciting! How many times do you let the phone ring before you answer it? depends how long it takes me to find it! If you could meet one person, dead or alive, who would it be? My man, JC! Fave quote? Wow... so many... i guess ill go with, "I guess i just feel sorry for you cuz u didnt know you were going against... A SUPERSTAR!~!~!~!" tee hee Zodiac sign? Virgo? Half empty or half full? Half-full What’s your fave number? 7!~! Root beer or Doctor Pepper? Dr. Pepper i suppose? Mud or jelly wrestling? Hmmm im quite partial to mud Skiing or snowboarding? Skiing, only cuz i can... havent tried snow boarding yet... Day or night? Day... well... night too... hmmm... it all depends... i love summer nights! :):):) Summer or winter? SUMMER!!! Silver or gold? Silver. Diamonds or pearls? Diamonds are a girls best friend!~! (haha whoever said that odviously never met cameron! lol) but yes i do like diamonds. Sunrise or sunset? Sunset :) Have you ever broken a bone? Yeah... wrist Do you hate anyone? Nope... man that was a bad one to end on!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       HEY THUR  how is e'ryonez summa goin??? GOOD! haha well yes... the past couple days have been quite eventful... Yesterday i went to 6 flags wit cameron and anna! It was super super fun! Man the FUNNIEST things ALWAYS happen to us!!! haha... man... we saw lil bow wow thur... being attacked by random screaming crazed girls! haha. Now THERE is something worth seeing! So yeah... then that night at like 10:30 i went ova to Jody's church for a lock in! It was AWESOME!!! haha man i've never laughed so hard over the randomest things. lol... bbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbbiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiggggggggggggggggg  BOOTY BIG BOOTY BIG BOOTY, AHHHHHHHHHHH BIG BOOTY!!!  haha... Wooow. Good times good times. So yeah, needless to say i didnt sleep... and NO jody, i WASNT tired! haha. As a matter a fact, when i got home i was really really hyper, so i went with my dad to work on his houses that he bought... man we cleaned that thing ALL DAY!!! ahhh... and finally yes, i admit it, when i got home i CRASHED! Geeze i didnt know my dad was a slavedriver! haha. Naw, it really was fun actually! So... then cameron woke me up, showed me Flipper... her new car... (i named it! tee hee) and we sat in it for quite some time! haha. Aaaaand now im here... yippie. Ehh... i'll prolly do a survey now... ;) lolol
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. My name: Cameron Alyse Mclendon 2. Where/When did we meet?: MATH CLASS in 8th grade baby!~! 3. Take a stab at my middle name.: Uh..lemme "guess"... Alyse! 4. How long have you known me?: almost 3 yrs 5. How well do you know me?: VERY VERY VERY well! to say the least! 6. Would we be classified friends or acquientances?: haha BEST FRIENDS! 7. Do I believe in God?:  yeah! 8. When you first saw/met me what was your impression?: Wow... shes a wierd one! 9. My age?: 16! 10. Birthday?: December 9!~! 11. Color hair?: Red Head! haha 12. Color eyes?: Yella 13. Am I tall or short or average? AVERAGE! haha 14. Do I have any siblings?: YES! katie n kyle 15. (If opposite sex) Have you ever had a crush on me?: OF COURSE! haha (If same sex) Have you ever been jealous of me? naw... well mabye of ur parents... remember? lol 16. Who am I in love with?: ME!!! Oh... and Adam Eugene 17. What's one of my favorite things to do?: laugh uncontrollably with me! haha 18. Do you remember one of the 1st things I said to you?: Mmm i dunno... all i remember is our first phone conversasion... you sang veggie tales... THE WHOLE TIME! 19. What's your funniest memory of me?: Omigosh... TOOOOO many to count!!! 20. What's my favorite type of music?: mmm purdy much everythang 21. What is the best feature about me?: your smile 22. What is my worst feature?: ur calousy feet 23. Do you look up or down on me...as a person?: i look eye level.  24. Do you think I have morals and values?: ummm yeah! 25. Am I a leader or a follower?: prolly leader 26. Am I shy or outgoing?: outgoing! 27. Can you picture me dancin'?: haha OOOOOOO yeah baby! 28. Can you picture me rollin'?: mmm yeah? haha 29. Would you say I am funny?: yes! 30. Am I a rebel or do I follow all the rules?: We're rebels baby!~! haha lunch... good times good times!  31. Any special talents?: yes yes yes 32. What's my best accomplishment?: mmm hard to say... choosing me as a friend? haha naw... ummm just where ya r spiritually is a big accomplishment. 33. Would you consider me a friend?: OF COURSE... man these are dum Qs! 34. Would you call me preppy, sexy, a raver, a homie, average, sporty, punk, hippie, glam, nerdy, jappy, sk8er or something else?: sexy, average (haha only cuz adam sed it) Gorgeous and ummm yippy! 35. Have you ever seen me cry and visversa?: yes and yes 36. If there were one good nickname for me what would it be?: FLOOZIE!~! 37. What is your favorite thing to do with me?: MAKE MUffinS and cuddle! 38. Do I drink? hahahahhahahahhaaha 39. Do I do drugs? ye-- i mean no 40. Have I ever been there for you?: YES! 41. Am I fun to be with?: YES! 42. Am I smart?: Yeah, when ya wanna be! 43. Am I conservative or unconservative?: as conservative as you can! haha 44. Do you love me?: YES! 45. Would ya ever go out with me?(if you are of the same sex I would definitely prefer you not to answer questions 45-47!) haha fine fine... 46. Would you ever make out with me? ADAM wood! 47. Would I make a good b/f or g/f?: for ADAM... 48. Name one way that I have changed your life or made an impact in it: Man, how have u not? Your the bestest friend i could EVER ask for! You've changed my life flooz!  49. What is something about me I don't know?: haha NOTHING 50. What is something about me that few other people know? that you were born with 3 extra toes!~! hahaha 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. My name: 2. Where/When did we meet?: 3. Take a stab at my middle name.: 4. How long have you known me?: 5. How well do you know me?: 6. Would we be classified friends or acquientances?: 7. Do I believe in God?: 8. When you first saw/met me what was your impression?: 9. My age?: 10. Birthday?: 11. Color hair?: 12. Color eyes?: 13. Am I tall or short or average? 14. Do I have any siblings?: 15. (If opposite sex) Have you ever had a crush on me?: (If same sex) Have you ever been jealous of me? 16. Who am I in love with?: 17. What's one of my favorite things to do?: 18. Do you remember one of the 1st things I said to you?: 19. What's your funniest memory of me?: 20. What's my favorite type of music?: 21. What is the best feature about me?: 22. What is my worst feature?: 23. Do you look up or down on me...as a person?: 24. Do you think I have morals and values?: 25. Am I a leader or a follower?: 26. Am I shy or outgoing?: 27. Can you picture me dancin'?: 28. Can you picture me rollin'?: 29. Would you say I am funny?: 30. Am I a rebel or do I follow all the rules?: 31. Any special talents?: 32. What's my best accomplishment?: 33. Would you consider me a friend?: 34. Would you call me preppy, sexy, a raver, a homie, average, sporty, punk, hippie, glam, nerdy, jappy, sk8er or something else?: 35. Have you ever seen me cry and visversa?: 36. If there were one good nickname for me what would it be?: 37. What is your favorite thing to do with me?: 38. Do I drink? 39. Do I do drugs? 40. Have I ever been there for you?: 41. Am I fun to be with?: 42. Am I smart?: 43. Am I conservative or unconservative?: 44. Do you love me?: 45. Would ya ever go out with me?(if you are of the same sex I would definitely prefer you not to answer questions 45-47!) 46. Would you ever make out with me? 47. Would I make a good b/f or g/f?: 48. Name one way that I have changed your life or made an impact in it: 49. What is something about me I don't know?: 50. What is something about me that few other people know? 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THE BASICS*~  Your Name- Susanna Elizabeth Crafton Nicknames- Suzy, Floozy,Zannie Birthday- August 23,1988  ~*HAVE YOU??*~  Been kissed? yes ma'am Eaten an entire box of Oreos? mmm nope? Been on stage? Yeah... haha Spring Play baby!~! tee hee good times Gotten in a car accident? haha yeah... whitney our 5 car pile up! Death Valley on horseback? Wuts death valley? i guess not.. pretty close tho since i almost died falling off a horse... in a valley... haha. Stayed home? Durrr Made homemade fudge? No... but that wood be funn!!! Seen the Eiffel tower? In pictures...  ~*FAVORITES*~  Shampoo: Panteen! haha (sp?) Soap: Caress body wash :) mmmm Color: Cruelean Day: This year? September 4 baby!~!~!~! Night: The night Jody asked me out! Band: Switchfoot! Season: Summer! Commercial: The Six flags one!!! ~*YOUR FRIENDS*~  Do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend? Yes ma'am Do you have a crush on someone: Yeah ;) lol Do you have a best friend? yeah! like duh! Do you rank your speed dial in order of favorite friends? Not really Who's your funniest friend? It depends... funny in wut way? lol  Who do you go to the mall with the most? haha CAMERON! lol Who do you e-mail the most? noone Who have you known the longest of your friends? prolly Joanna :) Who's the loudest? cameron Who's the shyest? prolly sarah b. Whose parents do you know the best? camerons :) mommy n daddy Who do you go to for advice? mmm either noone or cameron Who knows all your secrets? cameron and jody Who do you get the most surveys from? JODY!~! thanx baby!~! Who are you jealous of? noone. i like being me :) Who do you cry with? Cameron What is your usual quote? "yes ma'am" or "eat me for lunch"  ~*IN THE LAST 48 HOURS HAVE YOU*~  Cried? Nope. happy happy! Eaten fluf? FLUF??? if that means laundry detergent then yes! ;) Jody... haha. Helped someone? Yes Bought something? Yes Dissected something? def NOT Cut your hair? nope Worn a skirt? nope Worn a tie? yes--- i mean nope Been mean? i dont think? Been sarcastic? haha probly.. i dont really know... Gone for a run? nope Gone for a walk? yes Gone to the movies? yes! Shrek 2 baby! Gone out for dinner? naw Been kissed? yes'm Felt stupid? yeah! Said "I love you"? yeah Written a letter? haha NO Written a paper? haha big NO Taken a test? hahahhaha BIG BIG NO! Met someone new? nope Moved on? to what? Written in a journal? this is sorta a journal Watched your favorite movie? nope! need to do that! Talked to someone you have a crush on? haha yeah Given someone a present? nope Missed someone? yes Hugged someone? yes Had a nightmare? actauly yeah... kinda weird Fought with your parents? nope Fought with a friend? nope Been Scared? nope  ~*WHENS THE LAST TIME YOU*~  Showered? this afternoon Ate a meal? mmm five hours ago What are you wearing right now? thats not a "whens the last time"... but uh... pajamas! Are you tired? nope Are you lonely? nope cameron jus got hur Are you happy? yes! Are you wearing pajamas? haha You nailed it! Are you hungry? nope... she brought teddy grahms :) Are you eating? nope Are you talking to someone online? nope Are you ready for this survey to end? nope :) i liek surveys! :) How long did this survey take you? bout 15 min *Do you want all your friends to do this and send back? YES!  WELL YOU'RE NOT DONE!!!.... YAY! lol  >>>>FAVORITE STUFF>>>>   Type of sandwich: Subway! :) Coffee or hot chocolate? Coffe coffe coffee Cold or hot? weather? HOT HOT HOT Big or little? mmm it depends... big or lil wut? Gold brick? BIG! haha Lace or satin? Satin... i hate lace! Red or blue? BLue! New or old? new i suppose Here or there? THERE   OK YOU'RE DONE!!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My fat cheeks!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron the drag queen!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    us... tryin to be serious... ha!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron posed me... "Spanky spanky!"&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron sitting on a ball...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "PAWTY OVA HERE!~!" hahahahhaha&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    WEEEEEEEEEEE&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me tryin to figger out a fishing pole... Cameron says this is my thinkin face... hmmm&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "ooo im cameron!"&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "Im a wee school girl!"&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    MY TURN!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron is workin out!... or havin a baby!..?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron likes this one... eh.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    CAMERON! Upon My Dads Car!~!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ME! Upon My Car!~!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    HEATHER!!!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The "Raptor" Strikes again!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron... in a bucket!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me being a boi... playing poker... yeah.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron doesnt only drink!!! haha&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    me too...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    CAMERONS IS A BEASTLY VAMPIRE!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron says i am a "constipated mechanical raptor" &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron is a wild boar!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "Ow"&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron is silly&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ehhh i dont like this one... cameron made me do it.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron likes the wall!~!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Weird huh!?!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron likes cookie monster!...pants.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    haha... dont really know wut im doin... but it looks like im peeing on my post!~! haha&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cameron is a GORILLA!~!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay!~! I'm finally NOT bored! haha yehaw! Well prolly cuz i've been with cameron for the past four days straight! haha. Yeah... scrabble i must say, is addicting! haha so addicting that we've stayed up for two days straight playing it! haha. Well, other stuff too... but hot dang! we just werent tired!~! And we're still going... on no sleep whatsoever. But yeah, fun stuff. So yeah... get ready cuz were about to go crazy with the pictures again!~! Muahaha!~!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Schools out... im bored. haha. hey if u guys knwo of anythang that i can do... leave a comment. lol. So yeah... today i went to the awards thang with cameron. It was boring. haha. Me n cameron just commented on the whole thing. haha it was funny. O- that was after getting yelled at for not wearing chapel dress (who knew???) and being 12 minutes late... i mean comon... who is actually on time the last day of school? haha. o well. its ova so w/e. Then me, cameron, jody, and his beautiful family all went to Wa-ho! haha. fun stuff... then we left and me and cameron went Garage saling!~! woo hoo!~! haha. it was really fun! we got scabble and when we got home we played ebonic scrabble. haha best kind baby!~! Who knew "leanstix" and "debluetwig" were actually words!!! haha. Man were entertained extremely easily! lol. So yeah... now im sittin here letting my inner blackness out with Christian rap. haha. Yes yes. Allllllllrighty, i think ill go make somthing up thats fun to do...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      TELL US ABOUT YOU  What time is it? 11:11 pm *Name*: Susanna Crafton *Nicknames*: Suzy, floozy,  *Parent's names*: beth n tyler *Number of candles that appeared on your last birthday cake*: 15 *Date that you regularly blow them out (birthday):* aug 23 *Pets*: a cat-pookie a dog-theodore a bird-gonzo a turtle-squirt and 3 fish-fred, unnamed n unnamed... *Height*: 5-08 *Eye color*: dark chocolate (haha cameron) *Hair Color*: brown *Piercing*: ears   HAVE YOU EVER...?  *Had the drink Calypso Breeze*? mmm cant say i have...  *Been in love*? yes!~! *Been toilet-papering*? nope! want to tho! haha to mr garner! *Loved somebody so much it makes you cry*? why wood being in love make u cry   THE FUTURE:  *School*: uga baBA *Where You Want To Live*: Calfornia *How Many Kids You Want*: 2 *girl names*: Elizabeth Grace *boy names*: Landon Brian *What Kind Of Job You Want*: Psychiatrist *You Want To Get Married*: heck yeah! haha ask that aaafter the kid questions. haha.   WHO:  *Makes You Laugh The Most*: Cameron and Jody *Do You Go To For Advice or To talk About Things*: cameron *Who Do You Hate*: dont hate anyone... *Knows The Most About You*: cameron and jody *Is Your Best Friend*: Cameron anna and jody *Has It Easier, Guys Or Girls*: GUYS!!!! HECK YEAH!~!   WHICH ONE?  *Croutons or Bacon Bits*: Croutons! *2 doors or 4 (on a car)*: 4! no crawler ova ppl fo me! haha *Mr. Pibb or Dr. Pepper*: doesnt matta! *Coffee or Ice-cream*: COFFEE ICECREAM! lol *Shampoo or Conditioner*: conditioner! *Bridges or Tunnels*: hmmm... random... but uh... both? tunnels are cooler in an erie sorta way... *One pillow or two*: one *Adidas or Nike*: adidas... school sponser baby! haha *Nike or Reebok*: nike *Adidas or Reebok*: adidas   WORD ASSOCIATION (FIRST THING THAT COMES TO MIND)  *Rock*: moses *Green*: hair *Wet*: rain *Cry*: sad *Peanut Butter*: joanna  FAVORITES:  *Salad Dressing*: ranch *Color of socks*: white? *Memory*: Prom *toothpaste*: crest white exprssions-orange *Food*: Frozen Yogurt!~! *Song at the moment*:  *TV show*: that 70s show *Toothbrush*: i dunno? *Subject in School*: NONE!!! BOO SCHOOL!!! haha actually psychology *Flower*: rose :) *Color*: cruelean blue *NON-ALOHOLIC DRINK*: WATER!~! :) *Sport to Watch*: basketball *Country Song*: earl had to die *Sesame Street Character*: ELMO BABY!~!~!~! *Disney Character*: mmm i dunno i really like simba and nemo *Warner Brothers*: i dunno? bugs bunny?   RANDOM QUESTIONS  *When was your last hospital check in*: when i broke my arm *Do You Drink*: nope *How many times did you fail your permit and Drivers License  Test?*: haha none *Where do you see your self in 10 years?*: married and being a psychiatrist *Who is the last person that you got mail from before  this one*? i dunno *Have you ever been convicted of a crime*? mmm not really *Which single store would you choose to max your credit card*? mmm khols! :) *What type of car you drive now*? lexus... when i can drive... ha! *What do you do most often when you are bored*? SURVEYS!~!~! *Name the person that you are friends with that lives the  farthest away from you*: Anna!!! *Are You In A Gang Or Club*: yeah man... me n my gangs *Motorcycles*: NO!!! THEY ALMOST KILLED MY DAD!!! ...twice! *What Is Your Favorite Kind Of Clothes*: i dunno... cute n comfortable ones??    *Are You Close Minded*: no *Are You Open Minded*: yeah *Are You A Player*: no *Can u be in love w/2 people at the same time*? not romatically *Bedtime*: hmmm in the summa who knows when! during school, like 12 ish *Humiliating Moment*: mmm nope... i dont get embarrassed  *what time is it now*: 1:49 pm... the next day haha. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever... {x} Fallen for your best friend? CAMERON! haha no. {x} Made out with JUST a friend? Nope {x} Been rejected? nope {x} Been in love? YES! {x} Been in lust? nope {x} Used someone? nope {x} Been used? PLENTY of times! {x} Cheated on someone? Nope {x} Been cheated on? Yep {x} Done something you regret? Yes  Who was the last person... {x} You touched? Weasle {x} You talked to? Cameron of course.. still talkin too.. {x} You hugged? Cameron {x} You instant messaged? Austin {x} You kissed? Jody {x} You yelled at? mmm my mom? {x} You laughed with? cameron lol  Have you/are you/do you.... {x} Considered a life of crime? YES! everyday! haha no... {x} Considered being a hooker? can say that i have! ;) {x} Considered being a pimp? yes. haha j/k no. {x} Are you psycho? haha sometimes ;) {x} Split personalities? lol nope {x} Schizophrenic? nope {x} Obsessive? nope {x} Obsessive compulsive? nope nope {x} Panic? nope {x} Anxiety? GEEZE NO! {x} Depressed? no {x} Suicidal? No {x} Obsessed with hate? no. {x} Dream of mutilated bodies, blood, death, and gore? ew no {x} Dream of doing those things instead of just seeing them? nope... but ANNA DOES!!! sick girl! {x} Understanding: yes {x} Open-minded: yes {x} Arrogant: no {x} Insecure: Sometimes, not now. {x} Interesting: i dunno {x} Hungry: nope {x} Friendly: yes yes {x} Smart: I dunno, i suppose... {x} Moody: naw never {x} Childish: ALWAYS {x} Independent: yeah {x} Hard working: i wood say so {x} Organized:NO WAY! {x} Healthy: yeah... clogged free arteries baby! {x} Emotionally Stable: i guess u could say that ;) haha j/k {x} Shy: heck no! {x} Difficult: only when i cant make desicions {x} Attractive: depends on ur own oppinion {x} Bored Easily: heck yea! y do ya think im doin this? {x} Thirsty: actually yeah... {x} Responsible: when i really wanna be... {x} Sad: not now... life is good {x} Happy: yes {x} Trusting: yeah {x} Talkative: heck yeah {x} Original: yeah {x} Different: lol yeah haha me n cameron sportin the wierd side of girls {x} Unique: haha in a wierd sorta way {x} Lonely: yeah {x} Color your hair? once {x} Have tattoos? nope {x} Piercings? ears  {x} Have a boyfriend? yes ma'am! :):):) {x} Floss daily? unless i forget {x} Own a webcam? yeah... dont use it tho {x} Ever get off the damn computer? mmm... yeah {x} Sprechen sie deutsche? yes {x} Habla espanol? si  Currents {x} Current Clothes: bathing suit and t-shirt {x} Current Mood: BORED haha but happy... sorta dazed {x} Current Taste: orbit {x} Current Hair: pony {x} Current Annoyance: Cameron singing "were the kids in America" and burping to me lolololol. {x} Current Smell: orbit {x} Current thing you ought to be doing: sleeping {x} Current Desktop Picture: haha me n camerons chuckie cheese pic!!! it rox!!!!!! {x} Current Favorite Group: SWITCHFOOT {x} Current Book: The great divorce- cs lewis {x} Current DVD In Player: i dunno  {x} Current Refreshment: water and gum {x} Current Worry: my poison ivy and ribs {x} Current Crush: my love, jody!~! {x} Current Favorite  {x}Celebrity: iii dunno {x} Food: FROZEN YOGURT! {x} Drink: lemon water! {x} Color: blue {x} Shoes: flip flops baby! {x} Candy: MILKYWAY MIDNIGHT! {x} TV Show: That 70's show {x} Movie: ZOOLANDER and SUPERSTAR {x} Dance: mmm the urban heat dance!!!! {x} Vegetable: Mmmm Broccali! {x} Fruit: APPLES ROCK!  On Dating.... {x} Long or short hair? long {x} Dark or blond hair? dark {x} Tall or short? tall  {x} Mr. Sensitive or Mr. Funny? Funny! duh! {x} Good guy or bad guy? good... but too good is boring...  {x} Dark or light eyes? Jodys eyes... ah i love em! {x} Hat or no hat? mmm depends... prolly no hat {x} Pierced or no? naw {x} Freckles or none? No preference {x} Stubble or neatly shaved? doesnt matta {x} Rugged outdoorsy type or sporty type? sporty type  On preferences.... {x} Chocolate milk or hot chocolate? hot {x} McDonalds or Burger King? mcdonalds... cuz bk is NASTY {x} Marry the perfect lover or the perfect friend? mmm BOTH! {x} Sweet or sour? sweet def! {x} Root Beer or Dr. Pepper? dr. pepper {x} Sappy/action/comedy/horror? comedy!!! {x} Cats or dogs? dogs  {x} Ocean or Pool? pool! {x} Cool Ranch or Nacho Cheese? cool ranch {x} Mud or Jell-O wrestling? Wow!!! Theres jello wrestling??? duuuude! as much as i love mud... im sportin the jello!~! {x} With or without ice-cubes? WITH! mmmm ice is awesome {x} Shine or rain? both! i love rain {x} Winter/Summer/Fall/Spring? SUMMER {x} Vanilla or Chocolate? Chocolate!  {x} Gloves or mittens? wuts the difference??? {x} Eyes open or closed? depends.... when? when ur sleeping... mmm closed... when ur awake.... mmm open. lol {x} Fly or breathe under water? fly!!! {x} Bunk-bed or waterbed? waterbeds are wierd.... {x} Chewing gum or hard candy? chewing gum!!! ahhh im addicted {x} Motor boat or sailboat? motor {x} Lights on or off? on! on! on! {x} Chicken or fish? chicken... yum.  What's your favorite:. {x} Number? 7! {x} Holiday? Christmas! {x} Radio station? Q100 {x} Place? St simons/ sea island {x} Flower? rose {x} Scent? boys {x} If you could be anywhere, where would you be? with jody... at the beach {x} What would you be doing? sleeping on the warm sand {x} What are you listening to? nothing... eh i dont liek silence {x} Can you do anything freakish with your body? i can do just bout anything with my toes... lol {x} Do you have a favourite animal, no matter how lame it may be? Squirrels n monkeys
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What comes to mind when you hear..  ..snow?: no school!  ..rain?: SOO MUCH FUN!  ..tornado?: cows  ..summer love?: greese (summer lovin)  ..Jon?: Kessler? haha  ..Mike?: Maddison... haha melody!  ..Shea?: Martin   ..banana?: FROZEN!~! Ewww moooooom!   ..dizzy?: dean (baseball)   ..Laura?: Stalker   ..Juan?: Mexico   ..car?: LISENCE!  ..white?: cameron  ..peppermint?: patty  ..New Found Glory?: American flag    ..placebo?: placenta lol   ..orange juice?: yumm  ..candid camera?: SMILE!~! Your on candid camera!  ..sister?: Jobeth (sister i never had)   ..brother?: WEASLE!~!   ..hate?: NO! LOVE!   ..school?: OUT!!!!!!!   ..President?: Presidents day   ..football?: Beefy   ..rap?: Brush yo sholdas off!   ..pop?: Up agianst the wall (n sync)  ..rock?: school... our rock  ..punk?: kelly osborne   ..sex?: bad   ..death?: heaven  ..baby?: Cute   ..duuude?: SWEEET!   ..the end?: HARAY! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. Kissed your cousin: mmm cant say i have 2. Ran away: Yeah 3. Pictured your crush naked: mmm nooo 5. Broken someone's heart: lol yeah... im glad too! naw j/k 6. Been in love: yes sir!~!  7. Cried when someone Died: No... noones died 8. Wanted someone: mmm i dunno... wanted someone? 9. Broken a bone: yeah... muh wrist 11. Lied: haha yeah! 12. Cried in school: yeah   WHICH IS BETTER:   13. Coke or Pepsi: coke... eww pepsi! but water is better than both!!!!! 14. Sprite or 7UP: Sprite  15. Girls or Guys: Guys haha... girls can be mean and catty 21. Tall or Short: TALL   22. Pants or Shorts: pants! ugh hate shorts WITH THE OPPOSITE SEX:  23. What do you notice first: mouth... i know, its wierd... and hair 24. Last person you slow danced with: i'd like to say jody... but it was cameron in the mart today... haha 25. Worst Question To Ask: Am I fat? AHHHHH I HATE IT! JUST NEVER EVER SAY THAT EVER!!!!!!!!!  THE LAST TIME:  26. Showered: last night 27. Taken a bath: 2 nights ago  28. Changed Clothes: couple hours ago... sitll in my bathing suit... haha at 12... yeah... lol   WHAT IS (your favorite):  29. Your Good Luck Charm: cameron! haha 30. Person You Hate Most: mm i dont HATE anyone... but im sure if u knew me ud know the one person i dont like  31. Best Thing That Has Happened to You this year: Prom with Jody 32. Color: Cruelean Blue (its the BEST blue EVER!!!!) 33. Movie: Zoolander and superstar!!!  35. Juice: V8 Splash  36. Finger: i dunno i really like pinkies... 37. Ice Cream: Birthday Surprise @ Eatin Ice Cream  39. Season: Summer baby!~! 40. Breakfast Food: Cearal, apples, and coffee babY!~!  DO YOU EVER:  50. Sit by the phone waiting for a phone call all night: nope  51. Save Aim conversations: i ahve like twice... for blackmail haha   52. Save E-mails: not really  53. Wish you were someone else: NOWAY!~!  54. Wish you were a member of the opposite sex: Naw... that wood be wierd  BEST:  56. Cologne: CURVE baby!~! 59. Romantic memory: Prom  HAVE YOU:  62. Made out with JUST a friend?: nope 63. Been rejected: no  64. Been in love?: YES!~! 65. Been in lust?: no 66. Used someone?: naw 69. Been cheated on?: yeah! haha sixth grade!!! thats sad huh? 70. Been kissed?: yeah  71. Done something you regret?: yeah    WHO WAS THE LAST PERSON...  72. You touched?: Allysa... a baby  73. You talked to?: Cameron 74. You hugged?: Cameron  75. You instant messaged?: Jody 76. You kissed?: Jody 77. You had sex with?: nobody 78. You yelled at?: My mom 80. Who broke your heart?: my family 81. Who told you they loved you?: cameron  DO YOU...  82. Color your hair?: i did once lol cameron... wow 83. Have tattoos?: nope 84. Have piercings below the waist?: mmm nooo 85. Have a boyfriend/girlfriend/both?: boyfriend  86. Own a webcam?: yeah 87. Own a thong?: haha mmm yes... 88. Ever get off the computer?: occasionally  oops dunno where those questions went  90. Habla espanol?: Si! Con senor hicks!  91. Quack?: YEA!~! Comeon who doesnt???   HAVE YOU/DO YOU/ARE YOU...  92. Stolen anything over $50?: nope  93. Smoke?: a cigar... when i was like 6! GAG! 94. Schizophrenic?: def not 95. Obsessive?: def not  96. Compulsive?: def not 97. Obsessive Compulsive?: def def not lol 98. Panic?: nope... thats a dum question  99. Anxiety?: noooo 100. Depressed?: noo only for like a week  101. Suicidal?: nope
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well hey thur!~! I'm bored... yeah... sad huh? First day outta school and i can barely  take it. haha. but yeah, today was really really fun! Me n my floozie went to the mart all day!~! Whoohoo! it was really fun! n then i babysat and now im here! Yay. Well thats all... so ummm i guess ill go try n fix my poison ivy. Yehaw... how exhilerating. lol
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ADAM'S BUTT!~!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      LAST PERSON WHO...   x. Slept in your bed: Anna H and Anna T x. Saw you cry: mmm... probly wes n my dad x. Made you cry: my mom x. Spent the night at your house: "The Annas" x. You shared a drink with: mmm my flooz ;) x. You went to the movies with: Jody (a really really really long time ago! haha) x. You went to the mall with: cameron x. Yelled at you: Jeni... haha x. Sent you an email: Noone really...   HAVE YOU EVER...  x. Gotten in a fight with your pet: actually yea... last night... totally random. x. Been to New York: nope x. Dreamed something really crazy and then it happened the next day: yeah... sumthin bout mr goodwin... haha x. Had an imaginary friend: BOB MIKEY CAMPBELL IS AWESOME!~!  RANDOM   x. Red or blue: blue x. Spring or Fall: spring  x. Are you bored: Heck ya x. Last noise you heard: my neck crack... yummy x. Last time you went out of the state: The cruise...  x. Things you like in a the opposite sex: Long Hair ;) x. Do you have a crush on someone: Yeah!~! x. What book are you reading now: The great divorce... awesome book bout heaven and hell... Sportin CS Lewis baby!  x. Worst feeling in the world: feeling unloved x. What is the first thing you think when you wake in the morning: how much i would pay to stay in bed x. How many rings before you answer: mmm like 0 lol x. Future daughter's name: Elizabeth  x. Future son's name: Joseph or Landon... heck... or both! x. Do you sleep with a stuffed animal?: haha HECK YEAH! lots! x. If you could have any job you wanted, what would it be: psychiatrist or actress x. Are you a lefty, righty or ambidextrous: righty x. Do you type with your fingers on the right keys: lol nope x. What's under your bed:LOTS of pictures... and animals x. Favorite sport to watch: basketball baby! x. Current Age: 15 (blah.. sucky age lol) x. Siblings: 1 x. Cousins: Tooooo many! haha x. Location: K-Town x. College plans: UGA baby!~! x. Piercings: ears... as far as you know ;) haha j/k x. Boyfriend/Girlfriend: boyfriend... I LOVE YOU JODY!   EXTRA STUFF   x. Do you do drugs: nope x. Do you drink: nope x. Who is your best friend: Cameron anna and jody x. What kind of shampoo and conditioner do you use: Like 7 diff kinds x. What are you most scared of: clowns :( x. What clothes do you sleep in: pajamas... haha x. Who is the last person who called you: Cameron of course! x. Where do you want to get married: outside sumwhere.. unless it rains... lol x. Favorite number: 7!~! x. Been in Love: Yes... my first and last x. What type automobile do you drive: Lexus x. Are you timely or always late: when i drive, u betta believe im timely!~! other than that, heck no :( x. Do you have a job: haha does babysitting count? x. Do you like being around people: i thrive off of ppl! haha x. Best feeling in the world: when someone makes u feel loved x. Are you a health freak: def not lol   STUFF   x. Have you ever loved someone you had no chance with: yes... but some how God gave me a chance x. Want someone you don't have right now: nope x. Are you lonely right now: sorta... noones ova n im bored x. Ever afraid you'll never get married: i  was  worried x. Do you want to get married: YEAH!~! x. Do you want kids: yeah... ummm... not till im  good n ready tho lol   IN THE LAST 48 HOURS, HAVE YOU...   x. Cried: no x. Bought something: O Yeah!~! The mart baby!~! x. Said "I Love You": yes ma'am x. Wanted to tell someone you loved them: more than ever!~! x. Met someone new: yeah x. Talked to someone: yup x. Missed someone: heck yeah!!! x. Hugged someone: yes yes x. Fought with your parents: no x. Dreamt about someone you can't be with: nope x. Had a lot of sleep: YES!~! ahhh bliss!~!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This one is for you james... haha wut is up with that face??? haha&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha... I'm so sorry for all the dumb pictures! lol Me n cameron were messin around and we were excited cuz we just figgered it out! haha. Dude its so awesome! i love this thang! haha. Needless to say, i went crazy. tee hee. Well have fun with em! haha
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my favorite picture of all times! This little girl was so dirty and bug-infested, but she was the cutest thing i EVER did see!~!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Anna and I in MEXICO!~!~!~!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Isnt this crazy!?!? that was last year but man... what good times!~! ;)&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Awww I love this pic!!!'&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Awwww priceless. lolol&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hahahaha... soooo funny!~!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Theres my *HOTTIE*!!!!!!!!! (in da white) :)&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Flying MANDY!~! haha I swear that rope swing is a death trap!!! :(&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Bestest friends... EVER!!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tee hee... my brother!!!! AHHH!!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the best picture ever!!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That Jody and I!~!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wierd&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok ok... yes i know that i am a copier and i copied jody and cameron... but hey im bored... bored in general and VERY bored of Xanga. Dum xanga... pay for pictures??? i dont think so!!! lol. Ok so yeah... YAY FOR SUMMER! haha Well... yay for summer... for ME at least!~! Crazy! Im a Junior!~! Hmmm... not much diff... but hey... were not sophomoric... (haha Taylor Darden) lol. Woooow. So yeah... thats why im bored. Hmmm dang... im really really tired tho. i think it was a mix of that crazy math test and runnig around for a few hours with 5 pounds of quarters in my pants... haha... either way, im beat. haha. Yeah... needless to say, today was wierd... randomest stuff happend to cameron and i. haha. Our achoholic waiter, CAKE, UPS man, random guys taking pictures of us, lots of money in my pants... haha which is (by the way) a really good idea when ur bored! haha... drive around and pay for everything in change! haha. good times good times. Ok well this is getting long and boring, so im gunna go read or sleep... sumthin boring like that until i have to babysit. Yehaw!~! LOVE YA BUNCHIES!~! HAPPY SUMMER!~!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>