<Blog>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Read this site. And then someone please explain to me why we don't deport all these people.  Nothing like having a community of people right here in our own country that share the same beliefs and ideals of Zarqawi and Bin Laden.  Then on their membership page you get this.  ADC Special Announcement from ADC Board Chairperson Safa Rifka and President Mary Rose Oakar: ADC Announces New $10 Basic Membership  (Membership packet includes all the materials you will need to wage your very own fatah right here in America)  An important step in adding 100,000 new members by ADC's historic 25th Anniversary in 2005. We take enormous pride in the tremendous efforts and successes of ADC over the years,  (September 11, 2001) and are seeking to enhance this record of consistent achievement on behalf of civil  (Terrorist) rights at home and peace and justice  (Destruction of Zionist pig Israel)  in the Middle East. In order to expand the capacity of the organization to meet the needs of the Arab-American  (immigrant terrorists) community, ADC is announcing a new basic membership fee of $10, which is intended to greatly expand our membership (soldier of allah because we're running low)  base. This is an important step in adding 100,000 new members by ADC's historic 25th Anniversary in 2005. QUESTION: What will ADC gain through a greatly expanded membership (Recruitment) ? ANSWER: Demonstrate to the American  (Great Satin) people, Congress, and Administration (Great Satin himself, George W Bush) , that we represent a significant constituency of active and engaged Americans  (Terrorists) which brings together people from a broad ideological spectrum and transcends religious (really only islam ), class, and geographical divisions.Provide ADC with an even larger network of activists  (active terror cells) to speak out on issues of concern toArab Americans (Thought you just said you represented a 'broad ideological and religious spectrum?) , and to the broader American community.Open ADC's membership to others who share the organization's goals and ideals  (of theocratic Islamic Global Rule) and to continue our tradition of coalition building with other national advocacy groups and individuals (Other peace loving terrorists orders of the world ). Attract a wider membership which better represents the size and achievements of the community of millions of Arab Americans it represents in the United States (because we really need to replace all of our brothers who have been killed or blown themselves up in Iraq and Afganistan) .Develop a sustainable financial donor base for ADC (Because the ever wise masterfull benevolent leader Osama is hiding in a cave and lost his checkbook) . QUESTION: What are the new membership fees (How big is my bomb going to be?) ? ANSWER: There are several new categories. All memberships will be individual with differing benefits:  (depending on how big a bang you want to go out in. And the number and quality of virgins you want in paradise)    Student membership, $5 (includes used L.A.W. tube and one gross of bottle rockets)Hey! What did you expect for five stinking dollars!? You wont receive any virgins with this packet because if you actually do get yourself killed with it...well, virgins don't like stupid terrorists. Duh!   Basic membership, $10 (Includes used wine bottle, old washcloth and one match. You have to provide the gasoline)Again...what did you expect for ten measly dollars? See basic membership description about your virgins.   Sustaining membership, $75 (includes ADC Times, the newsletter of ADC) (also includes specially edited koran with all the mushy peacnik stuff removed. Get straight to the intollerant anti west rhetoric with this sure to be classic gospel of hate. Also with a list of the most preferable methods of martydom)Once again...it's still only seventy five dollars. Please go to the end of the longest virgin line.   Contributing membership, $250 - $499 (includes above plus video)  (also included in this kit is the microsoft airliner flight simulator. We leave the getting in the cockpit part up to you. And a coupon for your own set of once used virgins)   Sponsoring membership, $500 - $999 (includes above plus book) (What book you say? Well it is none other than the catalog of Osama's Warehouse of Martydom Pleasures. The definitive book of all things terrorism. Also includes coupons for up to $100 off your first $10,000 purchase)   President's Club, $1,000 - $4,999 (includes above plus invitations to select events) (some of the events you could be invited to are... The Bagdad premier of 'Taming of the Jew'. Book signings by the author of 'my life, the ever so short career of a palestinian suicide bomber'. And you will receive an autographed copy of Al Zarqawi's new book, 'Proper Field Dressing and Cleaning of Your Infidels')   Chair's Council, $5,000 - $9,999 (includes above plus briefing by President Oakar) (in your personal briefing you will receive a list of terror cells near you looking for new members. And as an added bonus you will receive a 10% discount on a get away vacation to the terrorist training camp of your choice)   Benefactor's Circle, $10,000 + (includes all of the above) (Your generosity is greatly appreciated. And our sincere wishes and prayers that allah will bless you with a brand new batch of virgins.)  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We are Americans plain and simple. Not American-Arabs, African-Americans, Mexican-Americans or any other kind of American. Just good old Americans.  We are against any type of hyphenated American other than American-Americans who want special treatment just because their ethnicity has a hyphen in it.  You are either an American. Or you can go home.  First meeting will be byob at my place this Saturday. Be sure to bring your guns and bibles. Oh..and don't forget your white hoods too!  We'll discuss an agenda once the first keg has been floated. 
     

    
</post>


<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Check out this website. It is political but... it reports both sides of most issues. Good reading for those interested in getting all view points.    urlLink ">Real Clear Politics  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The United States of America is NOT a Democracy… we are a Constitutional Representative Republic who’s leaders are democratically elected. There IS a difference.  An individuals right to free speech stops where his speech becomes demonstrably (is that a word?) harmful to another. An insult is not harmful. No one ever died from getting their feelings hurt. And you do not have a right to not be insulted. Get over it.  An individual right to own a firearm is more than a right. It is the responsibility of every citizen of this once great nation. I’ll stop here on this one since there are volumes of stuff to discuss about this later.  The Federal Government has no business taking my money and redistributing it to people who refuse to get a job. Or sending it to other countries to help people that would just as soon kill us all as look at us.   No politician should be able to serve more than two terms in elected office… PERIOD. There should be no such animal as a career congressman or senator. We have term limits on the top elected office, why none of the others?  Repeal the Seventeenth Amendment.   Lawyers…. You can’t live with em…and because of them you can’t kill them. Why is it that all other businesses have money back guarantees if you are not satisfied with the results of their work but lawyers get their money up front and more as their service goes on but never with regard to whether you got what you paid them for or not?  Lawyers should never be allowed to run or serve in any elected position.  This is America, the language is English… learn it….deal with it… or LEAVE. In case you didn’t understand me… Este es America. El idioma es ingles. Aprendalo. O Adios.   Child support payments should be directly tied to a fathers visitation with his children. It should be a two way street. No pay no see and also… no see NO pay. Be a lot of unhappy malicious vindictive ex-wife mothers out there if that were the case.  Marriage is between one man and one woman. What goes on in the privacy of your own home is no ones business but your own. If you choose to spend your life with a member of the same sex more power to you… I’m happy for you…. No really… But did I mention that marriage is between one MAN and one WOMAN? …  It should be as difficult to place something on someone’s credit record as it is to take something off. And if it’s MY credit report why do I have to pay someone for it?  Convicted violent felons do not have rights… Why is it no one seems concerned with the cruel and unusual punishment inflicted on their victims but every liberal hand wringer is whining about whether or not Charlie Manson has the best cable package for our money?  It should be the responsibility of a convict’s family to see to it that they are clothed and fed while in prison. The government supplies the cell block (climate control optional) the family provides EVERYTHING else. If they choose to let them rot then that’s there problem.  I think the movie Starship Troopers hit on a pretty good idea. You are not a citizen until you have HONORABLY served your country in uniform. No service, no citizenship, NO vote. This probably would not solve all of our problems but it would certainly make people appreciate what we have because they actually had to do something for it.   Bring back the roadie!!! What is so wrong with stopping at the ice house after work and picking up ONE cold beer for the drive home? If you are DWI fine then you go to jail… but no one ever got drunk off of one beer. Well….I did have a Barley Wine once that about knocked me out… but that’s a beer in name only.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ?
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do people actually believe that the likes of John Kerry and Hillary Clinton have anything other than their own best interests in mind?  And why does any sane person think that the UN would ever do anything good for the United States?  Build a wall that would make the Great Wall of China look like a 3 year olds lego project and run this wall all the way around this country. Then kick all the hand wringing one world socialists OUT. Drill for our own oil. Build our own cars.. yes.. big stinky gas hog SUVs.. And tell the rest of the world to go pound sand.   Once we stop giving money to every third world banana republic with a tinpot dictator we will have more money to tend to our own.  That is all...    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One hell of a reading tutor that one is. I bet Dad is going nuts between wanting to give the kid a high five, buy him a beer and cigar or grounding him for life. I guess the cousin turned him in because he was jealous he wasn't hitting that too. And you have to feel for the husband. Got booted to the couch for a 14 year old.    urlLink Teacher has sex with 14 year old student    urlLink More than just a tutor 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink July 4th Fireworks 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sleepless nights By Burt Prelutsky  Posted: June 30, 2004 1:00 a.m. Eastern © 2004 WorldNetDaily.com   It used to be that if I couldn't get to sleep, it was usually because I'd had coffee with dinner. How I miss those halcyon times when it was simply caffeine that had me awake at 3 a.m. Nowadays, it's all the imponderable mysteries that have turned me into the poster boy for insomnia.  One night, not too long ago, I found myself pondering how it was that the Greatest Generation of Americans had come to have such sluggard kids and grandkids. How can the men and women who battled their way through the Great Depression and World War II even stand to sit across a dinner table with these squirts? I realize that it's a cliché that each generation is said to look askance at the next – to question its intelligence, its speech, manners, its taste in movies and music, its clothing and even its intestinal fortitude. But you know what? When you take an objective look at the past 50 years, it's been one long steady decline.  Americans used to be raised to believe in the individual's striving to succeed. At what point did everybody decide they were entitled to entitlements? The latest example of this was hearing the resounding cheers of young people that greeted John Kerry's promise of a free college education. Even if we overlook Kerry's shameless trolling for votes, what makes these teenagers believe they deserve such largesse from the American taxpayer?  It's bad enough that in a country where more youngsters should be encouraged to attend trade schools, most college loans are never paid back. But at least there's a chance of reimbursement. But a free ride just because a kid would rather go to school than get a job? And as for those outstanding loans, if it were up to me, I'd hire the Mafia to start collecting them.  As for Kerry, what can one say about such obvious politicking? At least when the ward heelers in Chicago bought votes, it was strictly cash on the barrelhead, none of this pie in the sky business.  But there's no end to the demand for what I refer to as unentitlements. Take gas prices and the current so-called crisis at the pump. In recent weeks, the price of a gallon of gas has gone up about 40 or 50 cents. Well, for openers, that would at least suggest we didn't invade Iraq, as the Bush-bashers have contended, in order to gobble up all their oil. But, then, that crowd never quite got around to explaining why the president so often sides with Israel, the one country in the Middle East whose only oil supply comes from olives.  To get back to the rising cost of unleaded, one would think, judging by the squeals from the American consumer, that the world was coming to an end. You would get the idea that there is a passage in the Bill of Rights guaranteeing that Americans will pay the same price for gasoline as their grandfathers. I'm not going to suggest that extra quarter or half buck a gallon isn't a hardship for some folks. But not for most. We have a country filled with people who will spend over a hundred dollars to buy brand-name sneakers for their kids, blow ten bucks on a lousy movie and another few dollars for seven cents worth of popcorn, squander a fortune on play stations – and, most telling of all, forty grand on an SUV that gets about four blocks to the gallon!  When I point out that gas wasn't free before this, and that people managed to survive, I've had friends say that the problem isn't just at the pump, but the additional costs added on to everything we buy because of the added costs of shipping them. To them, I point out that, inevitably, the price of gas will go down, but the added-on costs of all those other items won't – but nobody will raise a stink about it, just as nobody will say anything nice about the falling price of petrol.  Speaking of SUVs, how is it that everyone who interviews Arianna Huffington, archenemy of those over-priced, over-sized vehicles, never nails the lady for her blatant hypocrisy? Let's face it: The only reason anybody has even heard of her is because she once married a wealthy bisexual and then derived untold millions from dumping the shmoe. With all that money, she has been able to set up shop as the reigning doyen for L.A.'s limousine liberals. None of which, I hasten to point out, makes her a hypocrite. No, what makes her an Olympic-caliber phony is the fact that this single lady lives alone in a Brentwood mansion with her two tots, and I am willing to make a good-sized wager that it requires a lot more energy to heat and cool the Huffington homestead than a squad of soccer moms consume driving to and from the playground.  There are those who suggest I count sheep as a cure for my sleeplessness, but it becomes increasingly difficult to focus on four-legged sheep when there's such an abundance of the two-legged variety making me crazy. For instance, it strikes me that there is no lie, no matter how obviously false, that won't be taken up by those on the left and repeated ad nauseam. Both Joseph Stalin and George Orwell pointed out the effectiveness of the oft-repeated lie, but even they would be astonished at how gullible Americans have become.  As I earlier pointed out, those opposed to the toppling of Saddam Hussein claimed that America was merely after Iraq's oil – and insisted that we would do well to take our marching orders from the French and the Russians. All these many months later, in spite of the fact that Iraq is deriving all the income from its oil sales – and it's been established that Russia and France, for all their moral posturing, were simply out to protect their billion-dollar oil deals with Saddam – the left continues to parrot those same silly slogans.  Another big lie floating around is that in the wake of 9-11 the entire world loved America, but George Bush squandered all that good will. What malarkey! For one thing, most nations don't love America and never did. We are rich and powerful. Rich, powerful individuals, let alone nations, are not beloved. They are feared and respected and, more often than not, envied.  Sure, we received a certain amount of sympathy after 9-11, but it was temporary in nature and, in many cases, not even terribly sincere, and that would have been the case no matter who was in the Oval Office. Heck, for a while, New York City, of all places, was looked upon fondly, and even Red Sox fans refrained from booing the Yankees when they came to play in Fenway. It's the same way with certain widows. For a period after their husbands are buried, people can't do enough for them. Inevitably, though, things return to normal and people once again allow themselves the luxury of treating the women like the rude, annoying pests they've always been.  If America is as awful as her critics claim, why is the U.S. the country with the biggest immigration headache? I mean, maybe you know a lot of people packing their bags and moving to France and Germany, but I don't.  Some cynics would claim that foreigners only want to move here for financial reasons, but I don't buy that. Still, even I'm not such a Pollyanna that I believe that our constitutional guarantees of freedom, liberty and religious tolerance are the total answer, either.  Rather, I believe that so long as somebody who looks, speaks and thinks like James Carville can achieve such enormous success in this land, America will remain a beacon for every geek in the world. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cannot believe I actually spent eight bucks to see this.... um... fantasy... delusion...?? Not sure how to describe it. Can any sane adult capable of rational thought actually believe anything moore has to say in this? Some parts are obviously taken out of context and others are just plain lies. Much like  urlLink Bowling For Columbine ,  urlLink FarenLIES 911  is just more of michael moore voicing his personal hatred of America. The whole thing comes off as a bad script of SNL or a not very well thought out Southpark episode. I've seen better satire on the BBC and that's not saying much.   urlLink FarenHYPOCRITE 911    urlLink Big Fat Stupid LIBERAL White Man    urlLink Moore Lies dot Com    urlLink Moore Watch    urlLink More Moore  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gives ya warm fuzzy feelings, don't it?   urlLink Rashid Goes To Paradise   Hope his virgins aren't recycled due to the heavy traffic into paradise lately.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The lib that sits next to me in the office is talking on the phone saying how wonderful the michael moore film is. Huh? Dude... it's just a bunch of liberal bullshit... About like bolling for columbine wasn't a completely whiney bunch of anti gun mush... You people don't really believe that stuff do you? Come on... That's as bad as the republicans jumpin on the 'Clinton Chronicles' bandwagon way back when. Not to say that slick willy wasn't a completely ethically bankrupt criminal with the morals of a priapic goat. But I digress.....   America?...sheesh.. One big steamy heaping pile of apathy. Thats what this country has become. Is it any wonder that terrorists want to kill us all? Maybe they'd be doing us a favor.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wonder how long before the dems start dancing in this guys blood? My guess is they'll start asap so they can get new quotes in before the 5 o'clock news today.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it appears that those terrorist animals in Saudi have killed another American. We know who the guy is that they wanted released in exchange for the release of the hostage. So I say we go chop that guys head off... better yet. I have a sawzall I'll loan them.. It has a nice dull bent blade they can use too. Maybe dip it in pigs blood before the 'procedure'.   And while we're at it, all new munitions that are manufactured and sent to Iraq should be sprayed with bacon grease before being packaged. Send the pictures of this happening to al-jizmeera. Let em put that in their terrorism crack pipe/camel shit spoons and smoke it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well...not yet. But I will be in a few months. Things are looking up.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So yesterday evening on the way home the highway was all but shutdown. As usual only one side should have been effected by the 'accident' but all the rubberneckers have to muck up the comute for the rest of civilization. The cause of the problem... Some guy and his wife/girlfriend of several years decided to stop on the overpass and duke it out. Then he proceeds to throw her over the side and 85 feet below into the traffic. Um... Ok.. From the witness reports she was giving as good as she was getting..right up to the point where he heaved her over the wall... Beats having to pay alimony and several thousand bucks to her attorney. But then as he apparently realizes that there were witnesses and givin the warped feminist court system we have today he knows he's royally screwed so he jumps over himself. Poor guy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Almost forgot I had this thing.. guess I should start posting more often. Wonder if anyone actually reads it?  Was sitting around bored the other evening while my wife was at work. Started diggin through all the old computer games and came across the original Diablo. So I played it for a while... Yeah, it's old and antiquated... and still a bit addictive. But it sure beat getting out in the heat and mowing the lawn. Maybe tonight while she's working I'll venture to battlenet (the online gaming place that you play against/with other players) and see how I do. Been a while.  Need to think up a catchy name for my character... first I'd better decide which one I'm going to be...    
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is this really suprising to anyone?&nbsp;Especially to those that have honorably served this country?&nbsp;Every military vet&nbsp;has come&nbsp;across officers and nco's that nobody liked being around. Total morons that you couldn't begin to figure out how they got to where they were in the command structure. Usually they were there because they played the politics game well.   Read the book 'Once An Eagle'. Then decide whether John Kerry reminds you of Sam Damon. The&nbsp;selfless&nbsp;soldier turned&nbsp;field commander whos first thoughts&nbsp;were always of his troups. Or Courtney Massengale. The shameless political hack that never makes a command decision without analyzing its possible effects on his career with no&nbsp;regard for the men under his command.   I'm sure there are some mindless handwringing socialists&nbsp;that will watch the videos of Kerry's Vietnam 'heroics' and think him the valiant hero.&nbsp;Not a one of them will stop and think 'how did they get&nbsp;this on film?'. Then you have to think&nbsp;not&nbsp;even Courtney Massengale would have&nbsp;been so vain as to&nbsp;take a movie camera into the field and stage 'live' action shots.&nbsp;&nbsp;Maybe we should change the name from the Democratic party to the Narcissistic Party. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      By  urlLink Barbara Kay FrontPageMagazine.com July 29, 2004   In the last days before the Democratic National Convention, John Kerry and John Edwards&nbsp;adopted a campaign&nbsp;slogan: “Let America Be America Again.” They were clearly pleased by its provenance, as the first line of a poem written by black poet Langston Hughes (1902-67).&nbsp;At the height of his fame,&nbsp;Hughes was known as the “Shakespeare in Harlem.” He also had&nbsp;long history as a Communist activist and virulent atheist. And this poem clearly echoes his admiration of Stalinism.  Hughes' personal history shaped him for a life of social protest. Born&nbsp;in deeply racist&nbsp;Joplin, Missouri, in 1902, he produced&nbsp;a distinctly black and proletarian protest poetry. At first, Hughes believed that assimilation would solve the Negro's problems and was an engaged participant in the Harlem Renaissance, which held out great promise for integration through black self-expression, but this&nbsp;faltered in the wake of the Great Depression.With it, Hughes' optimistic hopes for racial progress faltered, too.&nbsp;And his hope for a socialist utopia came to the fore.  Although Hughes didn't actually join the Communist Party during this period,&nbsp;he nurtured a genuine&nbsp;love affair with the Soviet cause. Having previously published his views through Crisis, the literary organ of the NAACP, Hughes turned to New Masses, the propaganda arm of the Communist Party USA. He joined the (Marxist) John Reed Club, and took on the job as director of the pro-Communist Suitcase Theatre, where Whittaker Chambers was also involved.&nbsp;Hughes stayed in the Soviet Union for nearly a year; his 1956 memoir, I Wonder as I Wander, chronicles a watershed voyage he made to the Soviet Union in 1932. The volume makes clear that, like so many superficially educated Americans,&nbsp;Hughes allowed himself to be exploited by the Soviets, becoming another of Lenin’s literary “useful idiots.”   He was inducted into the International Union of Revolutionary Writers and wrote passionate odes to Communism. As history rolled forward, Hughes seems to have vacillated between patriotism when WWII broke out and a revived attachment to Communism when Stalin emerged as an ally. During the war, Hughes served on the War Writers' Committee, writing anti-fascist poems, songs and stories, but then Hughes pivoted back to admiration socialism, calling Moscow "the world's new center."   Hughes was summoned to testify at the McCarthy hearings in 1953 but was able to convince the committee of his patriotic reinvention.&nbsp;Eric J.&nbsp;Sundquist&nbsp;recorded in Commentary,&nbsp;“Although he was a cooperative witness, his tightrope act left the distinct impression of a man who wished neither to defend nor to renounce his former beliefs but simply to set them aside, like an abandoned literary style.”&nbsp;This testimony did not obscure the fact that for many years, Langston Hughes was a vocal&nbsp;supporter&nbsp;of the Communist Party, and proud of it.   The poem John&nbsp;Kerry selected as his campaign slogan&nbsp;clearly reflects Hughes' years as an anti-American Marxist. His antipathy to the United States is echoed in&nbsp;the poem's refrain, “It never was America to me.” “Let America Be America Again”&nbsp;is hardly a patriotic salute to this great nation but rather a stark&nbsp;portrait of&nbsp;an Evil Empire:   "I am the poor white, fooled and pushed apart,I am the Negro bearing slavery's scars.I am the red man driven from the land,I am the immigrant clutching the hope I seek--And finding only the same old stupid planOf dog eat dog, of mighty crush the weak...."   In another verse,&nbsp;Hughes mocks America's designation as "The Land of the Free":   "Who said 'the free'?...  The millions on relief today?  The millions shot down when we strike?  The millions who have nothing for our pay?  For all the dreams we've dreamed  And all the songs we've sung  And all the hopes we've held  And all the flags we've hung,  The millions who have nothing for our pay -  Except the dream that's almost dead today."&nbsp;   As the verses unfold, it becomes clear that Hughes is evangelizing for his radical faith:   "From those who live like leeches on the people's lives,We must take back our land again,America!...   "We, the people, must redeem  The land, the mines, the plants, the rivers,  The mountains and the endless plain -  All, all the stretch of these great green states -  And make America again!"   When Hughes says "We, the people,” he does not use the phrase in the same sense that the&nbsp;Founding Fathers did in&nbsp;the Constitution, but rather the way Marx, Lenin and Trotsky employed it: the revolutionary Vanguard of the coming socialist State.&nbsp;   In&nbsp;his retrospective of Hughes' work,&nbsp;Sundquist cited “Let America be America again” as poetically&nbsp;“embarrassing.” However, it was another&nbsp;pro-Marxist poem -- "Goodbye Christ" -- that would&nbsp;inspire the FBI to launch a probe into&nbsp;Langston Hughes' activities.&nbsp;In the poem, Hughes&nbsp;presents the Church ceding&nbsp;power to&nbsp;its Leninist vanquishers.&nbsp;"Goodbye, Christ"&nbsp;reads, in part:   "Listen, Christ,  You did alright in your day, I reckon -  But that day's gone now.  They ghosted you up a swell story, too,  Called it Bible -  But it's dead now.   "Gooodbye,  Christ Jesus, Lord God Jehovah,  Beat it on away from here now.  Make way for a new guy with no religion at all -  A real guy named  Marx, Communist Lenin, Peasant Stalin, Worker ME."   Clearly, the fact that John Kerry and John Edwards have allowed the tenor of their presidential campaign to be set by a propaganda poem written by a well-known Stalinist is troubling. However, this is&nbsp;not the first time the campaign has borrowed from avowed Marxists. John Edwards' “Two Americas” stump shtick echoes&nbsp;earlier American socialist propaganda.&nbsp;In the words of a&nbsp;typical Edwards stump speech:   “Today under George W. Bush, there are two Americas, not one. One America does the work, while another America reaps the reward. One America pays the taxes, while another America gets the tax breaks.”   We can imagine that Edwards might very well find much to admire in Hughes words, “the millions on relief,” and “the millions who have nothing for our pay.”   Yet Edwards’ words also find an eerie echo in the remarks of James P. Cannon, a founding member of the Trotskyist movement in the United States. During a speech at the 1948 convention of the Socialist Workers’ Party, Cannon said:&nbsp;   “There are two Americas – and millions of the people already distinguish between them. One is the America of the imperialists – of the little clique of capitalists, landlords and militarists, who are threatening and terrifying the world. This is the America the people of the world hate and fear. There is the other America – the America of the workers and farmers and the ‘little people.’”   Sure, the enormously wealthy&nbsp;Kerry and Edwards would have been hated by Hughes and Cannon, derided as the&nbsp;“little clique of capitalists...the people of the world hate and fear.” But the question remains: Why would the Democratic candidates continue to identify themselves with a writer like Hughes, who used his work for such vitriolically anti-American purposes? And why use the words of a revolutionary leftist like Cannon? They can’t plead ignorance, because several publications have brought the repugnant connections to their attention. They have not apologized, nor have they quietly withdrawn the quotations. Apparently, Kerry and Edwards are not ashamed to be identified with democracy’s most virulent enemies.   Far from being ashamed, in fact,&nbsp;Kerry&nbsp;has determined to appropriate&nbsp;the words of a dead leftist poet for his own purposes. In order to cement the association, he has gone so far as write&nbsp;the preface to a new release of Hughes' poetry (or have it ghostwritten for him). The volume, to be published in early August, contains&nbsp;"Let America be America Again." In the forward, Kerry speaks of the Great Depression which motivated many writers to look for hope in Communism and points to the "duality of meanings" in Hughes' "America" poem: America as a land that has disenfranchised the Negro but is still a beacon of hope for all people, regardless of color. But there was no duality of meaning in the&nbsp;poem. On the contrary, the poem was specifically written to say that America is a land whose only hope was to adopt Soviet style communism.   People are known for the company they keep. George W. Bush often quotes the Word of God. John Kerry seems remarkably comfortable in the company of Langston Hughes, Joe Cannon and, through them, with Stalin. Are these the kind of presidential companions we want to see in the Oval Office?   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bla bla bla.....blubber blubber.... (shaking head back and forth repeatedly)  Three nights of dems on tv and I feel dumber. These people haven't said one thing that they're going to do if they get back in power. They only seem interested in telling us how evil Dubya is and how he's messed up everything in this country.&nbsp; Slavery is his fault? The great depression is his fault? Oh and Haliburtons to blame for Al Sharpton's hair.   Is it a bad thing that I watched jessie jackson's entire speech through an old rifle scope? Not the leupold vx 50mm that I have now. But an old redfield 40mm. He just looked better with the crosshairs on his forehead. I put it on his chest a couple times but it just wasn't the same.   Oh joy! John Mellencamp is on. What a surprise.&nbsp; Smalltown is as smalltown does. Wonder why the dixie sluts haven't made an appearance?   &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While there is nothing out of the ordinary about this on its face value... When you add the rest of the headdline  'While Representing Bush at U.N.' . Ya just have to go HMMMM.  Several bits of information in this article make the point of why kerry and his kind should never be allowed in a position of authority.   In the second paragraph we see  'In a speech delivered in Boston yesterday, Peggy Kerry told a campaign crowd of feminists...'  More evidence that we should never have given them the vote. Except maybe where the betty crocker isle should be at the local grocery store. A feminist is what you get when you combine a low iq, complete lack of common sense, hatred of anything male and an overdose of estrogen.   Next we see this  'In her campaign speech Kerry said her brother John would reinstitute U.S. funding for the U.N. Population Fund, which President Bush has defunded over UNFPA support for coercive abortions in China. Kerry also said her brother would ensure U.S. ratification of the U.N.   urlLink  Convention on the Elimination Against All Forms of Discrimination Against Women   , something opposed by President Bush. She also pledged that her brother would appoint only pro-abortion judges to the U.S. Supreme Court.'  UN this, UN that...Um....Ok... Why elect a leader to our country that admittedly would rely on a corrupt organization run by some of the most bankrupt and failed countries on the planet? Why not just cancel all elections from here on out, call our good budy kofi and say 'tell us your bidding my master?'.  Everybody says 'Can she do that?'&nbsp;    'Her comments caused not a few jaws to drop at the State Department. One high-ranking official told the Friday Fax, "Even if it's legal, how can she claim to effectively represent Bush's policies at the U.N., if she is bashing those same policies in a speech in Boston."     It appears that Kerry violated no federal law in making campaign appearances for her brother. At one time, career civil servants like Kerry were forbidden to make campaign appearances, though that has now changed. What is not yet clear is whether Kerry violated any internal State Department guidelines.'   She may not have violated any laws, but that doesn't mean that what she did is right. And... if she gets what she deserves and is escorted out of the building, read (FIRED) then it's a campaign related political move by the Bush administration. So now everyone at the UN knows she doesn't believe in what she is supporting. Not saying she hasn't already made that known.&nbsp;That in itself is grounds for her dismissal. Me? I'd fire her just because she sports the same hawkish looks of her brother.....shiver.... SKANK.  The Secret Weapon...   'Monday's speech was not the first time that Kerry has actively campaigned for her brother. She introduced the singer Carole King at a John Kerry fund-raising concert and has spoken at a number of his campaign events. In fact, she was introduced yesterday as a "secret weapon" to solidify the radical feminist base for her brother.     According to the Washington Times: "In introducing Ms. Kerry, Feminist Majority President Eleanor Smeal said she had heard of misgivings about the Kerry-Edwards ticket. Women are wondering whether they are 'really with us,' she said. There is no question that Mr. Kerry and Mr. Edwards 'have a huge track record with us,' Ms. Smeal said. 'And he has a secret weapon,' she said, referring to Peggy Kerry and her many years of work with feminist causes."'    &nbsp; With a name like Eleanor Smeal it's no wonder the beyatch is&nbsp;carpet munchin man hating feminist.    'Kerry spoke yesterday at an event called "She Party," which was held at the Harvard Club and was intended as a pun upon the Boston Tea Party. According to a NOW invitation, the party was part of its "grassroots revolution against the Tyranny of King George."'    &nbsp; 'She Party'??? So whats that? A bunch of man hating lesbians standing on the ss minnow (fishy smell pun intended) tossing used tampons into the river? 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Subject: Big Bad John   Every mornin' on the Hill you could see him arrive Standing six-foot-four, weighing one-twenty-five Kinda' scrawny at the shoulders and lacking a spine And when he spoke at all, it was mainly to whine  (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John   Nobody seems to know what's in John's soul His 'beliefs' are based on the latest poll Though he'll say what it takes to get your votes It's the leftist agenda that he really promotes - Big John.   Someone said he came from Boston town Where he joined the Navy and gained renown 'Earning' three purple hearts and one bronze star The home folks said, "This boy will go far" (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John (Big John)   Then came a day back in '71 When he renounced all the medals that he had won Then turned against his country and his Navy friends And sold them out for his own selfish ends? (Big John)   He appeared before Congress and on left-wing talk shows Giving aid and comfort to America's foes It was clear to see whose side he was on Some say he helped cause the fall of Saigon -  Big John (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John (Big John)   He claims to be for the working poor Yet he owns 5 mansions from shore to shore He never had to work a day in his life 'cause he learned it helps to have a wealthy wife! -  Big John   Now he wants to be our next President and Commander-in-chief of those he resents: The American soldiers who fight and die To give him the freedom to tell us his lies  (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John (Big John)   Thousands have sacrificed their young lives To help ensure that our nation survives A vote for Kerry is a slap in the face To all the brave soldiers that he's disgraced   FADE   (Big John, Big John) Big Bad John (Big John)  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The lib in my office is admonishing one of his sons that he should see moore's movie and decide for himself whether it's true. From the sounds of it the kid has decided and is learning the facts but that doesn't make daddy too happy. 'Republican propaganda' is what he calls all the 'lies' about the movie.   Never forget the time that his son called to tell him that he was going to vote Republican in the next election. When asked why he said because his pastor at his church had explained some things to him and it made sense to him. So dad says 'you need to find a liberal church that isn't just a mouth piece for the government'..  Oh boy. Sounds like 'deciding for yourself' really means do what daddy says. Momma says Republicans are the devil. And Bobby Bouche (sp?) never argues with momma.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Very refreshing. Another sensible person that won't just forgive and forget what happened on 9/11.   urlLink StillAngry.Org   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To hear Peter Jennings and Cristian Amanpour tell it you'd think saddam hussien has been subjected to horrible treatment because he has to wear a regular suit to his trial. The once proud leader of Iraq now sits haggard and worn looking in the courtroom? Um...HELLO!! The guy murdered millions of people. He is a psychopathic deviant. I wonder...Did any of his victims get a lawyer before they were dropped into vats of acid or Pitched feet first into paper mulchers and wood chippers? I need a drink.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well well.... looks like there actually are some Iraqi people that are thankfull for the freedom they have received. To bad we don't see anything about this on CNN or in the New York Slimes.   urlLink The Real Story?  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Drum roll please. The word of the day for Monday, 9 August 2004 is......   urlLink Barking Moonbat                         
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Found a blog by a guy currently serving in Iraq. He gives daily posts and updates on the goings on over there. Everything from chow hall discussions to driving through an ambush in the streets of Mosul. Whether or not you agree with the war you cant not support our guys over there. Here's an excerpt from one of his posts.  " Every time we drive around Mosul I notice small improvement or step forwards for these people. Little things. Like today I noticed that a lot of the Iraqi police were now wearing black kevlar helmets. That's new. I remember when we first got to Iraq almost a year ago, a lot of the Iraqi police didn't even have uniforms, just a baseball hat and an AK47. Now they wear slacks, work shirts, bulletproof vests with the words POLICE written in yellow Arabic, they carry brand new AK47's and Glock 9mm pistols and they drive around in new white police cars and trucks. I'm noticing Internet caf‚'s one by one popping up on every street. New stores opening up. Billboards. Satellite dishes on rooftops, that were non-existent awhile ago. Things are slowly improving for these people out here ."  The link is in the title of this post. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wonder if the leftist elite media will even mention this?  The first ever pro America film festival. Right here in Dallas. Never been big on film festivals but this is one I'll have to attend.  Wonder if the big fat lazy white pig michael moore will be there?              
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Charlie Daniels Angers Arab Community..  Awe..That's terrible. Bunch of ragheads angry because they are what they are? Oh well... No use crying over spilt camel shit.  The song starts with,  "This ain't no rag, it's a flag and we don't wear it on our heads. It's a symbol of the land where the good guys live. Are you listening to what I said?"   So what's the problem?   "Someone who is trying to get popular through bigotry, bias and hatred should not be welcome, especially in a city like Dearborn with its rich diversity," Imad Hamad, regional director of the American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee, told the Detroit Free Press.     Think I should start the American-American Anti-Anti American Committee. Thats the ticket. Better fire up a new blog.  I'm outta here.   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heard this guy on the Mark Davis show that I listen to daily. He is part of a group that preys on child internet predators. Their moto? "As Long As Our Children Aren't Safe From Predators... Predators aren't safe from US.".  Outstanding! So all the pervs cruising for kids will have to think twice before acting. Entrapment? Nope. All they do is pose as kids and wait to be approached, they initiate no contact with anyone. Kids contacting kids? No Problem. An adult has no business in a chat room full of kids in anything other than a administrator/content monitor.  I know I don't want another adult chatting up my daughter when she's in a room talking with her school friends.  These guys rock. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Frenchurian Candidate's Band of Brothers isn't exactly a band... More like a solo brother. I wouldn't consider one out of nineteen an overwhelming support base.   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We can only hope this is realized. Just think...no more annual headaches about tax returns. No more socialist security will be extorted from your check every month. We would actually get to keep what we work for. Now thats a concept I could sign on to.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gotta love it! Heres the new moniker for John F'n Kerry.  Rush Limbaugh is a god! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>