<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know we've been having trouble with the web form I made - Sorry! If you all could just print it out an snail mail it back to me that would be great!  I really want this Family Reunion to happen!  I appreciate everyone's help in getting this accomplished.  We will have a great time and it will be sooo great to see everyone!  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Want to stay at home and make money? With our wonderful team and support system you can! NO STOCKING! NO SELLING! NO DELIVERING! NO PARTIES! NO LARGE INVESTMENT! Be your own boss, make your own hours and best of all you can do it all from the comfort of your own home! Visit my site and GET STARTED NOW!   I am a proud mom of 4 four great kids. I was looking for a way to spend more time with them and still contribute to my family’s income. I’m happy to say that I’ve found a company I can believe in. I get to enjoy working from home, with my kids by my side! Best of all, I am making my family healthier and helping others to do the same. What a great feeling! We work from home without having to sell any products, go door-to-door, purchase inventory or host parties(been there-done that!). FREE TRAINING, FREE WEBSITE and 100% RISK~FREE! Our Team partners with a 18yr old PROSPEROUS company which allows us to work in the comfort of our own home. Visit my website ASAP for more info that can make a difference in your household for a LIFETIME!!! http://sabrinahill.stayinhomeandlovinit.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  alt="Search Engine Submission and Internet Marketing" width="88" height="31" border="0">      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ben busy painting.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Zoe the Princess!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Kira, Zoe and Quinten in Kira's room.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Kira when she was confirmed in our church.  She worked very hard to get to this day!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is my (almost) all grown up Kira.  Isn't she beautiful!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    What a cool dude! (Quinten at Easter 2004)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Then the eggs hatched!  We had 5 little baby birdies!  They were sooo cute!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Then she laid eggs.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A bird built a nest in our laundry room.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Amy and Desiree when they visited a couple of months ago.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Here is my Cockatiel.  His name is Pretty Boy.  Everyone hates him because he is so loud!  I love him anyway!  If I hated things just cause they are loud I would hate my whole family! LOL!  He can sing a repertoire of TV theme songs!  I think he watches too much TV Land!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    We also put in French Doors!  They are soooo much better than the yucky sliding glass doors we had before!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    We just tiled and painted our house - well actually we haven't quite finished yet!  It is a work in progress.  It looks so great already though!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Zoe just loves her baby brother!  Aren't they soooo cute!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I have proof that Victor will hold a baby!  )He says he won't hold babies cause he is afraid he'll break them!)  Look - No broken babies here!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is Quinten's baptism.  He was just a few weeks old.  Pastor Herman had just been installed the weekend before so this was his first bapism in our church.  We attend Good Shepherd Lutheran Church in Gulf Breeze, FL.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    We couldn't pry the microphones from Bobby and Victor's hands!  I had to leave my Karaoke machine there that night.  They kept the neighbors up all night with thier "lovely" voices!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    We had a blast singing Karaoke over at Dale & Ann's.  I think this was Thanksgiving 2003.Victor, Bobby and Sean were the stars of the show!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Grandma Hill holding Quinten at Christmas.  He was so little!  Just 3 weeks old.  Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Kira's VERY OWN guitar!  On our way to that family Heavy Metal Band!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Kira and her mom (me).  This is before she got her braces off.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is us.  In the hospital right after I had Quinten!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A vase I painted for a teacher present.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Quinten in our pool.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Our friends Randy and Karl at Karl's house on Memorial Day.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Kira and her friend Anna on Memorial Day.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Zoe's too!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Like Ian's new haircut?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>