<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          It seems my blog isn't doing so well so far... Maybe it's because people don't know about it. I have put a link in my xanga, but I'm sure people don't read it anymore because I said I wasn't going to use it anymore. Hmm.... hell of a way to advertise, right?      I haven't been typing about anything in a while... I know there's alot to type about, but nothing really standing out saying, "Type me!" It is a good feeling to start again. I have to say, this is kinda fun, although difficult. I'm just not a very well worded person. I would have a hard time explaining things. Then again, that's what makes me a difficult person to understand. I find myself at many times in this kind of situation:              Friend: I don't get it.....             Myself: never mind.....      I guess my head is just wired differently... There are some things that other people can understand, but I don't get it. Heh, I guess all geniuses are like that... right?...... right?....... hello?......         It's kinda funny, alot of people type in xanga and other journals the same way one would talk. I could tell that alot of entries were like this. I know that when I'm adding to my site, it's at a slow pace. When reading it, it would me my own voice in my head going over every word just right. Pauses at the right place, emphasis on the right words, just slow enough reading to make it seem like it's full, and my voice making it not boring and monotonous. It would be like I was telling someone this.      I'm sure when others read it, it isn't the same. I'm not a true writter, so I suppose there's nothing that I can really do about it.        I was just talking to my sister. She showed me something really cool that she found. On amazon.com, you can buy discount cds as low as $2 (still in the original plastic). If you buy anything over $25, shipping is free. So my sister is having me make a list of cds that I want. So far I've picked out Korn - Take a look in the mirror, and Sum 41 - Does this look infected.       Anybody know any other good cds? In the genre of rock of course.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
            How should I have the music on this site?         Not at all        windows media player showing at the bottom        invisible with loop        invisible without loop        with a song request        with a playlist of more than one song          
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This would be my first post ever in this site.  I used xanga before this, but it didn't seem to work out.      So far my experience with this site hasn't been a good one. I've been messing around with the template all day. No luck really.... I thought if I edited a pre-made template, I would have a better chance of making a good website. I took a screenshot and messed around with it in photoshop. It looks pretty good there, but I can't seem to get my site to look like it. I think I need to learn more html coding.      urlLink My Blog Sample    note: I took a sample picture from blogger. If you notice, I inverted it first. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>