<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hah, it's funny: i'm fuckin  swamped  in homework, you couldn't possibly know, yet here i am. ahhhh i'm gonna kill myself for that one. I don't know i guess with all  this  going on i just felt like venting. I'm so confused. I swear to god it's been so long since i seriously liked a guy, let alone ahd him like me back. this is almost foreign to me guys. i feel like a damn loser. ack, and now, to be put in the situation.. how the fuck do i act?! i just don't know man. i feel hella left out of my own life at this moment. i need a cigarette like you wouldn't believe and that menthol shit Ali gave me ain't gonna do. yuck. I don't know how you cats do it, it's like smoking gum: b-o-r-i-n-g! where's my flavvvooorrrrrr? where's that gross, tar-y smell on my fingertips?.. reminds me of my daddy, who, speaking of, is here today! wow, he actually stayed since saturday. this is crazy. but he's leaving tomorrow again. how strange to be unaccustomed to your own father, but i'm beginning to get the hang of it. ahhh,i'm really annoyed. my ex just im-ed me to ask me what car i drove cause he thought he saw me down at southcenter. no dear, it wasn't me. i hate it when people only wanna ask you a question and then they're like ok bye. fuck you. damn. i just uploaded some heinous pics of myself from my phone. i'm cracking up about god knows what. how horrific. speaking of horrific, my braces are coming off nexxxt monday. not labor day. the one after that. i'm so fuckin excited. 4 fuckin years man, i deserve to see some teeth. fuck, let em go back to their crooked, over-bitten ways. i couldn't care less. hmm.. looking forward to this weekend. the way i'm getting all pumped about jamal's party makes it seem like i've never been to one before. dios mio, if i could only stray further from the truth. jamal called me about it today and got me even more psyched. hahah. i am alsooo looking forward to folklife. hopefully a lot of people will be there despite promising storm-clouds looming overhead. and maybe, just  maybe  he'll be there. man what a weird way to start off a..whatever. i mean, we hardly talk, and then this? ahh.. not how i wanted things to go at all. i feel like i'm in middle school "he likes you", "she likes you back" type shit. except it's a lot more awkward when you can fully understand the circumstances surrounding such a situation. what the fuck is a girl to do. okay i'm acting childish. i'll get on with my math now, DAMMIT! there's nothing stopping me now that i'm done.....
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh.. midnight on saturday and i'm just sitting at home watching tv with my parents. This week has been so fucking stressful. I've been up all night every night busting my ass for unappreciative teachers. I've been living off cigarettes and coffee but here I am and i'm still alive. Well, hardly, but whatever. Let's see, spent the day sleeping, got a 2:00 wake up call from Saige, hopped in the shower, met up with my mom at 6:00, went to the mall, then we met up with my dad, who's in town this weekend, for dinner. Right now i'm doing absolutely nothing.. wondering how long these 4 cigarettes will last me and how long this newfound sobriety will last.....1 week and counting.....................
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, well well. So we meet again, eh online blogs? This is silly, really, that, despite communication with friends, family, diaries, and countless strangers, I feel compelled still to hop the bandwagon of this millenial phenomenon of "blogging." Who the fuck came up with that name anyways? Bless their souls... Let's see though what happened today. Nothing really. It was pretty damn boring, but I was in a good mood so let the rivers flow. Ha, late again to first period. You'd think that speeding down the freeway at 85 mph would get you there on time, but like my dad always says "you can't catch the hands of the clock with the hands on the steering wheel," or something to that effect. God, I'm chronically LATE. Or slow... I don't know but it really fucks with me man. Anyways, my first period teacher is an uptight little fucker and he is constantly on my ass for tardies. Whatfuckinever I could care less. Let's seeeeeee.. aced my bio exam (hopefully), gotta up that C man! Spent pretty much the whole day racing to finish this powerpoint presentation on drugs. Shit. You'd think with my exposure I'd be able to finish the fucker good, but nooooo. Scrambling to finish it down to the last seconds. Stress, stress, stress. Well, looks like tonights gonna be a coffee night. Hey, can't complain though - only a couple weeks left before these caffeine powered up-all nighters are few and far between. Instead they'll be replaced by drunk induced slumbers at random peoples houses. I am ecstatic. Ha, well speaking of coffee I am in dire need. Gotta get on that homework. Stay salty.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>