<Blog>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-02 12:47 p.m.  Supposed to be in school now… Haha… But not feeling well, so at home… Well, to be honest, recovered from the fever this morning but din feel like going to school… Juz felt that going to school todae would be a waste of time… Besides, got Bio test tmr… Can stay home n study mar… Haha… A good idea right?  Aniwae, Nick is bz today… wun be meeting him…Hmm… I dun realli care lar… Juz that I quite sianed now at home… Actually, my sister came home yday… Den is like I cant stay home n rest if not she will wonder why n tell my mom… And although my mom knows that I m not feeling well, she will still want me to go to school… So, I had to go to Mac’s in the morning todae n sorta like shelter for a while before my sister goes out… Came back at abt 11.30… N she was asking why I came home so early… So I juz said something like school ended early etc. n later have to go back to school again for SSS… Hehe… Bad gal… Good liar…  Well, finished typing the excuse letter juz now… Had it printed out n forged my mom’s signature… Doubt my Mrs. Tan would know… Hmm… I love myself!!! Oh well, glad I din go to school todae… Realised that I realli din know quite a lot abt Sexual Reproduction… N tmr is the test… Darn… I m so dead…  Aniwae, I know it is weird but I juz feel like trying out writing… I have been penning songs n poems n stuff… But nv wrote… I believe that writing will improve my English… And I seriously need improving aniwae… I know pple will probably think I m so sick etc. or wad, but I hope that through my story, pple will get to know the feminine side of every girl n different points of views that can be displayed through a person’s character…  Another thing is Steph has suggested that I should post the story on websites like fanfiction etc. But, I dunno… Its like this is my story… N I dun realli intend to put my story up for everybody to see… Perhaps if it is a success among u all, I might consider the suggestion… But right now, I juz wanna write n see your comments on the story…So, after reading it, Pple… Please tag my board… Even if u dun like the story,  Please please give your comments… I m totally ok with constructive criticisms… Erm, please refer to the next entry for the first paragraph of the story...  Quote: When patterns are broken, new worlds emerge.  P.S  I totally love this quote…Hope u will like it too…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-01 9:52 p.m.  Blogging now even though I should be studying sexual reproduction… Hmm… I know that it is an interesting chapter n that I should feel happy studying it… But, cant help it… there is like no kick in learning it when there is no practical… Hehe… Not that I have no knowledge of my own though… Ha-ha…=P  Hmm… I realli think locking my blog for good is a Ultra good idea… except, got pple start to complain already lar… Sorry… But if I dun lock, then it is like pole will start using the stuff that I write to make fun of me etc. N I just cant stand that… It doesn’t feel right…   Oh well… Cant think straight… Having a terrible migraine due to fever… at like 38 degrees… totally six… I feel like hot n bothered all over… I hate having fevers… Remember that when I was young n having a fever, mom n dad will force me to drink Barley water… One of the reasons y I hate Barley now… Yuck!!! Won be going to school tm… My mom still wants me to go to school lar… She say just eat medicine n den go… I dun care… I m not feeling well, n that’s that! I will personally write the excuse letter n forge my mom’s signature myself… Bleahz…   Wow… neck cramp… Man, my immune system has just gone down the drain… Must remember to not kiss Nicholas that often… I totally dun wanna pass the virus to him… Glad that my ulcer has been better… Ha-ha… Pole say drink a lot of water will help… M doing that now… Mom says it is due to me being too ‘hearty’… you know the Chinese saying… as in like the body is not cooled… She say must eat watermelons n oranges… Good to reduce the ‘heat’… However, the thing is we dun have both of the fruits at home… Only grapes n bottles of wine… Eekes…  Drank Vodka just now… Hope it helps to bring my temperature down… Aniwae, as I was saying, was studying the sexual reproduction for this Saturday’s Bio test…Hope I can score well…Although I must say that I if I dun, well, it doesn’t mean that I m not reversed in it… I m just more into the real thing… Not writing stuff… Haha…just joking…  Well, this Sunday, m going to the esplanade to help out with the art stuff with Gerald they all… Heard that they r truly busy with the stuff as they might not be able to finish making stuff to sell… Poor things… Its realli taxing on them… Hope everything goes well in the end…  Oh… forgot to say… in the end, I had to leave when Nicholas came back for only a while… So crappy… But like Stephanie says, no hanky-panky… Ha-ha… Well, not that I realli care lar… Its just that being able to kiss is the sur-plus lar… It’s the communication that matters… Yep… I think that’s all today… Will go n watch American Idol’s results later… Truly hope Camille just goes… Looking at her sing is a torture that I do not deserve… Haha… I m sounding like Simon… Lames…  Quote: Everything is always okay in the end. If it's not okay, then it's not the end.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-01 3:34 p.m.  Okie… Cant believe I m at home alreadi…( Although technically, I m not at home… m at Nicholas house…) Whoa… Now realli feeling very well… Got realli irritating stomach cramps… Stupid menstrual cramps lar… This is like the Realli BAD part of being a women… Its like not that painful sometimes but right now, its this realli aching thingy that wun go awae… Okie… Apparently, onli gals who experience it will understand…  Aniwae, after com lab, we went back to have Chemistry… My other good fren who doesn’t like Chem… Xiao ying din cum to school todae… Haha… But the plus side was the chem. lesson was realli interesting n all that… I dunno why lar but this few daes, Ms Chan cut down on the sarcasm a lot… n I mean A Lot!!! Which is a good thing… Bcoz u definitely dun see me complaining… Then during the lesson, bcoz the other side of our building was drilling n all that, we could feel this mini vibration… Its sorta like a small earthquake… Hmm… Interesting… At least, I din feel like sleeping…  Todae’s April Fool’s… Our class not very on but we kinda played a trick with Mrs Lee our Bio tcher… It was rather lame to be honest, but all of us were quite tickled… Wad we did was to like all suddenly lay down on the table n fall asleep… But she wasn’t like totally shocked n all that… Sad… Not fun one…=P  In the end, during recess, saw like Zhi lin , Gillian and Shi min all going home… did mention to zhimin that I wasn’t feeling well n saw them leave… wanted to leave n come home to rest too… Of course, I went home first lar… Den went to nick’s house… Hmm… He’s working… so nobody at home at home lar… Went in n well, here I m…  Btw, I decided to lock my blog for good… It is like my blog is the most interesting kind in class n pple read it to make fun of me… I mean, I do agree that I read blogs to like entertain myself bcoz its realli interesting n all that… But, not to make fun of anione… N I feel that the feeling realli sucks lor… However, I do intend to give my blog address to some of my favourite frens… U know who u r… Haha… This pple… I believe I can trust… They dun make fun of me although they might feel my blog interesting which I oso dunno why lar...???  Hmm… Glad that I came back early todae… Realli not feeling well now… I juz puked juz now… Sheesh… Got terrible migraine oso… If I stayed on in school, I wouldn’t have been able to live through two periods of Maths… Haha… Lucky I smart…=)  Well, that’s all for now… I realli wanna study Bio… Dun waste this precious time… Likt that den can score well for Saturday’s test…=) Cya~!  Quote: Learn as if you were going to live forever. Live as if you were going to die tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-01 8:37 a.m.  Blogging... This is written during my elit test juz now... First of all, I was wrong... Totally wrong! You CAN FAIL elit test...Thus, I am here to declare  that i will study for any elit test in future...REALLY! I am so freakingly gonna give up.No idea wad the hell is going on. Din study... period. Sigh...  Oh well, wun let this thingy affect me todae... Hmmm... Now me n zhimin r passing notes to each other... during a Test... Haha... Is this considered as cheating? Hmmm... Shoot... I dun care...  Okie... So out of like three questions in the test, i did all... but like 3/4 of a page for the first... two paragraphs for the second... n like one sentence for the last... Sheesh... I m so pathetic...  Okie, so i m in the com lab now doing lame stuff like checking out wad happened on my bdae on any year lar... So, i conclude... the government is truly lame... Truly... Aniwae, better go n do this english thingy or i wun be able to finish... Cya soon... Btw, sorrie dun have quote for this entry... All my quotes r at home... So, too bad...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-31 9:40 p.m.  Juz wanna edit some stuff that I said b4… Hmm… Abt making out with Nick? Well, I meant kissing… n not u know… having sex… it’s an entirely different matter… Haha… Thanx to Zu Hao who enlightened me abt it…(smilez) Okie, so I m supposed to feel stressed abt tmr’s elit test… Well, sorrie but I m not… I mean, lit is realli easy to score… besides, its on King of Castle… n it’s like 4 chapters that kind… N to add on, its passage-based… Whoa… I can dun study n get like 16/25… Haha… Okie… Shouldn’t be gloating… To all Geo students… Good Luck Man!=)  Okie… so nothing happened betwn me n nick todae… But wad was realli funni is that I realli cant kiss him properly… Omg… Its like Soooooo sooooo soooooo PAIN! Stupid ulcer lar… Freaking thing… located at the wrong part of my mouth… Sheesh… Well, its comfirmed… I passed on the flu to nick… poor thingy… he keeps sneezing n sniffing… Awww… Sorry dear…   Advice no.1: Dun ever try kissing anione where u have a ulcer…  Okie, aniwae, I was deliriously happy todae… got back the chem. test paper… the common test one… Hmmm… got 26/40… n to me that’s realli good lar… Why? Becoz I felt that the test was rather hard… N there was this huge question that I din understand on… Was totally crapping… Cant believe I even passed… And… furthermore, the entire’s class average was abt 26,27,28 that kind lar… Din see much pple with 30+… I was rather proud of myself… Yea baby… I rawk! Hmmm…ego… Haha…  Advice no. 2: Dun alwaize think u will fail… weird things do happen…  Okie… Wad else is there to say? Oh, towards Zu Hao’s realli blatant question… I asked Nick… He told me lar… But I promised not to tell anibody… I mean, its not as if my classmates know him but I feel its like respecting one’s privacy… so I realli wun tell… Zu Hao, dun be so curious… It ain’t good for u… Advice no. 3: Should I say Curiosity kills the cat? Nah… Sounds corny…  Well, that’s abt it todae… Hey, my life is not a serial lar… Doesn’t have to be like ultra interesting everyday lar… Bleahz… Going to watch American Idol later… Hope its interesting todae…  Quote: Life's short. If you don't look around once in a while, you might miss it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-31 5:43 p.m.  Stupid Ms Chan… Sheesh…she juz like told me during chem. today that I have chem. tutorial with her to go through our combined science test paper… Haiz… Then in the end ended like abt 3.30… I feel ultra bad lor… Nick was downstairs my house waiting for me… Darn… Why muz it alwaize seem like I m being so mean to him? Not like I wanted to get back so late right? I m realli sorry Nick… Realli sorri…  Aniwae, nothing happened todae except that we had temperature taking today… Sheesh… Den like half the class nv bring the thermometer n that stupid Mrs Tan still insisted that she wants to write down our names n sent it over to the principal office thingy… Den we would have to buy the thermometer… n all that…Crap lor… Other class tchers all dun care one…   Den onli our class had to go n buy… But I din buy in the end lar… Although I did write my name down on the payment list n told them that I will pay tmr, I dun intend to buy at all… I did take the cranky thermometer though but in the end I returned it… Hmm… I dun care lar… Come n find me for all I care… I wun buy it… Sue me lar! Freaking assholes!!!  Oh well… going to have to do household chores now… listening to Rayner’s Britney’s cd… Shadow n Everytime rox!!! The songs r realli sweet n all that… Oh man…=)  Quote: Most people walk in and out of you life. But only friends leave footprints in your heart.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-30 10:01 p.m.  Today is Tuesday… Yay~ Great day… Why? Bcoz there is no chem. lessons… Haha… Dun need to look at that Ah Sao’s face… Bleahz! Aniwae, we had Bio practical today… Was totally slacking as usual… Fell asleep in the middle of the lessons… Opps! =P The cranky emaths test truly sucked to the core… Did the easy ones then couldn’t help succumbing to ‘zhou gong’… Yday lar… Talk to nick until like 3+… Haiz… Den so ultra tired today…Sheesh… Oh, ran with Mabel for the Real 2.4km run today at Bedok Stadium… Felt like a Big accomplishment… Kept encouraging her n all that… Guess wad? She passed… Although it wasn’t like pass with flying colours, but hey, she PasseD!!! That’s realli good already...  Aniwae, Nick drovw his frens car over to my house n picked me up… We went over to his house n I cooked dinner for him… Poor thing… His parents r like in Australia now n there was all the frozen food etc. So I juz whipped up a few simple dishes for him… However, looking at him eat was realli like a good way to lose your appetite… He was like so ravenous n was gobbling all the food that kind… Sheesh… I was going like ‘Does the food taste realli that bad’? N he was like talking with his mouth full that he was realli famished n felt that the food tastes nice… 2nd Accomplishment of the day…=)  Oooo… Found a bottle of Tequila In the wine storage bar… Haha… Nick said that he din think that his parents would miss it so we opened the bottle n shared like half of it… Hmm… Had to take cab back though… I din want drink driving thingy… Well, my mum wasn’t home yet so lucky me… If not I was afraid that she will know that I drank…  Aniwae, had a great time with nick today… He was trying out so new stuff with his com n I juz lied on his bed to look at him… Hmm… Is it me Or do guys alwaize look exceptionally cute n handsome when they sare concentrating on something? Okie… it’s juz me… Hmm… That’s all for today I guess… N stop guessing Rachael… Yes, we did make out… N to Zu hao, Yes I m still a virgin… N to the Rayner… pls stop advertising my blog! Okie… that’s all folks! Cya soon.  Quote: Love starts with a smile, grows with a kiss, and ends with a tear. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-30 5:08 p.m.  Back home after emaths tutorial today… Wanted to pon so that I could go out with Nicholas… But decided that studies was a lot more impt. lar… Hmm… I know that my blog is realli very well read by lots of pple in my class but it kinda means no privacy anymore… Pple start to make fun of wad I write n all my feelings inside my blog have now bcome an entertainment to them… I realli have a good mind to lock my blog up… Perhaps I will…  Oh, Nicholas juz called… Erm… My mum’s coming home late today so I m going out for a ride with him… Glad I could still meet him today… Now I feel truly bad… Yea, I mean, I do like him… But I dun love him… I have nv come across that strong feeling towards any of my bfs’ b4… But someone else? Yea… Aniwae, by the looks of it, he likes me n all that… Guess it’s abt time to break up with him… I feel so sorry… Like I have been toying with his feelings… Playing him around…   I have alwaize been like the player… Standing around the edge of The Game of Love…An onlooker… n nv truly joining in bcoz I m afraid to get hurt… Everytime before the relationship gets too far, I pull back n put myself into reality… I dun wanna go too deep… I dun wanna get hurt… I wanna have the fun out of a relationship… Experience the great feeling of being loved but nv realli truly loving back in return…  Love is like quicksand…One step n u r in… If u have a fast reflex, u pull out fast… n u live… If not u get sucked down inside n will nv be able to come out… Even when u do… you will be with lots of injuries… n that takes a huge time to heal… perhaps even nv… Things r juz not wad they seem to be… Things r also nv as easy as they seem to be…  Quote: To love at all is to be vulnerable.  (I agree with that saying a lot… N I dun wanna be vulnerable… I dun wanna feel lost… I dun wanna lose myself… so the onli thing I can do is to pull back quickly…Nicholas…I’m realli sorry…)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-29 9:46 p.m.  Nicholas is so sweet… I forgot that we were supposed to meet at the Bedok Town Park thingy behind my house today n was late lar… After coming from school n all… However, knowing him, I knew that he will nv get angry n scold me so I decided to stroll over there… Guess wad I saw? He was sleeping at the park bench there… As in realli nodding off n all… So CUTE!!! Oh man… I din have the heart to wake him up but when I sat down, guess he felt my presence n all n he woke up… Who knew that a guy sleeping could look so Cute? Oh man…  He was oso realli sweet… Din say anithing abt me being late but the first thing he did was to kiss me… Aww… Can’t help it… He’s so sweet… Juz thinking of him makes me smile so uncontrollably… I decided to ask him to come to my house since he was so tired… He was like working overnight for some club or something… I can’t realli be bothered but it pains me to see him like so tired… Sigh…   Aniwae, that’s how he ended in my house n sleeping on my bed… I juz went to lie down on my bed… n it has like his smell on it… Man… so manly… I dun ever want that smell to go away… I bet See Ching can identify with that… Haha… Perhaps onli she will know wad I mean…=)Okie, so I m thinking of him n he juz called on the phone a while ago… Haha… I dunno how he does it but he seems to know that I wanted to talk to him n he called me… Speaking of which, Rachael would probably call me ‘da qian jin xiao jie’ again…   Hey, it’s not my fault that I dun like to call him right? Juz like to have him calling me… I dun like to be the one calling the guy… Weird huh~? N oso abt hating to have to push open the doors of places or wadeva for the guy…Nah… Will nv wanna do such stuff… Women r to be pampered u know?=)  Okie… Mum n Dad juz had a quarrel over I dunno wad… Gtg… Hope they dun start on me… Cya soon~!=) Ooo… Got quite a nice quote today… But I can’t realli relate to it bcoz I dun realli put in as much as my boyfriends’ in the relationship…  Quote: The magic of the first love is the ignorance that it can never end.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-30 10:01 p.m.  Today is Tuesday… Yay~ Great day… Why? Bcoz there is no chem. lessons… Haha… Dun need to look at that Ah Sao’s face… Bleahz! Aniwae, we had Bio practical today… Was totally slacking as usual… Fell asleep in the middle of the lessons… Opps! =P The cranky emaths test truly sucked to the core… Did the easy ones then couldn’t help succumbing to ‘zhou gong’… Yday lar… Talk to nick until like 3+… Haiz… Den so ultra tired today…Sheesh… Oh, ran with Mabel for the Real 2.4km run today at Bedok Stadium… Felt like a Big accomplishmof children with this deformity. They are bit leery of organizations from "rich countries" as they put it.. who come in, do surgery and then leave a 3rd world country- often times practicing surgery rather than performing it. (This is very common with some medical groups- although they mean well. )  When they learned our organization returns to the same country for the past 16 years providing additional surgeries to the same patients and additional care, they realized we were seriously committed to our cause. Not only did they offer all their materials (I just have to get them translated and give them credit), they invited Dr. Clawson and myself to London for a gala event this September where ALL the European cleft palate and cleft lip organizations come together- including Spain (which would be a wonderful resource for us, as they speak Spanish...)  The meeting was more than I expected and I feel I made some wonderful friends! It was a truly a rewarding experience!  Looking forward getting back to you all, as its good to be home...... Jen some wonderful friends! It was a truly a rewarding experience!  Looking forward getting back to you all, as its good to be home...... Jen 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-29 5:21 p.m.  Whoa… Juz reached home… Came home from school quite a while ago lar…Hmm… Had to buy food for my dinner at the interchange… So sianed… Quite stoned now… Aniwae, quite boring day at school today lar… Oh… Erm, in the end the cranky phonecall was from Zu Hao with Cheryl n Rayner standing beside him… So like them… the ultra lame kind... Sheesh… Total RETARDS… Well, that’s not the impt. thing today lar… no bad thingy in school today… forgot to say though… yday talked to Michael online… That’s why in quite a good mood today…=) So long nv talk to him already… got miss him lar… But glad that he’s alright in life n all that…=)  Stupid chem. tcher… Wah… I realli curse her zu zong shi ba dai man… Hope she bu de hao si… Please lor… She realli dun like me juz bcoz I m the onli gal in class from combined science… She is a f***ing bitch lor… Wad the hell is her problem? She ask question then I juz say ‘Yes’ n she muz make a big fuss over it n be so damn freaking sarcastic towards me… Wah lao… Sorri to say, but she realli veri ‘san ba’ lor… Dotx… I realli think this is the reason why she is divorced…(Joanne say one) I mean, wad guy can stand her? Muz have been blind to marry her…   Yar… I agree that she is a good tcher lar… But come on lor… She doesn’t respect us as students at all… I mean, basic courtesy is to respect one another but apparently the word ‘Respect’ is not found in her dictionary… But she expects us to have that word in ours… Go Kiss Your Ass, Bitch!!! Alwaize for no reason come n bully me… Like xiao ying would say… GET A LIFE!!! I seriously think u need one… Bcoz u lag it! Freaking ccb… Goodness… Haven’ said that word for so long already… I m realli pissed now lor…  Nicholas is sleeping in my room now… Haha… He looks so ultra Cute!!! Hmm… Juz looking at him can make me feel much better… Stupid Ms Chan… Spoil my day onli… Lucky I got Nicholas… Or else, I assure u, tml Ms Chan’s car tire’s sure got no air one… n her car sure got scratch one… Last time I almost got around to scratching Mrs Goh’s car but someone… I can’t rmb who pulled me away… Haha… Dun pissed me off man…Bitch! I can’t assure u of wad I wun do bcoz when I m angry, I tend to do stuff that will make pple regret that they ever pissed me off b4…   Steph n Rachael will probably know that… Haha… Rmb abt that idiot guy who keep trying to pick us up last year? Rmb wad I did to his motorcycle? I know u all disapproved lar, but hey, Kor taught me all this one… I mean… A gal’s gotta have something to protect herself right?=) Kor taught me a lot of stuff lar… If pple would know they will be realli shocked at wad I do… Haha… Those who know, dun say lar… Let me still have an ok gal image kk? =)  Nicholas juz woke up… So cute!!! His hair now is like all tousled now… Awww… I m going to kiss him now… Hehe… Brb… ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Juz sent him off… He better go fast ar… I dun want my mum to come home n find out… I might as well juz go jump down a building right? Dotx…Yay~ Juz went to the fridge… My Dad opened a new bottle of wine… New Stock some more… Helped myself to it… Poured like a glassful… Hope he doesn’t find out that I drank it… Or I will die… Hehe… Going to bath now… Will blog later...  Quote: Life is like a beautiful melody, only the lyrics are messed up.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-28 9:25 p.m.  I juz realized that not a lot of pple blog everyday… And that means that it’s realli boring for me… Sheesh… Is everyone’s blog so boring? Hmm… does anione think that my blog is boring? I wonder… Aniwae, lots of things happened to me today… Went to my club at like 8+ this morning… I was in a rather good mood n jogged for about 4km… Sigh… got aching muscles now… But I dun regret… It’s like after jogging, u r too tired to think… n lately, I think I have been thinking a lot too much… Like I say… Sec4 is a realli stressful year… After all that sweating thingy, I went to Sauna and Jacuzzi… Quite a long time nv go alreadi so I couldn’t with stand the heat n came out after like 30min…Hehe…  Listening to a piano version of ‘chun zai’ now… I like it much better like that… with out pple singing… Haha… Eh… Went out with Cherylnn n Gerald in the afternoon… They had this English project thingy which required them to check out stuff on Singapore that happened on their birthday… It’s like a national thingy that every student has to do… I think… But Mrs. Tan nv ask us to do leh…   Hmm… Lucky us… Ate at Bk for lunch… Was rather boring… Din know why… Juz that nothing interesting lar...But lots of things have been going on in my mind lately… Like… Wad do I realli wanna be when I go up? Do I realli wanna juz waste my life away like that? If I dun, shouldn’t I be doing something productive?   Then, wad exactly is productive? To me it’s to get out there in the society n start working to earn money… then I would be able to realize my dream (which is to earn big bucks…) faster… I know that many pple will probably think that I have realli wistful thinking as studying n learning stuff is realli impt. n all that…I’m sorry… But I realli think that learning able stuff like Differentiation isn’t gonna help in my future job unless I plan to be a Tcher or Chemist or Mathematician… Which is far from wad I wanna be… Trust me…  Right now, I m realli like having a case of identity crisis… To be honest… My one goal in life is not to “Be happy” like most pple… It is to live each day to the fullest… So that I will nv regret… I hate regretting… Its juz one of the few things that I can’t tolerate… And I can definitely assure u that if I were to die right now… I would die with many regrets…   Many pple ask me… Why m I like ‘Shen Yinhe’ in Westside Story…( For those of u who watch the show, u would probably know that she realli loves money…) Well, let me tell u now… perhaps it is not about truly loving money… But abt having a sense of security… I may have a perfect family in pple’s eyes but that doesn’t mean that I m perfectly secure…Think abt it… Pple say that money is not the most impt. thing in the world… that there r much more impt. things that r worth more… like love… happiness… etc. I dun agree… Call me practical…   But I know wad money can do to a person with a happy family… Or a family that was once close could go to court over who gets more share of money… Money is a realli scary thing… And I rather control it than to have it control me… Pple tell me that money cannot buy anithing… Who says that? How much is pride worth? How much is a girl’s virginity worth? How much is happiness worth? I believe that with money… one can own the world… one can have power… one can have fame… one can have happiness… Although many pple tell me that money might not be able to help one’s emotional self-being…  But if a poor artist has talent, wad he lacks is money to put up an exibit to let everyone be able to see his talent… isn’t it? This guy who might have a poor self- esteem could well be a man of confidence the very next day… Perhaps pple have different perspective’s in their lives… but I firmly take my stand… At the very least, I know that if I had a million dollars… I would be a much happier person…While that’s all for today… Got lots of thoughts still n I juz can’t seem to write anymore…  Quote: Hope sees the invisible, feels the intangible and achieves the impossible.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-27 9:51 p.m.  Today was a rather slow day… but I liked it… First of all, we had the English comprehension test in the morning… It was about tarantula’s etc… But it quite easy… I mean, I might not score like very high but I m quite sure I will do better than the last one… which FYI is like 24/50… failed by one mark…  After the test, we were supposed to have Flag Day… But thanx to helping out to paint Street Soccer Court in our school, I had enough CIP hours alreadi… about 20+ n that’s a lot, so I opted not to go…   Instead, went out with Cherylnn from 4A n we went to eat Mac’s for breakfast… I had hot cakes while she had Mcmuffin meal… It was rather nice talking to her lar… I mean, I can relate to her n stuff n she is realli friendly n all… But, she is like seriously a Women’s Rights kinda gal… As in she is realli a true blue Feminist kinda gal… Know wad I mean? I mean, I can relate n understand sometimes that guys r juz so total retards n should be abolished from the world etc… but then again, its juz sometimes…  After breakfast we went to see her Skincare doctor… I mean, I know I m slow but I seriously din like realli realized that her skin condition has Realli realli improved a lot thanx to the medicine that the doctor gave to her… He is one helluva docter man… Cheryl introduced Cherylnn to him n one can realli see the before n after results… Hmm… I went home after that n slept for quite a while before waking up to do my work… Sounds like a slow n bboring day but it felt rather peaceful...  Oooo… I forgot to mention the ‘weird’ n ‘creepy’ phone call that I got in the afternoon… Haha…I was realli amused at all…To be honest, I wasn’t the least bit scared… I mean, come on… It was so fake…The person was like so pathetic…He even like asked for me before he talked in that kind of rough, hoarse, and throaty voice… I swear I tried to keep a straight face but I couldn’t help it…   Juz keep giggling n all… Obviously the person thought he was realli cool n all, speaking in that kind of alienly n retard language… I realli felt true pity for a person wasting time to do this… Wad do u expect? That I will be pertrified n scared out of my nerves? Oh please… to that person who did it, Grow Up… I m sure your parents r ashamed by you…  After the phone call, I tried to think of who would be that lame to do it n guess wad? The onli two pple I was thinking of was Yuen Hoi n Rayner… I know there was more possibilty on Yuen Hoi n all that but I did remember reading Cheryl’s blog n seeing that when they were bored they played prank calls on pple… So, Rayner if u guys r the ones that did it, I have serioulsy an advice for u… Dun be a Retard… There r too many pple in the world who r alreadi like that so stop acting like one to degrade yourself…=)  Another thing is I was thinking of changing relocating my blog from here to Blogspot… It’s not bcoz lots of my other frens use blogspot but bcoz diaryland’s html stuff is realli very n I mean Very ma fan… as in troublsome… So… I guess, when I have the time, I will be shifting over to Blogspot… Pple who are reading this, pls look up for more updates to see when I will be relocating…=)  Quote:Every life has a story. And every story is a life.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-26 8:41 p.m.  Hmm… nothing special today… going to do my literature later n hand in tmr no matter wad… Hope Ms Ng doesn’t kill me…hehe… Eh… today zhimin got debate… haiz din go… now I wish I went… But then again, tmr got English compre test… So, today better sleep early… Oh… I remember wad I wanna say… I was realli quite pissed today leh… that stupid Ms Chan scold me that I was sleeping again!   Darn her lor… I was nice enough to like open my eyes during her entire lesson when I was like freaking tired n all that… I mean, I realli tried lor… That is wad pisses off… She juz accused me of closing my eyelids… What the hell lar… Go Kiss your Ass Ms Chan…!!!  Okie… i dun wanna talk about her animore… makes me more angry… I juz uploaded a poem that I wrote… It’s when I broke up with Derrick (which for your information is my 3rd bf)…   Wad the hell lar... I can't put the poem into stanzas bcoz this diaryland juz refuses to co-operate... I m so considering to go n use blodspot or blogdrive... Arghh... Sorry to those who wanted to see the poem... I dun wanna put it up coz of this blog's html...  Quote:Laugh and the world laughs with you. Cry and you cry with your girlfriends.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-26 5:42 p.m.  Yay~! Today is Friday… Hmm… Finally the end of the week is here… Wah… I sound so glad… Well, I realli am… It’s juz that after the holidays, I get tired very easily after being used to the slacking everyday… Ooo… Right now, I m supposed to be like at the SSS thingy but I pon~… haha… According to Constance (one of my frens) she say that she oso got SSS but she din wanna go coz she was waiting for someone else n so both of us nv go… Seriously, I dun mind studying… It’s juz that I dun wanna be under someone else’s eagle eye… Constance got went to check n she said onli like 6 pple went for the SSS… Aniwae, she decided to stay in school to study n wait for her fren at the same time lar…  Hmm… I muz remember to write the letter of excuse later… Gonna be a naughty n forge my mum’s signature… tmr gonna go find (Mr Chan) who is the tcher in charge n talk to him… If he wants like a letter than I will pass it to him… If not, well, who cares? Nicholas juz called… Aiyo… no biggie lar… he was saying I m such a naughty gal etc. Well, I certainly DUN care!!! It’s not as if I can’t study on my own n needs to be supervised right? I mean, to be honest, my grades have improved since sec3… My average has alwaize been like 50.5, 51.5 but now is up to 54.8 n my L1R5 has gone from 27 to 20… that’s a lot ok…  Going to bath now… bbl…=)  Quote: You can only go as far as you push.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-25 5:43 p.m.  Today was a fun day… Hmm… Yar, I know that there were two tests today but it’s like right after the tests, my entire body juz slackens… hehe… so I m relaxing at home right now…=) First of all, I felt that the chemistry test was rather hard even though it was a lot easier than the last one… Hope I can at least pass…=P The amaths test was rather ok too lar… Hehe… I know I very bad but Gerald got tell me some of the questions b4 the test…   However, I oso dun realli understand wad he was writing… my last question I think I was wrong… like that lose about 6 marks… but no matter wad, I hope that I can pass lar… this time I realli tried my best n studied a lot for it… onli slept for 2hrs yday… surprisingly, I din realli feel that tired in school lar, but I m definitely gonna sleep early today…  Eh, Mrs. Lim our maths tcher oso din cum today so Mr Chan came to baby-sit us… Oh… here’s the fun part… Hehe… the tcher I juz cursed yday? Ms Chan? Well… she totally lost her voice today…=)It was so bad that she had to type on her labtop to ‘talk’ to us… haha… good 4 her… I hope that she will nv get her voice back… who ask her in class alwaize like to talk so loudly n yell at us… Yea man… finally get my revenge…  Going to bath now… be back later! ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Me n Yin Wen went home tgt again today… Hehe… Met Issac n Yuen Hoi n Tim. Gan at Macs… Accidentally hit Yuen Hoi’s dick with the swing of my arm…Haha… erm… I realli din do it on purpose… realli!!! C’mon… I m SO not deprived… I mean, according to Steph’s words “You can have sex with Nicholas alreadi u know?” Yea… I know steph… But I dun want him to be charged with having sex with a minor… Besides, I m not that desperate lar… Pls… I mean, I totally understand that everyone gets horny in a while but not like I must have it on the spot kinda thingy… Nah… Juz hasn’t happened to me yet…=)   Got to go check out stuff for my elit hw lar… Supposed to do on responses to A Poison Tree by William Blake… Sheesh… I find it ok lar… But all in all, I dun like to depict poems… I mean, they r u to appreciate n understand but not to like analyse n pore over every word in it… It’s like then the meaning of the poem isn’t there animore you know wad I mean? Kinda like if a person turely wants to understand wad it means, let that person read it over n over again or look up for notes n guidelines to understand it but not like the way we r using poems in elit now… it juz feels weird u know wad I mean?  Yay~ Tonight got American Idol again… Can watch tv…=) Hmm… Wad else is there to say huh~ There was this realli interesting thingy I wanna say leh…Oh… Haha… Yep… In chinese class today, our tcher was commenting that Rayner’s work that he hands in is alwaize in seaweed sheds… Haha… Juz thinking of it makes me smile… Dunno why but juz find it realli funny… Haha… *Grinz* Oh, n another thing is I have decided to add special features in my blog… I have decided to add a quote everytime I end an entry…It can be about my life or anithing that has juz happened or juz on anithing in the world… Oh, n to those who have requested to see my poems online, well, I thought about it n have come to a decision.Yes…I will kindly update poems that I write to my blog…=)  Another thing is I m feeling rather upset with myself now…. I wanna change my layout of my blog… I do like it but I think there can be some nice changes to it to make it better… Like I would prefer to have the links n miscellaneous stuff on the left side of my blog… Hmm… hope I see Tafiq online later… can make him do it for me… And… I wanna change the font of my blog… It looks very plain n sianed… I want something more unique!!! I juz can’t stand having my blog like the total same as every other person’s blog… Oh, phone’s ringing... brb!  That was nicholas… He is so lame… wanted to meet me after school tmr… Haha… poor guy! I have that stupid SSS…erm which stands for Supervised-Self-Study thingy tmr… Darn… I juz can totally predict my social life going down the drain… But, I muz agree that with the time, I m sure that I can like study some realli useful stuff for my O’s if I realli put myself to it…=)  K… guess that’s all for the day… Oh, n my mom has been in realli weird moods lately… She seems to be totally ok n suddenly the next minute she snaps at me for no particular reason or her face juz changes into that ‘I’m in a sour mood’ kinda thingy… Sheesh… Oh well, gtg for now… cya later!  Quote: You come to love not by finding the perfect person, but by seeing the imperfect person perfectly... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-24 10:01 p.m.  Okie… I m like ultra stress now… guess why? Bcoz of tests lar… wad else? Aiyo… I haven’t studied finish chem yet n I seriously do not wanna fail… I dun wanna fail no matter wad… n I realli dun wanna cheat too… How? Onli resort? Study lar… Sheesh… but I think I truly need to take a break… I have a terrible migraine, a bad stomache , cranky cramps n had diarhoea juz now… this alwaize happens when I m stressed.. n that totally sux!   Rayner juz sent me a totally cute picture of cloud… he looked realli handsome… I think I m falling for him… How? I dun wanna be unfaithful to nicholas… *sobz* I m now under the spell of cloud’s charms… hehe… being lame… gotta relieve my stress… yea… gonna pia~ later tonight… which reminds me I haven’t done anithing for my amaths test yet… Great! Juz Great!!! Oh no… I m like so DEAD!!! Better go now…till next time…cya soon~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-24 3:34 p.m  Okie… so I juz came home from school… Hmmm… think I m quite early… Lucky dun have chem tutorial… need the time to study for the chem n amaths test tmr… Todae was a rather boring day lar… except for chem tutorial… wah… I was realli fuming with ms chan lor… I mean, juz bcoz I m the onli combined sciece student in class doesn’t mean she can alwaize pick on me… yar… I admit, so I m not smart or able to understand the Qualitative Analysis well… but that doesn’t mean that she can use that to pick with me right?   I mean… it’s like out of all the students who have questions in class or needs help wadeva, she decided to stand next to me n point out everything that she is not happy about…she was going like: Do u even understand wad u r doing? No… this is Wrong… Which solution is this? You messed up the answers… Hello! I din mess up the answers ok… the lab technician label the solutions wrongly lar bitch! Grrrrr… I juz can’t wait to box her!  Ok lar… that will be all… I gtg n study first… will be back at abt 9+ to finish this entry… ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Oh my god… I m like so totally embarrassed kinda thingy… Sheesh… I m like at Stephanie’s house now bcoz Aaron was on the way there n he came to pick me up in his car (Aaron is steph’s bf FYI)… Haha… realli hot n all that so I went to take a bath at steph’s house… Hmm… And guess wad? I din take any of her clothes in to change… so I was like wrapped in the bath towel b4 I came out of the bathroom… n her door was like juz closed not lock… I mean the door to her room lar… N guess wad? Aaron juz burst into the room like that…   Oh my God… for all the money in the world din prepare me for the ultimate shock… luckily the bath towel was like totally ok n din drop or I swear I will nv go out of my house for the rest of my life… Aaron was a totally decent guy… he juz like opened his mouth n gaped at me but hurriedly turned around… haha… realli nice guy… luckily, steph’s not angry with me… but she was so amused that she laughed till she cried… juz great!   But she’s realli nice… she promised not to tell anione… Haha… but it’s totally ok with me… Hey, I m not called open for nothing… Hmm… now that this is up on my blog, lots of pple r gonna know but hey, like I say, I m totally ok with it…I mean, who in the world will be totally ok with talking about sex for about 3hrs plus at Macs? Juz me, Gerald n See ching… Haha… n we scared about the 2 grps of customers who sat beside us when we were talking… I wun tell u aboput wad we talked about…  *Grinz* It’s juz too explict! But I will be nice to say it’s realli juz all about our sexual experiences n stuff… How to get on high etc. Hehe… Explict enough right? Muahahaha… (evil laughter) Aniwae, lately haven’t realli been able to sit down n talk to them about stuff n that totally sux… It’s like no one is there to listen n everything is bottled up inside u… Aww… Well, hope all of us can be free on one nday n go out tgt… well, Aaron juz came into the room… (I m currently in Steph’s room)… better go… cya… 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-23 9:18 p.m.  So… I juz studied for my chem test on Thursday juz now… Whoa… the weather at my house here realli sucked juz now… it was blazing hot n then it rained realli heavily… lucky no clothes or else mummy will be in a even bad mood bcoz the clothes wun be dry etc. Sigh…But luckily now the weather is a lot better… Nice smoothing wind… Hmm~… Okie… Aniwae today was a rather eventful day if u would consider the fun time learning about sexual reproduction in Bio class… Hehe…  Although we din have my favourite lesson which is chinese…Why is that my favourite lesson? Gee… I juz like being able to talk to pple who r fun n they all sit like around me… Yay… hehe… aniwae, erm… We learnt about the female body parts today n sexual intercourse where it will produce twins… I think it’s realli amazing to have a twin bcoz it’s like one in a million chance kinda thingy… Whoa… sometimes I kinda envy Zhi lin n Zhi nin or like Joanne n Jeannette…It’s totally cool coz like no matter wad u do u know u alwaize have somebody to fall back on… somebody who understands...  Then, we oso learnt about the menstral cycle… Eww… that’s realli juz like the worst part of being a gal… the painful torment u have to go through everytime of the month… Speaking of which, I was talking to see ching about it in e.lit class today… hehe… guess who started it? Sheila I think… Aniwae, me n ching were talking about the blobs of red stuff that look like blood that was discharged sometimes but not everytime during menstration… n she asked me if it was a blood clot but I told her it was juz our uterus lining… hehe… den Ms Ng (our elit tcher) came along n ask us wad we were talking about n when we told her, she sorta like gave a blank n ‘okie…’ face n walked away in a hurry… Oh well, guess she juz isn’t that open with sexuality… or perhaps she is juz reserved… I think it’s the latter… hehe…  Oh… n I asked ching if she was regular yet n she said she was… well… I m still rather happy with my own menstral cycle coz it’s still not regular… meaning that it can come once in 2-3 mths… haha… Meaning that I dun have to experience that terrible pain every month… But the bad side is that u nv know when it will come n sometimes it realli comes at a realli n I emphasize Realli bad time… Oh well… guess there is the perks n the unperks…  Eh… wad else did I wanna say huh~… Darn can’t remember…Oh… I rmb now… we ran the 2.4 again today… I did ok lar… better than last time… ran about 17+ min… I know I can do much better but I was realli tired n lazy to run real well n well, I juz ran n have fun n yell at whoever I see to ‘jia you’… So… realli wasn’t serious… Erm… the real final run is like next week kinda thingy… I think I should go n train… than can run erm like 13-14+ min… haha… hope so lar… Hmm… I dun think there is anithing else interesting todae… so signing off~ …cya soon!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-22 8:45 p.m.  Okie… so much things happened betwn me n nicholas… Hmm… apparently, one of rachael’s frens know one of nicholas frens… n they had a photo of him n another gal in the picture… The thing was if it was juz a normal picture, I realli wouldn’t mind at all but the bad part was it was abvious that there was something going on betwn them… I mean, they were realli close n standing next to each other his hand was behind her back kinda thing… I m rather pissed after seeing the photo… and it was a recent taken photo… the date was there!   I dunno wad to do now… haven’t talked to him in a while but he called me juz now… I din ask him about the photo but he was realli glad that I m willing to talk to him n all that… Wonder if I should be nice n juz forgive him…  I know that I keep saying I forgive him alreadi but everytime I think of him n all that… I juz think about wad happened (pls refer to previous entry) n even though in my heart I know I forgive him, I juz can’t bring myself to realli like talk to him properly… Haiz… I dunno lar… But juz now I talked to him, he wanted me to go out with him this Friday or Saturday… I told him I had to check my schedule… Hehe… even though I had nothing on on both days… make him think like I m realli unavailable kind… mean hor?=)  Ooo… I forgot to say… my mom is down with flu due to stressing too much over the Ah Bian matter… okie, maybe not real flu but she seems realli sick n lethagic lar… Haiz… Ah Bian can realli wreak havoc man… Btw, wad hw is there today? None I hope… Hmm… Oh, n I m so PROUD of myself… my layout for this blog had many changes that I wanted to make as the font of the words were either too big or too small… n the colours of the background etc. is all changed by me!   The original template design which is shown at my layout... had rather weird background colours like purple for background n white words… Eww… But I like the design n the picture of the princess… so I changed the rest all by myself… cool huh~?  Why m I so proud of myself? Well… considering I m a gal who knows absolutely nothing about HTML… n all that… I m rather surprised that I managed to figure out the weird codes n change the code colours n font size etc. Yea man… I rock! =P
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-22 4:48 p.m.  Today is the first day of school after the March holidays… nothing much happened lar… but I got to comment on something… eh… got new pple from the Higher Chinese class cum to our Express class… to be honest? To be honest, I dun realli mind that much… but it’s like the entire class becomes bigger n the tcher changes to be stricter to control the class mar… n I can’t stand it lar… It’s like she kinda change from a fun tcher to a strict tcher… not interesting anymore… I know I shouldn’t be so mean but in my heart I can’t help but blame those pple… But nvm… I know the feelings will go away in a while…=)  Haha… finally finished my Chinese compo today in school n studied finish for my Chinese test in the morning… But… I m rather upset… I din know 3 Chinese words n 1 ‘zhao ju’… sobz… hope I still manage to get 40 n above lar… like that will get 80+ for overall…  Hmm… juz looked at the newspapers juz now… saw that in the Prime News headlines: Taiwan on the Brink of Political Crisis… I know there has been riots n all that over there… Of coz this will happen… this is wad will happen when stupid Ah Bian becomes the President… He realli doesn’t deserve to be the President lar… Aniwae, enough talk about that… I m still rather unhappy about Ah Bian winning so I dun wanna talk about it…  Eh… there is a chem. test coming up in a few days time on Thursday… common test… meaning that it is rather impt. haven’t studied for it… I think will pia for it later… Hmm… I oso haven’t done my e.lit hw… Opps… hope can finish all of it later too… Later tonight got America’s Top Model… Yay~ like the show… there is much bitching involved… realli interesting…   Oh, n speaking of chemistry… got back my last test… Sigh… I failed… realli upset about failing… din think I would lar… got 12/25… failed by half a mark… I felt that the test was rather easy… but lots of small careless mistakes actually made me lost lots of marks when added together… Guess I will have to study like mad to pass the coming test… Okie… realli tired… Cya later… Still got stuff that happened to me juz a while ago… u wun believe it but it’s realli interesting! =P
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-22 4:48 p.m.  Today is the first day of school after the March holidays… nothing much happened lar… but I got to comment on something… eh… got new pple from the Higher Chinese class cum to our Express class… to be honest? To be honest, I dun realli mind that much… but it’s like the entire class becomes bigger n the tcher changes to be stricter to control the class mar… n I can’t stand it lar… It’s like she kinda change from a fun tcher to a strict tcher… not interesting anymore… I know I shouldn’t be so mean but in my heart I can’t help but blame those pple… But nvm… I know the feelings will go away in a while…=)  Haha… finally finished my Chinese compo today in school n studied finish for my Chinese test in the morning… But… I m rather upset… I din know 3 Chinese words n 1 ‘zhao ju’… sobz… hope I still manage to get 40 n above lar… like that will get 80+ for overall…  Hmm… juz looked at the newspapers juz now… saw that in the Prime News headlines: Taiwan on the Brink of Political Crisis… I know there has been riots n all that over there… Of coz this will happen… this is wad will happen when stupid Ah Bian becomes the President… He realli doesn’t deserve to be the President lar… Aniwae, enough talk about that… I m still rather unhappy about Ah Bian winning so I dun wanna talk about it…  Eh… there is a chem. test coming up in a few days time on Thursday… common test… meaning that it is rather impt. haven’t studied for it… I think will pia for it later… Hmm… I oso haven’t done my e.lit hw… Opps… hope can finish all of it later too… Later tonight got America’s Top Model… Yay~ like the show… there is much bitching involved… realli interesting…   Oh, n speaking of chemistry… got back my last test… Sigh… I failed… realli upset about failing… din think I would lar… got 12/25… failed by half a mark… I felt that the test was rather easy… but lots of small careless mistakes actually made me lost lots of marks when added together… Guess I will have to study like mad to pass the coming test… Okie… realli tired… Cya later… Still got stuff that happened to me juz a while ago… u wun believe it but it’s realli interesting! =P
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-21 7:56 p.m.  Sheesh… And yes… it’s like the last day of school… Sobz… I will miss being lazy n slacking around etc. Aniwae… enough of all that, my mom is still freaking pissed over the Taiwan elections thingy… Oh man… the house is like a dark cloud… n a storm is about to brew… Because my other relatives in Taiwan… namely: my aunties’ n uncle (my mom’s side)… n oso my mummy’s frens… well… most of my relatives such as my Da Yi… n Xue Zhen Ah Yi… n etc. they r all Ah Bian pai… aka… Ah Bian supporters… which oso means they r glad / overjoyed / ultra happy that Ah Bian won lar…Of coz my mom doesn’t wanna call n talk to them… who would wanna share their joy...joy that a lousy leader… A conniving sly jerk is the President???  Like I say, wad kinda crap is that? I totally repeat… Only intellectual pple know that Ah Bian sux n should not be the President… Lousy crap man… only pple who have no guts no confidence in himself will go n do such a sympathy stunt to get sympathy votes by the stupid aunties n those farmers… pple who live in the rural area, the villagers… those who nv study… go n give their sympathy votes to this stupid Ah Bian… Haiz… I know complaining wun help but at least the onli thing I can do is complain… too bad I m a Singaporean not Taiwanese… cant go back n vote n help Lian Chan… Haiz…  Aniwae… today is the last day of the March holidays n to be honest… I m realli upset… din realli enjoy my holidays… din finish my homework yet… feels like I did nothing… din even have proper fun… no chalets… no partying… all wasted… I m in an ultra bad mood now… Haiz… My mom n dad r watching A Bug’s life on tv now… hope mummy’s mood gets better… Haiz… so irritating… I haven’t’ done my Chinese compo yet… gonna pia for it later… haven’t studied for my Chinese test too… n my maths hw too… Wad the hell lar…  Btw… some pple r asking me wad happened to me n Nicholas… go read my previous entry please… I dun wanna recount wad happened again… I said I forgive him… yea… I do… I realli do… juz that I dun wanna talk to him n all that yet… juz thinking of him makes me upset again… kinda like still rather angry lar… but not that pissed anymore… Opps… forgot to say… I was so pissed yday that I talked to my kor… eh… the online one… I haven’t even met him b4 n I was basically in a bad mood n kinda yelled at him… you know… well, sorry for that…   I realli din mean it… but than… sorry again… Haiz… guess that’s about it… I wanna go watch the show now… i might go n watch the malaysian elections later... but not so interested lar...If I got time, will come back to update my blog but if not… I might not be able to come on everyday every night bcoz school is starting n I m sure that I wun have the time…so cya soon… I hope…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-20 10:39 p.m.  Freaking pissed… Ah Bian actually won the Taiwan election… It was DAMN foul play man!!! In case you dunno, i m partially Taiwanese… my mum’s a Taiwanese so my family realli tunes in to all news about Taiwan… I m so pissed now… Wad kinda crap is that? So many pple predicted that Lian Chan will win this year n bcoz that stupid sly, conniving, Bastard Ah Bian… went to get someone to shoot him n make himself look pitiful to get sympathy votes from all those Ah So n Auntie’s in Taiwan… Lian Chan lost… Just GREAT… Act pitiful to get those sympathy votes… Sheesh… Get a life… I mean, I can bet bcoz Ah Bian oso knows that there is a huge possibility that Lian Chan will win this year that’s why he staged an act like that...  I totally can’t believe it… I mean, the entire stage play by Ah Bian was so damn FAKE!!! I mean… C’mon… At that kinda situation… there was so many bodyguards… n he had to get shot… oso, it was like a graze past his stomach… I mean, we r not stupid enough to get bluffed… How come the bullet juz nicely grazed his stomach n not go through his stomach? What kinda lousy stage play is that? At least act more real lar…  My mom’s in a ultra bad mood bcoz of it… She got high blood pressure n now her pressure goes even higher up… Those stupid pple who voted for Ah Bian in Taiwan… Stupid no brain pple… Do u know that if u vote for him… the economic in Taiwan will be getting worst n worst? Oh man… I so wanna curse him!!!   Now my house is in a chaos… mummy’s totally in a bad mood n my entire family has that dead mood surrounding all of us… Arghhhh… I hate Ah Bian!!! My mommy’s realli worried too… coz she works at the Taiwan embassy in Singapore… n there might be like a chance she will get fired… due to all those very chim-o-fied reasons… Sigh… all those stupid ah so’s n auntie’s juz played right into Ah Bian’s hands man… I m so darn Upset!!! Realli realli bad mood now!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-19 2:02 p.m.  Juz another day at home… haven’t been going out lately… I know I have been telling pple that I m fully booked the entire week kinda thing? But… to be honest, I juz want to spent time with myself… I want to be alone… weird isn’t it? Lots of pple in the world hates to be alone… they feel lonely… but to be honest, I like the feeling of being alone… n I realli dun mind it…   I know some pple who dun mind it but would prefer to be with company than to be alone… but to me, I muz alwaize have this alone time with myself… kinda like a special time I set aside for myself… Yea… being alone is totally ok with me… juz dun overdose me with it… hehe… It’s like a medicine… heals the wound that pple inflict on me or perhaps the wounds that r self-inflicted… I dunno but the alone time that I have? Alwaize makes me grow stronger…=)  Hmmm… listening to BoA’s cd again… I realli like her song “Song with no name” n of coz “Love & Honesty”… Yea… I like the fast songs too… but not realli in the mood now… I dunno wad’s wrong with me… I haven’t realli been in the mood for anything lately… n I juz keep staying at home staring into space… sleeping… pigging out… watching Jap VCD’s… Sheesh… wad the hell is wrong with me?   I think I m suffering from a bad case of identity crisis… Anyway… call mommy juz now… she was having lunch hour… seems that she is feeling much better… Haiz… I better go n do my Chinese compo now… Opps… haven’t studied my Chemistry test chapters yet… Better go… cya later! =)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-18 9:13 p.m.  Okie… so I had a realli bad day today… I juz totally feel like I have been wasting my holidays away… I haven’t realli been studying although I know I should n everything juz seems to be wrong… It’s a case of BHD (bad hair day) n got up from the wrong side of the bed thingy… I m having a bad bad case of depression… Sigh… Haiz… can’t help it… it’s a reflex action… I keep sighing even my mom is scolding me… Speaking of which… I m realli worried abt her… She is getting old n all that n her arm at the elbow there is alwaize aching n giving her problems…It’s so bad that she has to take painkillers everyday… Sigh…I wish she will truly get better…  I keep looking at my desk n stuff n think… I should clean up pack my things neatly…After all, I m quite a neat freak thanks to my mom…I inherited her genes… but I juz keep slacking n slacking… n I tell myself I should study but keep putting it off too… I m such a procrastinator… It totally sux! I haven’t touch my Chinese which I should have bcoz I have a test on it the coming Monday… I haven’t studied for my chem. When I have a test on it next week too… Sheesh… What the hell… I realli dunno wad’s wrong with me… Arghhh… I totally hate myself…  N I told myself that I shouldn’t be so nice n forgive Nicholas so easily? But… I finally picked up his call n I gave in to his pleas… Oh man… I m such a soft-hearted person… but I dunno… I can be such a bitch n a cruel n hard-hearted person at other times… see? Split personality… One side of me wants this n the other side… that… Sheesh… I m like alwaize engaging in a war with myself all the time… It totally sux! It’s like so Duh~! Never mind… losing track of all the things I m saying now too… dunno wad’s wrong with me… I m like Gerald say… totally Bi-polar… so, dun bother me… let me wallow in self-pity n so on…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-18 1:04 p.m.  Hmm… I quarreled with Nicholas today… again… Should I start with the entire story? Yep, I guess so… okie, here goes: We were kinda happy juz talking crap n making fun of each other… then he wanted to make out n I was kinda agreeable… I mean, it was in the mood… but Hey, I m not the kinda of gal which wants to have a bf or juz go out with him with the intention of getting laid ok… it was juz in the mood at the moment n I juz let him kiss me… but as things alwaize go, he was HOT, n I mean real hot… he realli advanced too fast n we were on his couch so he was realli rough with me n all that… Sigh… of coz I told him to stop n slow down etc. n of coz he din… so I sorta pushed him on the floor n slapped him…   Hey… it’s not my fault… I din wanna slap him… he din respect me, so wad can I do??? A gal’s gotta protect herself… or no one would help her even if she screams ‘Help!’… it’s like a reflex action… trust me gals… I learnt this the hard way… but wait! There’s more… Apparently, Nic was angry… n wad can I say? I mean, we r all mature adults… Opps! For those who dunno… Nicholas is currently my boyfriend or as other pple might say, stead… and while he is like the 4th guy in my life although I feel that for the rest of my ex… we are not like couples…   I mean, including Nicholas… luckily he doesn’t know I have a blog or else I swear he would strangle me…hehe… Aniwae, back to where I was, I alwaize treat this guy’s in my life abit more den my normal guy frens but never like totally past the frens’s line… it’s sorta like past the frens line but never towards the boyfren line… it’s like more than a fren but no more then a boyfren… u get wad I mean? Sheesh… nvm… If u get it, u do but if u dun then u dun… there’s no point explaining…  So, back to wad happened… He was angry of course… that I slapped him n all that n guess wad he told me? He called me a slut n whore n said that it’s not the first time I serviced a guy… n y should I stop him from continuing etc… Whoa… after listening to him, I got so pissed… I was fuming mad… n trust me, u wun wanna cross my paths when I m angry… I mean, Hello… that’s sorta like a common knowledge… n I kinda juz stared him down… but I bet if u were there, u would be able to see the fire burning in my eyes… n dun mistake it as passion, bcoz it most certainly is not… so, guess wad I did other then stare him down?   NOTHING… haha… u should have been there… he was shocked n embarrassed n realli like din know wad to do… but I juz left… I walked out of his room n house juz like that… Cool huh~? Yea… n Isabel strikes… n she Scores!!!   Now? He’s been calling me for the past few hours so I hung up the phone…=) Hmm… apparently I think he heard that I was realli open from my frens n perhaps he thought that I did it with my ex… the 3rd guy… Derrick… but hey, Derrick is such a gentleman… he wun force anything on me not like Nicholas… Sheesh… thinking of it now juz makes me in a ultra bad mood… Sorry… that’s why I din write in my blog yesterday… but I wun care… y should I let this scum bother me n affect my life?   To be honest, I m glad he is begging me now… the feeling is realli great… haha… n well, of coz I wun break up with him due to such small reasons… y give him a reason to hate me? When I realli break-up with him… I would do it in such a way that it totally breaks his heart… in such a way that he will nv forget me for the rest of his life…I want him to feel sorta like ‘shen bu ru si’… how do u say that in English? Eh… I dunno… go ask someone if u dun understand wad I m saying…  Hehe… so right now, I m still deciding on when I should forgive Nicholas… soon I think… how about tomorrow? Okie… tomorrow is a good day… well, I gtg now… cya later…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-18 1:04 p.m.  Hmm… I quarreled with Nicholas today… again… Should I start with the entire story? Yep, I guess so… okie, here goes: We were kinda happy juz talking crap n making fun of each other… then he wanted to make out n I was kinda agreeable… I mean, it was in the mood… but Hey, I m not the kinda of gal which wants to have a bf or juz go out with him with the intention of getting laid ok… it was juz in the mood at the moment n I juz let him kiss me… but as things alwaize go, he was HOT, n I mean real hot… he realli advanced too fast n we were on his couch so he was realli rough with me n all that… Sigh… of coz I told him to stop n slow down etc. n of coz he din… so I sorta pushed him on the floor n slapped him…   Hey… it’s not my fault… I din wanna slap him… he din respect me, so wad can I do??? A gal’s gotta protect herself… or no one would help her even if she screams ‘Help!’… it’s like a reflex action… trust me gals… I learnt this the hard way… but wait! There’s more… Apparently, Nic was angry… n wad can I say? I mean, we r all mature adults… Opps! For those who dunno… Nicholas is currently my boyfriend or as other pple might say, stead… and while he is like the 4th guy in my life although I feel that for the rest of my ex… we are not like couples…   I mean, including Nicholas… luckily he doesn’t know I have a blog or else I swear he would strangle me…hehe… Aniwae, back to where I was, I alwaize treat this guy’s in my life abit more den my normal guy frens but never like totally past the frens’s line… it’s sorta like past the frens line but never towards the boyfren line… it’s like more than a fren but no more then a boyfren… u get wad I mean? Sheesh… nvm… If u get it, u do but if u dun then u dun… there’s no point explaining…  So, back to wad happened… He was angry of course… that I slapped him n all that n guess wad he told me? He called me a slut n whore n said that it’s not the first time I serviced a guy… n y should I stop him from continuing etc… Whoa… after listening to him, I got so pissed… I was fuming mad… n trust me, u wun wanna cross my paths when I m angry… I mean, Hello… that’s sorta like a common knowledge… n I kinda juz stared him down… but I bet if u were there, u would be able to see the fire burning in my eyes… n dun mistake it as passion, bcoz it most certainly is not… so, guess wad I did other then stare him down?   NOTHING… haha… u should have been there… he was shocked n embarrassed n realli like din know wad to do… but I juz left… I walked out of his room n house juz like that… Cool huh~? Yea… n Isabel strikes… n she Scores!!!   Now? He’s been calling me for the past few hours so I hung up the phone…=) Hmm… apparently I think he heard that I was realli open from my frens n perhaps he thought that I did it with my ex… the 3rd guy… Derrick… but hey, Derrick is such a gentleman… he wun force anything on me not like Nicholas… Sheesh… thinking of it now juz makes me in a ultra bad mood… Sorry… that’s why I din write in my blog yesterday… but I wun care… y should I let this scum bother me n affect my life?   To be honest, I m glad he is begging me now… the feeling is realli great… haha… n well, of coz I wun break up with him due to such small reasons… y give him a reason to hate me? When I realli break-up with him… I would do it in such a way that it totally breaks his heart… in such a way that he will nv forget me for the rest of his life…I want him to feel sorta like ‘shen bu ru si’… how do u say that in English? Eh… I dunno… go ask someone if u dun understand wad I m saying…  Hehe… so right now, I m still deciding on when I should forgive Nicholas… soon I think… how about tomorrow? Okie… tomorrow is a good day… well, I gtg now… cya later…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-16 7:04 pm  Today was juz another normal day… Hmmm… but I went to watch Dirty Dancing 2 with Mabel… Oh man… it was such a great show it can’t be anything better… the dancing n moves were realli good too… The bad part was the ending lar… I can’t stand it that the two main leads couldn’t be tgt… Hmm… I like happy endings… so if they could be tgt, the show would have been perfect… the funny thing was there were onli 5 pple in the entire cinema… I realli wonder how they earn but I guess it was a little early as we watched at 12.45… n it was at Century Square… I like the seats there better then the Tampines Mall one… Shaw Organization is much better Golden Village… Oh, n the popcorn n stuff… I felt that it was realli cheap… Me n Mabel shared a popcorn n drink Large combo n it was like $5.50 split into two…that’s like $2 plus each… Whoa… Dirt cheap…  The show was realli mostly about dancing… kinda like the Latin… Salsa kind… very sexy n very very sensual… I juz loved it… Hmm… maybe I should get someone to buy me the VCD… Yea… Would love to watch the show again… It was definitely worth it… Unlike the cat in the hat… but luckily that show was a treat from yuen hoi or else I would have been so pissed, I wouldn’t wanna go n watch this show… Hey… a girl’s gotta save mar… hehe… Oh man… now I can’t stop thinking about the dance moves now… realli very good… Hmm… wish I had the time n money to take up dancing like that… From young, I alwaize love dancing n grooving n singing n acting n all that… I confess… I m a true-blue bathroom singer… hehe… wad’s wrong with that? I think it’s realli cool… I m very sure I’m not the onli person who sings in the bathroom in this world… right?  Aniwae, I realli wish I had the money to enroll into such dance classes… oh well, maybe when I grow up then… Sigh… see? Money is such an impt. factor… If I had a huge load of money now, I would seriously cut classes n use the money to do wadever I want… I mean, my parents r alwaize nagging at me to get good grades bcoz of money… They go like if I dun study… I wun be able to do well in the future bcoz no one would want to hire me n I wun be able to live on my own blar blar n they dun want to still have to support me when they r old… bcoz it should be the other way round but they know that with my meager ‘salary’ (if I m able to get a job that is…)   I wun even have enough for myself so they juz hope that I can get good grades… get an okie job… earn abit of money n live with it… they dun expect me to support them… they juz dun want to support me anymore…(I bet lots of u r nodding your head to wad I say now… to those who agree… give me a five man… no, make that ten!)So, it all boils down to money… right? If I had the money… I can slash some of it somewhere n use the rest now… to do stuff that I like… so to me… money is real impt. n that is partly the reason why I love money so much… to those who know me well would know that I love money… Well, there u have it… that’s the reason…  Okie… I juz went to cook rice for dinner later… I m so dead… promised to cook rice for mummy before she comes home n I forgot… hope she comes home later or else if she is back n the rice isn’t ok, I m so dead…Hurry up rice…Okie, back to where I was… eh, basically I juz wanna say I think Dirty Dancing was a great show… n I seemed to have crap this much… haiz… oh well… waiting n waiting n waiting… rice, please hurry up… dun let me get scolded by mummy…   YAY! It’s done.. okie, mom coming back soon… think I better go now… see ya tmr…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-16 12:15p.m.  Oh… sheesh… my bdae is 14th of may n already got pple asking me to hurry list out my wishes… hmm… let’s see… I think it’s rather mean to tell pple to go buy wad I want but hey, since u want to know… well, here goes…  To those who know… I realli want the Westside story 3rd n 4th album… din have enough money to go buy so cant watch finish the show… sobz… Oooo…. N I know I have been complaining like crazy… but I have realli set my eyes on that pink Dior bag… Oh man… It’s so pretty…It’s like the ultimate bag that I realli want… even the Prada bags that I liked a lot last time r nothing compared to it… Hehe… Last time Cheryl keep saying she wanted the erm… wad bag was it?   Let’s see… Louis Vuitton bag… yep… that was the one… the white one with lots of nice LV words on it… cool man… but I seriously like the pink Dior one more… hehe… Hmm… Oooo n I welcome make-up… all kinds of make-up… of coz I only like some brands… that day Rachael asked me… MAC or Bloom would be fine… Za is rather nice too but I like Dirty n Wet & Wild n Red Earth… Sigh… if onli I had money… hehe… I know… I totally sound like a bimbo but hey… girls u dun ‘ai mei’ r not girls okie… so, I m juz a typical normal gal! =P  I think clothes r fine so stop asking me wad clothes I like coz well… I dun realli like pple to give me clothes as a bdae present lar… I juz find it weird… Although if u realli think u have nothing to give me den fine I accept 37 degree clothes… or clothes from Topshop or Miss Selfridge… other then that… I personally suggest u dun buy for me coz I scared if I dun like it then I wun wear it for a lot of times so I dun wanna waste your money okie? Then… accessories r totally fine too… I m a rather girly person so I like necklaces n bracelets… preferably necklaces lar… Oooo… which reminds me… I so wanna kill me my mom… she juz wun allow me to go pierce my ears… darn… so PLEASE dun give me ear rings… I dun have ear holes to put them in… sobz… Sigh… wad else did u guys ask huh~?  Eh… school bags izzit? Hmm… for school bags, I like 37 degrees one… but better dun buy me school bags without asking me coz the same goes for clothes… I got rather unique tastes n if I dun like it I wun use it… Eh… I think that’s all right? Well, I gtg now… going to watch Dirty Dancing with Mabel later… cya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-16 12:15p.m.  Oh… sheesh… my bdae is 14th of may n already got pple asking me to hurry list out my wishes… hmm… let’s see… I think it’s rather mean to tell pple to go buy wad I want but hey, since u want to know… well, here goes…  To those who know… I realli want the Westside story 3rd n 4th album… din have enough money to go buy so cant watch finish the show… sobz… Oooo…. N I know I have been complaining like crazy… but I have realli set my eyes on that pink Dior bag… Oh man… It’s so pretty…It’s like the ultimate bag that I realli want… even the Prada bags that I liked a lot last time r nothing compared to it… Hehe… Last time Cheryl keep saying she wanted the erm… wad bag was it?   Let’s see… Louis Vuitton bag… yep… that was the one… the white one with lots of nice LV words on it… cool man… but I seriously like the pink Dior one more… hehe… Hmm… Oooo n I welcome make-up… all kinds of make-up… of coz I only like some brands… that day Rachael asked me… MAC or Bloom would be fine… Za is rather nice too but I like Dirty n Wet & Wild n Red Earth… Sigh… if onli I had money… hehe… I know… I totally sound like a bimbo but hey… girls u dun ‘ai mei’ r not girls okie… so, I m juz a typical normal gal! =P  I think clothes r fine so stop asking me wad clothes I like coz well… I dun realli like pple to give me clothes as a bdae present lar… I juz find it weird… Although if u realli think u have nothing to give me den fine I accept 37 degree clothes… or clothes from Topshop or Miss Selfridge… other then that… I personally suggest u dun buy for me coz I scared if I dun like it then I wun wear it for a lot of times so I dun wanna waste your money okie? Then… accessories r totally fine too… I m a rather girly person so I like necklaces n bracelets… preferably necklaces lar… Oooo… which reminds me… I so wanna kill me my mom… she juz wun allow me to go pierce my ears… darn… so PLEASE dun give me ear rings… I dun have ear holes to put them in… sobz… Sigh… wad else did u guys ask huh~?  Eh… school bags izzit? Hmm… for school bags, I like 37 degrees one… but better dun buy me school bags without asking me coz the same goes for clothes… I got rather unique tastes n if I dun like it I wun use it… Eh… I think that’s all right? Well, I gtg now… going to watch Dirty Dancing with Mabel later… cya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-15 9:09 p.m.  Sheesh… today is the 3rd day of holidays… I know I should be studying n all that given my results as a sec4er… sigh… However… I must emphasize on the however…hehe, I m here updating my blog… lousy day today too…I juz feel like I haven’t really done anything fulfilling today… like there is something I wanna do… to perk me up I guess? Okie… this is really hard to explain but if u understand than u do… if u dun den u dun…right now my life is rather uneventful… (Thank heavens)   I mean, hey no offense but if its supposed to be eventful, make it more easy for me to live… not like a few weeks back where I keep losing my stuff n being extra ultra unlucky… sheesh… now that was bad!!! Realli BAD!   Aniwae, I was thinking of like making a planner to kinda like plan on wad I should study n do in the holidays… However, see, I m emphasizing on the however again… I have to plan to write wad I should study in the planner n that takes brains n of coz, I m totally slacking here now… so I m nowhere to finishing my planner… sheesh… do u get wad I m saying? I m kinda lost with my words too… dun worry I wun blame u if u call me weird…   Hey… it’s one of my middle names… of coz the champion word is unpredictable… den cums weird n perhaps bimbotic n den bitchy… sheesh… all in all, its kinda taxing for pple who want to truly know me unless I give info… so hey… look at my diary… its supposed to portray ones inner erm… self right? Like… inner being kinda thing… u get wad I mean? =) sure do hope so… opps… digressing… Okie back to topic...  Sec 4… haiz… of coz it’s tiring… it’s the year when u feel more alive… wanna party more… like go out… have fun… hang out… chill out… n wad r sec4s in Singapore supposed to do? STUDY… Arghh… the word itself is bad enough… wad more having to plan to do it… sheesh… sometimes I wish I was in Legally Blonde… u know? The movie? Well… being a bimbo sure aint that bad… I mean, wad if u have the looks… juz go grab a rich guy… n your future is totally secured… hmmm… of coz it’s a plus if u fall in love with the guy or if the guy is a womanizer but hey… we r living in the 21st century right? Pple call us the Gen-Y pple…right? (I think) aniwae…if the man can womanize, why cant we go find a lover of our own? Sigh… I can just bet… the guy who womanizes is normal… juz bcoz he is rich… n women? We r called whores... or sluts… so mean right? Bleahz… Opps… digress again…hehe back to the topic…  As I was saying… I think being a sec4 is realli tough n all that… I kinda wish when I was back in sec3… I think of my secondary years… sec3 was the best… sec1 I was realli bitchy… sec2 well… I mellowed down a lot… but was still very hmm… how do u explain it? See...? I was that bad… I dun even know how to describe myself… hehe… Okie… thought of the word… infamous… yeah… I was infamous… lots of pple knew me…n it wasn’t juz the pple in my same level… it was realli pple from all levels… I mean… now the sec4s… there are like 80% to 90% of pple knowing me but I dunno their names… some of them r like acquaintances… I alwaize say hi n bye to them but I dun even know their names… sounds mean I know but hey… wad do u expect me to do? Go up to them n say for the past few years I have been saying hi n bye to u but I nv knew your name? Whoa… I think I will get slaughtered by them man… haha…   However… lots of bad things happened during those years… n I have realli mellowed a lot through out the years… of course to say I regret my actions is not entirely true although I muz agree I could have handled a lot of situations differently…   However, when I went to sec3, I grew up a lot… lots of things happened… good things n bad… BUT I muz say I realli enjoyed being a sec3… wad with knowing new frens…like Tafiq…some of them even my best frens now… such as Gerald… See Ching… Cheryl… Sze Hwei… Yin Wen… Trina… Mabel… etc. n although I had some clashes with Swee Fan… I certainly think of her as a very good fren now… n I m realli glad to know her… Hmm… I treasure my frens a lot n hope that we will still keep in contact with each other forever… smilez!=)  Sigh… after juz looking through everything that I wrote… I feel so cheated of a life… Sec4 is realli a fun year bcoz guys finally mature… hehe… u know wad I mean… it’s a lot nicer to talk to them in class now… I mean in a frens way lar… dun u go think of something else… but… I guess I’m realli stuck with studying… sigh… wadeva it is… I hope that I can survive through the whole entire process without losing any frens due to lost of contact… n of coz the ultimate goal… to get into Temesek poly…!!!  That’s all folks… gtg… Till next time…cya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-14 6:05 p.m.  Yeah!!! great man... i have a new com... man, i m so happy i dunno wad to say or think... Well, first of all i wanna thank god for the new com... i m like so dying here without my com to update my blog... its like i cant tell someone my feelings n well, that juz seems weird... okie... i m having tuition in a while... at 7pm... so cant talk to much n too long... is juz that lots of things have happened since i updated u and...i cant help it... i m so excited with my new com n being able to finally wrtie in my blog again... YAY~!   Sheesh... i know i sound stupid... but i realli REalli like this com n m so happi to have a new com... ok... all this talk about my new com blah... sigh... i wish i could cont, but i realli have to go... will definately be back after my tuition... so wait up n i will tell u lots of my stuff later on... meanwhile, smilez... it's a brand new com!!! perhaps pple think ..."So What?" but to me... it's a real luxury... realli!!!=)   Hmm... finished my tuition quite a while ago.. think i m gonna spent the rest of the night updating my blog... ok, so wad happen the past few days?   Let's see... it's like the 2nd day of holidays now... haiz... i dunno why... huge mood swing... now? i seriously feel ultra tired n dun wanna type anithing... eh... update u tmr can?=)   Okie...m back again... apparently, erm... me n yuen hoi...rayner...cheryl...sheena n zu hao to watch the butterfly effect... however as the screening 4 it was kinda late we were debating to watch the haunted mansion or the cat in the hat... n so they chose to watch the cat in the hat... but seriously... it was so bad, no other movie could have compared to it... i m most certain it would bag this years worst movie ever!!!   Luckily, yuen hoi paid for my movie ticket as it was a treat by him to tag along n be the middle women btwn them...(coz... i can relate to rayner n cheryl they all n yuen hoi too... wad can i say? I m a friendly person...hehe) bcoz they kinda had a big fight btwn them from last year... n rayner apologised... so everything's kinda alright btwn them now lar... (yuen hoi n rayner quarreled)    Aniwae... back to wad i wanted to say... the show was totally atrocious... disgustingly lousy... n huge waste of time... a pain to the eyes n ears... a thorn in the mind... seriously... who would wanna make such a show??? Mike Myers... i cant stand him... i know i shouldnt be complaining like crazy... i mean, i din pay for it... but hey... waste of my time.. n of coz yuen hoi's money!!! For those who know me will know that money is very impt. to me... n even if it wasnt my money... i oso veri heart pain to see the money wasted like that... haiz... i should quit talking abt it... makes me more n more pissed thinking abt it...=( Hmm... see? Thanx to the stupid movie, i keep losing my chain of thoughts... i got lots n lots of stuff i wanna say.. but keep forgetting...   Aniwae, now the weather is realli bad... can go out even if i want to... watching BOA's mtv thanks to gerald... hehe... he lent me his cd... then at least i wun get bored to death at home...   Sigh... i think i will go n watch tv now... if i got time, will update my blog later... cya!=)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-05 7:36 p.m.  Yeah... finally i can use a not so bad com to type my entry... hmm... guess wad? Yup... i m at the library... bedok one lar... hehe supposedly studying for bio test tmr... sigh,i m so darn freaking tired... in any case, lots of things have happened over the past few days, n well, i m here to tell u about all of them!!!  First of all... i told my parents n sister about the handphone thingy that it was stolen... haiz... n of coz there was huge fuss over it n such but my parents r pissed for SO the wrong reasons... my mom is pissed coz i told them two days later... n coz i lied to them that i lost my handphone on that particular day instead of two days before... so nothe right thing to be pissed about right??? Sheesh... where are her priorities? i mean, if i knew she wont be pissed that the handphone was stolen, i would have told her right away instead of two days later right? But i also din becoz of another reason lar... it was my sisters bdae that day... aniwae, hope my sister wun be too pissed with me animore...  And to top it all, now see ching is truely pissed with me... 4 i realli dunno wad... juz wanna say that i m a reasonable person, n i have searched my past doings and couldnt realli find out about the reason why she is so not happy with me... so, oh well, will juz hear her out another day and hope i din offend her unintentionally...=)  Now... where was I? Hmm... oh... life truely sucks this few days... sigh... wad else is there to say? Nothing much lar... gtg n study... Till next time! (Which i hope wun be too long coz my house com crashed n my dad's gonna get a new one...)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-03 7:55 a.m.  Okie...rushing for time here... m in the skool using the skool's com updating my diary... sigh this is so pathetic!!! In any case, as i mentioned earlier, my house com has crashed and oh sigh... gotta type in skool... so boring...  Btw, i SOoooo need to learn html... someone Pul-lease teach me... aniwae... hmm... gerald was commenting on my chained thoughts coz i dun use full-stops and all that... sorri... like my sentences/thoughts to be connected... so not my fault right???=)  I oso need to get a life... i mean, sheesh... i was so bored yday i had to talk to myself so that i could fall asleep... i mean:" Women... get a life!!!"... so not my fault!!!  So, wad did i wanna just wanna say huh~? Hmm...Oh... pple have been complaining to me... Hmm... "Women... i wanna know more about your boyfren... Is nicholas cute?"  My answer? Yes, he is realli cute... N i do kinda like him...hehe...=P  Sheeesh... Fine... damn the bell just rang... i gtg soon but hmm... will cum to update lar... as usual, i can nv finish my diary ontime... alwaize have to0 cum back n edit... so sucky...   N... i got this new thingy from our skool...the A$$ H0le Skool... Sigh... got this donation card that of coz wants us to donate AGAIN... should i go on??? Oh... man... gtg now... cya soon... hope my house com can work and stop fighting a battle with me... Haiz... realli gtg... I will miss you... =(
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-01 8:19 p.m.  Okie... i know i should truely clarify lots of stuff with you...first of all...is it so weird to find out that i have another name and that it is Isabel? Well, i kinda like that name and to be honest cant stand my real name... so, thats something else you will know about me...=)  Another thing is well,as you know, i have a rather huge circle of frens... which i feel is a good n bad thing at the same time...i react realli diffentely when i m with different pple... let's see... when i m with my classmates, i m usually like the da jie thingy you know? n when i m with my clique in skool its like they treat me like a bimbo, so well, i feel more of being the 'xiao mei' among them...  You know wad i mean? Then with my other frens... its like, i m both at the same time...hmm...how to explain? its like, this is all me you know? I know it sounds weird, but even with different personalities, it's still me and i juz portray different sides of me at different time... i mean, i can be such a darn bitch n then such a stupid n blur bimbo... but, i guarentee that it is all me...not faking...  The other day Sze Hwei asked me about my 'other' frens... n it was like a life that my good frens such as ching,gerald,cheryl n of coz hwei dunno about... i do understand that feeling... it's like you have a good fren that has so another life... one that u seriosly dunno about... and have no idea about it... i thought about it n to be honest, i would feel interested too... i mean, who wouldn't n it feels weird right? But i realli wanna say that as much as i have a different life out there with my other frens, hwei n you all... r still my best frens ever...n i feel so glad that i know you all...   Hmm... except that i have something to complain about...is it just me or do i feel that sze ching has changed alot? It's like we dun even talk now... yep, i do sit her car to skool but its like we r strangers... dun have anithing to talk about n she alwaize gives me this buay song face like she is ultra pissed with me...hey, wad did i do man? tell me if i did something wrong right? i wun mind... i wanna change... i mean if it is a change for the better, hey why not? But of coz please give me time... i m not superwomen...   However, i sometimes kinda wonder...is bcoz of steven(her  bf)? Dun you get me wrong... i m so happi for them when i see them tgt...i alwaize feel tt there is tt love in the air... you know wad i mean? So, cool tt both of them r tgt but i cant help feeling tt bcoz of tt, we realli lost contact with her... everyday after skool she goes to find him...n she used to have this frens day n boyfren day during the week but now its all boyfren thing... okie... fine.. i know i sound like a jealous freak but who cares? i miss my fren.. is there abithing wrong with that?Bleahz...=P  Hmm... wad else is there that i wanted to say? Okie... i remebered... erm, i m SOooooooo going on a diet... Fat penguin... juz call me that... sigh... i cant help but growe fat right?Food RoX... n no fair... pple eat as much n i do n i seem to be the only one growing fatter n fatter n FaTTer... pleah... this totally sucks...  In any case...right now i m still thinking of stuff i need to clarify... other then yes i m mysterious bcoz i like to be...i feel that i wun ever show 100% of myself to anibody but different percents to different pple bcoz... if i do that would mean that i would get hurt easily bcoz i do let things get to even though i say i dun... cant help it... u got a sensitive gal here... so, to prevent getting hurt... i would realli do anithing...even if it means hurting others in the process... sorry... i believe that this is a surviaval world n this is just one of my survival tatics... so...well, too bad if u wanna know stuff about me... bcoz u wun be able to unless i allow myself to tell you that particular part of me...=)  Wad else is there? Questions anibody? Juz ask then... i love to answer the... so feel free to ask then... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-02-27 11:43 a.m.  Okie... so i just edited my last entry and now i m in my skools com lab... doing social studies stuff... and of coz updating my diary... Sigh...  Bad luck realli follows me where ever i go... Guess wad again?I lost my handphone in the bus on the way to school today... Dun think i dare go home animore... Sigh...   Okie, so i m at home now...come to think of it, i seriously dun think i lost the hp... i think someone stole it... sigh...juz thinking of me makes me upset again... nvm... i realli m praying that someone will return it or this guy would finally find his conscience n so on... nvm them...   Hmm...today school ended early, coz last friday the O level results of our school was out... Pple did rather well, and our tchers n everyone was in a good mood... =) Aniwae, today i went to pastamania with my classmates: Yin Wen, Mabel, Trina, Charis....so fun... hmmm except that they had Geo test yday so bo bian we left straight after eating... so sianz...  Haiz, so i m still fretting about my hp now and so on but i guess thats all for this entry...nothing else to talk about...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-02-17 11:50 p.m.  hey... this sucks man! i m mugging for my chem now... got like lots of test for this week and i got 5chapters for my chem test...k lar gtg will update on this entrie next time...cya then  Okie...long time after the chem test... did very badly for it... got 9/50... failed like hell... Sigh... And then everything bad seems to be happening to me after valentines day... I oso dunnoe why but i seem to have the worse luck in the world... first, i left my wallet in the chemistry lab and nearly died of fright when i realised that i lost it... then, at saturday...i borrowed my sisters PoPular card to grab stuff... oso got Mummys NTUC link card to pay for soem family stuff... guess wad?  I lost both of the cards...they dropped out of my wallet without me knowing it... and i realli dunno why?  Of coz mummy went bersek and yelled at me for hours... and the few days after that she was alwaize in a bad mood... scolding me for the lamest stuff ever... Damn... i m realli unlucky... Seems to be that everything is going wrong in my life now... Sigh...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-02-14 9:26 p.m  Hey...today is valentine' day...i know this sounds lame..but to all lovers out there...just to wish u guyz a great valentine's day and may u love forever...=)   Today is my first entrie on this online blog thingy...feels kinda weird that i m typing instead of writing but oh well... Aniwae,just to do a intro on myself...well,isabel is so not my name...but i dun like my name so,most of my good pals just call me is... and..i m fifteen now going on sixteen in may 14th...i like dragons and my fav. animal is penguins... i hate studying wont mind working and i m very practical... hmm...i love writing poems and songs and I'm very into music.Jazz...R&B...Pop...Country...u name it!  I think alot...call me deep or sensitive but i think a human's character is a very special and interesting thing...i love observing other pples character...its one of my fav. pastimes...i hate hypocrites and pple who just like to find trouble with me...erm...i can be very blur but stuff that i do sometimes can amaze my frens...so basically, if u want me to describe myself in a word, it would be UNPREDICTABLE... i like to keep pple guessing...if one is so predictable, well...it juz takes the fun out of life... Another thing is i love the night... call me a party animal...=P I think sunsets are nicer then sunrise...   I love the sea,sky and looking at breathe-taking scenes... I know... i should stop or this will nv end... it takes time to know a person, so i hope that in future,u can get to know me better... well...had a rough day so bye and cya soon!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-02 12:47 p.m.  Supposed to be in school now… Haha… But not feeling well, so at home… Well, to be honest, recovered from the fever this morning but din feel like going to school… Juz felt that going to school todae would be a waste of time… Besides, got Bio test tmr… Can stay home n study mar… Haha… A good idea right?  Aniwae, Nick is bz today… wun be meeting him…Hmm… I dun realli care lar… Juz that I quite sianed now at home… Actually, my sister came home yday… Den is like I cant stay home n rest if not she will wonder why n tell my mom… And although my mom knows that I m not feeling well, she will still want me to go to school… So, I had to go to Mac’s in the morning todae n sorta like shelter for a while before my sister goes out… Came back at abt 11.30… N she was asking why I came home so early… So I juz said something like school ended early etc. n later have to go back to school again for SSS… Hehe… Bad gal… Good liar…  Well, finished typing the excuse letter juz now… Had it printed out n forged my mom’s signature… Doubt my Mrs. Tan would know… Hmm… I love myself!!! Oh well, glad I din go to school todae… Realised that I realli din know quite a lot abt Sexual Reproduction… N tmr is the test… Darn… I m so dead…  Aniwae, I know it is weird but I juz feel like trying out writing… I have been penning songs n poems n stuff… But nv wrote… I believe that writing will improve my English… And I seriously need improving aniwae… I know pple will probably think I m so sick etc. or wad, but I hope that through my story, pple will get to know the feminine side of every girl n different points of views that can be displayed through a person’s character…  Another thing is Steph has suggested that I should post the story on websites like fanfiction etc. But, I dunno… Its like this is my story… N I dun realli intend to put my story up for everybody to see… Perhaps if it is a success among u all, I might consider the suggestion… But right now, I juz wanna write n see your comments on the story…So, after reading it, Pple… Please tag my board… Even if u dun like the story,  Please please give your comments… I m totally ok with constructive criticisms… Erm, please refer to the next entry for the first paragraph of the story…  Quote: When patterns are broken, new worlds emerge. P.S  I totally love this quote…Hope u will like it too…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-01 9:52 p.m.  Blogging now even though I should be studying sexual reproduction… Hmm… I know that it is an interesting chapter n that I should feel happy studying it… But, cant help it… there is like no kick in learning it when there is no practical… Hehe… Not that I have no knowledge of my own though… Ha-ha…=P  Hmm… I realli think locking my blog for good is a Ultra good idea… except, got pple start to complain already lar… Sorry… But if I dun lock, then it is like pole will start using the stuff that I write to make fun of me etc. N I just cant stand that… It doesn’t feel right…   Oh well… Cant think straight… Having a terrible migraine due to fever… at like 38 degrees… totally six… I feel like hot n bothered all over… I hate having fevers… Remember that when I was young n having a fever, mom n dad will force me to drink Barley water… One of the reasons y I hate Barley now… Yuck!!! Won be going to school tm… My mom still wants me to go to school lar… She say just eat medicine n den go… I dun care… I m not feeling well, n that’s that! I will personally write the excuse letter n forge my mom’s signature myself… Bleahz…   Wow… neck cramp… Man, my immune system has just gone down the drain… Must remember to not kiss Nicholas that often… I totally dun wanna pass the virus to him… Glad that my ulcer has been better… Ha-ha… Pole say drink a lot of water will help… M doing that now… Mom says it is due to me being too ‘hearty’… you know the Chinese saying… as in like the body is not cooled… She say must eat watermelons n oranges… Good to reduce the ‘heat’… However, the thing is we dun have both of the fruits at home… Only grapes n bottles of wine… Eekes…  Drank Vodka just now… Hope it helps to bring my temperature down… Aniwae, as I was saying, was studying the sexual reproduction for this Saturday’s Bio test…Hope I can score well…Although I must say that I if I dun, well, it doesn’t mean that I m not reversed in it… I m just more into the real thing… Not writing stuff… Haha…just joking…  Well, this Sunday, m going to the esplanade to help out with the art stuff with Gerald they all… Heard that they r truly busy with the stuff as they might not be able to finish making stuff to sell… Poor things… Its realli taxing on them… Hope everything goes well in the end…  Oh… forgot to say… in the end, I had to leave when Nicholas came back for only a while… So crappy… But like Stephanie says, no hanky-panky… Ha-ha… Well, not that I realli care lar… Its just that being able to kiss is the sur-plus lar… It’s the communication that matters… Yep… I think that’s all today… Will go n watch American Idol’s results later… Truly hope Camille just goes… Looking at her sing is a torture that I do not deserve… Haha… I m sounding like Simon… Lames…  Quote: Everything is always okay in the end. If it's not okay, then it's not the end.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-01 3:34 p.m.  Okie… Cant believe I m at home alreadi…( Although technically, I m not at home… m at Nicholas house…) Whoa… Now realli feeling very well… Got realli irritating stomach cramps… Stupid menstrual cramps lar… This is like the Realli BAD part of being a women… Its like not that painful sometimes but right now, its this realli aching thingy that wun go awae… Okie… Apparently, onli gals who experience it will understand…  Aniwae, after com lab, we went back to have Chemistry… My other good fren who doesn’t like Chem… Xiao ying din cum to school todae… Haha… But the plus side was the chem. lesson was realli interesting n all that… I dunno why lar but this few daes, Ms Chan cut down on the sarcasm a lot… n I mean A Lot!!! Which is a good thing… Bcoz u definitely dun see me complaining… Then during the lesson, bcoz the other side of our building was drilling n all that, we could feel this mini vibration… Its sorta like a small earthquake… Hmm… Interesting… At least, I din feel like sleeping…  Todae’s April Fool’s… Our class not very on but we kinda played a trick with Mrs Lee our Bio tcher… It was rather lame to be honest, but all of us were quite tickled… Wad we did was to like all suddenly lay down on the table n fall asleep… But she wasn’t like totally shocked n all that… Sad… Not fun one…=P  In the end, during recess, saw like Zhi lin , Gillian and Shi min all going home… did mention to zhimin that I wasn’t feeling well n saw them leave… wanted to leave n come home to rest too… Of course, I went home first lar… Den went to nick’s house… Hmm… He’s working… so nobody at home at home lar… Went in n well, here I m…  Btw, I decided to lock my blog for good… It is like my blog is the most interesting kind in class n pple read it to make fun of me… I mean, I do agree that I read blogs to like entertain myself bcoz its realli interesting n all that… But, not to make fun of anione… N I feel that the feeling realli sucks lor… However, I do intend to give my blog address to some of my favourite frens… U know who u r… Haha… This pple… I believe I can trust… They dun make fun of me although they might feel my blog interesting which I oso dunno why lar...???  Hmm… Glad that I came back early todae… Realli not feeling well now… I juz puked juz now… Sheesh… Got terrible migraine oso… If I stayed on in school, I wouldn’t have been able to live through two periods of Maths… Haha… Lucky I smart…=)  Well, that’s all for now… I realli wanna study Bio… Dun waste this precious time… Likt that den can score well for Saturday’s test…=) Cya~!  Quote: Learn as if you were going to live forever. Live as if you were going to die tomorrow.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-01 8:37 a.m.  Blogging... This is written during my elit test juz now... First of all, I was wrong... Totally wrong! You CAN FAIL elit test...Thus, I am here to declare  that i will study for any elit test in future...REALLY! I am so freakingly gonna give up.No idea wad the hell is going on. Din study... period. Sigh...  Oh well, wun let this thingy affect me todae... Hmmm... Now me n zhimin r passing notes to each other... during a Test... Haha... Is this considered as cheating? Hmmm... Shoot... I dun care...  Okie... So out of like three questions in the test, i did all... but like 3/4 of a page for the first... two paragraphs for the second... n like one sentence for the last... Sheesh... I m so pathetic...  Okie, so i m in the com lab now doing lame stuff like checking out wad happened on my bdae on any year lar... So, i conclude... the government is truly lame... Truly... Aniwae, better go n do this english thingy or i wun be able to finish... Cya soon... Btw, sorrie dun have quote for this entry... All my quotes r at home... So, too bad...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-31 9:40 p.m.  Juz wanna edit some stuff that I said b4… Hmm… Abt making out with Nick? Well, I meant kissing… n not u know… having sex… it’s an entirely different matter… Haha… Thanx to Zu Hao who enlightened me abt it…(smilez) Okie, so I m supposed to feel stressed abt tmr’s elit test… Well, sorrie but I m not… I mean, lit is realli easy to score… besides, its on King of Castle… n it’s like 4 chapters that kind… N to add on, its passage-based… Whoa… I can dun study n get like 16/25… Haha… Okie… Shouldn’t be gloating… To all Geo students… Good Luck Man!=)  Okie… so nothing happened betwn me n nick todae… But wad was realli funni is that I realli cant kiss him properly… Omg… Its like Soooooo sooooo soooooo PAIN! Stupid ulcer lar… Freaking thing… located at the wrong part of my mouth… Sheesh… Well, its comfirmed… I passed on the flu to nick… poor thingy… he keeps sneezing n sniffing… Awww… Sorry dear…   Advice no.1: Dun ever try kissing anione where u have a ulcer…  Okie, aniwae, I was deliriously happy todae… got back the chem. test paper… the common test one… Hmmm… got 26/40… n to me that’s realli good lar… Why? Becoz I felt that the test was rather hard… N there was this huge question that I din understand on… Was totally crapping… Cant believe I even passed… And… furthermore, the entire’s class average was abt 26,27,28 that kind lar… Din see much pple with 30+… I was rather proud of myself… Yea baby… I rawk! Hmmm…ego… Haha…  Advice no. 2: Dun alwaize think u will fail… weird things do happen…  Okie… Wad else is there to say? Oh, towards Zu Hao’s realli blatant question… I asked Nick… He told me lar… But I promised not to tell anibody… I mean, its not as if my classmates know him but I feel its like respecting one’s privacy… so I realli wun tell… Zu Hao, dun be so curious… It ain’t good for u… Advice no. 3: Should I say Curiosity kills the cat? Nah… Sounds corny…  Well, that’s abt it todae… Hey, my life is not a serial lar… Doesn’t have to be like ultra interesting everyday lar… Bleahz… Going to watch American Idol later… Hope its interesting todae…  Quote: Life's short. If you don't look around once in a while, you might miss it.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-31 5:43 p.m.  Stupid Ms Chan… Sheesh…she juz like told me during chem. today that I have chem. tutorial with her to go through our combined science test paper… Haiz… Then in the end ended like abt 3.30… I feel ultra bad lor… Nick was downstairs my house waiting for me… Darn… Why muz it alwaize seem like I m being so mean to him? Not like I wanted to get back so late right? I m realli sorry Nick… Realli sorri…  Aniwae, nothing happened todae except that we had temperature taking today… Sheesh… Den like half the class nv bring the thermometer n that stupid Mrs Tan still insisted that she wants to write down our names n sent it over to the principal office thingy… Den we would have to buy the thermometer… n all that…Crap lor… Other class tchers all dun care one…   Den onli our class had to go n buy… But I din buy in the end lar… Although I did write my name down on the payment list n told them that I will pay tmr, I dun intend to buy at all… I did take the cranky thermometer though but in the end I returned it… Hmm… I dun care lar… Come n find me for all I care… I wun buy it… Sue me lar! Freaking assholes!!!  Oh well… going to have to do household chores now… listening to Rayner’s Britney’s cd… Shadow n Everytime rox!!! The songs r realli sweet n all that… Oh man…=)  Quote: Most people walk in and out of you life. But only friends leave footprints in your heart.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-30 10:01 p.m.  Today is Tuesday… Yay~ Great day… Why? Bcoz there is no chem. lessons… Haha… Dun need to look at that Ah Sao’s face… Bleahz! Aniwae, we had Bio practical today… Was totally slacking as usual… Fell asleep in the middle of the lessons… Opps! =P The cranky emaths test truly sucked to the core… Did the easy ones then couldn’t help succumbing to ‘zhou gong’… Yday lar… Talk to nick until like 3+… Haiz… Den so ultra tired today…Sheesh… Oh, ran with Mabel for the Real 2.4km run today at Bedok Stadium… Felt like a Big accomplishment… Kept encouraging her n all that… Guess wad? She passed… Although it wasn’t like pass with flying colours, but hey, she PasseD!!! That’s realli good already...  Aniwae, Nick drovw his frens car over to my house n picked me up… We went over to his house n I cooked dinner for him… Poor thing… His parents r like in Australia now n there was all the frozen food etc. So I juz whipped up a few simple dishes for him… However, looking at him eat was realli like a good way to lose your appetite… He was like so ravenous n was gobbling all the food that kind… Sheesh… I was going like ‘Does the food taste realli that bad’? N he was like talking with his mouth full that he was realli famished n felt that the food tastes nice… 2nd Accomplishment of the day…=)  Oooo… Found a bottle of Tequila In the wine storage bar… Haha… Nick said that he din think that his parents would miss it so we opened the bottle n shared like half of it… Hmm… Had to take cab back though… I din want drink driving thingy… Well, my mum wasn’t home yet so lucky me… If not I was afraid that she will know that I drank…  Aniwae, had a great time with nick today… He was trying out so new stuff with his com n I juz lied on his bed to look at him… Hmm… Is it me Or do guys alwaize look exceptionally cute n handsome when they sare concentrating on something? Okie… it’s juz me… Hmm… That’s all for today I guess… N stop guessing Rachael… Yes, we did make out… N to Zu hao, Yes I m still a virgin… N to the Rayner… pls stop advertising my blog! Okie… that’s all folks! Cya soon.  Quote: Love starts with a smile, grows with a kiss, and ends with a tear. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-30 5:08 p.m.  Back home after emaths tutorial today… Wanted to pon so that I could go out with Nicholas… But decided that studies was a lot more impt. lar… Hmm… I know that my blog is realli very well read by lots of pple in my class but it kinda means no privacy anymore… Pple start to make fun of wad I write n all my feelings inside my blog have now bcome an entertainment to them… I realli have a good mind to lock my blog up… Perhaps I will…  Oh, Nicholas juz called… Erm… My mum’s coming home late today so I m going out for a ride with him… Glad I could still meet him today… Now I feel truly bad… Yea, I mean, I do like him… But I dun love him… I have nv come across that strong feeling towards any of my bfs’ b4… But someone else? Yea… Aniwae, by the looks of it, he likes me n all that… Guess it’s abt time to break up with him… I feel so sorry… Like I have been toying with his feelings… Playing him around…   I have alwaize been like the player… Standing around the edge of The Game of Love…An onlooker… n nv truly joining in bcoz I m afraid to get hurt… Everytime before the relationship gets too far, I pull back n put myself into reality… I dun wanna go too deep… I dun wanna get hurt… I wanna have the fun out of a relationship… Experience the great feeling of being loved but nv realli truly loving back in return…  Love is like quicksand…One step n u r in… If u have a fast reflex, u pull out fast… n u live… If not u get sucked down inside n will nv be able to come out… Even when u do… you will be with lots of injuries… n that takes a huge time to heal… perhaps even nv… Things r juz not wad they seem to be… Things r also nv as easy as they seem to be…  Quote: To love at all is to be vulnerable.  (I agree with that saying a lot… N I dun wanna be vulnerable… I dun wanna feel lost… I dun wanna lose myself… so the onli thing I can do is to pull back quickly…Nicholas…I’m realli sorry…)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-29 9:46 p.m.  Nicholas is so sweet… I forgot that we were supposed to meet at the Bedok Town Park thingy behind my house today n was late lar… After coming from school n all… However, knowing him, I knew that he will nv get angry n scold me so I decided to stroll over there… Guess wad I saw? He was sleeping at the park bench there… As in realli nodding off n all… So CUTE!!! Oh man… I din have the heart to wake him up but when I sat down, guess he felt my presence n all n he woke up… Who knew that a guy sleeping could look so Cute? Oh man…  He was oso realli sweet… Din say anithing abt me being late but the first thing he did was to kiss me… Aww… Can’t help it… He’s so sweet… Juz thinking of him makes me smile so uncontrollably… I decided to ask him to come to my house since he was so tired… He was like working overnight for some club or something… I can’t realli be bothered but it pains me to see him like so tired… Sigh…   Aniwae, that’s how he ended in my house n sleeping on my bed… I juz went to lie down on my bed… n it has like his smell on it… Man… so manly… I dun ever want that smell to go away… I bet See Ching can identify with that… Haha… Perhaps onli she will know wad I mean…=)Okie, so I m thinking of him n he juz called on the phone a while ago… Haha… I dunno how he does it but he seems to know that I wanted to talk to him n he called me… Speaking of which, Rachael would probably call me ‘da qian jin xiao jie’ again…   Hey, it’s not my fault that I dun like to call him right? Juz like to have him calling me… I dun like to be the one calling the guy… Weird huh~? N oso abt hating to have to push open the doors of places or wadeva for the guy…Nah… Will nv wanna do such stuff… Women r to be pampered u know?=)  Okie… Mum n Dad juz had a quarrel over I dunno wad… Gtg… Hope they dun start on me… Cya soon~!=) Ooo… Got quite a nice quote today… But I can’t realli relate to it bcoz I dun realli put in as much as my boyfriends’ in the relationship…  Quote: The magic of the first love is the ignorance that it can never end.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-29 5:21 p.m.  Whoa… Juz reached home… Came home from school quite a while ago lar…Hmm… Had to buy food for my dinner at the interchange… So sianed… Quite stoned now… Aniwae, quite boring day at school today lar… Oh… Erm, in the end the cranky phonecall was from Zu Hao with Cheryl n Rayner standing beside him… So like them… the ultra lame kind... Sheesh… Total RETARDS… Well, that’s not the impt. thing today lar… no bad thingy in school today… forgot to say though… yday talked to Michael online… That’s why in quite a good mood today…=) So long nv talk to him already… got miss him lar… But glad that he’s alright in life n all that…=)  Stupid chem. tcher… Wah… I realli curse her zu zong shi ba dai man… Hope she bu de hao si… Please lor… She realli dun like me juz bcoz I m the onli gal in class from combined science… She is a f***ing bitch lor… Wad the hell is her problem? She ask question then I juz say ‘Yes’ n she muz make a big fuss over it n be so damn freaking sarcastic towards me… Wah lao… Sorri to say, but she realli veri ‘san ba’ lor… Dotx… I realli think this is the reason why she is divorced…(Joanne say one) I mean, wad guy can stand her? Muz have been blind to marry her…   Yar… I agree that she is a good tcher lar… But come on lor… She doesn’t respect us as students at all… I mean, basic courtesy is to respect one another but apparently the word ‘Respect’ is not found in her dictionary… But she expects us to have that word in ours… Go Kiss Your Ass, Bitch!!! Alwaize for no reason come n bully me… Like xiao ying would say… GET A LIFE!!! I seriously think u need one… Bcoz u lag it! Freaking ccb… Goodness… Haven’ said that word for so long already… I m realli pissed now lor…  Nicholas is sleeping in my room now… Haha… He looks so ultra Cute!!! Hmm… Juz looking at him can make me feel much better… Stupid Ms Chan… Spoil my day onli… Lucky I got Nicholas… Or else, I assure u, tml Ms Chan’s car tire’s sure got no air one… n her car sure got scratch one… Last time I almost got around to scratching Mrs Goh’s car but someone… I can’t rmb who pulled me away… Haha… Dun pissed me off man…Bitch! I can’t assure u of wad I wun do bcoz when I m angry, I tend to do stuff that will make pple regret that they ever pissed me off b4…   Steph n Rachael will probably know that… Haha… Rmb abt that idiot guy who keep trying to pick us up last year? Rmb wad I did to his motorcycle? I know u all disapproved lar, but hey, Kor taught me all this one… I mean… A gal’s gotta have something to protect herself right?=) Kor taught me a lot of stuff lar… If pple would know they will be realli shocked at wad I do… Haha… Those who know, dun say lar… Let me still have an ok gal image kk? =)  Nicholas juz woke up… So cute!!! His hair now is like all tousled now… Awww… I m going to kiss him now… Hehe… Brb… ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Juz sent him off… He better go fast ar… I dun want my mum to come home n find out… I might as well juz go jump down a building right? Dotx…Yay~ Juz went to the fridge… My Dad opened a new bottle of wine… New Stock some more… Helped myself to it… Poured like a glassful… Hope he doesn’t find out that I drank it… Or I will die… Hehe… Going to bath now… Will blog later...  Quote: Life is like a beautiful melody, only the lyrics are messed up.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-28 9:25 p.m.  I juz realized that not a lot of pple blog everyday… And that means that it’s realli boring for me… Sheesh… Is everyone’s blog so boring? Hmm… does anione think that my blog is boring? I wonder… Aniwae, lots of things happened to me today… Went to my club at like 8+ this morning… I was in a rather good mood n jogged for about 4km… Sigh… got aching muscles now… But I dun regret… It’s like after jogging, u r too tired to think… n lately, I think I have been thinking a lot too much… Like I say… Sec4 is a realli stressful year… After all that sweating thingy, I went to Sauna and Jacuzzi… Quite a long time nv go alreadi so I couldn’t with stand the heat n came out after like 30min…Hehe…  Listening to a piano version of ‘chun zai’ now… I like it much better like that… with out pple singing… Haha… Eh… Went out with Cherylnn n Gerald in the afternoon… They had this English project thingy which required them to check out stuff on Singapore that happened on their birthday… It’s like a national thingy that every student has to do… I think… But Mrs. Tan nv ask us to do leh…   Hmm… Lucky us… Ate at Bk for lunch… Was rather boring… Din know why… Juz that nothing interesting lar...But lots of things have been going on in my mind lately… Like… Wad do I realli wanna be when I go up? Do I realli wanna juz waste my life away like that? If I dun, shouldn’t I be doing something productive?   Then, wad exactly is productive? To me it’s to get out there in the society n start working to earn money… then I would be able to realize my dream (which is to earn big bucks…) faster… I know that many pple will probably think that I have realli wistful thinking as studying n learning stuff is realli impt. n all that…I’m sorry… But I realli think that learning able stuff like Differentiation isn’t gonna help in my future job unless I plan to be a Tcher or Chemist or Mathematician… Which is far from wad I wanna be… Trust me…  Right now, I m realli like having a case of identity crisis… To be honest… My one goal in life is not to “Be happy” like most pple… It is to live each day to the fullest… So that I will nv regret… I hate regretting… Its juz one of the few things that I can’t tolerate… And I can definitely assure u that if I were to die right now… I would die with many regrets…   Many pple ask me… Why m I like ‘Shen Yinhe’ in Westside Story…( For those of u who watch the show, u would probably know that she realli loves money…) Well, let me tell u now… perhaps it is not about truly loving money… But abt having a sense of security… I may have a perfect family in pple’s eyes but that doesn’t mean that I m perfectly secure…Think abt it… Pple say that money is not the most impt. thing in the world… that there r much more impt. things that r worth more… like love… happiness… etc. I dun agree… Call me practical…   But I know wad money can do to a person with a happy family… Or a family that was once close could go to court over who gets more share of money… Money is a realli scary thing… And I rather control it than to have it control me… Pple tell me that money cannot buy anithing… Who says that? How much is pride worth? How much is a girl’s virginity worth? How much is happiness worth? I believe that with money… one can own the world… one can have power… one can have fame… one can have happiness… Although many pple tell me that money might not be able to help one’s emotional self-being…  But if a poor artist has talent, wad he lacks is money to put up an exibit to let everyone be able to see his talent… isn’t it? This guy who might have a poor self- esteem could well be a man of confidence the very next day… Perhaps pple have different perspective’s in their lives… but I firmly take my stand… At the very least, I know that if I had a million dollars… I would be a much happier person…While that’s all for today… Got lots of thoughts still n I juz can’t seem to write anymore…  Quote: Hope sees the invisible, feels the intangible and achieves the impossible.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-27 9:51 p.m.  Today was a rather slow day… but I liked it… First of all, we had the English comprehension test in the morning… It was about tarantula’s etc… But it quite easy… I mean, I might not score like very high but I m quite sure I will do better than the last one… which FYI is like 24/50… failed by one mark…  After the test, we were supposed to have Flag Day… But thanx to helping out to paint Street Soccer Court in our school, I had enough CIP hours alreadi… about 20+ n that’s a lot, so I opted not to go…   Instead, went out with Cherylnn from 4A n we went to eat Mac’s for breakfast… I had hot cakes while she had Mcmuffin meal… It was rather nice talking to her lar… I mean, I can relate to her n stuff n she is realli friendly n all… But, she is like seriously a Women’s Rights kinda gal… As in she is realli a true blue Feminist kinda gal… Know wad I mean? I mean, I can relate n understand sometimes that guys r juz so total retards n should be abolished from the world etc… but then again, its juz sometimes…  After breakfast we went to see her Skincare doctor… I mean, I know I m slow but I seriously din like realli realized that her skin condition has Realli realli improved a lot thanx to the medicine that the doctor gave to her… He is one helluva docter man… Cheryl introduced Cherylnn to him n one can realli see the before n after results… Hmm… I went home after that n slept for quite a while before waking up to do my work… Sounds like a slow n bboring day but it felt rather peaceful...  Oooo… I forgot to mention the ‘weird’ n ‘creepy’ phone call that I got in the afternoon… Haha…I was realli amused at all…To be honest, I wasn’t the least bit scared… I mean, come on… It was so fake…The person was like so pathetic…He even like asked for me before he talked in that kind of rough, hoarse, and throaty voice… I swear I tried to keep a straight face but I couldn’t help it…   Juz keep giggling n all… Obviously the person thought he was realli cool n all, speaking in that kind of alienly n retard language… I realli felt true pity for a person wasting time to do this… Wad do u expect? That I will be pertrified n scared out of my nerves? Oh please… to that person who did it, Grow Up… I m sure your parents r ashamed by you…  After the phone call, I tried to think of who would be that lame to do it n guess wad? The onli two pple I was thinking of was Yuen Hoi n Rayner… I know there was more possibilty on Yuen Hoi n all that but I did remember reading Cheryl’s blog n seeing that when they were bored they played prank calls on pple… So, Rayner if u guys r the ones that did it, I have serioulsy an advice for u… Dun be a Retard… There r too many pple in the world who r alreadi like that so stop acting like one to degrade yourself…=)  Another thing is I was thinking of changing relocating my blog from here to Blogspot… It’s not bcoz lots of my other frens use blogspot but bcoz diaryland’s html stuff is realli very n I mean Very ma fan… as in troublsome… So… I guess, when I have the time, I will be shifting over to Blogspot… Pple who are reading this, pls look up for more updates to see when I will be relocating…=)  Quote:Every life has a story. And every story is a life.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-26 8:41 p.m.  Hmm… nothing special today… going to do my literature later n hand in tmr no matter wad… Hope Ms Ng doesn’t kill me…hehe… Eh… today zhimin got debate… haiz din go… now I wish I went… But then again, tmr got English compre test… So, today better sleep early… Oh… I remember wad I wanna say… I was realli quite pissed today leh… that stupid Ms Chan scold me that I was sleeping again!   Darn her lor… I was nice enough to like open my eyes during her entire lesson when I was like freaking tired n all that… I mean, I realli tried lor… That is wad pisses off… She juz accused me of closing my eyelids… What the hell lar… Go Kiss your Ass Ms Chan…!!!  Okie… i dun wanna talk about her animore… makes me more angry… I juz uploaded a poem that I wrote… It’s when I broke up with Derrick (which for your information is my 3rd bf)…   Wad the hell lar... I can't put the poem into stanzas bcoz this diaryland juz refuses to co-operate... I m so considering to go n use blodspot or blogdrive... Arghh... Sorry to those who wanted to see the poem... I dun wanna put it up coz of this blog's html...  Quote:Laugh and the world laughs with you. Cry and you cry with your girlfriends.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-26 5:42 p.m.  Yay~! Today is Friday… Hmm… Finally the end of the week is here… Wah… I sound so glad… Well, I realli am… It’s juz that after the holidays, I get tired very easily after being used to the slacking everyday… Ooo… Right now, I m supposed to be like at the SSS thingy but I pon~… haha… According to Constance (one of my frens) she say that she oso got SSS but she din wanna go coz she was waiting for someone else n so both of us nv go… Seriously, I dun mind studying… It’s juz that I dun wanna be under someone else’s eagle eye… Constance got went to check n she said onli like 6 pple went for the SSS… Aniwae, she decided to stay in school to study n wait for her fren at the same time lar…  Hmm… I muz remember to write the letter of excuse later… Gonna be a naughty n forge my mum’s signature… tmr gonna go find (Mr Chan) who is the tcher in charge n talk to him… If he wants like a letter than I will pass it to him… If not, well, who cares? Nicholas juz called… Aiyo… no biggie lar… he was saying I m such a naughty gal etc. Well, I certainly DUN care!!! It’s not as if I can’t study on my own n needs to be supervised right? I mean, to be honest, my grades have improved since sec3… My average has alwaize been like 50.5, 51.5 but now is up to 54.8 n my L1R5 has gone from 27 to 20… that’s a lot ok…  Going to bath now… bbl…=)  Quote: You can only go as far as you push.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-25 5:43 p.m.  Today was a fun day… Hmm… Yar, I know that there were two tests today but it’s like right after the tests, my entire body juz slackens… hehe… so I m relaxing at home right now…=) First of all, I felt that the chemistry test was rather hard even though it was a lot easier than the last one… Hope I can at least pass…=P The amaths test was rather ok too lar… Hehe… I know I very bad but Gerald got tell me some of the questions b4 the test…   However, I oso dun realli understand wad he was writing… my last question I think I was wrong… like that lose about 6 marks… but no matter wad, I hope that I can pass lar… this time I realli tried my best n studied a lot for it… onli slept for 2hrs yday… surprisingly, I din realli feel that tired in school lar, but I m definitely gonna sleep early today…  Eh, Mrs. Lim our maths tcher oso din cum today so Mr Chan came to baby-sit us… Oh… here’s the fun part… Hehe… the tcher I juz cursed yday? Ms Chan? Well… she totally lost her voice today…=)It was so bad that she had to type on her labtop to ‘talk’ to us… haha… good 4 her… I hope that she will nv get her voice back… who ask her in class alwaize like to talk so loudly n yell at us… Yea man… finally get my revenge…  Going to bath now… be back later! ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Me n Yin Wen went home tgt again today… Hehe… Met Issac n Yuen Hoi n Tim. Gan at Macs… Accidentally hit Yuen Hoi’s dick with the swing of my arm…Haha… erm… I realli din do it on purpose… realli!!! C’mon… I m SO not deprived… I mean, according to Steph’s words “You can have sex with Nicholas alreadi u know?” Yea… I know steph… But I dun want him to be charged with having sex with a minor… Besides, I m not that desperate lar… Pls… I mean, I totally understand that everyone gets horny in a while but not like I must have it on the spot kinda thingy… Nah… Juz hasn’t happened to me yet…=)   Got to go check out stuff for my elit hw lar… Supposed to do on responses to A Poison Tree by William Blake… Sheesh… I find it ok lar… But all in all, I dun like to depict poems… I mean, they r u to appreciate n understand but not to like analyse n pore over every word in it… It’s like then the meaning of the poem isn’t there animore you know wad I mean? Kinda like if a person turely wants to understand wad it means, let that person read it over n over again or look up for notes n guidelines to understand it but not like the way we r using poems in elit now… it juz feels weird u know wad I mean?  Yay~ Tonight got American Idol again… Can watch tv…=) Hmm… Wad else is there to say huh~ There was this realli interesting thingy I wanna say leh…Oh… Haha… Yep… In chinese class today, our tcher was commenting that Rayner’s work that he hands in is alwaize in seaweed sheds… Haha… Juz thinking of it makes me smile… Dunno why but juz find it realli funny… Haha… *Grinz* Oh, n another thing is I have decided to add special features in my blog… I have decided to add a quote everytime I end an entry…It can be about my life or anithing that has juz happened or juz on anithing in the world… Oh, n to those who have requested to see my poems online, well, I thought about it n have come to a decision.Yes…I will kindly update poems that I write to my blog…=)  Another thing is I m feeling rather upset with myself now…. I wanna change my layout of my blog… I do like it but I think there can be some nice changes to it to make it better… Like I would prefer to have the links n miscellaneous stuff on the left side of my blog… Hmm… hope I see Tafiq online later… can make him do it for me… And… I wanna change the font of my blog… It looks very plain n sianed… I want something more unique!!! I juz can’t stand having my blog like the total same as every other person’s blog… Oh, phone’s ringing... brb!  That was nicholas… He is so lame… wanted to meet me after school tmr… Haha… poor guy! I have that stupid SSS…erm which stands for Supervised-Self-Study thingy tmr… Darn… I juz can totally predict my social life going down the drain… But, I muz agree that with the time, I m sure that I can like study some realli useful stuff for my O’s if I realli put myself to it…=)  K… guess that’s all for the day… Oh, n my mom has been in realli weird moods lately… She seems to be totally ok n suddenly the next minute she snaps at me for no particular reason or her face juz changes into that ‘I’m in a sour mood’ kinda thingy… Sheesh… Oh well, gtg for now… cya later!  Quote: You come to love not by finding the perfect person, but by seeing the imperfect person perfectly... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-24 10:01 p.m.  Okie… I m like ultra stress now… guess why? Bcoz of tests lar… wad else? Aiyo… I haven’t studied finish chem yet n I seriously do not wanna fail… I dun wanna fail no matter wad… n I realli dun wanna cheat too… How? Onli resort? Study lar… Sheesh… but I think I truly need to take a break… I have a terrible migraine, a bad stomache , cranky cramps n had diarhoea juz now… this alwaize happens when I m stressed.. n that totally sux!   Rayner juz sent me a totally cute picture of cloud… he looked realli handsome… I think I m falling for him… How? I dun wanna be unfaithful to nicholas… *sobz* I m now under the spell of cloud’s charms… hehe… being lame… gotta relieve my stress… yea… gonna pia~ later tonight… which reminds me I haven’t done anithing for my amaths test yet… Great! Juz Great!!! Oh no… I m like so DEAD!!! Better go now…till next time…cya soon~
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-24 3:34 p.m  Okie… so I juz came home from school… Hmmm… think I m quite early… Lucky dun have chem tutorial… need the time to study for the chem n amaths test tmr… Todae was a rather boring day lar… except for chem tutorial… wah… I was realli fuming with ms chan lor… I mean, juz bcoz I m the onli combined sciece student in class doesn’t mean she can alwaize pick on me… yar… I admit, so I m not smart or able to understand the Qualitative Analysis well… but that doesn’t mean that she can use that to pick with me right?   I mean… it’s like out of all the students who have questions in class or needs help wadeva, she decided to stand next to me n point out everything that she is not happy about…she was going like: Do u even understand wad u r doing? No… this is Wrong… Which solution is this? You messed up the answers… Hello! I din mess up the answers ok… the lab technician label the solutions wrongly lar bitch! Grrrrr… I juz can’t wait to box her!  Ok lar… that will be all… I gtg n study first… will be back at abt 9+ to finish this entry… ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Oh my god… I m like so totally embarrassed kinda thingy… Sheesh… I m like at Stephanie’s house now bcoz Aaron was on the way there n he came to pick me up in his car (Aaron is steph’s bf FYI)… Haha… realli hot n all that so I went to take a bath at steph’s house… Hmm… And guess wad? I din take any of her clothes in to change… so I was like wrapped in the bath towel b4 I came out of the bathroom… n her door was like juz closed not lock… I mean the door to her room lar… N guess wad? Aaron juz burst into the room like that…   Oh my God… for all the money in the world din prepare me for the ultimate shock… luckily the bath towel was like totally ok n din drop or I swear I will nv go out of my house for the rest of my life… Aaron was a totally decent guy… he juz like opened his mouth n gaped at me but hurriedly turned around… haha… realli nice guy… luckily, steph’s not angry with me… but she was so amused that she laughed till she cried… juz great!   But she’s realli nice… she promised not to tell anione… Haha… but it’s totally ok with me… Hey, I m not called open for nothing… Hmm… now that this is up on my blog, lots of pple r gonna know but hey, like I say, I m totally ok with it…I mean, who in the world will be totally ok with talking about sex for about 3hrs plus at Macs? Juz me, Gerald n See ching… Haha… n we scared about the 2 grps of customers who sat beside us when we were talking… I wun tell u aboput wad we talked about…  *Grinz* It’s juz too explict! But I will be nice to say it’s realli juz all about our sexual experiences n stuff… How to get on high etc. Hehe… Explict enough right? Muahahaha… (evil laughter) Aniwae, lately haven’t realli been able to sit down n talk to them about stuff n that totally sux… It’s like no one is there to listen n everything is bottled up inside u… Aww… Well, hope all of us can be free on one nday n go out tgt… well, Aaron juz came into the room… (I m currently in Steph’s room)… better go… cya… 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-23 9:18 p.m.  So… I juz studied for my chem test on Thursday juz now… Whoa… the weather at my house here realli sucked juz now… it was blazing hot n then it rained realli heavily… lucky no clothes or else mummy will be in a even bad mood bcoz the clothes wun be dry etc. Sigh…But luckily now the weather is a lot better… Nice smoothing wind… Hmm~… Okie… Aniwae today was a rather eventful day if u would consider the fun time learning about sexual reproduction in Bio class… Hehe…  Although we din have my favourite lesson which is chinese…Why is that my favourite lesson? Gee… I juz like being able to talk to pple who r fun n they all sit like around me… Yay… hehe… aniwae, erm… We learnt about the female body parts today n sexual intercourse where it will produce twins… I think it’s realli amazing to have a twin bcoz it’s like one in a million chance kinda thingy… Whoa… sometimes I kinda envy Zhi lin n Zhi nin or like Joanne n Jeannette…It’s totally cool coz like no matter wad u do u know u alwaize have somebody to fall back on… somebody who understands...  Then, we oso learnt about the menstral cycle… Eww… that’s realli juz like the worst part of being a gal… the painful torment u have to go through everytime of the month… Speaking of which, I was talking to see ching about it in e.lit class today… hehe… guess who started it? Sheila I think… Aniwae, me n ching were talking about the blobs of red stuff that look like blood that was discharged sometimes but not everytime during menstration… n she asked me if it was a blood clot but I told her it was juz our uterus lining… hehe… den Ms Ng (our elit tcher) came along n ask us wad we were talking about n when we told her, she sorta like gave a blank n ‘okie…’ face n walked away in a hurry… Oh well, guess she juz isn’t that open with sexuality… or perhaps she is juz reserved… I think it’s the latter… hehe…  Oh… n I asked ching if she was regular yet n she said she was… well… I m still rather happy with my own menstral cycle coz it’s still not regular… meaning that it can come once in 2-3 mths… haha… Meaning that I dun have to experience that terrible pain every month… But the bad side is that u nv know when it will come n sometimes it realli comes at a realli n I emphasize Realli bad time… Oh well… guess there is the perks n the unperks…  Eh… wad else did I wanna say huh~… Darn can’t remember…Oh… I rmb now… we ran the 2.4 again today… I did ok lar… better than last time… ran about 17+ min… I know I can do much better but I was realli tired n lazy to run real well n well, I juz ran n have fun n yell at whoever I see to ‘jia you’… So… realli wasn’t serious… Erm… the real final run is like next week kinda thingy… I think I should go n train… than can run erm like 13-14+ min… haha… hope so lar… Hmm… I dun think there is anithing else interesting todae… so signing off~ …cya soon!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-22 8:45 p.m.  Okie… so much things happened betwn me n nicholas… Hmm… apparently, one of rachael’s frens know one of nicholas frens… n they had a photo of him n another gal in the picture… The thing was if it was juz a normal picture, I realli wouldn’t mind at all but the bad part was it was abvious that there was something going on betwn them… I mean, they were realli close n standing next to each other his hand was behind her back kinda thing… I m rather pissed after seeing the photo… and it was a recent taken photo… the date was there!   I dunno wad to do now… haven’t talked to him in a while but he called me juz now… I din ask him about the photo but he was realli glad that I m willing to talk to him n all that… Wonder if I should be nice n juz forgive him…  I know that I keep saying I forgive him alreadi but everytime I think of him n all that… I juz think about wad happened (pls refer to previous entry) n even though in my heart I know I forgive him, I juz can’t bring myself to realli like talk to him properly… Haiz… I dunno lar… But juz now I talked to him, he wanted me to go out with him this Friday or Saturday… I told him I had to check my schedule… Hehe… even though I had nothing on on both days… make him think like I m realli unavailable kind… mean hor?=)  Ooo… I forgot to say… my mom is down with flu due to stressing too much over the Ah Bian matter… okie, maybe not real flu but she seems realli sick n lethagic lar… Haiz… Ah Bian can realli wreak havoc man… Btw, wad hw is there today? None I hope… Hmm… Oh, n I m so PROUD of myself… my layout for this blog had many changes that I wanted to make as the font of the words were either too big or too small… n the colours of the background etc. is all changed by me!   The original template design which is shown at my layout... had rather weird background colours like purple for background n white words… Eww… But I like the design n the picture of the princess… so I changed the rest all by myself… cool huh~?  Why m I so proud of myself? Well… considering I m a gal who knows absolutely nothing about HTML… n all that… I m rather surprised that I managed to figure out the weird codes n change the code colours n font size etc. Yea man… I rock! =P
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-22 4:48 p.m.  Today is the first day of school after the March holidays… nothing much happened lar… but I got to comment on something… eh… got new pple from the Higher Chinese class cum to our Express class… to be honest? To be honest, I dun realli mind that much… but it’s like the entire class becomes bigger n the tcher changes to be stricter to control the class mar… n I can’t stand it lar… It’s like she kinda change from a fun tcher to a strict tcher… not interesting anymore… I know I shouldn’t be so mean but in my heart I can’t help but blame those pple… But nvm… I know the feelings will go away in a while…=)  Haha… finally finished my Chinese compo today in school n studied finish for my Chinese test in the morning… But… I m rather upset… I din know 3 Chinese words n 1 ‘zhao ju’… sobz… hope I still manage to get 40 n above lar… like that will get 80+ for overall…  Hmm… juz looked at the newspapers juz now… saw that in the Prime News headlines: Taiwan on the Brink of Political Crisis… I know there has been riots n all that over there… Of coz this will happen… this is wad will happen when stupid Ah Bian becomes the President… He realli doesn’t deserve to be the President lar… Aniwae, enough talk about that… I m still rather unhappy about Ah Bian winning so I dun wanna talk about it…  Eh… there is a chem. test coming up in a few days time on Thursday… common test… meaning that it is rather impt. haven’t studied for it… I think will pia for it later… Hmm… I oso haven’t done my e.lit hw… Opps… hope can finish all of it later too… Later tonight got America’s Top Model… Yay~ like the show… there is much bitching involved… realli interesting…   Oh, n speaking of chemistry… got back my last test… Sigh… I failed… realli upset about failing… din think I would lar… got 12/25… failed by half a mark… I felt that the test was rather easy… but lots of small careless mistakes actually made me lost lots of marks when added together… Guess I will have to study like mad to pass the coming test… Okie… realli tired… Cya later… Still got stuff that happened to me juz a while ago… u wun believe it but it’s realli interesting! =P
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-21 7:56 p.m.  Sheesh… And yes… it’s like the last day of school… Sobz… I will miss being lazy n slacking around etc. Aniwae… enough of all that, my mom is still freaking pissed over the Taiwan elections thingy… Oh man… the house is like a dark cloud… n a storm is about to brew… Because my other relatives in Taiwan… namely: my aunties’ n uncle (my mom’s side)… n oso my mummy’s frens… well… most of my relatives such as my Da Yi… n Xue Zhen Ah Yi… n etc. they r all Ah Bian pai… aka… Ah Bian supporters… which oso means they r glad / overjoyed / ultra happy that Ah Bian won lar…Of coz my mom doesn’t wanna call n talk to them… who would wanna share their joy...joy that a lousy leader… A conniving sly jerk is the President???  Like I say, wad kinda crap is that? I totally repeat… Only intellectual pple know that Ah Bian sux n should not be the President… Lousy crap man… only pple who have no guts no confidence in himself will go n do such a sympathy stunt to get sympathy votes by the stupid aunties n those farmers… pple who live in the rural area, the villagers… those who nv study… go n give their sympathy votes to this stupid Ah Bian… Haiz… I know complaining wun help but at least the onli thing I can do is complain… too bad I m a Singaporean not Taiwanese… cant go back n vote n help Lian Chan… Haiz…  Aniwae… today is the last day of the March holidays n to be honest… I m realli upset… din realli enjoy my holidays… din finish my homework yet… feels like I did nothing… din even have proper fun… no chalets… no partying… all wasted… I m in an ultra bad mood now… Haiz… My mom n dad r watching A Bug’s life on tv now… hope mummy’s mood gets better… Haiz… so irritating… I haven’t’ done my Chinese compo yet… gonna pia for it later… haven’t studied for my Chinese test too… n my maths hw too… Wad the hell lar…  Btw… some pple r asking me wad happened to me n Nicholas… go read my previous entry please… I dun wanna recount wad happened again… I said I forgive him… yea… I do… I realli do… juz that I dun wanna talk to him n all that yet… juz thinking of him makes me upset again… kinda like still rather angry lar… but not that pissed anymore… Opps… forgot to say… I was so pissed yday that I talked to my kor… eh… the online one… I haven’t even met him b4 n I was basically in a bad mood n kinda yelled at him… you know… well, sorry for that…   I realli din mean it… but than… sorry again… Haiz… guess that’s about it… I wanna go watch the show now… i might go n watch the malaysian elections later... but not so interested lar...If I got time, will come back to update my blog but if not… I might not be able to come on everyday every night bcoz school is starting n I m sure that I wun have the time…so cya soon… I hope…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-20 10:39 p.m.  Freaking pissed… Ah Bian actually won the Taiwan election… It was DAMN foul play man!!! In case you dunno, i m partially Taiwanese… my mum’s a Taiwanese so my family realli tunes in to all news about Taiwan… I m so pissed now… Wad kinda crap is that? So many pple predicted that Lian Chan will win this year n bcoz that stupid sly, conniving, Bastard Ah Bian… went to get someone to shoot him n make himself look pitiful to get sympathy votes from all those Ah So n Auntie’s in Taiwan… Lian Chan lost… Just GREAT… Act pitiful to get those sympathy votes… Sheesh… Get a life… I mean, I can bet bcoz Ah Bian oso knows that there is a huge possibility that Lian Chan will win this year that’s why he staged an act like that...  I totally can’t believe it… I mean, the entire stage play by Ah Bian was so damn FAKE!!! I mean… C’mon… At that kinda situation… there was so many bodyguards… n he had to get shot… oso, it was like a graze past his stomach… I mean, we r not stupid enough to get bluffed… How come the bullet juz nicely grazed his stomach n not go through his stomach? What kinda lousy stage play is that? At least act more real lar…  My mom’s in a ultra bad mood bcoz of it… She got high blood pressure n now her pressure goes even higher up… Those stupid pple who voted for Ah Bian in Taiwan… Stupid no brain pple… Do u know that if u vote for him… the economic in Taiwan will be getting worst n worst? Oh man… I so wanna curse him!!!   Now my house is in a chaos… mummy’s totally in a bad mood n my entire family has that dead mood surrounding all of us… Arghhhh… I hate Ah Bian!!! My mommy’s realli worried too… coz she works at the Taiwan embassy in Singapore… n there might be like a chance she will get fired… due to all those very chim-o-fied reasons… Sigh… all those stupid ah so’s n auntie’s juz played right into Ah Bian’s hands man… I m so darn Upset!!! Realli realli bad mood now!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-19 2:02 p.m.  Juz another day at home… haven’t been going out lately… I know I have been telling pple that I m fully booked the entire week kinda thing? But… to be honest, I juz want to spent time with myself… I want to be alone… weird isn’t it? Lots of pple in the world hates to be alone… they feel lonely… but to be honest, I like the feeling of being alone… n I realli dun mind it…   I know some pple who dun mind it but would prefer to be with company than to be alone… but to me, I muz alwaize have this alone time with myself… kinda like a special time I set aside for myself… Yea… being alone is totally ok with me… juz dun overdose me with it… hehe… It’s like a medicine… heals the wound that pple inflict on me or perhaps the wounds that r self-inflicted… I dunno but the alone time that I have? Alwaize makes me grow stronger…=)  Hmmm… listening to BoA’s cd again… I realli like her song “Song with no name” n of coz “Love & Honesty”… Yea… I like the fast songs too… but not realli in the mood now… I dunno wad’s wrong with me… I haven’t realli been in the mood for anything lately… n I juz keep staying at home staring into space… sleeping… pigging out… watching Jap VCD’s… Sheesh… wad the hell is wrong with me?   I think I m suffering from a bad case of identity crisis… Anyway… call mommy juz now… she was having lunch hour… seems that she is feeling much better… Haiz… I better go n do my Chinese compo now… Opps… haven’t studied my Chemistry test chapters yet… Better go… cya later! =)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-18 9:13 p.m.  Okie… so I had a realli bad day today… I juz totally feel like I have been wasting my holidays away… I haven’t realli been studying although I know I should n everything juz seems to be wrong… It’s a case of BHD (bad hair day) n got up from the wrong side of the bed thingy… I m having a bad bad case of depression… Sigh… Haiz… can’t help it… it’s a reflex action… I keep sighing even my mom is scolding me… Speaking of which… I m realli worried abt her… She is getting old n all that n her arm at the elbow there is alwaize aching n giving her problems…It’s so bad that she has to take painkillers everyday… Sigh…I wish she will truly get better…  I keep looking at my desk n stuff n think… I should clean up pack my things neatly…After all, I m quite a neat freak thanks to my mom…I inherited her genes… but I juz keep slacking n slacking… n I tell myself I should study but keep putting it off too… I m such a procrastinator… It totally sux! I haven’t touch my Chinese which I should have bcoz I have a test on it the coming Monday… I haven’t studied for my chem. When I have a test on it next week too… Sheesh… What the hell… I realli dunno wad’s wrong with me… Arghhh… I totally hate myself…  N I told myself that I shouldn’t be so nice n forgive Nicholas so easily? But… I finally picked up his call n I gave in to his pleas… Oh man… I m such a soft-hearted person… but I dunno… I can be such a bitch n a cruel n hard-hearted person at other times… see? Split personality… One side of me wants this n the other side… that… Sheesh… I m like alwaize engaging in a war with myself all the time… It totally sux! It’s like so Duh~! Never mind… losing track of all the things I m saying now too… dunno wad’s wrong with me… I m like Gerald say… totally Bi-polar… so, dun bother me… let me wallow in self-pity n so on…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-18 1:04 p.m.  Hmm… I quarreled with Nicholas today… again… Should I start with the entire story? Yep, I guess so… okie, here goes: We were kinda happy juz talking crap n making fun of each other… then he wanted to make out n I was kinda agreeable… I mean, it was in the mood… but Hey, I m not the kinda of gal which wants to have a bf or juz go out with him with the intention of getting laid ok… it was juz in the mood at the moment n I juz let him kiss me… but as things alwaize go, he was HOT, n I mean real hot… he realli advanced too fast n we were on his couch so he was realli rough with me n all that… Sigh… of coz I told him to stop n slow down etc. n of coz he din… so I sorta pushed him on the floor n slapped him…   Hey… it’s not my fault… I din wanna slap him… he din respect me, so wad can I do??? A gal’s gotta protect herself… or no one would help her even if she screams ‘Help!’… it’s like a reflex action… trust me gals… I learnt this the hard way… but wait! There’s more… Apparently, Nic was angry… n wad can I say? I mean, we r all mature adults… Opps! For those who dunno… Nicholas is currently my boyfriend or as other pple might say, stead… and while he is like the 4th guy in my life although I feel that for the rest of my ex… we are not like couples…   I mean, including Nicholas… luckily he doesn’t know I have a blog or else I swear he would strangle me…hehe… Aniwae, back to where I was, I alwaize treat this guy’s in my life abit more den my normal guy frens but never like totally past the frens’s line… it’s sorta like past the frens line but never towards the boyfren line… it’s like more than a fren but no more then a boyfren… u get wad I mean? Sheesh… nvm… If u get it, u do but if u dun then u dun… there’s no point explaining…  So, back to wad happened… He was angry of course… that I slapped him n all that n guess wad he told me? He called me a slut n whore n said that it’s not the first time I serviced a guy… n y should I stop him from continuing etc… Whoa… after listening to him, I got so pissed… I was fuming mad… n trust me, u wun wanna cross my paths when I m angry… I mean, Hello… that’s sorta like a common knowledge… n I kinda juz stared him down… but I bet if u were there, u would be able to see the fire burning in my eyes… n dun mistake it as passion, bcoz it most certainly is not… so, guess wad I did other then stare him down?   NOTHING… haha… u should have been there… he was shocked n embarrassed n realli like din know wad to do… but I juz left… I walked out of his room n house juz like that… Cool huh~? Yea… n Isabel strikes… n she Scores!!!   Now? He’s been calling me for the past few hours so I hung up the phone…=) Hmm… apparently I think he heard that I was realli open from my frens n perhaps he thought that I did it with my ex… the 3rd guy… Derrick… but hey, Derrick is such a gentleman… he wun force anything on me not like Nicholas… Sheesh… thinking of it now juz makes me in a ultra bad mood… Sorry… that’s why I din write in my blog yesterday… but I wun care… y should I let this scum bother me n affect my life?   To be honest, I m glad he is begging me now… the feeling is realli great… haha… n well, of coz I wun break up with him due to such small reasons… y give him a reason to hate me? When I realli break-up with him… I would do it in such a way that it totally breaks his heart… in such a way that he will nv forget me for the rest of his life…I want him to feel sorta like ‘shen bu ru si’… how do u say that in English? Eh… I dunno… go ask someone if u dun understand wad I m saying…  Hehe… so right now, I m still deciding on when I should forgive Nicholas… soon I think… how about tomorrow? Okie… tomorrow is a good day… well, I gtg now… cya later…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-16 7:04 pm  Today was juz another normal day… Hmmm… but I went to watch Dirty Dancing 2 with Mabel… Oh man… it was such a great show it can’t be anything better… the dancing n moves were realli good too… The bad part was the ending lar… I can’t stand it that the two main leads couldn’t be tgt… Hmm… I like happy endings… so if they could be tgt, the show would have been perfect… the funny thing was there were onli 5 pple in the entire cinema… I realli wonder how they earn but I guess it was a little early as we watched at 12.45… n it was at Century Square… I like the seats there better then the Tampines Mall one… Shaw Organization is much better Golden Village… Oh, n the popcorn n stuff… I felt that it was realli cheap… Me n Mabel shared a popcorn n drink Large combo n it was like $5.50 split into two…that’s like $2 plus each… Whoa… Dirt cheap…  The show was realli mostly about dancing… kinda like the Latin… Salsa kind… very sexy n very very sensual… I juz loved it… Hmm… maybe I should get someone to buy me the VCD… Yea… Would love to watch the show again… It was definitely worth it… Unlike the cat in the hat… but luckily that show was a treat from yuen hoi or else I would have been so pissed, I wouldn’t wanna go n watch this show… Hey… a girl’s gotta save mar… hehe… Oh man… now I can’t stop thinking about the dance moves now… realli very good… Hmm… wish I had the time n money to take up dancing like that… From young, I alwaize love dancing n grooving n singing n acting n all that… I confess… I m a true-blue bathroom singer… hehe… wad’s wrong with that? I think it’s realli cool… I m very sure I’m not the onli person who sings in the bathroom in this world… right?  Aniwae, I realli wish I had the money to enroll into such dance classes… oh well, maybe when I grow up then… Sigh… see? Money is such an impt. factor… If I had a huge load of money now, I would seriously cut classes n use the money to do wadever I want… I mean, my parents r alwaize nagging at me to get good grades bcoz of money… They go like if I dun study… I wun be able to do well in the future bcoz no one would want to hire me n I wun be able to live on my own blar blar n they dun want to still have to support me when they r old… bcoz it should be the other way round but they know that with my meager ‘salary’ (if I m able to get a job that is…)   I wun even have enough for myself so they juz hope that I can get good grades… get an okie job… earn abit of money n live with it… they dun expect me to support them… they juz dun want to support me anymore…(I bet lots of u r nodding your head to wad I say now… to those who agree… give me a five man… no, make that ten!)So, it all boils down to money… right? If I had the money… I can slash some of it somewhere n use the rest now… to do stuff that I like… so to me… money is real impt. n that is partly the reason why I love money so much… to those who know me well would know that I love money… Well, there u have it… that’s the reason…  Okie… I juz went to cook rice for dinner later… I m so dead… promised to cook rice for mummy before she comes home n I forgot… hope she comes home later or else if she is back n the rice isn’t ok, I m so dead…Hurry up rice…Okie, back to where I was… eh, basically I juz wanna say I think Dirty Dancing was a great show… n I seemed to have crap this much… haiz… oh well… waiting n waiting n waiting… rice, please hurry up… dun let me get scolded by mummy…   YAY! It’s done.. okie, mom coming back soon… think I better go now… see ya tmr…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-16 12:15p.m.  Oh… sheesh… my bdae is 14th of may n already got pple asking me to hurry list out my wishes… hmm… let’s see… I think it’s rather mean to tell pple to go buy wad I want but hey, since u want to know… well, here goes…  To those who know… I realli want the Westside story 3rd n 4th album… din have enough money to go buy so cant watch finish the show… sobz… Oooo…. N I know I have been complaining like crazy… but I have realli set my eyes on that pink Dior bag… Oh man… It’s so pretty…It’s like the ultimate bag that I realli want… even the Prada bags that I liked a lot last time r nothing compared to it… Hehe… Last time Cheryl keep saying she wanted the erm… wad bag was it?   Let’s see… Louis Vuitton bag… yep… that was the one… the white one with lots of nice LV words on it… cool man… but I seriously like the pink Dior one more… hehe… Hmm… Oooo n I welcome make-up… all kinds of make-up… of coz I only like some brands… that day Rachael asked me… MAC or Bloom would be fine… Za is rather nice too but I like Dirty n Wet & Wild n Red Earth… Sigh… if onli I had money… hehe… I know… I totally sound like a bimbo but hey… girls u dun ‘ai mei’ r not girls okie… so, I m juz a typical normal gal! =P  I think clothes r fine so stop asking me wad clothes I like coz well… I dun realli like pple to give me clothes as a bdae present lar… I juz find it weird… Although if u realli think u have nothing to give me den fine I accept 37 degree clothes… or clothes from Topshop or Miss Selfridge… other then that… I personally suggest u dun buy for me coz I scared if I dun like it then I wun wear it for a lot of times so I dun wanna waste your money okie? Then… accessories r totally fine too… I m a rather girly person so I like necklaces n bracelets… preferably necklaces lar… Oooo… which reminds me… I so wanna kill me my mom… she juz wun allow me to go pierce my ears… darn… so PLEASE dun give me ear rings… I dun have ear holes to put them in… sobz… Sigh… wad else did u guys ask huh~?  Eh… school bags izzit? Hmm… for school bags, I like 37 degrees one… but better dun buy me school bags without asking me coz the same goes for clothes… I got rather unique tastes n if I dun like it I wun use it… Eh… I think that’s all right? Well, I gtg now… going to watch Dirty Dancing with Mabel later… cya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-15 9:09 p.m.  Sheesh… today is the 3rd day of holidays… I know I should be studying n all that given my results as a sec4er… sigh… However… I must emphasize on the however…hehe, I m here updating my blog… lousy day today too…I juz feel like I haven’t really done anything fulfilling today… like there is something I wanna do… to perk me up I guess? Okie… this is really hard to explain but if u understand than u do… if u dun den u dun…right now my life is rather uneventful… (Thank heavens)   I mean, hey no offense but if its supposed to be eventful, make it more easy for me to live… not like a few weeks back where I keep losing my stuff n being extra ultra unlucky… sheesh… now that was bad!!! Realli BAD!   Aniwae, I was thinking of like making a planner to kinda like plan on wad I should study n do in the holidays… However, see, I m emphasizing on the however again… I have to plan to write wad I should study in the planner n that takes brains n of coz, I m totally slacking here now… so I m nowhere to finishing my planner… sheesh… do u get wad I m saying? I m kinda lost with my words too… dun worry I wun blame u if u call me weird…   Hey… it’s one of my middle names… of coz the champion word is unpredictable… den cums weird n perhaps bimbotic n den bitchy… sheesh… all in all, its kinda taxing for pple who want to truly know me unless I give info… so hey… look at my diary… its supposed to portray ones inner erm… self right? Like… inner being kinda thing… u get wad I mean? =) sure do hope so… opps… digressing… Okie back to topic...  Sec 4… haiz… of coz it’s tiring… it’s the year when u feel more alive… wanna party more… like go out… have fun… hang out… chill out… n wad r sec4s in Singapore supposed to do? STUDY… Arghh… the word itself is bad enough… wad more having to plan to do it… sheesh… sometimes I wish I was in Legally Blonde… u know? The movie? Well… being a bimbo sure aint that bad… I mean, wad if u have the looks… juz go grab a rich guy… n your future is totally secured… hmmm… of coz it’s a plus if u fall in love with the guy or if the guy is a womanizer but hey… we r living in the 21st century right? Pple call us the Gen-Y pple…right? (I think) aniwae…if the man can womanize, why cant we go find a lover of our own? Sigh… I can just bet… the guy who womanizes is normal… juz bcoz he is rich… n women? We r called whores... or sluts… so mean right? Bleahz… Opps… digress again…hehe back to the topic…  As I was saying… I think being a sec4 is realli tough n all that… I kinda wish when I was back in sec3… I think of my secondary years… sec3 was the best… sec1 I was realli bitchy… sec2 well… I mellowed down a lot… but was still very hmm… how do u explain it? See...? I was that bad… I dun even know how to describe myself… hehe… Okie… thought of the word… infamous… yeah… I was infamous… lots of pple knew me…n it wasn’t juz the pple in my same level… it was realli pple from all levels… I mean… now the sec4s… there are like 80% to 90% of pple knowing me but I dunno their names… some of them r like acquaintances… I alwaize say hi n bye to them but I dun even know their names… sounds mean I know but hey… wad do u expect me to do? Go up to them n say for the past few years I have been saying hi n bye to u but I nv knew your name? Whoa… I think I will get slaughtered by them man… haha…   However… lots of bad things happened during those years… n I have realli mellowed a lot through out the years… of course to say I regret my actions is not entirely true although I muz agree I could have handled a lot of situations differently…   However, when I went to sec3, I grew up a lot… lots of things happened… good things n bad… BUT I muz say I realli enjoyed being a sec3… wad with knowing new frens…like Tafiq…some of them even my best frens now… such as Gerald… See Ching… Cheryl… Sze Hwei… Yin Wen… Trina… Mabel… etc. n although I had some clashes with Swee Fan… I certainly think of her as a very good fren now… n I m realli glad to know her… Hmm… I treasure my frens a lot n hope that we will still keep in contact with each other forever… smilez!=)  Sigh… after juz looking through everything that I wrote… I feel so cheated of a life… Sec4 is realli a fun year bcoz guys finally mature… hehe… u know wad I mean… it’s a lot nicer to talk to them in class now… I mean in a frens way lar… dun u go think of something else… but… I guess I’m realli stuck with studying… sigh… wadeva it is… I hope that I can survive through the whole entire process without losing any frens due to lost of contact… n of coz the ultimate goal… to get into Temesek poly…!!!  That’s all folks… gtg… Till next time…cya!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-03-14 6:05 p.m.  Yeah!!! great man... i have a new com... man, i m so happy i dunno wad to say or think... Well, first of all i wanna thank god for the new com... i m like so dying here without my com to update my blog... its like i cant tell someone my feelings n well, that juz seems weird... okie... i m having tuition in a while... at 7pm... so cant talk to much n too long... is juz that lots of things have happened since i updated u and...i cant help it... i m so excited with my new com n being able to finally wrtie in my blog again... YAY~!   Sheesh... i know i sound stupid... but i realli REalli like this com n m so happi to have a new com... ok... all this talk about my new com blah... sigh... i wish i could cont, but i realli have to go... will definately be back after my tuition... so wait up n i will tell u lots of my stuff later on... meanwhile, smilez... it's a brand new com!!! perhaps pple think ..."So What?" but to me... it's a real luxury... realli!!!=)   Hmm... finished my tuition quite a while ago.. think i m gonna spent the rest of the night updating my blog... ok, so wad happen the past few days?   Let's see... it's like the 2nd day of holidays now... haiz... i dunno why... huge mood swing... now? i seriously feel ultra tired n dun wanna type anithing... eh... update u tmr can?=)   Okie...m back again... apparently, erm... me n yuen hoi...rayner...cheryl...sheena n zu hao to watch the butterfly effect... however as the screening 4 it was kinda late we were debating to watch the haunted mansion or the cat in the hat... n so they chose to watch the cat in the hat... but seriously... it was so bad, no other movie could have compared to it... i m most certain it would bag this years worst movie ever!!!   Luckily, yuen hoi paid for my movie ticket as it was a treat by him to tag along n be the middle women btwn them...(coz... i can relate to rayner n cheryl they all n yuen hoi too... wad can i say? I m a friendly person...hehe) bcoz they kinda had a big fight btwn them from last year... n rayner apologised... so everything's kinda alright btwn them now lar... (yuen hoi n rayner quarreled)    Aniwae... back to wad i wanted to say... the show was totally atrocious... disgustingly lousy... n huge waste of time... a pain to the eyes n ears... a thorn in the mind... seriously... who would wanna make such a show??? Mike Myers... i cant stand him... i know i shouldnt be complaining like crazy... i mean, i din pay for it... but hey... waste of my time.. n of coz yuen hoi's money!!! For those who know me will know that money is very impt. to me... n even if it wasnt my money... i oso veri heart pain to see the money wasted like that... haiz... i should quit talking abt it... makes me more n more pissed thinking abt it...=( Hmm... see? Thanx to the stupid movie, i keep losing my chain of thoughts... i got lots n lots of stuff i wanna say.. but keep forgetting...   Aniwae, now the weather is realli bad... can go out even if i want to... watching BOA's mtv thanks to gerald... hehe... he lent me his cd... then at least i wun get bored to death at home...   Sigh... i think i will go n watch tv now... if i got time, will update my blog later... cya!=)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-16 10:57 p.m.  Okie… I m cranky n veri veri depressed… I think I m suffering from a mild case of depression… Had a slight quarrel with my mom… I wun bother u with the details as they aren’t veri pleasant, but right now, I m not talking to her unless she talks to me…   N I will onli answer her questions… Other than that, I dun give a damn abt her n will juz give her an impassive face whenever I see her… Bleah… Mothers sux!!! It is of coz no wonder that I dun wanna bcom a mother with I grow up…(those who are familiar with this will know wad I mean…)  I juz bathed finish juz now… standing under the shower n feeling the water rush down my body was great… It felt totally cleansing n the water juz washed awae all my fatigue… If onli life can like that… A rain or downpour that rinses down your body n takes awae all the pain n sadness u experience… Oh well, wishes will onli be wishes… they can nv come through…  This few days have juz proven the extent of my ‘depressed’ mood… I have been snapping at some of my frens n being realli mean… Sorrie to those who have to put up with my cranky attitude… I truly din mean all the bad stuff I say…   Like I say, the breaking up thingy has realli taken a toll on me… Right now, I juz wanna hurry up n get over it… The exams r oso nearing n they r realli stressing me out… I juz listed my studying schedule for this weekend n I realised that it is kinda stupefying… Meaning that it is kinda crazy… I m mad enough to stuff lots of studying into 2 days… I m crap.  Watching Survivor as I type now… Oh man… those pple r so poor things… Missing their families n all that… Sigh… Ok, commercial break… I m typing as fast as I can now… Hmm… Nothing happened much todae in school… Chem was pretty Duh~ as usual, but I m rather surprised that she din pick on me like I thot she would… However, her grouchy face was still there as usual… Sometimes I realli wonder if she went through plastic surgery to make her face look naturally Chao Bin all the time… Hmm…  Ooo… I juz remembered… I went for SSS the first time todae… Amazing!!! Even Mr Chan was shocked to see me… Hehe… So proud of myself… Now I m pondering over whether I should go tmr or not… Hmm… Well, I guess I will have to go… I left my emaths tb n S.S tb in my locker… Coz I missed out on the S.S test yday, I have to retake the test on Monday… Shucks… Darn it…  As I came home todae, I counted the no. of lights on top of the shelter that leads from the bus-stop to the void deck of my house… 37… Weird number huh~? I know I know… pple reading this will probably be thinking of how bo liao I m… But I realli wonder… Having to walk that walkway everyday… n yet I truly doubt that the hundreds of pple who walk through it everyday  know how many lights light up the walkway…  I know that it sounds corny… But its not realli abt counting how many lights etc. But more abt the things in life… How many times have we as humans look past the impt. things in life? Whether it is bcoz of searching for fame…money…or juz bcoz of the stress that we face in every moment of our lives, we seem to forget that besides that, there r still more impt. things in life… N perhaps we should take some time out everyday or every week… To look back at how wonderful life can be at times… How we juz overlook the little things that we used to treasure in life…  I will juz leave u with that thought now… Be back tmr…  Quote: Life is eternal and love is immortal. Death is only a horizon. And a horizon is nothing save the limit of our sight.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-15 2:23 p.m.  Given my condition todae, I m so lucky that I din go to school… I cant talk… I m sot tired bcoz the medicine the docter has given me keeps making me drowsy, n I cant even hold a pen upright without my hand shaking… This is how bad it gets but the bad thing is the MC onli lasts for one day… So no matter wad, I have to go back to school tmr… I hope I get better by then…  Nothing much happened today… Nicholas came over my house to fuss over me… Although I feel totally weird out with him fussing over me since there is nothing to fuss abt coz I m practically asleep the whole time… The docter says I cant eat ani heaty food… Which onli leaves room for light porridge n so on… Sigh… How poor thing can I get? Freaking hungry now… I hate antibiotics… Makes u wanna eat… Sheesh…  Hmm… Hope I dun miss too much at school today…Given the present status which is that mid-yrs r looming around us I cant afford to waste animore time… M quite angry with myself for letting this cranky sickness overcome me… I was desperately trying to study juz now but I realli couldn’t help it n juz fell asleep… Oh man… This sux!!!  I realised that my life has been getting more n more boring lately… I have truly nothing interesting to write abt n I juz keep crapping abt being sick etc. Sigh… Perhaps I should stop blogging alreadi… its no point to now…  Quote: The cure for boredom is curiosity. There is no cure for curiosity.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-14 10:37 p.m.  Oww… Oww… n oww… Apparently I m infected with the get sick symptom… This freaking sorethroat is seriously killing me… I lost my voice n cant talk now… Haiz… Wad is the earth coming to???  Aniwae, I juz call yelled at by one of my not so close frens… She was like critisizing me for planning to dump Nicholas n wadsoeva… Hmm… Which reminds me… how did she know that I was abt to dump him? Oh sigh… the wonders of gossip… Well, wad can I say? I mean, I do have to bear the fact that I m sorta doing him wrong by not having a good reason to break-up with him… I juz wish he wouldn’t be so nice… So I could at least find so fault with him n give him a better reason for our break-up…  So now I m currently labelled as the cruel heartless bitch bcoz nicholas has been so nice n all that… Haiz… Someone… I desperately need advice… Juz wad should I do??? I have been trying to drown myself in studies for mid-yrs… but I muz admit… It is affecting me… Even though not entirely, but in a way… I juz wanna hurry get over it… Sigh…Another thing is that I seem to be kissing him with more fervor n desperation nowadays… I think he senses that something is weird… Hmmm… could it be the reason as to why I have this terrible sorethroat n 2 ulcers in my mouth? Oh man…  There will be no quote todae… can’t think…sorrie.  P.S From now on… I will unlock my blog… nothing more to keep from anione…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-13 9:42 p.m.  So damn hot… Sheesh… Wad a crazy hot weather… There isn’t anithing special that happened today so I guess my blog today would be rather short… Hmm… I know that I said I wun be blogging so frequently animore. But that onli takes effect from tomorrow onwards…  I took a long time n thought over a lot of things today… I have sorta chosen a date to break up with Nicholas… Hope things go well n he hasn’t grown too attached or fond of me… I realli dun wanna hate him too badly... I guess that’s all for today… Realli in no mood to think of anithing else…  Quote: If you think that the world means nothing, think again.  You might mean the world to someone else.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-12 9:53 p.m.  Okie… Nothing much happened to me todae, but I gotta make some announcements… First of all, as some of u might know… I m intending to break up with Nicholas soon… Pls do not try n change my mind… A gal’s gotta be strong so as not to get hurt… Besides, I totally do not wanna lead him on when my love for him is non-existing compared to wad he feels for me…   I do not wish to repeat my mistake again… Like Derrick… I don’t wanna hurt another person that badly animore… There is enough guilt in my conscience alreadi… I dun wanna add more to it… For those who know… Isabel & Derrick… the legendary couple… n the bitch who broke his heart… who else but me… Okie… enough abt that… I totally dun wanna revisit the pain I inflicted on myself n him…  So, like I say… Will definitely have to pick out a date to which I have to do stuff that juz labels me as a total heartless gal… But… I will still be courteous enough to tell it in his face n not through the handphone or internet or email etc. I find those ways totally cowardly… I mean, since I m the one who is going to dump him, den I wanna face up to all his scoldings/rantings/dressins-downs… At the very least, I suppose that I should be there in front of him so that he can look at me n yell all he wants… I feel that in a way…he is entitled to that…  Sigh… ok, enough abt all that… Another thing that I gotta say is that I wun be updating my blog everyday animore… As u all know, mid-yrs r coming… I m not gonna be in front of the com all the time alreadi… This is not good… I juz keep spending my time online… no time at all to study… Oh well, that’s abt all I guess…  M in a very bad mood now… Haiz… I feel very bad… having to dump someone… this is like the 4th time… N I can’t help but think of Derrick all the time now… How much I hate him… Wad I made him do indirectly… How I wish I can change the past… But things nv change do they? Regret… It consumes your soul… intrigues u… pulls you… n u fall and wallow in guilt… And slowly, it sucks the life force out of you…Till one day you can’t breathe… You can’t breathe without thinking of wad you have done… And it lingers… on n on…  Quote: It's hard to face reality when reality has many faces.   **One of my favourite quotes…**
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-11 9:42 p.m.  Sheesh… haven’t done the zhuo wen which I m supposed to do… Oh darn… Now I m watching the NKF thingy n blogging at the same time… Hmm… Aniwae, todae was quite interesting…   First of all, we were all at Rachael’s house… Her house is that kind erm… how do u call it? Terrace? Yea… I think so… Aniwae, there was this kinda like gathering over there n i was there too… Me n Steph n Rachael n some other pple… frens n all lar… Well, wad happened was there was this gal called Annie n she was so sticky… someone whom I will call a slug… like super glue… we specially went to Rach’s room for more privacy n all that… n she was like tagging along with us n commenting on every sentence that we were saying even though she din have much idea on wad it was… Have u ever have this kind of experience? Well, if u do, u will know wad I mean… Pleah… I was practically rolling my eyes the whole time…I will now tell u part of wad happened. The conversation goes like this:  Steph: My Dad is gonna get a new car… Rach & me: Realli? Annie: Yar… I think your Dad needs a new car aniwae…The one he has now is not nice Me: *Roll eyes* Me: Erm… Steph ar… So did u get scolded when your dad saw the bill of your cashcard? Annie: Aiya… Steph is so rich… so wad if she spends a little more?Its ok one… I doubt her parents will say anithing right? Rach: Eh… Iz, did Nick manage to get the day off next week? Annie: Iz, he is so busy all the time… u better watch out, he might be having another gal somewhere…  Okie… now that realli pissed me off… I think some of u might have encountered this kind of pple right? Sigh… So irritating!!! I realli couldn’t stop rolling my eyes… Duh~ Who does she think she is? Miss-know-it-all??? Oh well… nvm abt her… I totally can’t be bothered animore…  Okie, so after that, we had sort of like some refreshments which Rach’s Dad kindly provided… although he was oblivious to the fact that the fruit punch was ‘spiked’ with champagne… Hehe… Courtesy of Steph’s boyfren…  Then as we were all rather bored, we decided to play Spin the Bottle… Hmm… n I was so DARN Unlucky to get chosen by someone… I will be nice n wun mention his name… But I still m gonna comment on his kissing method… Or rather his lack of one… It was practically like Exchanging Spit with someone else… Of all the pple I have kissed even though some may have been bad, it couldn’t beat this! It was SO bad… His wet n clammy tongue… Eww… So vulgar… like this disgusting filthy thing invading my mouth… Bleah… I bet this is totally the main reason he doesn’t have a girlfrend… Oh man… GHASTLY…REVOLTING… REPULSIVE!!!  Okie… That’s abt the general idea of my ‘interesting’ life today… Btw, the quote I m writing today totally depicts wad I m feeling now…  Quote: Most men do not mature, they simply grow taller.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-10 9:35 p.m.  Okie, I know that my bdae is quite a long time away, but due to some requests by some particular pple, I have to update this sorta like Bdae entry again… I sounds so totally mean… Having to tell pple wad to buy for me… Wad I want, like ordering stuff… N I truly feel bad abt it, but since u reguested for this, well here I go…  1)I would die to have a V8… in other words, wad pple will call a video camera…Whoa~…If I can have that, it would awesome… I know this sounds corny n werid, but I kinda like being able to film stuff… Hmm… that’s a nice thought… maybe I will work in the films industry when I grow up…hehe…  2)Oh… a video camera would be nice… Hehe… I love taking pictures too… although the strange part abt me is that I dun realli like to be taken in a shot by other pple…  3) I know, I know… I wun be nuts to ask for a hp… It’s strange, but I m kinda getting used to the idea of not having a hp…Hmm… Aniwae, wad I wouldn’t mind having is a Mp3 player… It would be nice to be able to dl songs that I like n stuff…  Okie…right now, I m realli tired… can’t think of anithing else… Sigh… I guess that’s all… But I still like the idea of having a V8 for my bdae… Oh man… Why m I writing this? Nobody’s gonna give me such a thing for my bdae… I make it sound like my frens r so damn rich… Sigh… Sorrie pple…=~(
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-09 9:34 p.m.  Abt me saying that I m totally sianed today? Scratch that… Delete it… Thrash it! Hehe, it was in fact a rather eventful day for me… although it was onli for a few hours…  First of all, I managed to find someone who was free to go out with me in the afternoon… My dearest xiao xiao mei (lai bao)… Hehe, so we agreed to go to Bugis to eat n take Neoprints… I missed her so much… Had a great time with her, talking abt stuff n all that… I felt that the trip was realli worthwhile n meaningful… We talked abt lots of stuff lar… Hehe… Which of coz I can’t mention out here… Oh, n since I was like dead hungry (due to the fact that I haven’t eaten as I couldn’t find anione who was free to go out n havelunch with me until 3+) coz it was like 4+ alreadi n I thot that my stomach would juz start to digest itself, we hurried to a place to eat… Going up the escalator, I saw the signboard of Yoshinoya n decided to eat there…  The place was rather crowded but luckily we managed to find a place to sit down n eat… I ordered this Beef n Teriyaki combo meal… n a ice lemon tea… It was quite filling… Liked it a lot… So, we sat down n talked for a while, n she was like asking me quite a lot of questions… but I had fun answering them lar…=)  So here comes to the fun part… We were sort of like shopping around n all that… Juz walking around, n I realised that there was lots of AHS pple there… Hmm… Aniwae, after walking aimlessly around for a while, we decided to hurry go take the neoprints… There was somewhat a long queue but we juz stood there n talked somemore till it was our turn to the machine… Haven’t taken neoprints in a while… I felt that the pictures that came out was realli sucessful n all that… Oh man, juz can’t help staring at my ownself in the neoprint… I think I m falling in love with myself… Oh no… That is so NOT good…  Haha… But it was realli nice n all that… The designs n patterns that we added was realli nice… Oh man… I juz love the picture… =P hehe… See? I m getting too self-obsessed… Darn…  Okie, so after taking the neoprints, we wanted to sorta like sit down n perhaps have a small dessert that kind while we continue to discuss abt some stuff… But guess wad? All the sorta like restaurants were all full… N so, we went back down to the basement n back to Yoshinoya… Which, thank God was not full… After eating the meal juz now (which was a lot), I m surprised that I was juz like moderately full… So, I kinda like ordered another meal… The Beef value meal was delicious, but to be honest, after eating it, I was so full, I nearly felt like puking it all out again… Sigh… It nv pays to be a glutton!!!  Went home after all that… Hehe… Now I m still looking at that neoprint… We realli look great in it… Oh man… I know… I should juz Shut Up… Hehe…  Quote: Don't frown. You never know who is falling in love with your smile.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-09 10:52 a.m.  This is TOTALLY boring… I m ultra sianed n nobody is free to go out with me… Ok, I muz widen my social circles… This juz proves that I m friendless… Oh man… This is saddening… Sigh…  Basically, all my good frens r either out with their boufrens or sleeping like pigs n at home or at church… Now dun get me wrong… I m totally fine with wad they r doing… It’s juz that I m realli bored n of coz seriously hoping that someone will be free enough to go out with me… Arghh… Sian!!!  I nv thot this day would come when I would say that slacking at home is a chore… But I m saying it now n I m so wishing that someone… will juz be free n call me to go out… If u r free, juz give me a call… Ok, now that sounds desperate… Opps…Hehe…  Darn it… Nick has got to work… On this lousy boring day… I miss him…  Quote: Don't cry over anyone who won't cry over you.  *Which is why i nv cry over anione now... I haven't shed a single tear for such a long time...*
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-08 8:51 p.m.  I m like almost fine now except for a slight headache… Sigh, heard from Yin wen that I m in deep soup for skipping like 4 SSS… Not I wanna skip all the time ok… the first 2 times, I got something on… that was like the first Friday n Saturday… Den later, last week, was sick on Friday mar… Went to school on Saturday onli to take the Bio test… So, I din go for the SSS on last Saturday too… Now I got to present excuse letters n probably get into trouble with lots of pple…  I m So unlucky… Dunno wad’s wrong lar… But, the next time I m sick, I will juz go to school n sleep in class… at least, I got go… wun get into trouble that way… Lousy day lar… Nick not free to pei~ me… Sigh… Aniwae, somebody changed my blog’s pw… I can’t say who, but I so wanna kill him… Den play with my blog lar… Jerk! Haha… But its alright now… took revenge by puncturing out his motorcycle’s tires… Now he has got a flat tire… Hehe… I know I m So mean...=P  Daddy’s coming home today… Yay… Surprisingly I miss him… I know he realli wants me to do well in the O’s this year… Have been saying like I muz study hard etc. Yea… I know, stop stressing me out… Although I know you want the best for me, but I realli juz need encouragement n support… Not advice… I can give myself advice… But encouragement is a different matter… It is more touching n has more effect on a person when his or her loved ones give encouragement or support…  Okie, enough abt that… I think you know wad I mean… Well, to be honest, I think being in sec4 is realli torturous… My ambition or u can so call it as a ambition has absolutely nothing and I say again Absolutely nothing got to do with wad I m learning now or wad I have learnt so far… Oh sigh… I realli cannot stand Singapore’s teaching system… It SUX!!!  Well, being sick n staying at home the whole day oso sucks… It juz gets on my nerves being enclosed in an area… I know this sounds crazy, but I m a bit claustrophobic I guess… Even though my house is nowhere near being considered as small, but I juz can’t stand being enclosed in an area for too long… esp. when I m not doing anithing productive… It juz bugs the hell out of me… N I guess a huge contributing factor to me being in a cranky bad mood is oso bcoz I still feel a bit sick… Oh man, I know… I should juz shut up n quit complaining… Fine, I will…  Quote: For life in the present there is no death. Death is not an event in life. It is purely a fact in the world.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-08 7:31 a.m.  Okie, this is getting on my nerves. I m still very darn sick n of coz annoyed with myself for being sick… yesterday night, I was pretty fine n like realli on the road to recovery n then I muz get myself a fever of 38.4 degrees… this is pure crap! I studied for the history test ok… Darn… I wanted to do well in it leh… I m so furious with myself now… Furious n having a bad headache n so on… Even my vision is blurry n my eyes can’t open properly…  I dun mind missing school, bcoz I can realli like study at my own pace at home, but the fact is that, I m missing out on a lot of wad the tcher’s r teaching that could be realli impt. n all that… Oh man, I realli gotta get well soon… Sigh… If this goes on, how m I going to go for the mid-year’s being onli like half prepared? Realli stressed up for mid-yrs, if I dun do well, I think I might juz break down… Sigh… Let’s juz hope for the best…  Aniwae, with me being so dizzy n this blurry vision, I can’t realli see wad I m typing, so I guess its no use staying here n telling u how terrible I feel n how sick I m… i m juz going straight to bed n pray that I will get well soon…  Oh no, I juz rmb… tmr is Good Friday… that means no school, n I wanna go church… that oso means that I miss two impt. days at school where the tchers could have taught lots of stuff… Darn again… I hate my body’s immune system… Ok, scratch that… Can’t hate that… God created that part of me too… I will juz go back to sleep right now…  Quote: Good friends are hard to find, harder to leave, and impossible to forget. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-07 10:14 a.m.  I m realli feeling ultra sick… sneezing all the time n coughing like every other minute is NOT fun at all… Oh man… Reading my past entries… Felt that it is only recently that I type lots of words in Caps Lock to express my anger… which is not good… I gotta learn how to curb my anger… Darn…  Oh well, guess I can’t help it… Must realli stay home n rest so that I can be well enough to go to school for my elective history test tmr… Darn it lar… I realli cannot stand Ms Chan… Her way of teaching is like totally weird out n then is like I dun ever get wad the hell she is saying… Muz realli pia~ for the history test tmr… Sigh…  I think it must be that bottle of champagne that I drank the other day… finished the entire bottle in like half n hour… Is that bad or good? Hmm… M I considered an alcoholic then? I m not too sure lar… but dun realli think so… At least, I dun crave for beer or wadsoeva… I juz enjoy drinking it… Haha… =P   Eh… so, let me update on wad happened yday after the erm… not so pleasant entry of mine… Apparentely, somethings went on betwn Steph n Joanne… Hope Joanne isn’t angry with me animore… Aniwae, went to Nick’s house after staying at Steph’s house for a while… No one was at home as usual… Steph suggested we dig into his drawers to look at wad he keeps… I was curious too lar… n sorta agreed to the idea but I felt realli bad n all that… Hmm… Of coz we din go through all his stuff… That would totally be like invasion of privacy, but we found at his table drawer a photo album…  Guess wad? There was like photos of him n his parents n like his childhood photos inside… Awww… So sweet… Wad a sentimental guy…Sheesh… I blush to think of that… Hmm… I guess he muz realli miss his parents a lot… They dun realli care abt him much… n well, they are oso not on very good terms with each other… So, his life is rather weird… I have to admit… I dun mind living his life if I get the allowance he gets every month… I can’t indulge on wad it is, but save to say that its abt 4-digits…   Whoa… N he is like still working becoz he doesn’t wanna take the money… He says that he doesn’t want this kinda money… To him, its like if he takes it, it means that he doesn’t mind that his parents will divorce as long as he gets the money… N he doesn’t want that… Sigh… I hate to be mean, but that’s their family matters… n I have no right to step into it… n I dun intend too aniwae…  Lets go on… I was still looking at his photos n stuff n din notice that Steph had actually ‘ventured’ to other places… N she was like looking through his bed drawer… She found something there… Yep, I dun have to make u guess… It is wad u all r thinking… Condoms… No biggie… I mean, its not like I expect him to be some kind of a virgin boy or wad… that is… I know he isn’t aniwae… So, I wasn’t that surprised…   But Steph kept making a big fuss over it n she crack all those corny lame jokes that got me rolling in his bed with laughter… Sheesh… Steph… Wad will I do without her? Sigh… Why do most of my frens all migrate or go overseas to study? Darn it lar… I wanna be rich! Damn… Even Rachael is migrating too… N my all-time favourite kor too… Wad the hell... One day when I grow up, I muz migrate too…  Oh, back to where I was… So, abt the condoms thingy, Steph actually posed me this question... Whether I would do it with nick if he asked me too…Duh~  NO!!! Abusolutely NOT! I mean, not like I truly love him n all that… I gotta dump him b4 holidays pple… So, to all those who r speculating… No, I will not do it with him on my bdae or wadsoeva… Yep… We may do some other stuff… but no more then that…=)  I juz realised that this is a realli realli long entry… M gonna log off now… will update some more later... meanwhile, I m so gonna rest n then study abt ‘The Cold War’ in history… Sianed~  ***Oh, one last thing before i go... TO ALL reading my blog... I update 2 to 3 entries on my blog at times... so please please click on the previous button to make sure u dun miss out on anithing... Dun come n ask me stuff bcoz i have aleadi said them n would not like to say it again!!!***  Quote: Death is well understood, it's life that isn't.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-07 9:52 a.m.  Okie… abt yday’s entry? Scratch that… It was pure crap… A moment of fury… Juz to vent my anger… Well, things were not as bad as I made them be… But, I wun delete my entry bcoz that is truly wad I was feeling at that point of a time…  This is so like a clarifications entry… Hmmm… I oso wanna say that as much as I was complaining abt the Art fair n all that, it was bcoz I was tired… To be honest, it wasn’t all that bad… N I know that bcoz I m not in art… I would probably not know that much abt the hard work those pple put in… So, I m realli not in the position to say much…Although, the pple could have been more enthusiastic in helping to sell their stuff… (Happi now, Gerald?)  Okie… so, I have made my peace… Pls do not bear grudges on me for my previous entries… N if u think I suck, well, juz dun read my blog… that’s all I can say…  Quote: Nine out of ten people like chocolate. The tenth person always lies.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-06 4:11 p.m.  I m pissed… okie… not that pissed off animore… but I m still quite pissed. I blog to relieve stress n remember stuff so that when I wanna refer to stuff, I can alwaize check up on my blog… That’s all… no other reason… I dun blog so that pple can read abt my feelings n wad happened to me n make fun of me… I m seriously veri upset abt the fact that pple treat reading my blog as a amusement for them to laugh n talk abt… If this goes on, I m going to lock up my blog forever… I mean it…  First of all, today, Joanne kept blowing at ear during P.E when we were playing badminton… Yea, I admit, it was all like having some good-natured fun… But some pple seriously DUNNO the limit… there is alwaize this line which u can pass n cannot pass… be it betwn friends or family etc. Its called respect… Quoting from Trina, “I can laugh with u once… I can laugh with u twice… But dun expect me to laugh with u the third time”… Esp. since wad we are laughing abt is ME… Try n put yourself in the same situation… How would u feel?   So, yea, I was totally ok with it for a while… n then Zu Hao came to play with us n he was like making fun of everything that I did… whether it was me trying to catch the shuttlecock or wad… He juz kept imitating me n making fun of me… Everyone has their limit to things… And everybody has something called pride… It was seriously not funni, Zu Hao… And I m darn glad I din let u have the password to my blog… You r one person who dun know how to treat a person with respect… I thought that u might have change but sorry, I was wrong… You dunno wad respect means… n I doubt u ever will considering your attitude towards everyone… It is no wonder you make so many enemies in life…  Freaking pple… I was realli in a bad mood for the whole day bcoz of them… Rayner, Zu Hao, Joanne… I guess I was wrong abt u all… Looking n me n bursting out in laughter… Well, that is realli silly n makes u look like a retard…Rayner… I dun find it funni and amusing… Pple who know me well will most propably know… DUN n I mean DUN ever CROSS the line with me… no way… I have this huge tendency to bear a grudge on pple n even if I forgive you, I will alwaize remember wad you did to piss me off before…  Call me petty or wadeva, but dun blame me if something bad happens to u one day… I happen to curse n do stufff that I usually regret later… Ask my frens… They should know… M still feeling Freaking pissed off now… Wad the hell!  Quote: Dun piss me off… I can’t assure you of wad I’m capable of doing when I m angry
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-05 5:03 p.m.  M blogging now… Haiz… no other time already… later got maths tuition… Darn… cant stand tuition… I alwaize juz wanna fall asleep… cant help it… maths is boring… Aniwae, basically nothing happened in school todae…Although I muz say that there was much laughter all the time…  Well, first of all, we got like the Chinese test… felt it was like ultra easy n all that… can score realli high…=) Then, Ms Chan din come for S.S today… so happi… after which was Bio… Darn Mrs. Lee din wanna give out the test paper…but I did rather well… got 85.3%... so proud of myself… I love sexual reproduction!!!=) Haha… glad I managed to do well… After bio was maths… double periods… nearly died… it was torturous… but surprisingly, the day passed rather fast n it was finally at the last two periods… which was English… Zhimin n the rest got debates but we were all crapping around…So lame…  Den Rayner kept scaring me n making me scream… See lar… Bcoz of him had to change places n den Mrs. Tan thinks I m very noisy… I was perfectly quiet right from the start ok… Its bcoz of Rayner lar… Bleahz… And then Joanne kept blowing at my ear too… Sheesh… my ear is not for every one to blow u know… Wah, was realli sensitive n all that… Onli Nicholas can do that to me… In the end, my ear felt realli uncomfortable n hot… Yuck… Speaking of which, do u know that ears r a realli sensitive part of a person… I mean, 90% of the human race r all rather sensitive there… so dun ani how play around ar… Hehe…  To me, its totally fine when Nick licks my ear… Haha… he’s my bf… He has a privilege right?=P Oh, btw, have been trying to draft my chapter 2 of the story… Sadly, have had no success… Hope I can do a good one after the tuition later… Tmr got Vectors test… Arghh… So sucky! But I hope that I can do well for it too… Hmm… Wad else is there to say huh~?  Oh, came home today to find nick waiting for me outside my house… Wad to do? Let him in lar… He stayed for onli half an hour though… Din want him to stay too long… Will juz distract me… Got to study for the test tmr marz… I feel so naughty… Hehe… Gave him a love bite at his neck… which was realli like SO obvious… Hope his colleagues at his workplace later dun tease him too much abt it… =P   Aniwae, in answer to Jun wei’s question, erm… a love bite is like sucking at the other person’s flesh… Not realli truly biting at him/her n causing him/her to bleed… NO way… its not that… Haha… n oso, the mark/imprint that is left there is sorta reddish… with quite a few small spots… The reason is bcoz  the blood capillaries have broken n thus it looks like there is a blood clot there… Haha… oh, n after a few days, the mark left will turn a bit blue-blackish… like a blue black like that lar… Hmm… I m so naughty… Sigh… I cant help it…   Whoa… found this nice Champagne in the cabinet… Looks quite good… Is now in the fridge chilling… will take it out to drink later… Haha… My dad is now in Hong Kong… he went there for a small break… like a holiday lar… for 4 days… will be back in Thursday… Meanwhile, well, gonna drink finish that bottle today… before my mom comes home n finds out… Hmmm… if I remembered correctly, champagne has like the highest alcohol in it… Hmm… but I dun realli need to care lar… wun ever get drunk… which realli sux at times lar… Hehe… Well, better go now… Wanna go study… =)  Quote: When you love something, set it free and if it comes back, it's yours…if it doesn't, it never was.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-04 8:03 p.m.  Darn tired… So darn tired… So tired till I cant move… My legs are like weighing 100kg… I juz can’t move them… I dun wanna be bothered with thinking at all… See? I m crapping… Oh sigh…  Okie, right from the top… I juz came back from the esplanade… from helping See ching n the rest selling stuff… Its like a art fair lar… Something like learning all abt entrepreneurship and all that… That is so not the impt. part… the impt. part was I woke up like ultra early to go meet See ching n then we took her Dad’s car with Sze Hwei to the ‘Under the bridge’ thingy…   Which was basically pure crap bcoz there was like no air-con and all that… And it was rather hot down there… To add on, I helped out with publicity which was to basically walk around n tell pple to go to our stall… Stall 2… ‘Thumbnails’… it was freaking tiring… And that was like the MAIN reason why my legs are like engaging in a war with me now…  So I went around with Gerald, practically like begging pple to go to our stall… which to be honest, did not help in sales ONE bit… Oh well, so we decided to be smart and go back…=) Finally… had some time to sit down and rest… But trust me, it wasn’t for long… Soon after, had to be helping out at the stall and was like a salesgal… Calling out to pple… ‘Can I help you? or ‘Why dun u look around?’ and even ‘Hi, welcome to our stall… We sell blar blar blar…’ Sheesh… It was realli tiring… And to be honest, even though I m not obliged to help and all that, I felt rather pissed off lor…  In truth, ONLY me n Wendy were realli doing stuff… We were realli like selling our stuff etc. the rest was like doing I dunno wad… Seriously, why the hell did they even come for? Well, Gerald helped around... I mean, at least he got publicize in the front… but after we went back to the stall, they all started to slack… n I m not like the main person in charge but I was like putting my all n working my ass off for them n See Ching n Cheryl was like talking tgt…   Then when I tell them to like get customers n all that, they were like ‘We shouldn’t go n snatch other stalls customers…’ I mean , come on… the other stalls were the ones who came to snatch our customers in the 1st place… N it is bcoz we have pple who were slacking instead of doing their jobs there that’s why we had poor sales… Or least, could have gotten BETTER sales…  What the hell lar… Getting more pissed by the minute… Joanne n Jeanette were also ther helping out with doing the test tubes n stuff… At least they help around… But Kar Keat n Shi Yin n Mei Hui they all were juz a PURE bunch of LOSERS… Sheesh, why did they even come in the 1st place? Ultra extra… doing NOTHING!!! And Kar Keat was like asking me to entertain the customers who were looking around… HELLO… I m NOT from ART… I DUN HAVE to help u… why cant u help out??? Then, some more, he kept hogging the seats… 1 of the 2 pathetically given seats that we had…   Which comes to Yuen Hoi… I was ULTRA angry with him too… DIN do anithing, blocking the way all the time… being ultra extra… complaining abt how he shouldn’t have come in the first place… irritating me in hope of knowing more abt wad happened betwn Han Yun n the rest of the gang… He was juz a PAIN in the ASS!!! He was another idiot which kept hogging the seats too… Wad a loser…  Okie, I m pissed off… well, I guess its bcoz I m like I said, Freaking tired now… will not bad-mouth other pple now… I feel bad… Sigh… Well, that’s the gist of my day… And feeling so tired, I m going to do Yin Wen’s html thingy on her blog… Hope it turns out well… Will talk more abt the happy stuff that happened today, later… or perhaps tmr lar…  Quote: Desire is half of life, indifference is half of death.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-04-03 10:52 p.m.  This is lame...I m like blogging now... so utterly late... Darn, writing all those stuff is realli taxing on me... Not that i m complaining abt having to use too much of my brain juices, but to be honest, it requires a huge amount of imagination and of course the more impt. part is the language... How to express myself such that the words bcum totally erotic and that it seems like the perosn reading it is right there watching the scene...  Okie, enough of all that... in ani case, i m realli happi due to the comments i see tagged on my blog... realli sweet n all that... thanx for supporting me u all... Realli appreciate it!!! Will continue to write n hope u all can keep supporting me... =)  Okie, so i m watching All In now on Channel U...Realli like the guy...Love his eyes... Its realli deep... okie, I dunno how to explain this but if u understand, then u do...  Todae was a rather ok day for me...Had the Sexual Reproduction Bio test... Loved it! The onli Bio test which I felt was NOT challenging at all... which is a good thing... Really!!! I might be able to realli do well...=)  Okie, gtg now...will give a through update tml...=)  Okie, m back today... Sigh, m realli tired and all that but i juz wanna add that after the bio test, me n yin wen went to Macs to eat breakfast... met Tim. Gan n Xiao ying there... Gan was alone lar but Xiao ying was with her mom... they look rather alike lor... her mom is quite pretty for a mom... Xiao ying is juz like the darker version lar... Hehe...  Well, aniwae, after all the crap, we decided to go buy food n then i realised that i left my wallet in the 222 bus juz now... had to walk with wen all the way to the bus control station n get it back... Ah sigh... typical me... So blur n forgetful... sometimes, i can't even stand myself...  But we had a great breakfast yday lar... Talked abt many stuff tgt...=) Nowadays, dun realli have the time to talk to Wen already but yday was rather fulfilling...=)Thats all i guess... Yep...cya!  Quote:Growing old is no more than a bad habit that a busy person has not time to for. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okie, this is where I should be inserting like erm... the next 2 entries which will be realli explicit... I just feel that since i realli have no time to continue with the story etc. i decide not to copy n paste the entries over... That why, it wun be like somthing unfinished n left undone... So, well, to those who wanted to read it or wadsoeva, pls leave a comment on this entry n i will personally sent u the first chapter... onli chapter i wrote... hehe  That's all folks!!! =)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okie... Not onli is this a new design, but i actually transferred all my stuff to Blogger... Yea... Blogger rox! So much easier to control n type wadsoeva... Okie... Now back to business... so much things have happened during this past few days...  First of all... EXAMS ENDED!!! whoo-hoo~!  Secondly, I m pissed with most of my frens...  Thirdly, I LOVE rayner... Thank you for taking the hint! Smile smile... Hazel is so happi... Yea... Will get a new cd... HAPPY! =)=)=)=)=)=)=)=)  Will be back tmr to update...byebye  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Sianed… Todae nv go school… Of course lar… Dun feel the need too mar… Todae go to TJC n listen to them talk crap… Sigh… I m going to poly… So? No big deal lar… Hmm… Aniwae, like I said that I would continue yday’s entry, much things have happened since I last blogged n well, I will juz try n recall all of them…  First of all, my clique did not forget about my bdae at all… They actualli arranged this erm… Mini celebration at Haagen Daz ice-cream parlor with a cake n all that… Well, to be honest, I m veri surprised n happi n touched… Totally touched… But not when I know that Swee Fan was going… I mean, I know that I hhave made peace with her n all that…  Not like I hate her or wadsoeva but… I mean, the day before my Cheryl asked me if I was going to be free the next day n that we were all going out… But she nv said abt Swee Fan going along… I mean, I know I can be veri stubborn but then, they nv mentioned her going along n before the exams on Tuesday, she mentioned herself that she was going to play pool with some other pple… But right after the exams, she was like tagging along with us…  Wad m I supposed to feel? I mean I totally appreciate wad they did for me but I juz wanna spent that special time with my clique…my special frens n not like wadsoeva… It’s juz not right to me… So, I apologise afterwards for my very weird behaviour then n oso for my ultra bad mood at that time… but I still wun be in a good mood if this happened again… Its juz more of wad I feel lar… Kinda like this thing is between me n my good frens n I wun welcome outsiders at all…  Oh well, enough about that… Sigh… So tired…gonna sleep…be back later  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-02-13 6:33 p.m.  Blogging… finally! I realli miss blogging… In ani case, todae is Fridae. Yea. I can finally take a break from studying till next Monday… Bleahz. Exams suck. Not that I m like totally stressed up n all bcoz I m not. But, still… Exams Sux! Sigh… Having not typed stuff for so long, I m like a foreigner to this keyboard.  Aniwae, todae is May 14th.I m 16 n no one knows... My birthday… Yea… Right…  Happi Birthday to me Happi Birthday to me Happi Birthday to me~ Happi Birthday to me.  Sigh. Apparently, NOBODY remembered about my birthdae. At least, not my close frens cum clique… And I m not so bu yao lian to go n remind them… At least, that’s how I feel… I wun go around n remind pple abt my bdae so that they will remember n buy me a present etc. Nope. Not my style. In ani case, the number of pple who remembered my bdae can be counted on one hand… Oh well, wad to do? I din remind them. But then again, to be honest, I think it is a fren’s duty to remember abt your best frens bdae… No need to remind them. So, I received no presents…nothing. Kinda like last year… Hmm… Guess I gotta get used to my boring life since pple tend to treat me as an invisible person such that if I dun talk when we r out in a group, nobody notices…  Sometimes I wonder if I m just being sensitive but I alwaize notice everything abt everyone around me n the little details that pple dun remember. To be honest, that’s good in a way, but it truly sux in another… It juz seems like I care abt others n all that n when I m down or wadsoeva, nobody takes the time to notice n care… Yea right… Now I m beginning to sound pathetic. Sigh… I m NOT pathetic… My mom n dad remembered. Steph, Rach remembered. Some of my classmates remembered. Added to a nice total of erm… let’s see… 7 pple… Haha… So interesting huh~  Kinda like my sec2 year… No one remembered too… Oh no… Kinda feel my existence on earth being threatened… Like something is taking over n soon I will be left with nothing… Juz another invisible gal living on earth… Juz another human. Damn! I dun wanna be like that… It totally sux! One day, Juz one day… I m gonna make it big… Make it so BIG that pple will remember me… At least, I hope so… I dun wanna be juz another average person living on earth. I dun wanna be living for nothing… I want a meaningful life…  My Birthday wish this year? Of coz to do well for O’s n get into Temesek Polytechnic lar… Sigh… Another thing to be stressed about… Oh well, Wad to do? That’s life right? Which reminds me… The classmates that I m not so ultra close to remembered abt my bdae… My Best Fren in class… Or rather USED to be Best Fren until she got snatched awae from me by that parasite… Forgot abt my bdae too… Okie… I shall quit complaining… Or pple will start to say I m making a huge fuss over nothing…  Quote: I dun wanna be invisible.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-02-08 6:11 p.m.  Finally after eons… I m back again… I know I know, I told myself that I wun blog again until after exams but I realli have lots of things to say n besides, THIS IS IT! I have had it with mugging… Looking at another textbook now will juz drive me CRAZY! Pple out there mugging… I think u will understand wad I m trying say… Arghh… Exams SUX!  Aniwae, let us refrain from the veri veri stressful subject, lots of things have happened…  1.Gerald n me r NOT an item. Juz wanna stress that out… He is my fren alwaize will be… someone whom I dun have to act in front.of. Someone whom I can totally show the bad side of me in front of. Someone whom I can unabashedly talk abt sex n stuff like that…  2.Okie… Next, there is this person in class whom realli makes me SICK to the Stomach. Her initials? Well, I will be nice n not say it… Her name? Hmm… Since she is is so ULTRA thick-skinned n so proud of it… Let me publicise for her… Ms Lee Han Yun is the perfect candidate fot being a Bacteria… Esp. the kind which gets into your eye n infects your eye till even looking at her will want to make u blind…  Awww… I m SO sorry for being so direct n being SO mean… Its juz that I truly cant help it. She probably has this sign up on her forehead. Pls ROLL your EYES when u look at me! Well, wad cant I do? Try not to look her? Yea… Something like that… Unfortunately, she’s oso like a parasite… the kind who causes harm to anione… M I exaggerating? Yes… I cant help it. The pure sight of her even lurking at the side of my eye totally irks me… Perhaps I should start this anit-Han yun campaign… Hmm… I will consider…  So, let me count… The truly COUNTLESS times I have rolled my eyes… Ask Gerald… I think he will know wad I mean… Goosebumps… Eww…  Okie, so, like I say, lots of things have been happening… So much such that my lousy short term memory doesn’t remember… Hmm… To those who have been keeping track of my veri lamofied life? Good for u… U get the first hand knowledge to how sad n pathetic my life is now since I haven’t been drinking… In other words? One word…Sian. And… I juz realised that almost 80% of the humans I know on earth Smoke! No big deal to me, but the thought has crossed my mind… I think I will die of lung cancer when I grow up. N u know wad? I totally DUN give a damn. Like I said, I wanna die early, so no biggie here…  N another thing… Saw the Duh~ commercial abt “STOP wearing bras” thingy… Hmm… Perhaps I m Duh~ will stop wearing bras to sleep at night now… Some researchers say that if u do, your breasts will sag in the future… Wadeva… I dun realli care abt tt but its true abt letting your boobs have some ‘breathing space’ so, yea… will most do so…  And… update abt me n that deaf gal at home? Well? No progress… I m totally looking forward to FREE Living Space when she goes to Taiwan next week. So, Lord? Pls do me the favour n take it as my bdae present!  Well, that’s all I can think of now… cya soon… I hope.  Quote: The day which we fear as our last is but the birthday of eternity.  *** After so long without a quote, here’s one nice one…=)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-02-02 11:31 p.m.  Its been so long… Reallli so damn long since I touched this keyboard n used the computer… Lots of things to say as usual, but NO TIME! So wad to do? I will juz cut this all short. Resting now… Watching American’s Top Model. After I watch it I m so gonna MUG! Cant help it, exams r realli nearing soon… Sigh… Totalli stressed up.  Okie, forget abt the past few days… I have no time or brain energy to remember wad happened… In ani case, I will juz talk abt todae. Todae was basically a totalli fine day… Went out to have lunch with Gerald after school. It was kinda like a Study Date lar… I actualli asked him out on the weekends but was studying my ownself n couldn’t make it. Aniwae, so we went to the Soup’s Place… A realli nice shop at EastPoint owned by Lixing’s parents… Not bad… Food was ultra cheap n tasted truly fine… I felt that it was worth my money that kind…  Decent meal n decent price… Hmm… I urge pple to go there n try it… Okie… Getting to the point here. So, Gerald taught me lots of Emaths stuff… He basically summarised all of wad I was supposed to be learning this year into the few hours we spent there… Totally GRATEFUL… Sometimes I truly wonder… Wad would I do without Gerald? Hmm… I know… I alwaize bully him bcoz I have the right of the way… And he never gets angry with me… Aww… =P  Oh well… The results r out… Adrianne won… Like I knew she would… Haha… Went to check up on the results on the internet last time… Okie… This osos marks a Goodbye to blogging… Will most probably blog in a few days time… which to me is a living nightmare… Having to study somemore like crazy… Sigh… Going now… Bye… 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-28 7:21 p.m.  Cooking my own dinner now… Its ‘shui jiao’ which is like the chinese kind of dumplings… Hehe… I quite like that food… In ani case, when is that bitch of my sister going back? I seriously cant wait for her to go back to U… I totally miss my own space/freedom n a life without having to see her BITCH face… Arghh… Totally suffering at home now… Sigh…  M back… Juz eaten finish… Haiz… So stressed… MYE’s r coming soon… Totalli stressed!!! Wad the hell… I wanna complain lar… Mrs Tan SUX! Ms Chan SUX!(the chem one) Stupid lor… Okie… Basically, I din go to school yday… Again. So wad? Need to study right? Wah Lau… I realli went to my club to mug like hell lor… Stupid lar… Lots of pple r pissing me off lately… First the one at home… Den in school… When can I find peace?   Okie… Wadeva… Will not think abt crappy stuff… Aniwae, there is gonna be this parent-tcher meeting kinda thing… I bet will sure have quite a few tchers wanting to see me... Ms Chan for one… n Mrs Lim too since I know my Maths suck… Too bad right? Its not like I want to suck at it… Hello? Onli stupid pple gauge another person by their intelligence in tests, exams or wadsoeva… I m not trying to say that my IQ is ultra high but look at Thomas Edison… Not like he was smart too right? Teachers in school labelled him STUPID lor…  I dun believe that I wun be able to make it in the society juz bcoz I fail Amaths or Emaths or bcoz I juz get borderline passes for Chemisrty… This totally does not mean that I dun try my best n study hard at home or that I have no brains at all… Wad the hell lar… Talking abt this makes me more pissed… I tell u… One day I will definitely make my mark in the society n come back to show off in front of these stupid tchers faces… Look down on me lar… GO AHEAD!  By hook or by crook even if I have to throw awae my pride or wadsoeva, I make sure I will make it big man… I SWEAR it!!! I will proved to those bastards, jerks, bitches n dumbass’ that u dun have to do well in school or get A1’s all the way to be rich n get a good job in a company… Wad it takes in EQ!!! Pulling Strings!!! This world is not wad it seems to be n to those who bcum tchers? The NAÏVE type… the type who can onli work with pple like us… teenagers that dun have ani ulterior motive at all… Tchers r juz pple who cant survive in the society at all that’s why they chose to take this kinda job… Lousy… Losers… Go KISS your own ASS!!!  To those who look down on me juz bcoz I dun get good grades like u… Go BANG your head on the wall lar… U juz watch lar… Wait & See! One day when I realli do my best n work to my fullest potential, I will personally ask u back n see my success! Maybe if I m nice, I will even let u lick my shoe as an apology… BLEAHZ! IDIOTS!  Okie… finished ranting or venting my anger wadeva… m going back to mug… Will personally write the excuse letter n THROW it in Mrs. Tan’s face tmr… cya~!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-26 9:04 p.m.  I had a totally interesting day todae… Hmm… First things first… We got back our Oral results n I got 36… 36!!! 36 upon 40… Whoa… Is that cool or wad? I did feel that I did well but din think I was going to get this high bcoz like I said… Pat. Wong’s face was like totally misleading me… In ani case, I m NOT complaining abt the marks…=) So proud of myself… To those who din do well, I m not trtying to rub it in your faces but hey… perhaps its bcoz of the tcher u got? I mean… I shouldn’t be saying that Pat. Wong is bias coz she is not… I mean, I m not like her best student or wadsoeva n I had although I nv realli join in the bitching abt her but I do agree that she isnt a veri good english tcher… Besides, Yuen Hoi who got her din do veri well too…  I cant believe it… I m still kinda shocked… Expected a 32 or 34 the highest… but not 36… smilez… M in a good mood… n nothing can spoil that… Another good thing is that I completed Excretion of Bio n m right on time… I hope… for the mid-yrs… Hehe…  Okie… now to the interesting part of wad happened todae… First of all, I went to eat lunch with Gerald at Pasta… Had fun there…talked crap as usual… Hehe…Okie, then in the bus, I asked him to msg my sister bcoz I forgot to bring my keys n wanted to ask her if she would be staying at home… Told her that I would be going home at abt 4:45 n so on… She said she wanted to go out but will stay at home till I come home…Okie… get the facts clear… I m not lying… Juz telling the story straight… I DID NOT force her to stay home n wait for me right? I DID NOT say this to her… U MUZ stay home n wait for me… She was NOT obliged to stay home n wait for me… She VOLUNTARY agreed to do so… So far… M I right? This is not from my point of view… It’s a Fact…  Next up… I came home early after having a fun time with Gerald eating… I din want her to wait too long for me since she told me she wanted to go out… Isnt this like a normal thing a human being will do? Coz I feel bad that she has to wait for me n all that… so of coz I try n hurry back lar… Duh~! Okie… so now it comes to the main gist of the story… I came home n rang the doorbell for eons… Like approximately 15min? Yea… Kinda like that… Why did I have to ring the doorbell for so long? Hmm… Y dun we all go ask our veri DEAF n veri innocent sister? How the hell m I supposed to know that she was Hard of Hearing? I mean, God… Give me a sign… Hello~`…  That’s not all… Okie… tell me who wun be pissed off after ringing the doorbell for so long n having no one answering n yet knowing there is someone at home? Sheesh… I know I should have thought of going downstairs n call home but yea… call me stupid… I m totally ok with that… But I know I can nv beat my DUMBASS sister at that… She bags the award for Hard of Hearing plus Deaf plus Attitude Problem n Bitch all tgt… Wow… Should I give her a Standing ovation? Yes… Pple let’s put our hands tgt n clap for the total Freaking Bitch who is abt to receive her award… (*Applause*)  Right… Back to my veri ultra interesting story… She opened the door at last… After wad would seem like the time an old crippled lady took to walk from Singapore to America… N guess wad? She gave me a TOTAL PISSED OFF face n said “Wad’s wrong?” Bcoz I rang the doorbell consecutively for abt 1000times… N finalli she managed to hear the 1 time that she CLAIMS to have heard… Or rather not since she said that she DIN hear anithing at all n that the doorbell wasn’t working…  Wow! The doorbell wasn’t working… Realli? Nah… Me being me… Wasn’t born juz yday like she thought I was… I checked the doorbell again as I came into the house… It rang… LOUD & CLEAR… Perfectly fine… Now… Is it my ears that r hearing things not supposed to be heard or wad? I will admit… Patience is NOT my virtue… I was pissed at that moment… Of coz I was… Who wouldn’t be? I wun deny… I gave her the I-m-pissed-off face… I mean, in that kinda circumstances, I TOTALLY felt that she deserved it…   So I came into the house n heard her room kinda playing loud music… Quite loud lar… That is… Den of coz I was thinking… Qith music that loud? A perfect hearing person wun be able to hear the numerous times I BANGED my hand on the door n the MANY times I rang the doorbell… So, of coz I thought… If u din hear then fine… I mean, juz admit lar… I wun kill you… Juz DUN give me LAME excuses… so not my type… Duh~  N then I admit… I was pissed… I opened the windows at my room n my parent’s room with a loud sound… The sliding kind will give off a sound on huge impact to the side of the wall… So, yea… N she came out of her room YELLING at me… “I din hear u ring the bell at all ok… Dun go around banging the windows juz bcoz u r not happy” Yea… See I emphasize on the word YELLING… See ar… From the start… Who was the victim? Me… I stood outside waiting like hell n then who yells at me when I come in? HER! Did I yell at her? NO. Did I even SHOUT at her or raise my voice? NO.   See? Muz get the facts clear hor… I did nothing of that sort… Who was the LOW CLASS Bitch? Certainly not me…=) Okie… So, she started shouting at me abt how she din hear the doorbell n wadsoeva n that I m a attitude problem n wadsoeva n that how my mom alwaize calls her to complain abt me wadsoeva… Blar Blar Blar… Was I listening? Nope. I was juz putting the ironed out clothes back into my parents cupboard in my parents room… N then later she shouted at me if I was listening n I juz TOTALLY gave her the Cold Shoulder… I mean, I felt that she din derserve my attention towards her ONE bit… Nope. Hey… I wun waste my precious time talking to unreasonable n deaf bitches…  N guess wad again? She stood at the doorway of my parents room like she had the right to yell at me n I was so I in the wrong n when I put back all the clothes n was abt to juz walk pass her out of the room, she GRAB my hand n shout at me n asked if I was listening to her… Was I? Nope. Did I ignore her once me? Yes. I should have won the award for ignoring pple… Boy m I proud of myself… Dun ever let scums bother your life… Not worth one bit… Not even 1 second…  So, I juz shook my hand off, walked awae n off into my room… At that time, I realli felt the VICTORY man… I mean, I could totally see the victory flag being raised n all that in my head… Come on… Lets juz think abt it… She wanted to pick a fight with me or else she wun come over n start raising her voice at me right? So I usse the ignoration tactic… N I know for a fact that it sux when u r yelling/shouting or even cursing at someone who is indefferent towards u… Bcoz that someone doesn’t even give a damn abt wad u say abt her, u get even more pissed… Its more of like a psychological thing… How our minds work…  So who was more pissed in the end? HER. Who had fun? ME. Who won the fight? ME. Who lost the battle even before it started? HER. Who ultimalty had the best of it all? ME!!! Haha… I rock!  I know this is a realli long entry… Opps… will log off now… Hope I havent strained your eyes… Hehe… in ani case, the current situation between me n the hard of hearing bitch is cold war… N I mean the cold war without event the communication at all… I juz pretend as usual like how I did juz now that I dun have a sister n such a person doesn’t exist in my life… VICTORY!!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-24 9:36 p.m.  Yday was See Ching n Steven’s one year anniversary… So sweet… Sigh… I will stop thinking abt Nicholas… I will stop thinking abt wad happened… I wish I can juz do that…  Aniwae, I skipped SSS yday too… Din feel like going at all… Besides, Gerald Hwei n Cheryl were going to watch 50 First Dates…Ching din go… Of coz lar… She went to celebrate with Steven mar… I din go n watch though… Din wanna waste money… But I went to eat lunch with them 1st… We went to Mos Burger downstairs of Tampines Mall n ate there… nothing much happened… So, din feel like updating yday…  Today was English Oral day… I think I did quite okie but not sure if Pat. Wong is nice enough to give me an ok mark… yea… I purposely went to find her to be my tcher as she gave me a rather high mark last year… At least, I felt that it was rather high lar…32 or 33 upon 40… Cant realli remember thoroughly… Aniwae, our topic was on y we wanna scare ourselves… I juz crapped… Hope I did fine…  Well, havent been feeling at my best todae… Dunno wad’s wrong with me… I came home after Orals n then slept like a pig for 3hours… Later after studying history, I slept some more… I nearly went to bang my head against the wall after waking up n realized how much precious time I lost juz by sleeping n not studying for the mid-yrs… Perhaps I m giving myself too much stress such that I cant cope with my own body system… Wad did I juz say? I have no idea… Scratch that… Wad I meant was juz that my body cant take the stress I m giving it… Yea… That’s wad I meant…  Okie… So, taking my break time to update my blog now… Nothing much happened todae… But I muz say that I m suffering from realli BAD backaches due to carrying too much books to n fro from my school… Sheesh… I think I should not bring so much stuff to school from now on… I wonder if I can like ‘spoil’ my spine bcoz of that… Hmmm… Aniwae, my lower back of my spine n the muscles around it r realli like ‘bunched up’ such that I cant sit or stand properly… Sigh…  Well, as usual… no quote again… dun wanna rack my brains for a suitable quote… Gonna study biology now… cya soon… I hope…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-22 5:58 p.m.  I was in a realli down mood todae... Todae is the day...I broke up with Nicholas... Yea... To those who were wondering why I was in such a bad mood todae n was rather not myself... Thats the real reason... Lots of things happened...I will spare u the details n juz tell u that it was a amicable breakup... M I supposed to feel guilty? Well, I m not sure... But I sure dun feel good abt breaking up with him... I will miss him... I truly will...  I know that quite a lot of pple have been coming up to me n asking me why did I breakup with nicholas since I do have feelings for him... Frankly speaking? Its juz too hard to explain... To those who understand... Well, good for u... To those who dun... too bad... But I would be surprised to find someone who is able understand me... To know how I feel n why I do the things I do... Yea... I dun wanna talk abt it... So that's it.  Change of topic... I wanna complain lar!!! How do the SC's (student council) do stuff? Apparently I was kinda confused over lots of stuff n thought that I could squeeze with Sze Hwei's table or wadsoeva... Now the latest news is that I cant squeeze with them... N wads more... I have to join Swee Fan's table with the 4J class n xiao ying Okie...well... Not too happy with the arrangements here... I mean... I know nuts abt those pple n I dun like them... Other then Swee Fan of coz...But I m oso not as close to her... Besides, I feel quite a few pple there realli kiam pa... N I totally cant stand those pple... Dun wanna be feeling so weird the entire night... Sigh...  I wish I have a nice place to sit with all my frens... Haiz...N then suddenly someone told me that I might be sitting with rayner's table... Okie... Fine with that...I m totally ok with my classmates... I emphasize on the words... My Classmates. No more than that... I dunno the rest of the choir pple... n I paricularly cant stand one of the person there... Sigh... Too bad for me... Guess I m stuck with this arrangements... N erm.. to those reading this entry... I mean no offense...  No quote todae again... too tired... Besides, I gotta study like crazy for my history n chem test tmr... cya~!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-21 10:45 p.m.  Hmm… Lots of things happened todae… Well, one of the most impt. thing was having our Orals… It was rather easy n I felt that I was realli lucky… Got Wang Wenxian as my tcher… Actualli, Soon Li was available… But me n Joanne knew that she was veri niao~ one n wun give high marks… So we purposely hide behind the door n wait for a space for the nicer tchers… In the end Joanne went in b4 me n I waited for Wang Wenxian’s space to be free… Luckily Henry came out right after Joanne went in so I was sorta the last in that group n managed to get her… Yay~!  Thinking back, I kinda wonder if I did well or not… Oh sigh… Juz get over it… Since its over, well… I will juz be expectant n await for the results… I m currently eating my dinner soup again… It’s the leftovers of yday… Dun get me wrong… Not complaining abt leftovers… I mean, who m I to complain when there r pple out there starving bcoz of no food in Africa etc. Besides, I alwaize eat leftovers… So no biggie here…  Okie… Now abt the Big thing… The Graduation night… Or some would like to call it the Prom Night… The night where we r all Glamorous n all… Hmm… Nice thought of having to dress up etc. =) I know I know… I opposed to the idea like mad when pple kept asking me to go… Yep… I still do… I mean, First of all… Four Seasons Hotel? Pathetic… M I complaining? YES! Sheesh wad a place… Go to Ritz-Carlton or some other better hotel lar… I mean, Four Seasons… Please… n to those who were like “Four Seasons not bad wad…” Hellooo~~… WAD world do u live in? That is certainly not the best hotel around…  Okie… So u get wad u pay for… That’s certainly not true… I believe that if we had more competent n I mean COMPETENT staff in our school who were willing to negotiate abt the price in some other more renowned hotel… I would have gladly gone… Aniwae, which brings me back to why I m going… First of all… I truly wonder why too… But after reading Gerald’s blog yday, I realized that Gerald, Ching, Hwei n Cheryl r all going due to Hwei being roped in by Wendy… Another long story... Aniwae… after reading, I was considering whether I should go or not… Since my best frens r going… N well, I can alwaize be with them… Den, I called up hwei n asked wad happened n why they were going to go since we long decided to boycott this event…  So its here where the long story gets in n after talking to Hwei, I was like Totally considering on whether I should go to the Grad night too… N then… after further deliberation, I went online to talk to Ray. He was giving me some reasons to go bcoz I will feel left out… Which wasn’t realli a valid reason, but yea… I know wad he was trying to mean… Like having your frens all come back n talk all abt the Prom n I will be like I wish I had gone etc.   In addition, talking to see ching in the car todae was totally like comfirming my thoughts that I should go… So, I m… Well, I juz said that I would go if there is a seat…Its like we have to form a group to have a seating at the table… which is a table of 10… So, yea… I din have a seat… N according to wad I heard, registration had alreadi closed… But see ching said that she will help me go ask Wendy n grab a place for me…  Thank goodness, they still took pple in… So right now, its like I will be squeezing at their table… Which will have 11 pple… Which is no big deal since I doubt we will all be sitting down the whole time as u know… We would most probably be walking around, talking, taking pictures etc. You know… I can imagine the scene… Its gonna be typical… So… good lar… I got a seat n will have to pay for the deposit tmr…=)  Opps… I haven’t asked my mom for the money yet… Oh`o… Hehe… I hope she wun nag at me… Hmmm… Aniwae, tmr got emaths common test… which to no surprise, I haven’t studied yet… Hehe… Will be studying later lar… I was taking my time doing the emaths Probability hw juz now… N after that, I completed the Chem wks that i was supposed to hand in todae… Opps!...=P Aniwae, I was rather proud of myself… It’s a long time since I realli sat down n realli bother to do the hw that Mrs. Lim gives… N I found out this ultra careless mistake of mine that made me re-do the question15 again… Arghh… See lar… Take up so much of my time lor…   Speaking of which, I have this Crazy Chem test on Friday… Did I mention Crazy? Yea… It is crazy… I mean, Total Duh~ 16 chapters… N our DEAREST Ms Chan told us abt the test on Monday… So nice of her right? Okie… So the test type is MCQ… So wad? We still have to study for it right? To those who dun n r doing realli fine in chem… Boo to U!!! Right… So I would most probably have to study like a cranky idiot tmr… Great… Why couldn’t she be kind for once n tell us b4 the weekends so I could have at least flipped through? Darn her...  Lessons todae was alright… Nothing special to report… Surprisingly, Ms Chan din yell much at me during Chem Prac… Hmmm… Maybe I m improving…=) Okie… I will stop crapping n go… cya~  Quote: Wait, I just remembered something! I’m boring and your legs can’t work! Haha… I know… totally LAME quote… sorrie pple… m running out of nice quotes…
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-20 10:28 p.m.  Juz finished tuition n had my soup dinner… Sheesh… I dunno wads wrong with me but I dun seem to be having the appetite at all… Wadeva… Aniwae, todae was a total study day for me… Even though I din go to school, but nothing much happened as I was practically trying my best to not fall asleep due to effects of the medicine n cramp all stuff into my mind… I succeeded… I hope…  Lame day… Nothing to report… I juz realised that my blog entries r getting shorter n shorter… This is pure crap… My life is totally wasted away bcoz I have to mug… Wad the hell… I guess that’s y I hate studying… I guess u can call me a party gal… Haha… Steph will vouch for that… Aniwae, its 19 days to the start of exams… M gonna study later again… Sigh… Exams Suck!!! Statement of the century…  Tmr is our Chinese Oral… The school mid-yrs one… Not the O’level one… Luckily… My voice sounds weird n I have to keep clearing my throat… Even if I dun do well tmr, well, its not so bad… Compared to having a weird voice for O’s…right? Not the least bit stressed… Sheesh… I m do DuH~… Well, guess that’s all for todae... Btw, todae’s quote will be taken from the America’s Top Model that I saw yday night… Tyra Banks said it n I like her n oso felt wad she said was rather meaningful… So here it is…  Quote:Human is Beautiful, Perfect is boring.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-19 11:09 p.m.  Haha… Does that title shock u? Hmm… No lar… FYI, I m NOT hooked on drugs… Is juz that after eating the docter’s medicine, I feel much better… I told the docter I wanted the extra ultra strong kind… Guess he muz have given me quite strong drugs… Which reminds me, its been ages since I ate cough syrup… N now I have this red liquid thingy… Eww…  Aniwae, I m here now to officially fill u in on wad happened to me todae… 1st of all… the Chinese Test… Argh… I was so darn pissed off by myself… I felt that the front was easy… The back was easy too… But I din know how to do the construct sentences part…(zhao ju) Darn… I might not get my A1 after all… Damn lar… Well, to be honest, that kinda affected my mood for the day… Darn it… N then after school, I gotta take the S.S retest… So DuH~ I din know how to do a single question lor… I mean, I was supposed to study during the weekend, but guess wad? I din bring my book home…   Aniwae, I was totally shocked when I saw the questions… They were the same as the ones the rest had on Thursday!!! Wad the hell… If I had known… I would have juz asked Mabel to tell me how to do… But then, when I asked pple abt the questions on Thursday, they DID tell me… But I juz thought that it wasn’t gonna be that impt. animore since it came out alreadi… Sheesh… Stupid… I m such a stupid klutz…  Oh sigh… Aniwae, I have decided… Will go to school tmr… I simply cant afford to miss the 2 periods of Core Lit. n my 2 periods of Bio… I know Mrs. Lee will most probably kill me if I miss her lesson…Hehe… The rest of the lessons aren’t impt. lar… I know there is like a Amaths Vectors test tmr, but then… Oh heck… I will get zero zlich for it if I do take it… The same of I dun, right? So no point… Well, I guess that’s it then… Nothing else special todae… Hmm… I feel a slight breeze now… Thank the Lord…  Quote:   **Haha… I realli like this quote… Hmm… I m running out of  quotes now… Darn…**
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-19 5:45 p.m.  Tired…veri tired… Oh sigh… Wad should I blog todae? Nothing special happened… Ms Chan din realli pick on me too… Hurray!!! Hmm… I keep coughing n coughing like mad… The virus is back again… Oh sigh… Stupid parasite dwelling inside… Damn…  Will be seeing the docter later… Might be taking an MC for tmr… I know that exams r coming n I shouldn’t keep missing school… But I realli cant help it… My head aches like hell… My throat is sore… I keep coughing… sneezing n having this nose which runs without stop… Okie… I will stop going on n on abt being sick… I know its getting boring…  Well, guess I will end here todae… Have to study later… Sigh… Going to rest now… Cant think… No quote todae…=~(
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2004-01-18 9:49 p.m.  Supposed to be blogging as fast as I can now… Hmm… Quite proud of myself… I managed to study quite a lot this weekend… Safe to say, I MIGHT be able to make it for the exams n not have to pia~ like mad at the last minute… Aniwae, to those who miss me yday… I m totally sorrie… I was bz n all that lar… N to be honest, I was plain lazy… Felt too tired to blog… Hehe… Aniwae, thanx to my great frens encouragement, my mood is high again… Not feeling depressed n all that now… Yea man…  Hmm… Eating Guava now… Nice fruit… Hehe… I eat most kind of fruits lar… n vegetables too… So, not that particular… Wad did I want to say juz now? Hmm… Oh… I have decided to be nice n talk to my mom again… But still not that much lar… Besides, I realli dun have that much time to talk to her… M usually studying all the time… Wad m I studying? Bio lor…   Cant help it if I have a lousy memory right? I gotta remember things much eariler b4 hand… I know that some pple can juz look through the text 2 days b4 the exam n perhaps score higher than me… I find that realli discouraging at times… But who can I blame? I truly suck at studying… Sigh…  Aniwae, I feel the extreme pressure n stress now… Its onli a few days b4 the exams… I muz realli study like crazy… But one thing I gotta say is the way I relieve stress… Realli not good… I juz drank a six-pack beer todae… Din feel drunk at all… Luckily… But I think I will soon be getting liver cancer or lung cancer or something of that sort…  Tmr I got this S.S retest… Left my textbk in school on fridae… I thought that I could like go back to school on Satday to take it from the locker as I was going back for SSS as well… Who knew? I din… The school servants actualli pulled down the metal thingy that blocks the staircase… Oh sigh… Well, luckily I m smart enough to rmb that I have the S.S powerpoint notes thingy… M going to be reading that now lar… So, byebye… Today will be a short but Great quote… cya soon~  Quote: Death is the most beautiful adventure in life. (Whoa... so erm... sadistic... BUT I like!!!=P)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh well... Suddenly felt the urge to read her blog n guess wad? Hmmm... Someone was talking bad about me... Hmmm... Guess I juz know when who is talking bad behind my back huh~? N to think i nv talk bad about her... Ok... So i m not totally holy i can't stand her behaviour sometimes too... So i guess its mutual... Oh well... Heck...N I repeat... I know that Hwei is realli upset about the bdae celebration n all that... But like i said n must i repeat again? I spologise for my behaviour ok??? Sheesh... Why wun u juz let it rest? Hello...???Oh sigh... some pple nv listen... but i will be nice... I wun quarrel with them...  Dun see the point... Life's juz like that... U will alwaize have something that u can't stand about your other fren n so-called best frens... But wad the heck... I dun care... Realli can't be bothered... I mean, I dun regret wad i ever did... But like wad I alwaize do... I keep trying n striving to improve myself... I will try to watch out for my behaviour the next time...  But i wun take back about wad i said about Swee Fan... She n me? Alwaize frens... I mean... juz pure frens... I wun take it animore than that... N about frenship? Frankly speaking? I m totally like DUN CARE right now... Developing the Heck care attitude... Kinda wish that wad u not happy with me? Tell me in the face... Dun complain in your blog wadsoeva... I would honestly like to hear wad u feel about me... n digest that n strive to improve myself n not having to see pple crap about me behind my back...  Or something like that... Ok... Wad the hell m i saying? Blurred out... Sigh... Life juz sucks... N then again... Nv trust pple too easily... Guess i still haven't foung someone whom i totally trust yet... Cause then i will get hurt easily... Right now? Who cares wad u think... Ok... crap... I do... But i still wun be like deeply hurt... juz kinda like on the surface wound thingy...  Wad m I talking about? Crap... If u understand u do... U dun... too bad... I know my english sux!
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>