<Blog>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was absolutely battered on Chris' birthday  I've never had a worse hangover in my entire life  Got severely shedded last night as well.  It was some dude's leaving do at work so I went to that and then we were supposed to be going out afterwards but I stopped to make sure this little old woman was alright and by the time I'd done that everyone had just buggered off leacving me Matt and Lynsey  So we went to the White Swan (Matt's local gay pub) where they've got a 3am license.   Easily the most surreal experience of my entire life  Drag Queens, dancing doctors, lesbians...  Fucking twilight zone    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's my brother's birthday today  25  So i'll be back in Enfield. No doubt there will be tales to tell tomorrow.  Went to the Tuns with Eleanor last night (Matt went to this bizarre quiz thing where this bloke made a pass at him)  (after having made a pass at Kate B first)  (which is quite funny)  It was quiz night in the Tuns but Eleanor's rubbish at it so we didn't bother entering.  Won't be in the Arms tonight though (which is a shame). John's barred (for a really stupid reason) so we'll probably be in the George (which I hate with an absolute passion), and we can't go the Kings Head (because....erm well lets just say for reasons). Bar Form's shit as well.  Anyway you spanners, I'll see you all in hell  (The George)  laters.  Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday  Gonna get obliterated  Everyone can join me in hell  Peace and Love people  (whoever you may be)  R    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two?  Sodding hell we're rubbish  Call it ten and you'll be nearer the mark  Had a lock in at the Arms last night. Watched Swordfish with Darragh, Trav and Paul.  Got home around half two.  I am COMPLETELY rubbish.  Go to hell guys,  Richy    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As if you couldn't have guessed  We're sad and weak people  Two it is.  I absolutely swear...   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Darling you gotta let me know Should I stay or should I go? If you say that you are mine I'll be here 'til the end of time So you got to let know Should I stay or should I go?  Always tease tease tease You're happy when I'm on my knees One day is fine, next is black So if you want me off your back Well come on and let me know Should I Stay or should I go?  Should I stay or should I go now? Should I stay or should I go now? If I go there will be trouble An' if I stay it will be double So come on and let me know  This indecision's bugging me Esta indecision me molesta If you don't want me, set me free Si no me quieres, librame Exactly who'm I'm supposed to be Digame quien tengo ser Don't you know which clothes even fit me? Sabes que ropas me queda? Come on and let me know Me tienes que decir Should I cool it or should I blow? Me debo ir o quedarme?  Should I stay or should I go now? "Me entra frio por los ojos" (y es verdad) If I go there will be trouble Si me voy va a haber peligro And if I stay it will be double Si me quedo va a ser doble So you gotta let me know Me tienes que decir Should I stay or should I go? "Me entra frio por los ojos"   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really wish Matt would stop talking about beer.  We've all pretty much ground to a halt up here (apart from Eleanor who seems to be working far too hard)  (I still think she wants to take my job)  (Just for the sheer hell of it)  Problem is that if we go in for one (which I could do with then we stay for another five....as we did yesterday)  Managed to get to the Arms at 10 last night. John and Chris rolled in absolutely hammered. Other than that a fairly uneventful night. Although it was quite funny when John asked Amanda's mate if she was a lesbian and she looked like a rabbit caught in the headlights (well the Johnlights)  I felt quite sorry for her.  Walked Amanda and her mate home after and for reasons known best only to themselves they decided to take the most circuitous route imaginable rather than just walking down the road like normal people would.  It's not as though Enfield is the most scenic of places is it?  Crazy crazy fools    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am very bored.  I am doing dull risk stuff and I really can't facy any more of it.  I want to go home right now and I cannot believe there is another three hours and three minutes before I can go home.  I make make up some malady in order to get out of this place sooner than would otherwise be the case.  Looking forward to seeing my name in print - I do hope the Letters Editor chooses to publish it.  A friend once said that they publish your obituary if they print three letters so who can say!!  Dull, dull, dull, I want beer and I want it now.  I have some incredibly calorific banana milk shake here but its awful and I'd prefer a nice pint of something fermented and cool.  Oh well.  The writing of this note has killed four minutes, only two hours and 59 minutes now.   urlLink Hit me baby one more time! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been working on this smoking policy thing all day  Non-smokers make me sick  They can all burn while I light up with their burning flesh  Bastards   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just wrote a long post all about Saturday, which I'm not going to sodding repeat  And so:  Went on an epic session with Matt, Eleanor and Kev Saturday It just fell together randomly Impromptu is good (it was nice to have everyone down) (apart from Lynsey that is) (sodding Kent) And it was Valentines day anyway so she couldn't have come (sodding being single) Had my first drink at 12.30 and my last just over twelve hours later Seriously trashed Broke up one fight Stopped Kevin having another Spent some time sitting on the floor for reasons known best only to myself I'm not to drink black sambuka anymore (or Pernoud) Went to Bar Form after Where Eleanor lost her coat Even though it was right next to her Don't remember much after that at all  Anyway the guys saw my pub  (the original post was so much better than this)  (I mean there were jokes and themes and shit)  (and even this experimental narrative flashback sequence that I've been playing around with)  (You would have loved it believe me)  Anyway if you guys reading ever want to come down then please feel free  I'll even buy you a pint  (as long as you're not a pyscho killer that is)  (then you can just go to hell)  Peace and Love comrades,  Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Email me you spanners!   I have, after much consideration, decided that working on a Friday afternoon is, and shall remain, illegal for myself and my illustrious colleagues. However, work shall only be permitted on the following grounds:  a) Should your absentee boss actually be in work, standing over your shoulder because he has very little to do b) Somebody offers you a large incentive and when I say large I mean MASSIVE.   In the absence of either, although I presume the former may be alot more tangible than the latter, I am in fact doing SOD ALL  Here's to Olympian thumb twiddling
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am beginning to wonder if the Tuns is a black void. We enter and we do not leave... willingly... if given the opportunity we would gladly buy shares in its future because we know that we would be instrumental in its future.  Talking of people who never bugger off. I have one down here. He's never here yet when he is you so wish he wasn't! I would like a pint right now but G Force is preventing me from attaining my Friday afternoon goals...         urlLink Email me you spanners!   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can see that this will be addictive, I have to keep away.  Lots of problems: *  I am getting a cold *  I am doing no work and so need to come into work tomorrow *  I need a drink but I have to meet someone at 3pm *  I am going to throw up tonight  Oh well, c'est la vie   urlLink Reach out and I'll be there! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       VALENTINES DAY CAN GO TO SODDING HELL     urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm new to this, is this right?  After a week of not drinking I am feeling mildly merry and in need of another drink.  I may go when He goes.  Why will He never go.  He was supposed to be on leave today but He's always here.  Its a bit like genital herpes, or so I've heard: it never goes away ... and nor does HE.  Rich.  Get some work done.  When He goes we can have another pint.  I said me, camp not Mein Kampf  urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Davids birhtday last night  Wasn't sure if he was coming out or not so I stopped in the Tuns with Eleanor and Matt (and Alan turned up later) for a few and told my brother to call me if David was doing anything.  Which he didn't.  Left the Tuns about half ten and got to the Arms for chucking out time. Trav kindly let me buy a few beers (given that it was David's birthday) and we all just sat outside the Arms until about three in the morning. Bought some beers and fags from the Kebab shop and just sat there complaining about women (singles Valentines party in the Arms tonight. The likelyhood of me being there is around about zero. I can't think of anywhere on earth that I'd rather not be than there), until the point when we all decided that being alone is not a good thing.  Nice night though.  That kind of drunken three in the morning profundity.  Came in to work with the absolute worst hangover in the entire world  I could barely move this morning.  Proper drinking man.  Should be a Tuns night tonight I think. Will report back tonight or tomorrow.  Go to hell guys,  Richy    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fuck it, I'm going to the Tuns to do what I do best   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bang just gave me a free pint and a double JD for half price  Definite mission coming on tonight  Watch out the Arms    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jane Pugh's birthday today so we went to the pub at lunch-time.  Haven't eaten today and I've definitely got a little buzz on.  Couple of pints of Star.  Then went sweeping for the left over wine when everyone left.  Hmmmmm yes Richard is a pikey.  Very definitely thinking about knocking off and going to the pub.  Most of the office went to the pub today and the general noice level in here has gone slightly up.  Very hard to work when drunk. Must remember to eat before drinking. But then you don't get as drunk.  Being drunk is good.  The great escape  I'll see you all in hell,  Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woke up on the floor this morning (for reasons known best only to myself)  Not at all sure why. I mean why would I get off the bed to sleep on the floor?  What's wrong with me? (Alright don't answer that)  It'd take to long.  Seriously drunk last (well obviously)...please don't let me drink sambuka anymore. it does horrible things to me.  (and yes this journal will be mainly all about drinking)  but it's what I mainly do  (ok it's all that I do)  give a guy a break will ya.  At work now and I've had the worst hangover all day. Its inhuman forcing somebody to work under such conditions.  It's just not right. Fuck all this illegal immigrant worker exploitation shit. How about the hungover?  You don't hear people trying to help the drinkers amongst us do you.  One pound an hour? Fuck that shit. Try working with my hangover.  Oh I'm just not well  Somebody please help  (pint of Stella please)  Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Worked very hard at work today  (yeah I know shocking)  Could really do with a quick pint right now but none of the usual suspects are here. Matt's gone to get his wisdom tooth out, Lynsey's ill and Eleanor does her orchestra thingy today.  Bugger.  Don't know if I can wait all the way to the Arms.   What must I do guys?  Tell me what must I do?  (Oh and also for all those who know me. Anything I say after 9pm on a drinking night is to be completely and utterely disregarded)  (Just a general tip for ya'll)  Probably up-date tonight  (yeah I know you can't wait)  Go to hell,  Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I said, Friday and indeed Saturday were kinda interesting.  Although neither really officially count as work drinks. Friday only sorta qualifies because El came down, and Saturday not at all.  And indeed Friday's oddness had nothing to do with El at all.  Which is a first.  Anyway,  Friday I was drinking in the George (probably one of the worst pubs in the world, but hugely cheap, so we've taken to getting hammered in there for a couple of hours and then going back to the Arms. No matter how great a pub the Arms is it is still pretty expensive. Especially if you drink as much and at the rate that David and I do). Anyway we were in the George when David's ex-girlfriend comes in with...well some wierd bloke.  Apparently she'd just broken up with Chris (who she broke up with David for) and was going out with this new bloke.  (One thing you have to remember is that although David is clearly one of my best friends, I actually new March before I ever met David, and she's always been my friend even when they first broke up and it was seriously difficult for me for a while. There was this one funny night when I was off talking to March about something around the back and David was at the bar with Gordon and I have to keep going back and forth between the two. And I sit down next to David and he starts going on to me about how I'm his friend and how if I ever betrayed him he'd kill me/or it would kill him or something like that anyway. And I just thought that it was just random 'I love you/you're my best friend' drunkeness, until the next day when he apologises to me for accussing me of making a move on March)  Still one of the funniest things I've ever heard.  (not to mention slightly pissing me off for a while that he could think I'd do that)  But he was seriously contrite for a long time after that, and it's still something that I embarasses him.  Anyway March is my friend and I feel obliged to go and see if she's ok. She kinda invites herself over to our table. I think it was just me, Chris, David and Amanda there. David manages to stick it out for a while but eventually he leaves and Amanda has to go with him to make sure he's ok while I stay with March to make sure she's ok.  Which she's not (somewhere in between all this I also decide that it'll be a good idea to buy a round of aftershock).   Anyway I knew she was in a state after breaking up with Chris and I was trying to talk her and she was crying and all I can really do is hug her (funny I thought my brother was going to beat the guy she came in with up. I was hugging her and this guy says to me: 'easy mate, she's coming home with me alright.' My brother's got a bit of a temper anyway, I thought he was going to go mental). Anyway I have to get back over the Arms to meet Eleanor, so I ask the guy if he's going to make sure she gets home ok and he swears to me that he will, so I leave. March generally is ok and she'd been staying at his guys house for days anyway so I really didn't think there was a problem (so don't look at me like that)  (If I'd have known what a state she was in then I would have dragged her over the Arms and that guy could have gone to hell for all I cared)  Next thing I know there are police over the Arms because March is drunk and disorderely somewhere in town and this guys fucked off somewhere (and if I see that bloke again I'm gonna kick his arse. what a spanner), so she's given the Arms as an address where people know her (I should start giving the Arms as my address).  Anyway that apart it was a good night. I was massively hammered though. Why did I think it was a good idea to drink shots of black sambuca? Odd moment when I was sitting talking to David and Eleanor and I was just looking at David for about ten seconds without saying anything wondering if I should tell him about March. Decided that it was best not to. He was severely wound up anyway (he'd come back over the Arms and gone straight on the double JDs and coke) and there really wasn't anything that he could do about it anyway.  Not a happy man that night.  There was loads of police around the Arms on Friday (El's first visit to the pub and there are tons of police around. Probably not the best introduction to the wonderful world of the Arms. Although she did say she liked it. You can get an account from her. And then you'll see that I wasn't lying about it being the best place in the world) I also wound up going to sodding Edmonton on the train. I was waiting on the train with El for it to go when the doors shut and I just have to sit on the bastard two stops down the line. Eleanor lives in sodding hackney and she still got home before me. I was completely wasted.  Oh and Saturday. Same scenario. Got over the George around 3 (quite a few of us over there so it was kinda like the Arms On Tour...of course we never really stray too far from our spiritual home). Leave about half seven (fairly drunk) for the Arms and get over there and then I have no real coherent idea of what happened. Somehow I upset Kat because I was criticising her pool playing (but I was joking around and I ALWAYS criticise her pool playing, it's a running sodding joke and was so sodding CLEARLY not being malicious). Anyway her girlfriend comes over five mins later and tells me that Kat's really upset and I should be more careful of people's feelings and I'm just like: WHAT THE FUCK?  Quite funny though, I go to apologise to Kat (because I'm a nice man) and she apologises to me for me having to apologise to her.  Then later on (at the really REALLY drunk stage) I see Ollie sitting outside by herself so I go outside to see why she's upset, and the thing is that I really can't work out why she's upset. She is telling me, and I am talking to her (and being completely coherent), but I just don't get it. So I'm sitting outside comforting this woman but I don't know what's wrong and I have no idea what I'm saying. Anyway eventually Kat and I get her back inside and the night goes on and then Amanda comes over to me and asks if I can stay afterwards and that Paul says it's ok if I do. (And I'm like 'woo hoo!! Lock in!!)  Unfortunately no lock in.  Damn it.  Amanda wanted to talk to me about what Ollie had said to me because apparently they'd fallen out (Ollie, Kat and Amanda are really good friends) and that was why Ollie was upset. And now I'm having this long conversation with Amanda and I have absolutely no idea at all what I'm saying again (while being coherent) made all the worse because I have no idea what Ollie had said to me or I'd said to Ollie.  It's just odd how I get to a certain point in the night and I just talk utter nonsense. I mean I literally have no idea what I'm saying at all, even though I can be logical and coherent and really quite useful because whatever I said to Ollie clearly worked. Sod knows how I got home on Friday. I think I've got some kind of homing device built into my head.  Is this normal?  Tell me damn it.  (Oh and go to hell guys)  Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday night's at work are kind of erm...interesting.  Ok by interesting I mean mentalist.  As you will no doubt find out. It's a rare night out when there isn't crying or arguing of some sort. Which is wierd because we're all perfectly normal people (with some obvious exceptions)  Eleanor  Listening to Embrace: the good will out  'My Weakness is none of your business' has got to be my favourite song at the moment (as if you really care)  Well of course you care. You're here aren't you?  Can't really be bothered to write at the moment.  Be back later to tell you about my Friday night.  Go to hell,  Richy (Ok you're all just very bored)  (Or prurient interest types)   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Unfortunately, however, I have nothing of any interest to report.  Contrary to Richard's misplaced beleif in my ability to report regular mentalism.  My apologies to all.   And I am particularly sorry for myself...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here.  Bint.   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well good morning then folks.  How are we?  Went back to the Arms in the end at around quarter past nine. I was just going out of my head. Even with the benefit of your company (apart from the prurient sick interest people who are now really starting to piss me off)  Got in the Arms and everyone was hammered while I was stone cold sober. Not an experience I find particularly natural.  My brother had another fight with his girlfriend (as usual)  I think they've got a weekly quota or something.  (no really, these guys break up about twice a week. We've all just got to the point of ignoring it now. It's just what they do. I think they're defined by it)  Most odd   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes.  Indeed.  And once again my apologies, but come on none of you are being held here against your will are you (apart from Phil...but didn't we all agree not to talk about him)? Surely you've got to look at yourselves before you blame me. I mean what's wrong with you guys? What's wrong with your lives that you're all here?  Exactly.  Pot. Kettle. Black  Yes it's true I'm at home doing not at all very much (well talking to you guys). But you can't blame me for reflecting how empty and rubbish your own lives are (well except for the people here for their own sick prurient interest who just take delight in slumming it in our intellectually and emotionally stunted lives)  (and if you're one of those you can fuck off right now. we don't want your sort round here)  Well what's been going on with me? How might I entertain you?  (Well lieing would no doubt help)  But I'm not going to do that.  Because I respect you all too much  (well apart from the sick prurient interest people that is)  Right so I went to the shops and then I stopped in the Arms about 5 o'clock.  And well the  urlLink Arms  is my local; and also the best pub in the world (El, I put a link in...this is so cool). I kinda spend quite a lot of my time in there. Went in and there were just the usual suspects in there (Rudi and David) amongst them, and it was oddly subdued. The music was turned really low, there were only about 5 of us in there and I knew that I was only going to stay for a pint because I've been out everyday so far this week so I didn't have that 'let's get ready to get smashed' delight.  But in it's own way it was the perfect pub moment with us all just sitting at the bar (proper men sit at the bar) drinking and not really saying anything.  Proper bunch of alcoholics are we.   Anyway stayed for a pint (I only really went in to say hello to everyone. I haven't been in since Sunday) amd then came here. To you people. My friends. My family. The people that I will soon be stalking (all going well). And that's kind of it.  Effectively I am here because television is rubbish. Although you have to appreciate that right? I mean tv is a multi billion pound industry. People dedicate their lives to it, they aspire to it, they dream of it, they sell their souls (and occassionally their children) for it, but I choose you  All of you  (yes I know, apart from the sick pruprient interest people. bunch of spanners)  Above it.  Doesn't that uplift you? Aren't you filled with great pride? (but don't let that gradually turn into arrogance by the way. I mean I've seen it happen. I become someone's friend and all of a sudden they're king of the world. Just be grateful with what you have. I'm enough and I like you all just the way you are)  (bored and slightly needy)  (apart from the sick prurient interest people that is)  (is there a particular reason why they're still here? I mean shouldn't you be drinking wine and eating pasta or something).  Anyway the Arms. The Arms is (and yes, this is slightly sad) Cheers. Only cooler and with a better juke box. It's the kind of place where all the bar staff are your mates. And you know everyone in there....oh it's just cool  (yes I drink too much I know)  (wish I was drinking now)  bugger.  Anyway kids, hopefully next time I post you'll have something more interesting to read about. I'll try and get EL to post something for you tomorrow. She went out tonight so she should have some good stories. She normally does.  Go to hell guys,  Your boy Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And I can say email me you spanners  I know I'm sad, but I'm really digging this  (Sorry El, I'll take you off the email thingy if you want)   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright lets see if this works. I'm trying to add an email link to all my posts.  Yes I know, my I.T. Skills are shocking. This is no doubt the kind of thing that you can do with your eyes closed. (Well possibly not with your eyes closed. But really really easily anyway)  I'm as embarassed as you are. Really I am.  Oh and if this works then please do email me (pressure or anything. Just if you want to. Like)   urlLink Email me! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bored, bored, bored.  Working from home today and missing all of my pals (well apart from you guys obviously).  It's quite odd going all day without talking to anyone at all (actually that's not true, my brother called me a while a go). It's not our natural condition. As a species we require people around us.  Didn't really have a bad hangover today, which was good, but did have insane dreams  (which I can't remember)  not really much point in me telling you that I had insane dreams if I can't then tell you what was insane about them beyond the fact that I remember they were insane  I know I was just leading you all on  (like Charlotte)   - unlikely any of you will get that, but too sodding bad. it's funny -  (you'll just have to come drinking with us)  (well ok that would be hard for you to do given that you don't know who we are, or indeed where we are. but believe me boys and girls, it's worth it)  (course 'worth it' is very subjective. you have to be a fan of random mentalism, absurd conversations and little wit)  also you must be mentally defective in one or more ways  (honestly we require a doctors note and everything)  yes I know I'm rambling but I said I'm sodding bored didn't I? What's wrong with you fools?  Oh and here's another thing that I forgot to tell you about last night. I thought Matt was going to pull Karaoke dude. We were speculating about whether he was gay or not most of the night and Matt was getting quite pally with him, so he eventually sits down at our table and I tactfully left them alone to go and play pool.  Could be one for the future though. He may well be in there. What a duet those two could sing (you haven't lived until you've seen Matt do 'It's rainin' men').  Anyway kids I'll no doubt be back later to entertain (the insane).  all R's love 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Apparently it's now official  We can't go out for just one drink.  We are one drink deficient.  I know we've always suspected but now we know.  I'd talked to Matt earlier about stopping after work for a quick pint but we hadn't really decided anything and he was stuck in a meeting by the time it came to half 5 so I managed to persuade (yes I had to persuade very hard) El to stop for a pint and left a note for Matt to meet us in the Tuns if he still felt like it for a swift pint.  6 hours later I leave the pub.  Eleanor was supposed to be meeting her mates for a drink (I'll let Eleanor tell you that story), which obviously never happened and I called her around half eleven and the woman's playing scrable attempting to look sober  (how'd that go?)  Also bizarre txting deficiency  Txted Eleanor to make home sure she was ok. Or she txted me. I can't sodding remember and then I got on the underground, during which time El had replied to whatever I was saying and also txted again and I had ABSOLUTELY NO FUCKING CLUE what either of us had said.  I was living in an odd world of incomprehensibility  (like Texas)  Anyway boys and girls the lesson is never EVER go out for "just the one".  It cannot be done.  You will feel like a failure and be filled with self-loathing and disgust.  I'll see you all in hell  Richy 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello all  My new blog
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just wanted to add a title to my....  well you get the idea  (you know when I said that my life is really boring?)  (well I kinda meant it)  apologies kids  but you're in now.  you know you're intrigued. you know you're thinking to yourselves (right now): how can this possibly be?  surely not?  surely  surely no man could be this inane.  (just wait and see)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, well then. What should I talk about?  erm, I really should be doing some work  especially as my 'friend' Eleanor is trying to steal my job  not talking to you guys (whoever the hell you are)  (don't you have something better that you could be doing?)  believe me there's someone out there after you're job as well. You might think they're your friends now, but behind your back they're putting the knife in.  You don't know man, you weren't there.  Right I have to do this rubbish with some Bound Volumes.  See ya
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cherry or Apple?: Cheese  Single?: As hell  Do You wear PJs or sleep in the nude??: Cheese  Candles or incense?: Both for spanners  Car or truck?: I have no truck with cars  Laugh at a funeral?: Depends if something funny happened  Do you sleep with your stuffed animal?: Who are you saying's got a stuffed animal you spanner? Fuck off  Do you love anyone?: A few friends and family, yep.  McDonalds or Burger King?: McDonalds generally but you can't beat a Whopper at 11.50pm at Liverpool St.  What's the worst thing you have ever done?: Not inclined to say.  Obsession?: Self  How often do you clean your room?: Fuck that shit  What do you wanna name your kids?: Don't care, sellin' the bastards  Favorite cartoon?:(all together now) All for one and one for all Muskerhounds are always ready...  Rather be a Smurf or Scooby Doo?: Fuck 'em both  Tyra Banks or Mya?: What? Are they cars or something? Fuck off  Where are your piercings?: Heart  Drugs?: Shit man, what have you got?  Jerry Springer or Ricki Lake: Springer (hmmm low down white trash)  Have you got any pets?: nope  Brownies or cupcakes?: cheese. what's wrong with you people? I said cheese  What's better? bass or guitar?: What the fuck? How do you eat a guitar?  Is your writing messy or neat?: Neat  Where do you want to live?: The Enfield Arms.  How many kids do you want?: How many can I have? Sellin' 'em anyway ain't I?  Does anyone owe you money?: Fucking Teflon owes me £40 quid (piece of shit); Pete £20 quid (arsehole); Rusty £20 quid (drug dealing scum bag)  Are you happy or sad right now?:Dunno; don't care; what the fuck's it to you anyway?  Would you rather smoke two joints or do your homework?: What the fuck? Light those babies up.  How's school?: The London SCHOOL of Economics is a pile of shit. That's how School is  Do you go to church?: Funny story actually, but been quite recently. Was pissed.  What do you do when your bored?: This you dumbass  Beavis or Butt-head?: Neither  Book or magazine?: Book   Ever seen a ghost?: No (but Lynsey's got one in her house)  Do you believe in witchcraft?: No (but Eleanor's got two in her house)  Do you sleep with the music on?:Nope, I'd die in a fire. Stupid idea. Shut up idiot  King Of The Hill or The Simpsons?: Simpsons. Stupid question   Do men suck?: Ask Matt  Ever been arrested?: Nope, but here's to hoping  Steak or salad: Cheese.  Craziest thing you've ever done?: Starting a PhD  What's the band you hate the most?: Any RnB crap  Worst TV show?: Whatever crap stupid trash people watch. I dunno  Have you ever cheated on someone?: In what sense. Stop being so nebulous. Dumbass. You're starting to piss me off now  Have you ever been cheated on?: See above thicko (me? being deliberately obtuse? never)  Beer or wine?: How little you know me  Favorite number(s): Kinda question imbeciles ask  "Haha" or "hehe"?: See above imbecile  Bright or dark?: Bright  telling or no telling?:What?   ~~~~HAVE YOU EVER~~~~~  KISSED YOUR COUSIN: Fuck off bint  RAN AWAY: Mentally? Emotionally? Physically? Sort it out will ya  PICTURED YOUR CRUSH NAKED: What am I twelve?  ACTUALLY SEEN YOUR CRUSH NAKED: That would make my crush twelve as well. What are you sick or something?  BROKEN SOMEONE'S HEART: Doubt it very much  HAD YOUR HEART BROKEN: Um, yeah  CRIED WHEN SOMEONE DIED: Yeah (although Matt wouldn't)  WANTED SOMEONE YOU KNEW YOU COULDN'T HAVE: Hold on while I stop laughing  BROKEN A BONE: Nope, but you keep on with the stupid questions mate...  DRANK ALCOHOL: I won't even dignify that with an answer  LIED: What in the last ten minutes? You bet ya  CRIED IN SCHOOL: Yeah but when really little and fell down or something. I'm not a fag or something you know.  ~~~~~WHICH IS BETTER~~~~~  SPRITE OR 7UP: cheese  OBESE OR ANOREXIC: Obese  GIRLS OR GUYS: For what?   FLOWERS OR CANDY: Shut up. Candy? Are you a fucking American or something?  SCRUFF OR CLEAN SHAVEN: Beards are for cool people who don't give a shit  QUIET OR LOUD: Quiet. I'm an introverted social incompetent (you got a problem with that tough guy?)  POOLS OR HOT TUBS?: I don't wash  BLONDES OR BRUNETTES: Whichever's more drunk.  Now if you've read all that you're even stupider than me for filling the bastard in.  Go to hell my dears,  Rich    urlLink Email me you spanners!   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to my neices birthday straight from work yesterday  no actually that's not true. stopped in the Tuns for half an hour with Paul (he was waiting to get off to his seminar), he'd been hanging around most of the day drinking. I'd met him and Lynsey in the Lyceum Tavern for lunch earlier.  Anyway stopped in quickly for a quick can of coke and then headed home  It was quite nice. Lauryn's got an absurd number of toys. It's almost indecent.  Then just went home.  Watched some Star Trek. Tried to do some work. Went on the internet  I'm on at about twelve at night when Olivia e-mailed me (which was quite odd, until I realised that I'm not the only raging insomniac out there)...so in a way I was still in the Arms.  We should start up a 'virtual Arms' for all the people who can't make it down.  Eventually got to sleep at half two.  (Oh and I ate loads of cheese)  (I got a party bag from Lauryn's birthday and Sally put a hunk of cheese in it for me)  Watching Star Trek Voyager at 2 in the morning and eating cheese is as surreal as it is banal.  (Holy fuck that entirely sums up my life)  Paul was txting me last night and I was just thinking: man I want to be in the pub as well right.  Oh well kids, it is what it is.  Thinking about drinking on Friday but I'm not sure at the moment.  I'll no doubt let you know.  Peace and Love,  Rich    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Because I fucking drink too much  Spanners   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I quit drinking   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Stopped for a couple after work with Mr Revel, Mr Stephenson and Ms Johns and then headed for the Arms. Got there for half nine.  Walked in and there was Chris (not my brother Chris) who I haven't seen down the Arms in ages. So that was nice.  Whole book club type thing going on last night. Very Enfield Arms.  Amanda, David, Chris and Gay Richard (who always annoys me)  At home today and all alone  It's a sad sad situation     urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bizarre night last night  There was nobody around after work but I wanted a pint and wanted to avoid the rush hour so I went to the Tuns.  Alan came in for a half, but basically it was just me and Stella.  Then two people come in that I don't really want to talk to (not that I don't like them but I just didn't feel like it) so I grab my stuff and take it outside before they see me (ok they more than likely saw me, but I've given up on all that socially acceptable behaviour shit)  I'm a rebel  (what am I rebelling against?)  (what have you got?)  (I mean non-premium lager)  Anyway I grab my stuff and make a break for the border.  But there's nowhere to sit so I go and sit down on the steps of the Student Services Centre with my pint.  It was quite enjoyable actually  Cigarettes are always best enjoyed outside in the cold air  (with a pint)  When Andrew only walks past.  He must think I'm a mentalist or something.  Especially given that Kate and Lowenthal were in the sodding George all this time.  Made it to the Arms for nine.  Nice night.  John was behind the bar.  Gordon, Dave, Amanda and Kat were in  And then Chris and Trav turned up after watching the football somewhere.  Chris was royally trashed.  Developing an odd addiction to the quiz machine in the Arms.  Amanda's already hooked. I don't think that I'll be able to resist for very much longer  It calls to me in the night with its siren song of trivia.  (what must I do?)  Laters  (Potaters)  (yes and I know that's not how it's spelt)  leave me alone damn you all  R   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It seems that I get indigestion every day now.  Perhaps this is retribution for not getting hangovers.  I need some cemitidnine or ranitidine, the two most successful proprietory drugs in the history of mankind.  Cemitidine, developed by Glaxo (in the days before it merged with Wellcome and SmithKline Beecham (which was formed by successive mergers of Smith and Kline and SmithKline and Beecham) it stops production of acid in the Stomach and was used to prevent pain caused by ulcers but also for indigestion, heartburn and reflux sufferers.  It is now not covered by the patent and is now marketed as Pepcid AC.  And I need some now.  Anyway, onto my letter in the Times, I had a reply from a madman in Southampton who said:  "I would be interested to know in reference to your letter in the Times today in what way you consider yourself a servant of the editor. Not only a servant but an obedient and humble such. I agree with your views incidentally."  I replied:  "I am obliged to you for your letter of 17 inst. regarding mine in the Times.  Sadly the art of correspondence is being gradually lost and if through my efforts I can delay the inevitable, I certainly will.  Since Victorian times, people have remained (or begged leave to remain) their correspondents’ obedient and humble servants in formal letters, and I can think of few letters justifying formality as much as those appearing in the Times.  Believe me ..."  Milk of magnesia would be OK.  Last night I got home and discovered that another madman had written to me sending lots of newspaper clippings and incoherent rants.  I shall regale my friends over a pint of shandy at lunchtime with these rants as they are most amusing.  Ah, I am saved, I have some Andrews liver salts - and they always do the trick!  Yippee!!!   urlLink SheRa SheRa Princess of Power! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I know we've been through this before, but I really did go out for two pints last night.  I emailed Matt just before going home about going for a pint and he told me that he couldn't leave until half five, so I said ok and went to the bank and waited for him in the Tuns.  He turns up at quarter to six. By which time I've drunk my pint and started on the one that I'd bought for him. It was ok though because Mandy was in there and I talked to her (she's leaving us and going to Australia in June...the Tuns won't be the same). It's half term at the moment so the Tuns is basically empty and it's much more like a proper pub where you can go in and just chat with the bar staff for half an hour or so.  It may not be the Arms, but when it's like it is now it's pretty cool.  Anyway Matt turns up and I'm still semi with the plan (because by this point I'd had two and a half and if I have three then I'm definitely staying) and then the Bennett and the Lowenthal turn up.  And then the Cylwik boy turns up as well  And I'm caught in the trap  (and I can't walk out)  (because I love beer too much baby)  (we can't go on together without beer)  (without beer)  Managed to get out at 9 though for the Arms. Had a few pints there. Usual lot were in.  Trav and Lorna had been to Twickenham for a work conference thing so all their work people were out so I went to Taps (this new bar in Enfield to join them).  Jamo was absolutely slaughtered.  Went home and fell asleep on the sofa.  I'm gradually graduating (I love aliteration) from the floor.  And that, ladies and gentleman, was my night.  I'll see you all in hell,  Rich   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Paul came to the LSE yesterday lunch-time.  Haven't seen him in ages and we've always talked about doing a proper all-dayer so I knocked off work and went down to the Tuns  (Paul's one of ours)  (a drinking man that is)  went over the George to sit at the bar for awhile   (proper drinking men sit at the bar)  Managed to get absolutely trashed. Why did I think it was a good idea to start shotting JD and Coke?  Left Matt, EL and Paul in the George and headed for the Arms. Stopped at Wetherspoons to buy a bottle of Holsten Pills for the train home (come on, half an hour is a long time to go without a drink when you're half way through a session)  Got to the Arms and don't really remember very much about the evening. I'm getting that quite a lot nowadays. I can't remember the conversations I have.  Do remember this guy took his trousers off at the pool table to change into something else (and then just fell asleep)  quite odd  (well for anywhere but the Arms I suppose)  Oh and Trav pulled  remember that, but not much else  Ah, the demon alcohol  See ya kids,  Rich    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's Friday and we are pretty thin on the ground. Work is so quiet that I have resorted to reading La Belle de Jour. It's really quite good. I can understand why they want to make it into a book.   Made me laugh anyway ... chuckling away at my desk about the banalaties of sexual perversion... sexual perversion is always a good remedy on a Friday afternoon whilst waiting for 5 o'clock to come round.....  Makes the time go quicker ....    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That whole Arabian cut the right hand from a thief thing?  Well it's growing on me.  (boom boom)  Within the confines of the Arms anyway.  Last night we were sitting at the Bar when 30 quid went missing from the side of the till. Trav had put it down to get some change for it and when he turns around it's gone.  Ok that wasn't sensible but this is the Arms on a Thursday night. On a Friday or a Saturday fair enough, but it was all regulars last night.  (I mean quite possibly a fifth of the people drinking in there were staff or ex-staff)  Now at the bar were Jim and Nick at the corner and then Gordon and I facing the bar, and that's it.   When three guys walk in (one was a semi-regular...I won't mention his name). They were very definitely the only people standing right at the till at the time.  And I'd swear to that.  One of them definitely took it.  John and Gordon were all for dragging them outside and beating them up (because amongst other things Travis would have had to pay that 30 pound shortfall himself so it's not like they stole from Scottish and Newcastle plc, but they stole if from a good friend), but Paul and I were calming influences and Paul just phoned the police. And for that they were lucky because it was touch and go for a while with those two.  So we just decided that we'd sit around the back with them until the police arrived to sort things out. By this time the semi-regular had swiftly departed...so the way thinkings going right now we reckon it was him (things will definitely kick next week....this guy works across the road from the Arms and drinks in the town all the time).  But since the police have been called anyway we may as well wait it out with them.  Everything looks ok so I go around the front and talk to Tanya (who I haven't seen in ages) and Amanda (who I hadn't seen since...erm...yesterday...shit has it been that long already!) when.....  well  I'm not sure.....  This huge chaotic mess spills around the front and Chris is right in it wanting to kill one of these blokes (this complete City Boy wanker). I jump in and try and hold Chris back (it takes both John and I holding him back for all we're worth to do it) and this City Boy wanker (CBW) is just standing there holding out his hand for Chris to shake and smiling at him and I'm just like 'will you fuck off before I hit you myself...or better yet I'll let Gordon do it.' (Apparently this guy had said something to the effect of 'I'm gonna kill you next time I see you....yeah good move dumbass)  I let go of Chris and we manage to shove the CBW out of the door (gently of course)  Odd night. I'd only come in for a couple of pints.  Oh well just the Enfield Arms.  But then this also 'oh well just the Enfield Arms'  John takes up a collection afterwards for everyone to chip in some money to cover the 30 quid that Trav would have to pay himself  5 mins flat it must have been covered.  That's why I say, We are the Arms and we are the best....  Peace and Love  (although not to thieves)  Richy    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nice night tonight  It was horrendously packed with random people for the band and St Patrick's day.  We sat in the corner near the door in our little 'Enfield Arms Forever' enclave.  No hope of getting to the bar (I mean it was six deep at the bar) so Gordon went round the corner and bought a bottle of Vodka and two little cartons of orange juice.  Did a bottle between us in an hour.  Nicely drunk for the night.  No mentalism. Just friends.  It was cool when John came over and asked what we were drinking and Gordon just told him we'd bought our own in and he was like: fair play, I'd have done the same.  John knows we're not ripping off the Arms. We've both spend thousands in there  (shit, THOUSANDS!!!)  How the hell do you do that?  I could have bought a car with that  (or a Thai wife)  (actually no, I'm buying a nice Romanian)  well I'm shopping around anyway...is there like an Argos equivelant for post-order brides?  (and if not, why not damnit!?)  I haven't been out at the Arms in ages so it was nice to hang out.  Sometimes I really need the Arms. Sometimes (without getting all 'Cheers' on you guys) you need to know that there are people there who care about you.  I mean sometimes you just need that. You need your friends.  None of us are hero enough to do this on our own.  Not a one.  Definately need to spend more time there and less at the LSE.  The LSE is a vacuum where I have no grounding or history. I mean if I'm there with Lynsey or Matt or El and I'm feeling mentalist then there's only them there to ground me. And sometimes they could be off chatting or singing or whatever.  In the Arms there's always someone there.  And that's comforting  It's just like a safety net. Any of the times that I've been really hammered beyond belief it's been in the Arms (I suppose because sub-consciously I know that I'll always be safe in there)  Going to give the Tuns a rest for a while  Time to go home  Enfield Arms forever baby!  Peace Out my dears,  All R's love.   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm really starting to feel quite ill now.  Actually worse than I did yesterday. I want to go to the Arms and have some Irish Stew (it had better be tasty....I've been thinking about it all day. I love Irish Stew).  Just drank through it yesterday. Too pissed to know I was ill. But feel like absolute shit at the moment. Don't want to be here at all actually.  The King Size Blues are playing the Arms tonight so I'd like to be able to see them. Hopefully Rudi will get up and knock out a few.  Saw Kat and Olivia outside the Arms this morning in the garden.  I'm waiting for my train and they're waiting for the pub to open.  How's that fair?  Splitting headache and can't concentrate at all.  I'm gonna take a walk outside to see if I can shake off the funk  (yes I said funk)  (don't think that I've said that in my entire life...but now I have, and I feel gratified. I feel that finally I've amounted to something)  Damn all those who said I'd never make.  I've made it. You can all go to hell  (oh yeah it's quite funny, Kevin's dealing with a complaint from the mentalist. I'll fill you all in our history with him another time...suffice to say that we have a hammer on Eleanor's desk specifically for him)  I kid you not.  Right I'm going to do things with funk and shaking.  Laters,  R   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We met a dude who wanted to eat people last night  (Why do these things always happen to us? I mean seriously why is it always us?)  I genuinely mean the most complete nut job that we've ever met before (and believe me we've met one or two in our time)  He was a musician of some sort and he was just talking about how if he killed someone then he'd feel obliged to eat them (as a matter of respect....indeed I kid you not) and then he started going on about how if he found some bloke having sex with his wife then he'd feel obliged to fuck the bloke to maintain some sort of equilibrium.  Full on, 100%, no holds barred freak.  Pretty sure that we would have won the quiz last night if we didn't have to go to the Orchestra.  I've never been to something like that before so it was pretty cool but we couldn't get a seat so we had to stand up for an hour and a half which wasn't all that much fun as you can imagine (especially as we'd had a few pints beforehand), so I was more concentrating on my feet than the music, which is a shame.  Oh well, at least when we go out we've got stories to tell the next day.  I definitely prefer it that way.  Peace and Love my dears,  Richy    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes indeed, your guys are going up in the world.   Eleanor's orchestra are playing tonight so we're all going along  (we leave no man behind)  Extremely odd. You're talking to a guy (well not talking obviously but...oh sodding leave me alone) who won't go to an All Bar One because it's too posh.  Ah the things that we do for friendship  We're going to the Tuns first though (which may not be a good idea especially as our boss will be there) so mat turn up half cut.  Definitely going to get a seat at the back in case they're rubbish. Then we can go to the Tuns and come back for the end and 'Nora will never know.  Job's a good 'un.  R   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm seriously getting old  I've got such a terrible hangover  Went to the Tuns with Matt, Alan, Chris and the slave, then went to Enfield and met Simon in the Kings Head, then went over the George to meet Trav and John and then went to the Arms for last orders  Fucking hell I feel like shit  Somebody please fucking stop me.  (and it's still absurdly hot in here)  (somebody WILL die today)    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Matt's going out with one of the guys he bought tonight.  I remember the Friday of the Man Auction we all got in the Tuns and Matt was insistent that he wouldn't bid.  And I just said to him: oh yes you sodding will.  And naturally he did.  £100 sodding quid.  I don't know if he's audacious or a spanner.  Hmmmmm  Answers on a postcard please guys  (And it's still too fucking hot)  Rich   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And you   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah you as well.   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some people have been very lax in their writing duties and I'm not happy at all  You know who you are   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's insanely hot in the office today  What the fuck's going on? I mean it, I really don't feel well at all  It's not right I tell you, it's not right.  They wouldn't even treat French people like this, and they stink anyway.  I'm not happy about this I tell you. Not happy at all.  Lynsey kindly donated her fan to me but it's still too fucking hot.  (You got that it's hot right?)  Damn the world and its heat.  We really are in hell  Rich    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Tuns may have a Fit Nick, but we've got a Trav.  Who admittedly isn't particularly fit or anything but his inherent Travness more than makes up for it.  Plus we have things that go on.  We have issues and politics and people not liking people for things that happened years ago and stuff to brighten up those long dark nights.  Admittedly the Tuns Karaoke and Quiz kicks arse. But bottom line you can't go to the Tuns and sit on a bar stool in peace.  We are the Arms and we are the best,   We are the Arms so fuck all the rest  Richy    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We are the Tuns  We are the Tuns We are the Three Tuns, the Three Tuns Oy oy
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok we have the 3 Tun and we have the Enfield Arms  Both are cool  The Tuns is super cheap while the Arms is stupidly expensive.  (i say this because I've realised that I'm spending far more time in the Tuns than I am in the Arms recently)  We know a few of the staff behind the bar in the Tuns (and Paul did give Lynsey a bottle of champagne on her birthday...which Darragh would never ever do and Bang always gives me a few for free) but not in the same way that we know Trav and John and Amanda and Claire. I mean I don't have their phone numbers for a start. I haven't carried them home drunk. I don't go and play pool with them. They've never given me a lift home. I haven't walked them home in the freezing cold.   Well basically it's because they're not my proper friends and I think that's the point about the Arms. I can go in there on any night and there can be nobody in there but I know that I'll be talking to my friends because they're behind the bar.   I was watching Cheers this morning and I just thought to myself: fuck it, our pub's better than your pub. Cheers is shit. The Arms rules.  If there was a fight we'd kick their arses (not that we would, because Cheers is nice and we like them).  Must spend more time in the Arms I think.   Hmmm, yes indeed  Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Matt, Eleanor and I have resolved to curb our drinking  (You may have noticed that we do like the occassional drink)  We've decided that we're only allowed one week day drink (apart from the Friday obviously) and then only for an event or reason - for instance if someone's leaving or there's an event going on or for whatever reason one of us has had the absolute evil day from hell.  (Or fuck it, if it's just Karaoke)  I'm pretty sure that we'll have no problem inventing events if we really do need a mid-week drink.  I've been hitting it seriously hard for about eight days straight now  (and lost my sodding bag on the train last night. fucking hell)  Basically none of us can keep this up, and Matt and Eleanor aren't anywhere near as bad as I am. I don't think I'm an alcoholic but I drink enough to be and that's clearly a dangerous place to be in.  Think I'll go to the Arms tonight and drink lemonade. I haven't been in since Sunday and they might start to forget what I look like. Missing everyone actually. Who knows what wonders may have occurred in my absence?  Been drinking in the Tuns a lot. The last two nights were really cool actually.  The quiz on Tuesday where we came 2nd and Karaoke last night. Both really good nights. In fact the best Karaoke night and the best Quiz night that we've been to.  I feel really bad that we're going to have to give up one of them. It's like choosing between your children or something  (I'm Sophie)  Not that I have any children (but I could go out and steal some or something and then I would have...and then I could decide between them).  I wonder which of us is going to be the first to crack. I'm just not sure if my lifestyle can support it. I mean say you have your special dispensation day on a Monday and then a mate you haven't seen in ages calls you up and asks to meet up. What are you gonna do? Drink coffee?  (I don't do coffee)  Oh well I think we should take bets on it but personally I'm thinking Matt because he's generally the one who suggests stopping out for a couple (yes the infamous couple) after work and because he won't be able to resist the urge to go and see Fit Nick.  Anyway I'll let you all know how we get along.  Oh yeah and you kow that open invitation to the Arms that I gave you all? Well give me some advance warning on that will you? I may have already used up my special occassion day (and any of you guys coming to the Arms is clearly a special occassion)  Peace and Love guys,  Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Epic session over the weekend  Heroic and absurd  Ah but then that's our Richy  Peace and Love kids.  R   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to Alan's Stewards party at BRB in Soho last night  Alan's the Conferences and Events Manager and he has loads of Stewards for all his public lectures and things and every year he has a party for them for all the hard work they do.  Kate, Matt and I managed to get an invite. Chris (Kate's Chris) still works for Alan everynow and then so he came as well. Tons of free alcohol. Champagne, Stella, Vodka, Wine, Schnapps.  (I managed to have a drink of everything I think)  Completely wasted by the end.   Well have you ever known me to be somewhere where there was free alcohol and not be completely wasted?  The beer rain out by the end so I had to go on the Vodka and Red wine (yes I know, Red Wine and Richard do not mix). It was a good night. We had the balcony area looking down on the bar (don't know if you've ever been in there but it's a huge place). It was really cool. Like being in Carlito's Way or something.  Owe Kate ten quid. Why do I keep making these stupid bets on people getting together? I never win. I had to give Bang Bang a fiver on Monday for another stupid bet I made when drunk.  I'm just fucking stupid.  I haven't been in the Arms all week (well I stopped in briefly on Monday but that was quite late). Don't feel any pressing need to go now that Davids gone.  Anyway Alan rules.  We love Alan.  He can join us in hell if he wants    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Managed to fuck up big style at work  Severely pissed off. It's like when you're at school and you can't understand something no matter how hard you try. If i'd messed up because I was lazy or just wasn't giving a shit then fair enough. But I was dilligent about the whole thing. Technical things like that just really aren't my thing at all.  I think that I'm just super thick  I have an I.Q of 78 you know. Which officially makes me educationally sub-normal (now there's a huge surprise)  Fuck and run out of cigarettes. Need one  (Matt just e-mailed me to give me more work. Which is fair enough because I should have taken care of it before)  Bollocks to it all.  David went to Cornwall with Gordon yesterday.  Excellent. Just what I need. (Ok obviously I'm glad for him and he did need to get away but it's difficult losing such a close friend)  (I'm making it sound as though he's dead or something)  Oh fuck it, here's another survey that I've stolen from Olivia  If you were __ , what would you be?  [a flower] stinging nettle [a fruit] black grape  [a vegetable] I am a vegetable  [a spice] scary [a color] grey [a bug] dunno what that includes so go to hell [a smell] one that won't go away  Short Answer  [are you left handed or right handed?] right [are you smart?] hell no (I've got an I.Q of 78) [what's your middle name?] steven [how many personalities do you have?] what?  [how many piercings do you have?] none [tattoos?] not yet [do you like v-8?] as in the engine size? [what was your first word?] how the fuck would I know? [are you superstitious?] no [do you read your horoscope?] get lost, do I look like an imbecile to you? [do you believe in that stuff?] hell fucking no [can you do a cartwheel?] no [do you have bangs?] um, what? [do you have contact lenses?] nope [do you snore?] yep [do you drool in your sleep?] sometimes.. [do you lick your envelopes or use a sponge?] lick... [what languages do you know?] english  [what's the best awards show?] don't care [do you like onions?] yep [do you like cotton candy?] nope [do you like Pina coladas?] dude if its got alcohol in it then I like it [what instruments can you play?] none [What words/sayings do you overuse?] bint, spanner, kido [what do you sleep in?] shorts and a t-shirt [whats your bedtime?] whenever [how many pillows do you have?] 3 or 4. dunno Do you like to dance?] yeh [do you like to sing?] yep [are you any good at it?] hell no, I'm fucking awful [how many CDs do you have?] don't be stupid, how would I know? [do you like to talk on the phone?] I'm not sure that I have any strong feelings either way [do you like where you live?] the area yes [is your room messy?] yep [do you like your writing?] yep  [do you like to finger-paint?] I've actually never known what that is. I must have had a deprived childhood or something [are you organized?] nope [what do you put on hotdogs and hamburgers?] mustard [do you sleep with a stuffed animal?] stop being stupid you fool [do you sleep with socks on?] depends how drunk I am or cold it is [are you ticklish?] suppose so  [are you shy?] used to be mentalist shy. still pretty shy now though [do you talk to yourself?] sometimes [is your house 1, 2, or 3 stories?] 2 [do you have a basement or an attic?] attic [are you a morning person?] never really known what that means. I can get more work done in the morning but I prefer the evening. However I do like drinking from the early morning (which I've only ever done a couple of times)...so erm basically I'm a morni...oh fuck off [what's your favorite outfit?] dunno. don't care [do you believe in ghosts?] no, only nutters (Lynsey) do [what's your favorite feature] my rapier like wit [what do you do when you're nervous?] FTP   THE LAST PERSON WHO:   *Called You: Can't remember. Chris maybe *Saw You Cry: I don't cry in front of people.  *Hugged: Gordon probably when he left *You Went To The Mall With: I don't shop *Sent You An Email: Lynsey *Gave you flowers: never been given flowers *Bought you clothes: well mum and dad gave me a coat for Christmas so probably then  HAVE YOU EVER:   *Been To New York?: nope *Been To Florida?: nope *California?: nope *Hawaii?: nope *China?: nope *Canada?: nope *Danced Naked: possibly. but i would have been very drunk so can't be certain *Stalked Someone?: Hell yeah *Had A Mud Bath?: Isn't that an oxymoron (you moron)  *Tried to suduce someone?: Does rolhypnol count?               urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shall we kill her?   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       There are certain people who are too fucking stupid to live   I have no idea how they manage to even fucking dress themselves in the morning (although that said some of them look like they did it blindfolded)  Silly fucking bint  (sorry guys, just had to get that out of my system)   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (Deliberate pun)   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A friend of Paul's put his mates cock in his mouth for a fiver ... He's a construction engineer in North Wales and has a newborn daughter and an extended step family.   Where does he slot into this whole gay / class strata ladder thingy?         urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read the article in the Guardian today about why people Blog.  I've got no idea why I do really. I mean nobody reads the damn thing apart from a few friends and as I've said before most of them were present at the time and know what happened.  It's not as though any of us write anything profound in the damn thing (probably BECAUSE it's mainly read only by friends and there are things that you don't want your friends to know....but would be happy for strangers to read about. It's the anonymity element that's missing I suppose). Basically it's just become a 'what I did on my holidays' thing.  Description without analysis or reason.  Is that worthwhile? I don't know.  It certainly serves as a way of letting a group of people know what they've been up to without having to individually e-mail them.  But isn't that just laziness?  I do admire the way other people I know who keep Blogs are (almost) completely honest, but I don't see how anyone could do that.  I'm not sure that we lead completely atypical lives so unless you like reading about people who get drunk (alot) and do stupid things (alot) then there's nothing really very much of interest.  I mean I could tell you about the bloke in the Arms who punched Paul and Dean at chucking out time and then came outside and wanted to fight David and I (although it was quite funny. He says to David: 'Oi you Goth bastard do you want some do ya?' and David just looks at him and says 'no thanks we're fine for now.' And this guy just looks at him with no idear what to say to that and so he just walks off.  Now certainly that is a story, and perhaps you might be interested (if you lead a dull and alcohol free life) but otherwise what's the point of me telling it and you reading it?  It's slightly depressing  (life I mean)  (this Blog being a metaphor for all that's wrong with the world)  Ah but then the point is that we are in hell. Well that is that was why we set this thing up in the first place.  The hell of modernity  Well postmodernity for us I suppose  You have met the enemy indeed....  Hmmm...well given that this started because of an incongruity perhaps it's fitting that we continue in the same vein  I don't even know what I mean so I wouldn't expect any of you to  (help me out someone will ya)  All that is certain then is that I'll see you all in hell  (it happens to us all sooner or later)  Peace and Love you crazy kids,  R   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To clarify my point  First I didn't say that all middle-class people are gay, but that most gay people are middle-class.  I'm sure that even Matt can follow the logical difference.  I still maintain that straight men do not partake (I like that word) in homosexual activities.  If they do then they're not completely straight.  Who'd get off with a bloke for a bet?  Nobody who was straight.  And if you don't agree with me you can all go to hell   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So this is how it works see.    Richard believes that anyone (lets just look at men in this case) who, from the age of sexual maturity (according to the internet this is 15-17 years old) who takes part in any sexual behaviour with another man, including kissing is either gay or bisexual.    Even drunken kissing, or doing it for a bet or money or any other reason counts.  Even if you have no sexual feelings whatsoever and you do it, you are classified as gay or bisexual for the rest of your life.  Richard also assumes that all middle class people are gay or bisexual as well.  Lets assume that these days the working class population is 35% (it was 41% and dropping in 1991 apparently) and the rest is 65% (who according to Richard are therefore gay and bisexual, according to his definition).  We also have to assume that 10% of working class men are gay according to everyone else's definition as that is the generally accepted proportion so that's another 3.5%, so that leaves 31.5%.  Now in my own experience, I have got off with a number of straight working class men, lets say its just 3, we can assume that these are drunken people who are, by most people's standards straight and would never normally do this and will go off and have kids and be completely straight for the rest of their lives.  Now if every gay man in the country gets off with 3 straight working class people, that's 10% or the population x 3 = 30% of the population.  Therefore according to Richard's theory only 1.5% of the population is straight.  That's just a 442 500 straight men in the entire country.  BUT then you have the armed forces who partake in these things, lets assume that a mere additional 1% of them partake in non-heterosexual practices.  Lets assume that the number of the armed forces number 100 000 and the duration of the average length of service is 10 years, so every ten years that's a thousand and over the duration of the lifespan of an average adult man that's 60 years so that's up to 6000 extra leaving the number of Richard's straight men at 436 500  AND then there's prisoners, now prisoners don't get to go out at night, or get shore leave so they're a bit more desperate so lets assume that an additional 10% want to get their rocks off, especially after 2 years which is the average sentence in the UK prison world.  There are 75 000 people in prison and if we multiply that up with the ten percent and the lifespan of an average adult man we get 225 000  Leaving a mere 221 000 straight men in the entire UK.  That's only 0.7% of the population or one in 133.  If you have one, girls hang on to him, he's a rare commodity ... although your man is in all likelihood, according to Rich, gay as a 9 bob note!    urlLink Ready and waiting! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so here we are.  My weekend:  Thursday: not much to report, saw my brother's new house on Chapel St, its very nice, helped him put up some curtains but they dropped after putting them up and Warren had to redo the brackets by putting the bottom screw into the top hole, drill a new top hole and fill the bottom hole with polyfilla.  Went to the quiz at the Wickham and we did OK, I even worked out the size of the sphere created by the volume of all the water on the planet: I worked it out using the following equation: ((0.71 [% or surface covered by H2O] x 2 [miles deep] x 4 x pi x 4000 [area of a sphere inc radius of earth] / the cube root of(3 / 4 / pi) [volume of a sphere]: I won £2!    Friday: went to the new Tesco in Batley and then the new Asda in Dewsbury.  My parents fell out which is shit as they don't do anything when they are fallen out so I knew that my holiday weekend was destined to be shit.  My mum hates it if I do too much with my friends "you only come up here to see you mates and you treat this place like a hotel" but if I leave time to do things with my parents and then they fall out I end up doing sod all all weekend which is a real bummer.  I can sit and read the paper all day at home and not spend £40 on train fares.  Anyhew, Friday got decidely better when I went out in the evening.  I arrived at the Obediah Brooke public house, also known as OB's, Obi Wan Kenobi's or Spoon's at 8 after walking down, nicked a bottle off MJW and sat down.  There was also Harriet (aka Spug), Hayley and Karen.  We bumped into Rachel and Dean at some point but I don't really remember when.  Then Karen's gay brother arrived, he is called Stephen.  Quite chunky but not really my type (too much forehead I think) but he quickly demonstrated that he was very good company and definitely worth one.  I bought a round and then Karen bought another and we wandered down to the George, or Turnstile as it is known now.  Now, they don't sell Stella so in there I had a San Miguel and later I asked for a Guinness but ended up with another lager.  While we were in there, in the corner we were in there were 6 bummer boys, MJW, Stephen and I and MJW's friend Philip who turned up for a short while, Danny Boy, MJW's ertwhile dirty but very cute and young shag and the barman who was either called Ben or Simon.  While we were in there I won two bottled of VK, one for singing very loudly and another for doing the splits (american style), some high kicks and a pirouette to some old crap by Irene Cara, I don't remember which.  Then it was onto the Rose and Crown which is only called the Rose and Crown.  I sang the Wonder of you and had a very quick pint as we only were in there for a few mins, although I did manage to tell Danny Boy that I wanted to shag him.  Stephen and Karen did Burning Love (v1).  Pip then went home I think and we went to the Station Tavern (or the Royal as I know it) and I had another couple in there and sang with MJW Your song while Stephen and Karen sany the same song again (v2).  I think I made eyes at the cute DJ who Stephen said he'd got off with twice the lucky bugger!!  At this point I licked Stephen (and I think other people's but I don't remember who)'s  belly buttons and he liked it and I think it was at this boint I started acting like a letch.  Anyway, then we went to the Regal, paid out £2 to get in, I bought some more fags and a round and we danced and I got gradually drunker and don't really remember what went on. Apparently I had 3 pints here and was hammered when we left.  As we walked to Mucky Joe's (aka the Royal Kashmir) I told Stephen I wanted to shag him and I think I suggested that we had sex on one of the stalls in the market place but thankfully he said no.  We had a curry (I had a Chicken Bhuna, but my chapattis and rice never turned up and MJW's rice turned up but not his curry!!) and then we all went home.  I was still after Stephen and was convincing him that we should so it in West End Park but he said no.  K and MJW got a taxi one way and Stephen and I got another the other way.  I didn't get what I wanted from him but modesty and my gentlemanly morality prevents me from saying any more. I arrived home at 1.34 and fell straight to sleep.  Saturday was as boring as hell.  Went to PC world with my dad, ordered a chinese and while we were waiting for it had a pint in the Bull's Head with my dad (who used to live there) and he went on about how it had all changed since 1969.  Erm, that was it.  What a great day.  On Sunday we went out.  We went to Hawes which is 2 hours drive away.  We were there an hour and then came back.  I bought some nice cheese and some even nicer chutney and we had a cup of tea and a scone.  Chicken for dinner (which was lovely) and then OB's for 8.  Spug, Karen and MJW were there and after one we went to the George (another 6 benders, but 2 of em were different this time) and had another.  By this time we had agreed to go to Batley and we did, I sort of hoped that Stephen would be there but also hoped he wouldn't as I felt as if I'd made a fool of myself on Friday.  We went to Legends and got steadily pissed.  Karen got off with Andy, Harriet with Dobby and not with the bloke who she said she was on a promise with and Matthew and I just got to stare at James and Liam, which wasn't all bad!!  The frontier wouldn't let us in so we came home had a curry (no chapattis again!) and went home!  Then home on Monday.  It was a good Friday but the Saturday and Sunday day was a bit uneventful, I wish I'd have gone to Brid with MJ and Karen now, but c'est la vie.  Now all I have to do is book my train ticket for October!   urlLink I'm gonna go out, I'm gonna let myself get, absolutely soaking wet! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. Pierce your nose or tongue? Neither  2. Be serious or be funny? Depends. Serious, but with the occassional pretensious quip  3. Boxers or briefs? For who?  4. Whole or skim milk? Skimmed I think. Don't care really  5. Single or Taken? How stupid are you?  6. Simple or complicated? Complicated in a simple way  7. Law or anarchy? Law  8. Flowers or angels? What the fuck are you on mate?  9. Grey or gray? Grey you stupid stupid fuck. Do I like (read) like an American to you?   10. Read or write? Really does depend. I like reading e-mails   11. Color or black-and-white photos? Depends on the occassion  12. Sunrise or sunset? Dunno  13. M&M's or Skittles? M&M   14. Rap or rock? Classic ROCK! !  15. Stay up late or wake up late? Both, but at a push stay up late   16. TV or Radio? TV   17. Is it POP or SODA?  What are we talking about here?   18. X or O in Tic-tac-toe? What the fuck?  20. Eat an apple or an orange? Orange  21. What came first the chicken or the egg? Shut up  22. Hot or Cold? Hot   24. Tall members of the opposite sex or short? Not bothered  25. Sun or moon? Sun   26. Emerald or ruby? Don't care mate  28. Left or right? Oh shut up you pratt  29. 10 acquaintances or 1 best friend? 1 best friend   30. Vanilla ice cream or chocolate ice cream? Don't like ice-cream, it's rubbish  31. High or Drunk? Mmmmm...close run thing....drunk  32. Green beans or carrots? Green beans  33. Low fat or fat free? Who cares. How does it taste?  34. What is your biggest fear in the world? Getting barred from the Arms  36. Kids or no kids? Dunno actually  37. Cat or dog? At a push dog  38. Half empty or half full? Depends how drunk I am   39. Mustard or ketchup? Can't cut either  40. Hard cover books or soft cover books? Hard  41. Newspaper or magazine? Newspaper  42. Sandals or sneakers? Trainers you American fuckwit  43. Wonder or amazement? Oh for the love of God  44. Red car or white car? Red  45. Happy and poor or sad and rich? I know I've done this before but I'm already sad and Rich  46. Singing or dancing? Singing    *PRESENT*   What's in your CD player: don't use one. download all my music  What color socks are you wearing: barefeet   What's under your bed: dunno. stuff  What's the weather like: dunno, been in all day  What time did you wake up today: half 7 or so  What's playing on your TV: Star Trek Voyager  How many close friends do you have: a few  How many enemies do you have: um, I have people I intensely dislike but they probably don't mind me. Does that count?  *FUTURE*   Who do you want to marry: who ever I can afford  Are you going to college: heh heh  Where do you want to go: wherever  What is your career going to be: heh heh  Where are you going to live: At the bar         urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. Are you an innie or an outie? I honestly have no idea what the hell you're talking about mate. Clarity mon ami  2. Have you ever worn bell-bottoms? Am I being stupid here or something? But come again?  3. Have you ever written a song? We are the Arms, We are the Arms, We are the Enfield - Enfield Arms (same applies for the Secretariat. I'm sure you can work it out)  4. Can you make change for a dollar right now? Nope. Fucking Americans  5. Have you ever been in the opposite sex's bathroom? What does this mean? Like in a pub or something? Then yes.  6. Have you ever smelled your own feet? And this is different from 'can you sometimes smell your feet' how?  7. Do you like ketchup on or beside your french fries? Hate the stuff. It's the devil's work.  8. Can you touch your tongue to your nose? No  9. Have you ever been a boy/girl scout? Nope. Far too working class for that shit. We played with rubble and coal.  10. Have you ever broken a mirror? Dunno. Can't remember.  11. Have you ever put your tongue on a frozen pole? Why would anyone do that...oh shit sorry forgot this was an American survey. Dumb fucks.  12. What is your biggest pet peeve? Genocide.  13. Do you slurp your drink after its gone? How do you do that if it's gone? What in the name of God is wrong with you?  14. Have you ever blown bubbles in your milk? No. Stop it. Please fucking stop it you fool.  15. Would you rather eat a Big Mac or a Whopper? Whopper  16. Have you ever gone skinny-dipping? Nope  17. When you are at the grocery store, do you ask for paper or plastic? I don't understand the question. Are you talking about your method of payment? Don't they ask you that question? What the hell's wrong with your stupid country?  18. True or False: You would rather eat steak than pizza. False  19. Did you have a baby blanket? Dunno, ask my mum  20. Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? I always cut my own hair  21. Have you ever sleepwalked? No  22. Have you ever had a birthday party at McDonalds? No  23. Can you flip your eye-lids up? No  24. Are you double jointed? No  25. If you could be any age, what would you be? 18  26. Have you ever gotten gum stuck in your hair? Nah  27. Have you ever thrown-up after a roller coaster ride? Nah  28. What is your dream car? Can't think of one  30. Would you go swimming in shallow waters where, one year earlier, a shark had attacked a child? What for?  31. How many cavities do you have? Is this a trick question?  32. Have you ever eaten a dog biscuit? Not knowingly (or when sober)  33. If you were in a car sinking in a lake, what would you do first? Depends on far I'd already suck doesn't it  34. Have you ever ridden in an ambulance? No, but been in one  35. Can you pick something up with your toes? Yep  36. How many remote controls do you have in your house? Who gives a shit?  37. Have you ever fallen asleep in school? Of course  38. How many times have you flown in an airplane in the last year? 0  39. How many foreign countries have you visited? Can't be bothered to think about it  40. If you were out of shape, would you compete in a triathlon if you were somehow guaranteed to win. No. Can't be bothered. Rather go to the pub  41. Would you rather be rich and unhappy, or poor and happy? I'm already Rich and unhappy (pun)  42. If you fell into quicksand, would you try to swim or try to float? Does it fucking matter?  44. Do you ask for directions when you are lost? After a while, but generally if you're not a complete incompetent (American) you can find out where you are  45. Have you ever had a Mexican jumping bean? What?  46. Are you more like Cinderella or Alice in Wonderland? Oh shut up you spanner  47. Would you rather have an ant farm with no ants or a box of crayons with broken points? I don't know who's stupider. The people who write these things or the ones who answer them (oh yeah, it's the people who're bothered enough to read them)  48. Do you prefer light or dark bread? Really don't care  49. Do you prefer scrambled or fried eggs? I hate eggs. They're diseased  50. Have you ever been in a car that ran out of gas? Nope. That would be stupid  Thank you and goodnight   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dunno really.   I mean what's the point of this Blog? There are maybe three of you out there reading this thing (and even then infrequently), and of those reading it, most of you already know what I'm writing about because you were there.  Hmmm, I dunno  (as I said)   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haven't been up-dating much recently (as though any of you actually care)  erm so what's been happening then?  Been off work for a while  Sunday was a completely brilliant night. Seriously one of the best nights in there for ages. It was Darragh's birthday so there was Karaoke and a late bar. Wen't to the George with Chris and John first for a few cheap drinks and then over the Arms. By the time we got there Darragh was already shedded (I opened a sweap stake on what time he'd pass out. Francis won 25 odd quid on that....who would have thought that he'd make it to 10.45).   Quite odd really, we'd intended to take it slow and not have a big night but we all ended up completely hammered (I mean like super hammered). Everyone there was really drunk given that Darragh had laid down a barbeque during the day and loads of people had been drinking for ages.  Sang Suspicious Minds with Chris and John, and then John and I did 'I love Rock n Roll' and then I did 'Gay Bar' with Darragh.  Kat and Olivia were both pissed as well so they just stood at the front laughing at us.  Flash vision of dancing with Kerry to some ballad or another.  I was supposed to go to London for Kate's birthday but it was really just too much of a hassle for a Sunday (and as it happened I ended up having a brilliant time in the Arms)  Went on singing until they eventually chucked us out.  ("Oh you'll take the high road an' I'll take the low road, an' I'll be in Scotland before you For me and my true-love we'll never walk again on the bonnie, bonnie banks of Loch Lomond")  Saturday was a cool night as well. They had a band on (who were pretty good) but before they went on Rudi gave us his idea of a sound check for them and blasted out a couple of songs for us (he's seriously good). We're all at the front head banging away.  Good night  I was seriously trashed. I'd been drinking from 1. Met Natasha in the Stag (which was cool). Haven't seen her in ages actually. I mean if you don't count her birthday then it really is ages. She's right, we don't see enough of eachother.  (sort it out T)  Sodding drinking Stella as well. Never a good move. Although was taking it slow as T wasn't drinking.  Just pretty much been in the Arms for the week, missing my work guys actually. Shame I couldn't get out for Bennett's birthday, but Old Street just isn't really my thing, especially on a Sunday when it's a nightmare to get to and from.  Well that's me anyway.  How you guys been?  R   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Full name: You know my name, stop being stupid Nicknames: Don't have one Birthday: July 14 Birthplace: Hackney (I'm not proud of it either) Hobbies: Drinking Favorite types of music: Rock/Indie Favorite holiday: Summer Favorite color: Who gives a shit, let's have some serious questions Lucky number: This is a serious question? Idiot Favorite food: Human meat Favorite time of day: 11am when the pubs open Favorite TV show: Due South Favorite sport: Football Favorite movie: Can't name just one, so I'll name none Guy buds: Buds? Flowers? What are you babbling about Friend who talks the most: Matt and Lynsey run one another fairly close Friend who has the most gossip to tell: Matt normally knows what's going on Piercings or tattoos: Neither. They're for freaks. (I'm gonna get one. On my face) Favorite ice cream: Don't like the stuff, it's cold. What's that all about? Favorite soda: Soda? Fucking hell, another fuckin' American Favorite sport to watch: I already said. If you're not gonna listen then what the hell's the point of this? Loudest person I know: Matt Craziest person I know: A subject we've discussed at length. There are different kinds of crazy, and I know a few. At a push, of my friends, Eleanor    Have you ever..... Broken the law? Yep Broken a bone? Nope Lied? Am now Cheated on a test? Fuck yeah Had a medical emergency? Nope Been in love? What the hell's love mate? Shut up    Do you believe in..... Love at first sight? Not for a second. Who the hell does God? Not at the moment Aliens? What do I look like a nutter to you? Hell no Horoscopes? Now you're just taking the piss Spirits? Like Whiskey and Vodka? Yeah I've studied the area in some detail Yourself? Now you're just being a spanner. stop it    Which is better..... Coke or Pepsi? Could care less Oranges or apples? Dunno, it's all apples and orange's innit One pillow or two? two Deaf or blind? Dumb Pools or hot tubs? What is it with this pool or hot tub thing? I already said I don't wash Fast or slow? Fast or Slow what? Now or later? Sooner TV or radio? TV    About the opposite sex.....(where applicable) The first thing you notice: How drunk they are Must have personality traits: Inability to hold their drink Thing you hate about them: Sobriety Thing you love most about them: Inebriation     Who..... Makes you laugh the most? Me Do you go to for advice? Dear Deidre Do you hate? You, you American twat Knows most about you? That bastard whose been blackmailing me for the past two fucking years Has it easier, guys or girls? Women Do you ever save AOL conversations? No Do you save emails? If they're any good   Fantasies..... To live: Nah, rather not To marry: Stella Number of children: Said before, I'm sellin' 'em Names of children: I don't care, whatever people want to name 'em. why should I give a shit? Yearly income: A billion? I dunno, whatever I can have. Stupid question   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a good night yesterday  Went to this guy's (Paul) leaving drink in the Tuns and then when they shut early we decamped to the George where EL, Bennet and Alison were (didn't see them at first, they had to come and get me).  It all got a bit maudlin for a while because of everything with Kate H (she's really quite ill at the moment), but then we raised our glasses to her and recalled a few funny stories...and that's just basically the only way that you can deal with these things.  She's a nice women  We like her.  Here's to her.  And that's all you can do.  Would have liked to stay but had to get back to the Arms. Apparently Darragh had told a rascist joke while Chris was in the pub and Chris had called him a wanker and walked out. So I wanted to go back and talk to Darragh because there's just no way that I can continue drinkinking in there unless I do say something to him. You have to call people on that sort of thing.  Oh yeah saw Louise on the platform at Seven Sisters, quite odd. She been working until 9 at night. Sod that.  Anyway I missed Darragh last night but I'll have to talk to him at some point.  Wasted journey down in the end. It's odd always being torn between the Arms and my work guys. I find myself leaving the guys drinking just when the night's getting going and getting to the Arms when everythings kinda winding down.  Oh well, love them both.  Peace and Love,  Rich    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh god, what a week.  Well here I am after something of an absence from the old blogging.  Sorry about that.  So the Fred thing:  he was as pissed and leering at Mark and I told him to go home because he was drunk and he kept asking me what I meant and eventually I said that he was making my friend feel uncomfortable and he started off on one "you and your friends, you and your f***ing friends, don't you ever ask me for anything, you can f*** off ...  Five minutes later he was sat next to me and had forgotten all of it!  Anyway I am avoiding him tonight.  What else has happened.  Well I saw Troy at the weekend, that and Kate's BBQ were the highlights.  Kate's BBQ was good but I got very tired after not drinking enough I think.    Anyway this week has been OK, drank till 8 on Monday and watched the Corrie triple bill - or at least 2/3 of it!  Poor Todd.  If he ever needs a shoulder, or indeed any other anatomical aspect of me to cry on, he can have it (although I am so horny these days, I'd probably be happy for Norris to cry on my shoulder).  Tuesday was fun.  Mark Power, Ricky P, Ally Revel and me were drinking and these weird birds came over because they fancied Mark.  Also Ib came, Ib is a funny and sweet boy but he doesn't drink.  That doesn't mean that he only has coke, no, he does not drink ... anything, ever.  If you cut him open it would be like shredded wheat or spoonfuls of Horlicks when you put it in your mouth and you get all claggy - he must be the driest boy in the world.  Anyway, he is the former editor of the Beaver, I suppose Mark's predecessor and he comes and sits with us and has interesting chats but he comes into the Tuns, looks round for someone he knows and sits with them/us.  He seems to do it every day now - funny lad!  Anyway he's a nice boy and that's all that matters.  Wednesday was the Annual General Meeting of the Society of Archivists.  I attended and it was quite fun and I didn't end up getting home until midnight - what a night.  I drank alsorts and was a bit drunk - archivists are such drinkers.  God!  Lask night was fun.  One of the Lezzy Kates was leaving and we ended up with Steph.  She is mad and has massive bosoms.  She is really mad and when she gets drunk she gets madder.  I really hope she's not sitting with me at the HF dinner as she is literally bonkers with a capital bonk!!  And tonight its a quick drink apres work.  Bump into the tightest woman in the world and hopefully Mark "I've got the" Power and no doubt Ib as he wanders round and then home for friends and BIG BROTHER yippee!!!!    And then its the BBQ tomorrow and also a triple rollover.  That's £21 500 000!  I could so do with that money.  I would never return to LSE.  Ever  Have a nice weekend and lets hope you don't sit on your nads.  I did it earlier and it KILLS!!!   urlLink Touch me, touch me, I wanna feel your body! 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well folks it's that day of the week again!  Where we are let loose to wreak havoc in any way we see fit, plus an extra day thrown in for good measure, it's called a bank holiday! WEY HEY!!  This evening we have a few extra randoms joining us on our voyage to pissedness, MJW'S friends from his place of work, namely Ellie......she sometimes wears her tops inside out and her thong sticking out of the back of her pants, for no reason whatsoever! oh and she likes big black men, then there's Becky seemingly she likes to get drunk and show MJW her front bum, which is shaved into a Brazilian, Becky's bit of fluff Guy (don't know him), then Kathy, who likes partaking in our group snogging competitions in fact the last time i saw her we were snogging each other in the regal and the curry house, sometimes under the influence i forget i'm NOT a lesbian! oh well!  Then my Friend Lynn( she's wild )and her boyfriend Paul, not seen either of them for 18 months as they've been residing in Italy!  Then the usual suspects.......Spug, Rach, Dean, Mark, Ruth, Tina, Beth, Hayley, MJW, MJW's Sister Claire (who likes to have 2 glasses of wine and spend the rest of the evening shrieking MAFFHEW)and little old me!  Steven Horner is not joining us however as he is going to the Saville to meet his friend Adele, but no doubt he will be making a grand entrance in the regal sometime after 11.00pm. Don't think i'll have anytime for Porritt or Squaddie hunting i'm going to be busy! So who knows how the evening will pan out, but i've a feeling it's going to be eventful.......i'll keep you posted!  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok what happened at the weekend?  Not much really  Got royally trashed on Friday for Lynsey's leaving do. Knocked back five pints over lunch (well not only was it a Friday but Lynsey was leaving so it just had to be done...oh come on we had absolutely no choice. We're drinking people, what else could we do? We were compelled by our genes) and then we just decided to leave work and go to the Tuns  Just got drunk (although Matt did have a huge argument with Fred who was leering at Mark Power all night...which somehow I missed entirely, even though I was sitting right there...mainly because I was hammered)and not much else to report really.  Oh yeah Chris and I almost got in a fight at the pool table which was quite interesting.  Saturday I went to the Arms and drank, then went over to Taps where Chris was....he almost got in a fight with some bloke called Jim who was being a complete wanker to one of the barmaids. We drink in there a lot so I just went over to tell him to calm down as he was drinking with us and what he does reflects on us.  He gets angry and then I'm not completely sure what happened after that. It just kicks off and Jim gets bundled out the door and we keep Chris from going out after him.  Which was quite fun.  Sunday just did an all day drink. Well I say all day, but from about 5. Actually thinking about it I think that the fight was Sunday actually.  Oh I don't know. Does it really matter?  Last night went for our usual quick pint after work and ended up staying until close.  This odd Danish friend (but with an American accent)of Mark Power gave me her e-mail address.  Now that's why we drink  So we find odd things in our jacket pockets the next morning.  What other reason is there?  Matt's BBQ on Saturday, I hope I'm not being presumptuous in inviting all of our readers...  'Course you'd have to know where he lived first and that information is highly confidential.     urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Following on from Richard admitting to only having 3 pints! I too have had a very civil weekend, i don't know how it came about...it wasn't through want of trying.....but no dramas to report! none at all! Friday took the register at 8.00pm prompt in spoons, all present and correct...followed the same path of destruction we take every week, but the most interesting things to arise in the evening were MJW forgetting to turn his mic on whilst we were singing Rod Stewart's "first cut is the deepest" oh and him getting blown out by dirty Danny in the regal!  We even congratulated ourselves leaving sloppy joes because neither of us had been asked to keep the noise down/thrown anything/flashed at the staff/or the usual fallen asleep!  Saturday was even tamer, took the Porritt home at last orders promising him a REAL good time (was it excitement or fear i saw in his eyes?) yep that's right we were home and soberish at 11.30..............WRONG!!!!!  Sunday i was a domestic goddess, the Porritt meister left early doors, spent the rest of the day.........cooking, cleaning, washing, ironing, gardening!  AHHH....help i don't know what's happening!  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so sorry, I don't know how this happened but we stopped out for a drink tonight and we only stayed for three  I so hate to let you all down like that, but it's the truth and that's all I have to offer.  Sincere and humble apologies,  R   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well our girl Lynsey's leaving us today  We'll be going to lunch in a bit for a couple of pints and then out to the Tuns tonight hopefull for a properely mentalist night to celebrate all the other mentalist nights.  Lynsey, we'll miss you mate  Another one bites the dust...  Steve walks warily down the street,  with the brim pulled way down low  Ain't no sound but the sound of his feet,  machine guns ready to go   Are you ready,  Are you ready for this  Are you hanging on the edge of your seat  Out of the doorway the bullets rip  To the sound of the beat   Another one bites the dust  Another one bites the dust  And another one gone, and another one gone  Another one bites the dust  Hey, I'm gonna get you too  Another one bites the dust   How do you think I'm going to get along,  without you, when you're gone  You took me for everything that I had,  and kicked me out on my own   Are you happy, are you satisfied  How long can you stand the heat  Out of the doorway the bullets rip  To the sound of the beat   Chorus   Another one bites the dust  Another one bites the dust  Another one bites the dust  Another one bites the dust  There are plenty of ways you can hurt a man  And bring him to the ground  You can beat him  You can cheat him  you can treat him bad and leave him  When he's down  But I'm ready, yes I'm ready for you  I'm standing on my own two feet  Out of the doorway the bullets rip  repeating the sound of the beat   Peace and love kido,  R    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well alright since Karen raised the issue, why do I drink?  Answer: Because I like pubs. I like drinking in pubs.  If I'm in the house then I just don't drink at all. I don't see the point.  The pub experience can be so varied. You can be sitting at the bar all day by your self or with one another person or five or in the beer garden with ten or at the pool table...  Every time you go in it's diffent.  Ok why else?  Well because being at home is boring as fuck. Television is absolute shit. I like to read but I'm not going to finish work (mainly involving reading and writing shit) and then go home to read for six straight hours. What the hell's that about?  Plus I like doing shit. I like having stories to tell. I like having a laugh with my mates. I like meeting cannibals and mentalists.  I like stealing tables and ash trays and wheel barrows and midgets for no real reason.   I like meeting random people  I like ending up in a Gay Bar where Lynsey and Matt get off to throw some lesbian off the scent.  I like waking up on random sofas all around London  I like singing on tables  I like going to a party at someone's house that you've never met before in your life  I like waking up in the morning and thinking 'holy fucking shit, why did I do that?'  I just fucking like it  Come on people, mentalism is good. What the fuck's all this going to a wine bar thing and sitting down over a glass for an hour and then going home?  If that's your idea of fun then you can keep it.  Go out, have a laugh and then join our blog to tell the tale   Be proud. This is our 21st Century hell. Tell it to fuck off  Choose the pub. Choose a pint. Choose mentalism  Just make sure you get your round in  Peace and Love people,  Rich   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Email me you spanners!  Yesterday evening i had a full hours lecture on liver failure and the dangers of heavy drinking! from a very good friend of mine Helen who happens to be a doctor in Edinburgh.  I soaked up all the information and advice, pondered for a while on the way to the fridge to get the wine.......do i drink to enhance or escape my emotions? probably a bit of both!  So the outcome, i'm not going to stop drinking...i might think about cutting down, but not yet.  It's the funniest thing in the world, i'm happiest in the pub surrounded by my great mates, laughing, shrieking and talking bollocks! What else would i do with my weekends, i wouldn't have any stories to tell, the stories that make me, ME! the joy in my life would just go.  I wouldn't hear people saying, why are your weekends so outrageous? how do you manage to get into so much trouble? or Oh my god! here she comes, light the blue touch paper and stand well back!  So until the time comes when i meet a nice sensible boyfriend who will impregnate me, i'm going to carry on as i am!  Anyhow Helen's a raving lesbian, she licks fannies and she dare lecture ME coz i drink? Fuck that!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As always we went for 'a pint' after work and ended up staying until ten  Matt, Alan and I.  Then were joined by Ed (whose birthday it was), Mark Power and Elliot Simmons (I'm just surrounded by gay people. I seriously might as well just give up)  Mandy turned up later on as well  Mark's the editor of the Beaver and Elliot's the GenSec of the SU (I can't believe the night I asked him infront of about fifteen people if he was gay or not....I was drunk obviously)  Anyway that was a nice night.  Bang was behind the bar and just knocked out the cheap drinks all night. Brilliant stuff.  Made it back to the Arms for one drink  I'd forgotten about the taxi driver who tried to sell us drugs the other night.  Madness.  R   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is it a good thing to have half of your brain hurt when you cough?  Its the left hand side and I can't say I am overly happy.  I am not hung over and I am not tired and I am beginning to worry that it may be a cyst in my brain.  It may also be alcohol related buit i very much doubt it.  As you know I am a model of sobriety and temperance.   urlLink Email HIM you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God last night was such a car crash.  I nearly pulled a gay straight man, I asked fit Nick if I could fuck him up the arse and was nearly sold weed by a taxi driver.  On 4 hours sleep, I am managing very well indeed.   urlLink Email him you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Email me you spanners!  Well at long last...the very kind invitation to join your blog, has been accepted! God i'm thick, that was the most work i've done since October 1999, since i started working in this virtual reality t.v show! Today i have mostly been wading my way through the contents of the water cooler, trying to quench my thirst, it's the heat you see........nothing to do with the fact i was guzzling tinnies in the garden till the early hours of this morning, with small brother and another couple of randoms.  When will i ever learn? Some people are just born to party.  Tomorrow is weekend eve, so it's the law to start hard partying any time after today i quess!  YIPPEE!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You all know Lynsey's leaving on Friday right? Well on Monday Graham (her boss) took her out for lunch at Coopers.  They leave at 1 and come back at 5  (yeah I know, that's some kind of lunch)  Both of them are absolutely trashed. And I mean trashed. I've seen Lynsey drunk before (oh yes) but this was something else. I mean shou couldn't speak or walk.  When I got down there she'd already puked in the toilets (well in the sink in the toilets which she duly blocked)  Fucking five in the afternoon  AT WORK  We try and sort her out when she dissapears outside and starts puking right outside Tower 1 as half of London walks by.  Absolutely fucking classic  That's the kind of person I'm friends with. Only mentalist drinkers are wanted around here.  When we'd sobered her up enough to leave we went to the Tuns for drinks but couldn't get any seating so sat outside on the steps drinking. That was nice.  Anyway yesterday Matt and I went to the London Mayoral Debate that the LSE was hosting. Obviously had a dew drinks beforehand. It was crap though because Ken and Norris had to leave early to go to this London Olympics thing.  We stayed until about eight and then took the first opportunity to leave and go to the Tuns. Alan came along and joined us after the debate finished and we drank until half eleven or so.  When the Tuns shut Bang, Mandy, Ed, Fit Nick and us all went to the Walkabout and stayed drinking until half 2 in the morning or so  (I know it's been said before but we are so rubbish)  There was this weird band promoter there as well who seemed to be chatting Matt up all night but then wasn't.  Odd fellow  (Matt that is)  Cool night. Impromptu is best  Still can't work out how it happened though  From the Mayoral debate to some weird club at 2 in the morning.  Is this a talent we have or an affliction?  Answers on a stamped addressed envelope please.  Richy    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Whoever smelt it dealt it" "Whoever denied it supplied it" "Whoever made the rhyme committed the crime."   urlLink Email him you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah here we are my pretties, I have a mere 9 mins before my next meeting, just enough for a blog-ette.  Welcome Karen.  Ooh you are a dirty girl and MJW a dirty boy.  You with APorrait and bully squaddie and MJW with Danny Boy.    Oh by the way, Cleckheaton, my home town and major town on the River Spen is the capital of poofters.  There are more gay men there per head of population anywhere other than Chariots!!   I am coming home on 3 June 2004 AD for a long weekend.  As always it will includ ethe inevitable Friuday night and they go something like this:  1 Dad drops me off after Corrie to the JD Wetherspoon Public House, The Obediah Brooke, also known as OBs or Obi Wan Kenobi's.  We have 3 quick pints there and then move on to 2 The George, used to be good, now is shit but everyone goes and the boys are so fit in Cleck that you can't say no. 3 Then the Rose and Crown - used to be a rugby pub but they have Karaoke 4 Then the station, they have Karaoke as well, and the DJ is cute as hell and gay as a $4 bill and its good 5 Then the regal where we get royally pissed, me and Matt get really camp and have a wonderful time eyeing up the talent and finally 6 Mucky Joes - the worst curry house in the world but its just what you need when you get drunk in cleck.  I hope the lovely Steven Horner will be out, I can try to pull him again!  Anyhew Karen, welcome to the blog and I hope you post many many posts.  See ya - wouldn't wanna be ya - you blond slaaaaaaag.     urlLink Don't stop till you get enough!   T
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay here goes........my weekend of drunken debauchery for you all to howl at! Friday night events in sunny Clecksville kicked off as follows, met in the obediah brooke at 8.00pm prompt after having a 1 1/2 hour disco kip. Squaddie was at the bar....squaddie aka, Graham Jackson aged 29 in the army, was at school with Matt and MJW, also used to bully Matt in the cubs, i digress! Well Squaddie is the guy i took home 2 weeks previous and rode like a rented mule (my mothers so proud). Anyhow, he's a nice guy and could be future boyfriend material, much better than Andy Porritt (f*ck buddy of 1 1/2 years, 9 years my junior, friend of Matt's brother,  sexy little fecker but treats me like white trash!)   Soo, exchanged pleasantries with squaddie when in walked Porritt.........dilemma! Changed pubs to defuse the situation, downed 8 pints of cidre ala blackcurrant, was shrieking down the karaoke to irish rover and drinking random aftershocks, when in walked squaddie, copped off with him like you do when you're 16, went up to the regal bar hand in hand straight past Porritt (that'll serve him).   Went to talk to Andy, who blanked me......told him me and him were no more, looked for squaddie who'd done a bunk..............FECK.   So siddled over to Andy, like nowt had happened, dragged him to another club coz i was still thirsty, then went back to his house, thankfully his parents were away unlike last week, when i visited at midnight slightly worse for the booze, when his dad came to the door in his boxers...........oops!   So Andy tried to do me in his parents bed, i declined and said i'm sure we'll manage in your single bed! had a couple of jumps, waved at the milkman as i staggered off home looking like something the cat dragged in!     Saturday night no sign of squaddie :o( Andy was out, he ignored me all night......then left without me, so i burst into tears! me and Caroline (girlfriend of Matt's brother Warren) slagged him off till the cows come home, had a curry so cheered up a bit!   Sunday went boozing with MJW, had wife beater and ended up catching his feet when he was doing handstands in the turnstiles,( he was that leathered he has penciled in a $hag with dirty Danny on Wednesday night).........YAK!   Blobbed work yesterday due to my alcoholism....doesn't matter boss gone to Europe with his Harley Davison buddies! NO WORRIES!   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been in the house all day  Watching Due South at the moment. I love that programme it's got to be one of my two favourite of all time, although in terms of quality it's just so much better than TNG.  It's just fucking genius.  I defy anyone to watch it and not like it (unless you're a Canadian or something and object to the characterisation of your nation)  If you've ever seen it and not liked it then you're a fucking imbecile and you can go to hell.  Haven't had a cigarette all day. When I'm in the house I never really feel the need.   And yes indeed this has been the most boring post of all time.  I feel oddly proud of myself  Laters kids.  Richy   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Excellent Lock-in in Taps last night. We're all steadily migrating away from the Arms.  Don't know what time we eventually left but I was absolutely slaughtered by the end of it. Don't even know why we left when we did because Trav and I just stood outside talking for ages after  That was a smart move  They had a band in as well last night and they played some excellent sing along stuff.  It was a really good night.  Rudi and Geordie Phil were in as well so it was like a mini Enfield Arms tour.  The day before Alan, Matt, Eleanor and i went to the Tuns. We were only sodding supposed to go out for a couple of pints and I end up getting home at half twelve. We're so crap.  We need more stories of drunken excess.  More of you  More  Anyone got a drunken story to tell then you're in.  This is Hell.  The sooner you realise that the better.   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's horrible in the office today. It's just ridiculously hot. I hate it.  Came in early today with Matt so I'm going to go in a minute. Try and avoid the worst of the Rush Hour.  You know I haven't been straight home from work without stopping for a drink in weeks. I really can't remember the last time.  That's ridiculous.  I so much need a better class of friends  A new liver  A pub that doesn't sell cheap drinks  A shorter journey home everday.  Please arrange  Many thanks and kind regards,  R    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to the Globe theatre yesterday afternoon.  (we can do culture)  Alan used to work there so he arranged a free tour for loads of us. It was pretty cool actually (and we all got to knock off work early)  Walked down there from the LSE (and it was a really nice day as well)  Afterwards loads of us went to a pub down the road and sat outside in the beer garden which overlooks the Thames with a brilliant view of St Pauls.  That also was cool.  Eventually it just got too cold so we moved inside and stayed drinking for the evening until only Alan, Matt and I were left. It all got quite deep and meaningful for a while there.  Went back to Matt's and drank gin (I don't know why)and watched the League of Gentleman (which is funny anyway but when you've been drinking all night everything's funny).  Did I tell you my brother got barred from the George on Sunday.  He wanted to fight Dale.  (didn't help that Geordie Phil was in and wanted to help him take on the bouncers as well)  I mean how the hell do you get barred from the fucking George? That takes some serious doing. Obviously the boy's talented. I'm very proud.  Unrelated but someone managed to get an Enfield Arms bar stool into Bar Form the other night.  I feel oddly proud of my pub for that.   We manged to get a fucking bar stool past two bouncers. Now what other pub has people who could do that?  No actually allow me to re-phrase. What other pub has people who would want to do that?  Just had a bacon and cheese roll. Tasty. Best cure for a hangover going (hair of the dog excluded)  Laters,  R    urlLink Email me you spanners!   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      change is good   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've got nothing to say to any of you   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What the  fuck ?  She marries Affleck at the end?  The film's completely sick  Icky evil incensecestuous horribleness  The American's are moral fucking degenerates  What the hell's wrong with the woman?   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pearl Habour is one seriously shit film (it's on now)  What is wrong with the American mind?  As all the world knows I'm a sucker for cheap sentimentality (hell I cried at Cool Runnings), but this big stinking pile of trash...? It defeats even me.  They're all intellectually stunted  How is it that these people are busy taking over the entire world?  We should have a gigantic game of Trivial Pursuit or something to settle the issue  I think its got something to do with the water.  I hate not going out. It's just so fucking boring  I wonder what happened in the Arms today? Chris went out at about two this afternoon. Bastard. Expecting him to roll in hammered in not too long.  Anyway what did I do yesterday?  Oh yeah T came down and we went to the park (yeah I know, how fucking weird is that). She had to take her parents to the airport so she couldn't drink or stay too long so we went to the park. Spent the time trying to persuade her that Enfield isn't the complete shit hole she thinks it is (failed). But I love the place  It was really odd. We were in the park and we were talking about Natasha's sister almost being 30 and then I said that means my sister must be thirty as well and then as soon as I said Sally's name I hear someone shout my name....and it's Sally.  Oddness.  Went to the Arms after that for a nice day of drinking.  Played twenty questions with David, Gemma, Kerry and Amanda when we were all fairly hammered. Oh and this other game where you all say famour people's names and then you have to say another name beginning with the previous person's second name (which is hard when you're drunk)  Nice night.  Went over to Taps after (they had a late bar) and the landlady had a go at me about John being all...well John. It's alright when he's being 'John' (John has become an adjective) in the Arms because he's John and we know that's what he's like but in Taps people don't really know him and it might start trouble.  Chris had to take him home in the end because he was so hammered.  (Oh and Kate Beckinsdale in Pearl Harbour is such a fucking slapper)  (and what's with Hartnett and his best mate's bird?)  (I can't believe that I'm feeling sympathy for Ben fucking Afflek)  (How dare they do this to me?)  Americans...     urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The bastard only sodding came back didn't he   I swear that if Jesus (I've told you before that David's nickname in the Arms is Jesus right? Well because he looks like Jesus)himself had actually of walked into the Arms he would have had pretty much the same reaction.  We were all pissed and as always the pub was absolutely rammed (it was a Friday) when I just see David standing there and someone shouts out 'it's Jesus, he's risen' (oh alright it was more like 'Jesus is back', but allow me some dramatic license please) and he was immediately swamped (I don't know what the non-regulars would have made of the whole thing, but it was quite funny).  If he says he's leaving again I'm gonna knock the spanner out.  Talking of knocking people out, this guy wanted to fight me on Saturday, although it was my fault. The George in town was shut (they had no water or something) so we had a few extra townies in. Anyway we were all sitting around the back when this girl walks past in this ridiculous pink evening dress (I mean this is the fucking Arms) and being quite drunk I quite loudly commented that she looked like she was going to a wedding.  She got upset, told her Uncle and he wanted to fight me. I'm not entirely sure how things got resolved. I think his mate persuaded him that it would be a very bad idea for a townie to kick off in the Arms.  Anyway Saturday was Karaoke. Sang Bohemian Rhapsody and other things which I can't remember. It was a good night.  Well isn't Karaoke always good? Sang loads last Wednesday. For some reason no-one else wanted to sing, so it was basically just me, Matt, the Karaoke dude and The Man singing all night.   (One of these days we'll succeed in persuading El to get up and sing)  Although we did work out what we'd do if Matt had 22 trillion pounds.  Anyway how were weekends guys?  I'll see you all in hell.  The Colonel     urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Half of Clecksville have been at it like rabid dogs this weekend, everyone was pulling everyone else like it was the end of the world or something. Friday Lee was cracking onto Kay, forgetting he was engaged to be married and pushing aside the fact that Kay had a husband..........it was the funniest thing ever, we were in the station tavern and he was leaning really casually against a table, but unbeknownst him, he'd tilted the table and all bottles, glasses and ashtray had slid off onto the longsadle.........i thought i was going to wee!  Out of those of us who made it to the regal, most where caught swapping saliva at some point in the evening, yes you know who you are........Spug, Katy, Claire...ha ha bang goes your anonymity.  Saturday night they were still at it, Katy even met up with her Friday night shag again, Hayley pulled.......is their something in the air?  Well the only thing i've pulled this weekend is the door handle to open the door to sloppys......TWICE!    great stuff eh? yeah yeah we all know why!!  Other Weekend highlights.... I've had my barnett cropped...v.short! Tina arena got in a proper fist fight with a bird on Friday night (i wouldn't mind but i'd started it!). Fri. i went to hug Simon goodbye when leaving the turnstiles, only to realise it wasn't him, but a scarey doorman.......i'm such a twat!  I'm going to try harder to get in more of a mess next weekend! i feel a bit dull today! well....  That's all folks....      
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Absolutely fucking gutted.  I would tell you about the night but I genuinely can't remember a thing after the penalty shoot out. Absolute and complete blank. God knows what I could have been doing.  Met Chris and John in Taps at 4, then went over the George for some drink cheap drinks then went back to the Arms where I met up with Matt and Katie to watch the football.  Got absolutely slaughtered.  Its quite disturbing not knowing what happened for a good proportion of the night. Usually odds and ends come back to me. But this is proper black out territory.  I blame the referee    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Has someone slipped an extra Tuesday in this week?  I can't believe it's only 1/2 way through the week, what's going on?  Can't wait for Friday, there's loads of out, all the usuals plus friend Kay (she has 1 of those husband things but has a freedom pass for the night).  Mad friend Lynn and her chap Paul.  Plus Lee is home from Saudi Arabia WHOOPEE...  Only 2 more sleeps!  MJW is coming round tonight to show me the photos of the Fri Matt was home, oh heck! This is after he's been for a wax! which is a coincidence as i'm going for waxing tomorrow, obviously not the same bits that would be mad!  I'm talking shit again, i'm off!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wait until you hear about Matt's Friday  You're all gonna love this one guys    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Landlord dude: Alright we've still got a hundred or so tickets left. Who'll give me twenty quid?  Random dude: 20 pounds!  Pub cheers. We cheer  Matt: 25 pounds  Pub cheers. We cheer  Lynsey: 35 pounds!!  Huge cheers  Matt and Richard in unison: What the fuck are you doing?  (why would anyone go from £25 to £35?)  (hell why would anyone even bid when they've only got a fiver left in their purse anyway?)  Lynsey: I don't know why. I just did  Matt and Richard: You silly bint  We had to pool the remainder of our money  And then she sodding won.  Pub Cheers  Lynsey, Richard and Matt: Did that really just happen  Matt got to keep the DVD.  Lynsey is a hardcore fucking A mentalist  But we still love her   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ventured up to Bonny Scotland last Fri, stayed 3 days at my most eccentric school friend Helen's house (she's a doctor and was having a leaving party as she's moving hospitals down to Southampton). Random weekend, i'm still reeling.......instead of the regal last Fri, i was doing a Scottish Kayleigh in a bowling club in Inverness, i don't know how it came about.......i hate change, i must've lost all leave of my senses. The Karen everyone knows would not get in her car and venture up the M74 on a 5 hr journey...ALONE! Well arn't i a dark horse, change might be good after all, can't remember feeling this chilled out in ages.  Mind you Helen is BARKING mad, she's a self confessed addicted bargain hunter, she's racked up more push bikes, motor bikes, cars, landrovers, flats and houses all over Britain, i've never met anyone with their fingers in so many pies! Imagine all the stress, the last time i was stressed was my kettle broke about 6 weeks ago, i had to boil water in the microwave for 3 DAYS, IT WAS AWFUL!!!!  Anyhow back to the weekend, i'm waffling!  Fri was top, suddenly all these doctors were interested in me cause i talked funny, bring it on! drank and danced loads, got a taxi back to Edinburgh, where me Helen and Gilly stayed up drinking wine till the early hours (yep they're rug munchers).  Saturday proper chilled out, ate nice food gabbed for England, watched DVD's and DRANK! Had a long lie-in yesterday followed by a hearty breakfast (vegan but i managed).  Took just under 4 hours to get back, stopped half way to get Jim a fathers day card and pressie.  Quick bath and change then met Spug for a few Sunday Bevvies, Dean and Rach were already in Spoons (Rach and Spug have just returned from Puerto rico) so we had plenty to talk about.  Went to Turnstiles to see Simon, left at last orders for a curry (which wasn't very nice as i was soberish).  We all got a taxi home, was in bed before 12....thoughts on the weekend.  1. Don't be scared to take a trip (Matt you're next, i get free petrol) 2. Don't go to Sloppy Joe's Sober 3. Wish i was a lesbian 4. Shame i like COCK!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The joys of working with all males (Jewish ones at that). Well it has it's advantages, i get treat like a princess everyday, can scare bosses by mentioning menstrual cycles, so get to have time off whenever i like!  Get to do light duties like making cups of tea, get a company car to fetch lunches! Boss brings me fags from Marbella on a regular basis and just knocks them off my wage!  Get more freebies then anyone alive, all i have to do is entertain them with boozing and shagging stories and they LOVE me!  BUT.....they get to go home at 4.45pm today to watch the match, i however have to run the empire and stay until 5.30pm to lock up all because i have a fanny!  WRONG!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright so the weekend. I know you're all just dying to hear, I mean that's why you come right?  Ok, Friday we were moving offices at work so we all worked hard (well I say 'we', pretty much only Matt and I while the rest of them drank wine and watched us) shifting things around and then decided that we all well and truly deserved a drink (just for being us).  So we went to the Tuns and they'd put tables outside which was nice so we sat in Houghton street and got ourselves very drunk.  Usual suspects. Matt, Eleanor, Lynsey and I. Don't know why we decided to drink at warp speed (ok we're alcoholics) but I'd knocked back about seven pints of Stella by about half eight (not counting the two from lunch) and left Lynsey and Eleanor to go back to the Arms.  I was absolutely trashed and quite frankly did well to get back home. Got to the Arms and had one pint there and just generally wandered around feeling oddly nihilistic (well so I've been informed, I don't really remember). And...and here hold the presses...I actually went home before kicking out time (which I also don't remember doing)  Saturday was Builder Dave's birthday (he's not actually a builder, he's a plasterer, but Plasterer Dave just isn't quite right) so got to the Arms at 3 for an all dayer. Had a couple in the Arms with David, Builder and Kerry and then we went over to the George to get trashed on cheap drinks (which we did).  Headed back to the Arms where the less hard-core of Builder's friends were waiting for him and proceeded to drink. Natasha turned up pretty late, by which time I was quite drunk anyway and fairly sure that I wasn't all that coherent for the rest of the evening.  Sunday was the football...which we shall say no more about save...  'Did that really happen?'   (I mean seriously, I dreamnt those last two minutes right?)   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The blog is a day late and i got done.........the truth of the matter is i was busy yesterday catching up on the big brother website (not actually working, that would be mental). The weekend? how we love the weekends?  Steven was 25 on Fri, the party kicked off in the shoulder of mutton with approx 30 of his great mates, i'm sure he'd put all last years cards up as well, he can't be more popular than i am. Marlene was in attendance which was nice, but also meant we had to curb our behavior. I started to have withdrawal symptoms at 10.30pm so got Marlo to take me to Clecksville.........hooray!! Got a quick beer in the Turnstiles only to be told we were moving pubs, so snook it down my pants and took it to the rose, where we had a swift one. Then calamity... got to the Station and the doors were LOCKED!!   We had to go to the regal sober, it was the strangest experience ever! Hayley, Rach, Spug, Dean and myself sat in a line waiting for it to fill up..WRONG!! Solution? drink and fast, it worked a treat and i was soon busting shapes on the dancefloor, the birthday boy turned up with all his clan as drunk a lord, took him for a curry where we were joined by an old flame of mine, who shall remain anonymous, well he said he wanted to show me a real good time but had to get home and was in a rush....CHEEKY FUCKER!!! like i'd go back there anyway? SHUDDER.  Came out of sloppys and could hear KAREN in stereo, Steven laying on the market bars asking me to join him and Hayley and Spug holding a taxi door open shouting get in! which option did i take? work it out....  Sat was a tame evening to begin with just MJW, Claire, Dean, Tina arena with her Greek tan and myself, had a few in Spoons, Turnstiles, Rose, Station (where the Westlakes bought bags of sweets from behind the bar, You are NOT 12) then the Regal bar (the crescendo of the evening). Asked you know who if i was still dumped this week? seemingly NOT was the answer. STRUTH!! are all men like this?? sooo back to square one GROUNDHOG DAY.  He left about half 10 Sunday morning i went back to sleep with a smile on my face (someone fetch me a big gun). Then watched the footie drinking wine with lunatic mate Lynn on Sunday followed by big brother (love it). 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today Steven has reached a quarter of a century, how on earth he has managed it is anyone's guess, this evening we are going for a small sherry in The shoulder of mutton pub in Gomersal. Something tells me the takings will be down in Clecksville.  Not only will we be missing, but MJW is going to Leeds with Claire to celebrate her birthday which was yesterday....Blinking Geminis! what are they all about with their 2 personalities.  I'm betting a pound to a penny we'll end up in the regal bar tonight after last orders, i might even go to sloppy jo's afterwards.......After I've eaten humble pie, they did actually have my purse and it was retrieved with all it's contents on Tuesday evening!  So that's the plan for tonight, tomorrow i am going to have a marathon lie in, as i have had guests round every night this week, keeping me from my bed and making me stay up exceptionally late boozing..... NO GOOD!!  Tomorrow evening MJW and i are going for a tame night in Clecksville after he admitted what a state he was in last week, he has now dropped the rape charges made against Matt, given up soft drugs, has started going to church, is now t total and is looking for a nice wife..........YEAH RIGHT?  HAPPY BIRTHDAY STEVEN AND CLARE FOR YESTERDAY xxx
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mandy (from the Tuns) leaving drink last night  Got absolutely hammered  Can't realyl remember very much. I think that this might actually be the problem. I have vague recollections of doing stupid things but I just can't remember them.  Maybe I've not become as boring as I thought.  Oh yeah I did get home and e-mail people.  Woke up in the morning with about 15 emails in my inbox.  Think that I quite possibly may have done the verbal equivalent.  I need an inbox in my head  Didn't go out again tonight. Been watching loads of Seinfeld.  Seinfeld rules.    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sleepy oh so sleepy  But it's going to be too hot to sleep, I know it.  Oh the paradox. What must I do damn you all, what must I do? This paradox is doing funny things to my poor little mind.  Aren't I fragile enough already (and it's too hot)? We all know about my IQ of 78 and the resulting pyschological feelings of intellectual and class inadequacy. Don't they (the nebulous cosmic 'they' of the controlling forces of the universe)know what they're doing to  me ?  To your Richy?  Are you all just gonna stand there and let them do this?  I thought that you cared about me? I thought that I meant something to you for Christ's sake. I cared about you and this how you treat me? As thought I were nothing? A piece of shit on your shoe? I gave everything to you.  EVERYTHIING . And this is what I fucking get?  This  is what I fucking get?.....Well...well..then fuck you.  I mean it, fuck you.  Fuck you and the horse you rode in on, and the guy who cleans your horse's stable, and that fucking guy's fucking mum.  Bitch that she is.  Yeah, bet she's real fucking proud. Son's a fucking stable boy.  And he's 63.  Oh man it's just too sodding hot. It's made me oddly belligerent and intolerant all day. The 'what fruit are you' e-mail. She who shall remain nameless. Dude who wanted a cigarette. And the Big Issue dude (who  so  doesn't look like a tramp...the man dresses better than I do)  (and don't any of you so called wits say a fucking word)  Alright I'm gonna go and watch some tv and pray to the Sky Gods (Rubert Murdoch) for Thunder and Rain (to wash away Richard's pain)  Hope I come back better tomorrow.  Failing that let my barbs be cutting and sharp and wrath directed againt the unrighteous and unclean.  I'll see you all in hell.  R      urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello,   May as well add to Karen's email with my own short one as I have not blogged for a while.  Friday was good but after regular drinking from 5.30 I feel that an 8 o clock start is just too late so I was on a mission to9 drink and drink and drink - and I did!  All started off OK in OBs, I had 3 pints and found out about Bev and MJW's sister!  What a funny match ... what was Claire thinking!  Put my foot in it with Karen's sister who I forgot I'd met.  I am rubbish.  Then quickly to the Turnstile which was OK but my bro was a bit off for some reason - I think he was just tired.  Then we went to the Rose and that's where I started feeling nicely steaming.  I sand delilah which was quite good and then I sang Summer Nights with MJW's sis, but she was crap as she had the mic switched off the silly bint!    We only just made it to the Station and I sang its raining men to a really bad karaoke version and I ended up buying some nasy regals there - god they're awful!  But I needed some so it seemed like a good idea, Karen sang Irish Rover - which is always good and I sang and danced along while eyeing up the cute as fuck DJ who Karen's bro claims to have got off with the lucky bugger.  And then to the regal where it got quite nast as we were all so pissed.  Matt took his top off and was dancing with this cute rough straight boy in a very sexual manner until he was ordered by a bouncer to put it back on.  Then we saw Ricky Stead who is as fit as and only about 23.  He's a sweet boy and very friendly and has a nice face.  So we danced with him and then who should we see but Big Jugs!   Big Jugs is one of MJW's old flames.  I don't think he ever shagged her but she wanted him to.  I remember that they went away for a wedding to Huddersfield and stayed at the hotel by the station.  Anyhew, she has massive bazonkas and so is called Big Jugs, although my cousin called her Gentry Dairies (because of all the milk, geddit) she seemed well but her hair was a bit rubbish.  I also bumped into Rachel Hartley who guessed I was gay (how in the world did that happen?) who was with someone most bizzare, was it stinger?  I can't remember now.  And we sort of bumped into Steven (not Stephen as he informed me today) but I only said hello and that was it.  I don;t know why Karen and I kissed but we did, twice, at the bar.  She didn't complain I used too much tongue so I shoudl at least be grateful for that!  At the curry house it was apparent that MJW was trolleyed, as he didn't eat his curry.  I ate it but at least he paid and I almost had to carry him to the taxi rank.  I got a cab home with him, put him to bed (while he was one minute inviting me to join him in there and the next minute accusing me of sexual abuse) I rang for a cab and pushed the keys through the letter box and got another cab home.  Oh dear clecksville firday nights are very bad, but very funny.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well.......i've be bang at it for 4 days solid, the amber nectar that is! Friday was top, as you know Matt was home, plus friend Sarah was also in attendance, she's a nurse in Great Yarmouth and is a top boozer. Was umming and ahhing about whether to go out at all, felt the need to stay away from that bad man who makes me cry, but luckily he wasn't out so all was well!  Did the usual..... Spoons, Turnstiles, Rose, Station (that was open for business even after the stabbing)Regal bar then Sloppy joes, highlights of the evening. 1.Matt bringing the house down with his rendition of Delilah. 2.Sarah going on to halves as she didn't want to get drunk WHAT? 3.Me and Matt snogging in the regal to confuse onlookers. 4.MJW being as drunk as drunk can be,was caught smoking blo in the Regal had to be carried to sloppys where he promptly fell asleep. Tut Tut MJ 5.Claire Westlake only mentioning tongue sandwiches once, thank fuck.  So even with the absence of Tina, Beth and Dean House, the numbers were rounded up with extras like Matt, Sarah, Sarah Brown, Warren and Caroline.   Saturday went to a posh BBQ in Leeds, started on the Stella at 3.00pm ate loads and basically drank like a bastard for 11 hours.  Sunday.....it was one of those off the cuff nights, started off me and Spug having a quiet Sunday afternoon drink, later to be joined by Dean and Rach who were fashionably 3 hours late, well i don't know what happened but we ended up in the Turnstiles where my bezzie mate Simon (bar manager) not only fixed it so i could win jump the pumps, but got a member of staff to help me out. Jump the pumps is where you have to guess the name and artist of the next song and you get a minute behind the bar. I ended up with 9 free pints and 5 bottles of blue WKD......i don't know what happened but i left my purse in sloppy joes and realised when i got home, got taxi driver to phone up the CHIEF who said no we havn't found a purse, thieving BASTARDS!!!  So i ended up knocking Jim and Marlene out of bed at 12.45am (they're my parents)to get my spare door key off them, they're sooo proud!  Yesterday was Grandads funeral, very sad occasion but also a good excuse to get battered, i had 2 shandys in the day, then met up with my Sister Ruth (she's engaged to be married and is not a failure like Steven and myself), along with Mark her fiance, Steven and other brothers Martyn and David, we started off in Spoons for a cheeky cheap few then ended up drinking like very thirsty people in the Whickham arms, till not one of us could either walk or speak properly, Steven and i staggered off into the night to confront the staff in sloppys about my purse, unfortunately it was shut and rattling the iron doors shouting oi, gimmee me money and me key back, had no effect whatsoever.  So am at my desk today and feel like i've had a stroke..........not good!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right so what did I do?  Basically just went to the Arms.  And nothing much happened. Yesterday was nice. Sat in the beer garden with Michelle, Claire, Dale, Darragh, Chris and Lorna...and Lorna's mate who somehow got absolutely hammered on about four pints...David turned up late (he'd been at a barbeque).  All of us pretty hammered enjoying the weather and generally talking absolute shit.  Saturday did the Arms and then went over to Taps because Chris was in there and John was working.  Dunno what else to say. I'm just completely rubbish. I hate my rubbishness. My rubbishness knows no bounds. When it comes to being rubbish I'm the commander in chief of the Imperial Rubbish Guard.  It's an achievement certainly, but you can fuck the Oscar.  I used to have loads of cool stories to tell after a weekend on the piss and now I just feel that I'm letting you all down.  I know you expect tales of laughter and mystery, of daring do and 'oh God please don't', and it breaks my heart to let you all down like this, but really I'm just kinda going out and being civilised at the moment. Obviously I get wrecked but somehow interesting things don't follow on from that. You'd think that if you were to get a group of people (many of whom have mentalist tendancies), get them hammered and then unleash them upon an unsuspecting world, that shit would happen.  But basically it's just saying goodnight and then stumbling home...well your respective take-away of choice (hmmmm Oriental Chef...fried squid with chile)...and then home.  I really don't know how to resolve this sad state of affairs.  What happened to the crying people and the falling down people and eating people people?  Where have they gone?  Do something about it.  Yeah you.  I need you, don't let me down.  Rich    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Lets have it.    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right what did I do yesterday?  erm, went to the Tuns with Matt, Alan and Chris (plus the repro boys) then Kate turned up.   By the end only Matt and I were left, then got to the Arms for half nine and kinda stayed there until half 2 for a lock in.  Why?  Dunno.  Just because I suppose.  Good a reason as any innit?  But again nothing mentalist happened.   Interestingly though I did realise who someone was that I'd been e-mailing in a (Arms) group e-mail thing all day.  That's quite odd.  Anyway I'm fucking boring and I need interesting mad things to happen.  Eleanor was in the middle of a fight on the bus the other night (nothing to do with her naturally), but why has that kind of thing stopped happening to me?  Have I become a normal well adjusted member of society?  Fuck that if I have. I don't want to be.  Mentalism loves company    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just remembered.......now i've stopped blubbing like a 12 year old.  That the last pub we attend of an evening before climbing the stairs to the infamous regal bar, well it's now a crime scene......yep that's right, trouble in Clecksville.  The landlord and landlady had one humdinger of a row and she STABBED HIM IN HIS SLEEP, now she is one mentalist drinker we need to keep on the right side of, she's now in the slam and i don't know if Carl's out of hospital.  Well fear not folks we think it's business as usual, well it was open on Sunday night when we called for a nosy (i meant a pint) just before we went for a gee at the lovely sloppy joes, Mmmmmm.  But if it's not open at the weekend, what the fuck will we do? this is the pub that never shuts, the only pub that has Irish Rover on karaoke, where will sexy Martin D.J? it's the end of the world as we know it.......this is a pub with memories, i've taken my bra off in there and put it down MJW's pants, we hold our snogging competitions on the dancefloor there, where i complain Matt and MJW use too much tongue, OH FUCK..........i'm going to start crying again.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I'm going to bed  dunno if that's the same thing  'night my loves  R   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday I'm walking home from the pub with a traffic sign I've nicked from somewhere (don't know why...don't ask...I'm just not completely normal)  Police car pulls up  Policeman: oi where do you think you're going with that?  Me: ...um...back to where I got it from...?  Policeman: that's right, what the hell were you going to do with it anyway?  Me: you're asking  me ?  Now that's more like the Rich you all know and love.  (more of the same definitely required..by a factor of about 4 I'd say [well four if it's a random night out]....or 5 if you're on a Friday night...go as high as 6 or 7 if you're on classic 'lets really go for it' night...that or there's any free alcohol going around)   I need to do odd things on the tube and fall off of shit attempting ridiculous things. It's a genetic need or something.  Don't really know why but then equally I'm only really friends with people with the same imperative to mentalism.  Anything else is just fucking boring  Well anyway for those of you who prefer the quiet life that's why we're here.  We're here to serve and protect (your livers)  You can live our madness vicariously.  Enjoy  Peace and Love,  R    urlLink Email me or die   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THE FROG SONG   by Vernon Dalhart & Adaline Hood   I'm a little merry frog And I am another. That old lady on the log She's our darling mother. Father had his legs cut off But the Frenchmen ate them Naughty wicked cannibals!   How we froggies hate them! Knee deep, Knee deep. Nee-deep nee-deep nee-deep nee-deep. We're a pair of happy froggies Singing in the ponds and boggies. Knee deep (etc.) When we see a naughty boy, in we go, kah-chung. Good Saint Patrick, so they say, Kicked us out of Erin, But we're mighty glad to stay In the land that we're in. If the naughty boys would be And quit their naughty throwin' There's one now-- Good gracious me! We had best be goin'! Knee deep, knee deep. Beh-dah-dee, beh-dah-dee,                              Beh-dah-dee, beh-dah-dee. We're a pair of happy froggies Singing in the ponds and boggies. Knee deep, (etc.) When we see a naughty boy, in we go, kah-choo. We once had a brother too, Cute and cunnin' feller. He was spotted green and blue And a muddy yeller. Every night he'd serenade And the air he'd fill it. A Frenchman ended his career, Put him in a skillet. Knee deep, knee deep, beh-dah-dee (etc) We're a pair of happy froggies Singing in the ponds and boggies. Knee deep, knee deep.  Nee-deep, (etc.) When we see a naughty boy In we go, Kah-chook. And we had a cute sister. Her legs were so pretty. Then one day why we missed her-- Wasn't it a pity-- Cannibals came out our way Blinded little sister And they stuck some thing in her-- That was when we missed her. Knee deep, (etc.) (Etc.)     urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Weekends merge  Not entirely sure what happened Friday night.  Went to Taps with Chris...Lee and Steve turned up and then Trav. Drinking Stella and then went over the Arms at about half eight.  Remember going outside to talk to Builder Dave and Chris (a different Chris..i.e not my brother and not Cylwik)and not arsehole Chris from the Arms.  Then I came inside and was at the corner of the bar with Amanda and Michelle...and then fuck knows what happened. Can't remember a sodding thing.  Obviously a good night then.  Saturday was Matt's barbeque which was really nice. Only a few of us...Matt (obviously), Alan, Lynsey, Nat and Mark Power...but tons of beer...which naturally we had to drink (and indeed did).  Loads of food as well. Nice day sitting in the garden drinking and talking loads of random shit.  Um ok so Sunday Arms again and then onto Taps with John where they had a late bar and then once they'd closed Bar Form where Trav, Head and Michelle were. We're wandering around from pub to pub and we know half of the people in them.   (I'm beginning to think we drink too much)  (nah silly idea. what am I thinking)  Monday got to the Arms quite late. David was already fairly drunk so I had to go some to catch up.  Not much to report. Some bloke got beaten up by...well someone...anyway that was funny. This super drunk guy was being a complete wanker so eventually he just had to go (head first)  But other than that no mentalism.  Haven't had a mentalist night out in ages. I dunno what the hell's happening.  Damnit it I want more nutters and inexplicable happenings.  If you're only going out to get drunk it's pointless  It's just a means without an end.  Suggestions please people. This sorry state of affairs cannot continue. I don't like it.  It's just all so very wrong    urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why wank not bank? Well Friday evening was excellent, everyone turned up as expected the only draw back being, we seemed to split into three groups, but everyone made it to the regal, some of us even remembered it! We were all royally trollied....i'd pulled squaddie coz Porritt wasn't out, he was paying for everything while i danced like a loon with all my mates, MJW and all his clan had been drinking strong cider and were a right sight of spilling drinks, trying to coordinate their feet and a bit of blubbing thrown in for good measure. Took Squaddie home for some bedroom athletics, after 2 hours of horizontal jogging was bored as fuck so faked it to get shut of him. Have decided he doesn't float my boat and not to go there again! Nothing to do with Porritt honest govenor........  Saturday Grandad died, decided to go out and get hammered in his memory, he wouldn't want me to be moping around..after all! Went to Aldo's with MJW, Katie, Claire and Ellie, had a lovely meal plenty of wine, so was in high spirits when we arrived at the turnstiles..........only to be blanked by Porritt, this happens every single time i see him, after we've had a particularly mind blowing time in the bedroom the previous week..........jeez he's as emotionally developed as a 16yr old! Anyhow this bird was all over him like a rash, i wanted to go over and shake her till blood came out of her eyes. I am NOT dramatic.  Spoke to him in the regal, got a string of one word answers, then he hinted would i be upset if he pulled another bird! WHAT???????? so i pointed at Squaddie and said would you be upset if i'd shagged him last night, he said No do what you want, me and you are going nowhere, we're not going out, i can't tell you what to do, but if you have, then whatever we have between us can't be strong enough for you not to have done that to me!!! out broke a full scale row resulting in me bawling and him storming off home................Sounds familiar!  So have mainly been crying/drinking just about none stop since then and am sad as fuck at my desk!  Only 3 more sleeps till weekend and we get to see Matt, at least that's something to look forward to!  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Filthy dirty bastards..........gave me a GOAT curry, I am not happy!   I'd rather just have carrots like Beth's dog.   I feel........... not hungover or sleepy today, which is good seen as the mentalists didn't leave till 1.20am, i've decided red wine doesn't get me drunk! it's like water to me, no effect whatsoever! Ruth was on export and Tina and Beth.........Vodka.......nutters, on a school night as well!   Tonight is going to be a good one, i can feel it........  I'll be taking the register at 8.00pm prompt in O.B's.  MJW,Ruth,Mark,Spug,Tina,Beth,Claire,Katy,Hayley and all Tina's work mates as it's her Birthday are all dead certs.   Steven has guests for the weekend, shiney Elaine and Mrs. Brunnings!   What are your thoughts on yellow stillettos?   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Birthday Tina Arena, she's got the key of the door and all that bollocks!   To celebrate, we're gonna have a break from the norm! No fuck that we're off to Cleck.........."if it's not broke don't fix it".   Last weekend is but a distant blurry drunken memory........Highlights are as follows:   1.Sarah and boring Richard are at it yet again (but he's not boring anymore).......even though he's growing peas in his back garden.   2.Hayley is in lurve with big fat sweaty swamp thing (but he's nice and everyone sweats in the regal).   3.Rach has still got the lurgy as hasn't been seen since 1986 or summert.   4.Matt got egged (don't ask).   5.Beth is back, with sister in tow,&nbsp;with a new nose (it didn't look any different to me).   6.Spug left early Sat, after declaring "you can't get drunk on cheese"   7.Kay Wailes throws the poshest BBQ'S in the World.   8.The pink stillettos being a REAL hit and&nbsp;was asked to keep them on longer than necessary.(Steven's comment "maybe your feet smelt").   9.The Jews are all in Marbella for the most of August, i'm in charge of the company........hahahahahahahahaha!!!!!!!   10.Last but not least, why am i the only fucker blogging?   &nbsp;   &nbsp;    
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would tell you about my birthday but lets just say that it was a complete car crash and leave it at that (also it was two weeks ago and a complete blur)  My birthday was actually on Wednesday so went out for drinks then even though we hadn't intended to.  Actuallly celebrated on the Friday with the work guys   (free champagne, lots of pints, JD and coke, shots of sambuka and chilly chille (don't even ask)   Fell over twice and managed to fuck up my ankle. Still hurts. Absolutely smashed out of my head.   (and there was a thing with chairs and it's a wonder we never broke anything)   (and I dropped a box of paper cups which bounced out of my arms and hit a woman)  Then celebrated on Saturday with my Enfield guys (although Kev and Matt made it down)  Started at 3.   Don't think there was any one moment when I didn't at the very least have two drinks on the go.  Had 3 in the Arms I think then went to the George for the cheap drinks and then over to Taps.  By which team they were getting me quadruple JD's (amongst other things).  People kept turning up through the evening and everytime they did someone shoved another drink infront of me.  Got to the Arms. Pint and two sambukas later I just had to leave the building.  Right so what did I do last weekend.  Erm Friday round Enfield. Much of the usual I think.  Saturday was Kerry's birthday and the band were playing which made for a good night. Got to the Arms at about 3.  David had bought me a bottle of JD for my birthday so we say outside and consumed that from about half 6 onwards.  (Kinda drunk as you can imagine)  And this is my point.  Birthdays.  Your own, your mates.  They always end up in car crashes.  They're evil things which should be banned forever.  (well until next year anyway)    urlLink Email me you spanners!    
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My place of work is a fucking farmyard! The managing director called at the joke shop on his way to work this morning, he's spend all day giving unsuspecting punters sweets that make your tongue go blue, has been putting itching powder on chairs, i just lit a fag that exploded in my face and there's more coins lying around the place that give you electric shocks!  I can't cope anymore.......it's not even funny! make no wonder i am the way i am! i've headache with it all.....it's not normal is it?  I'm glad it's Friday and i can spend time with sane people, well sane isn't the word for any of my friends!  Anyhow i've bought new pink stillettos, i'm having an identity crisis! i've pushed aside the fact that i look like a geezer in drag in them and have convinced myself, they're the way forward........the ticket to my new mate, the man that will impregnate me and take me away from this asylum!  Yeah we all know i'll knacker them up in the regal tonight, by which time i'll be drunk as trousers and won't care..........  FUCK IT!! I'll get a new pair........  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Might still be pissed though! Top Top Top weekend, Friday was cool..Sarah was up from sunny Yarmouth,    Matt made one in (first time in a month).Even Steven was in attendance, (Beth was missing, she's had a nose job, like a film star.....that was the rumour at least).  &nbsp; Really great night, got to the Regal after Steven and i had sung burning love on karaoke. Forgot it was a night club and you could actually dance and eye up tasty men, so Sarah and i stood nattering for a good hour, putting the world to rights, with our pints of deisel! &nbsp; Got to 10 mins before last orders, Steven and i went to sloppys with Sarah refusing to join us,&nbsp; quote " there's far too many fit men out to go home this early". She turned up as we were finishing our gees ordered a dry naan bread and ate Steven's leftovers, still claiming she doesn't like curry! &nbsp; Sat.poor turn out only Spug, Hayley and myself! ended up in the Maltshovel for last orders which was a bit random, but very pleasant! I'd&nbsp;snook 2 lemonades in during the night as i didn't want to make a knob of myself over Andy leaving. Which i needn't have worried about as he was straight over the minute we got to the regal bar! yeah now he wants to act like the cosy couple, when he's off in a few weeks! had a few beers and a bit of a boogie then went to Andy's to do not very much sleeping............. I KNOW!!! &nbsp; Mad day yesterday, had to go back to bed when i got home, was f*cked literally...then raced round doing all my chores like a loon, as i wouldn't deserve to go to the pub if the housework wasn't done! &nbsp; Had a fab afternoon, me, Katy,&nbsp;Spug and all the gayers! drank loads and met up with Ruth, Mark, Rach and Dean...moved on to the Turnstiles with Simon P.A (top yorkshire d.j) or Simon pears and apples as we like to call him, as he's also a greengrocer! Hee hee........ &nbsp; So a bit of everything, drinking, dancing, karaoking, curry eating, shagging, loads of shut eye.......great days!!! &nbsp; Well until i start blubbing again!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Birthdays  &nbsp;  Just don't  &nbsp;  Trust me.  &nbsp; I know about these things.&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;   urlLink Email me you spanners!    
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday went to the SU Handover party with Alan and Matt on the promise of free alcohol (which only turned up at 11pm...and even then was only wine...which I drank anyway. Well it was free. What do you expect from me?)  It was just all incredibly gay. Bizarre.   Got very VERY drunk.  Woke up in the morning on Matt's floor (having gone to sleep on his sofa)lying next to a pot plant.  Kinda worried that I was hugging it.  I'd bought a few cans the night before so I polished those off for breakfast (well it was about half twelve by then so not that bad)and then went back to Enfield and got completely trolleyed. Left the pub at about ten.  (yes I know)   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't feel fine :o(  He's going to fucking Australia and leaving me, he wasn't even going to tell me, Katy (Hiya Karen) let it slip........it's only for 6 months and it's a good opportunity Karen, i've got family out there, were some of his mutterings! BASTARD.................  Solution? glass him in the jugular and find my policeman, were Steven's thoughts!  Anyhow Friday was SHIT, utter utter bab! Claire and Katy joined us after the virgin vie party, Katy was having traumas over that sloth she's been shagging..i'm sorry gold belcher chain, earring, tattoo, beer belly, shaved head, 13 yrs older than her and them knashers! what is the girl playing at? Steven was snogging Beth (that's not confusing)Claire was off!!!!!! Noone wanted curry so i threw the teddy out of the cot and was in bed at 1.30am bag of shite!   Saturday was excellent, Paul's engagement party MJW posing as my husband, plenty drinking, karaoking, MJW ate 47 chicken legs and said well the buffet wants eating a similar amount of times! works nights out are SOOO funny! anyhow my boss ended up paying for most of the booze, Leigh had 3 pints of stella and was shitfaced! Funny funny funny! i made it back to the regal for 12.45am Bargain £2 for 15 minutes, shot to the bar, found Porritt who was gushing, positively all over me, even said he'd missed me! YEAH WE KNOW WHY!!!!!! Fucking AUSTRALIA........ He still got his wicked way though, i'm so weak :O(    OH have there been tears, Steven is taking me out for a chinese tonight to cheer me up.  What am i going to do? 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's scary  And I'll be scared  Um...ok I'm a little girl, I'm not watching it  (Oh shut up it's scary and you know it)   urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last weekend seems forever away now........working weeks are just 1 day too long i've decided! I can manage 4 days but not 5..  Last Friday was a really good night, all girls....so in attendance were, Myself, Claire, Tina and her Mum (who is also called Karen),Katy, Rach, Hayley, Danika and another girl but i didn't catch her name! well we all had plenty to drink and managed to make it right until 1.00am without any dramas until the lights in the regal had been switched on and some bastards had nicked Claire's handbag.........oh fucking hell!!!! were there tears?  I took myself out of the equation, by running down to outbacks with Alex Green, who i've known since he was 3, for some more drinking and dancing,  what the fuck could i do anyway?  i was more drunk than i thought, as i skidded past 3 toilet cubicles banged my arm on the doorfame and broke my fall by cracking my bonce on the Kazi.........Taxi please. Well okay a lamb Korma.......joined by Rach and Tina at our favorite restaurant...   Saturday was well random, got to Spoons more or less the same crowd as last night, with a few lightweights missing! it was one of those nights where there were loads of people you know out, how popular am i? Chatted to Micky Foxall for a bit and Nellie, then mad Friend Lynn turned up with Paul and a friend of theirs Tino, who was an Italian Cockney and sold cabbages for a living! Pot Rat was at the bar and glanced over a few times then looked at his feet, like he was trying to remember where he knew me from! he was stood with some of Claire's NEW friends, James and Matthew............??????  It was a good night, Tino was buying double aftershocks and trying to impress us with his drinking antics...WHATEVER!!!! The regal was okay but everyone had coupled off and i spent a good hour refusing the advances of Richard barrow boy i emboss pictures on to china beakers for a living! We all went for curry and Claire was busy making a new friend in Tino, say no more!  Sunday was Grandmas birthday, she's batty.......it was an open house, Jan Star and Uncle Michael were the only one's present when i arrived, but Grandma still insisted on playing pass the parcel, as you do........i won a pencil, quickly wolfed some trifle down and made a hasty exit, muttering Families......  Tomorrow evening we are a bit thin on the ground, as Spug, Hayley and Rach are all in Wales, Matt is at his works summer do and Katy and Claire are spending the evening at a make-up party!???  So just Tina arena, Beth and Dean......i'm sure we'll manage!!!!!!!!!!      
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right then.   Last night was excellent. The Party on the Plaza. Except it wasn't on the Plaza because it was pissing down.  So instead it was the party in the Senior Dining Room. I had to go up and help them shift the tables around.  Of course come six o'clock the sun came out and it would have been a perfect evening for it.  Right so two pints of Stella at lunch time. One pint in the Quad before I went up to the party and then inumerable bottles of beer  (IT WAS FREE!!!!)  Well until that ran out (hadn't eating anything all day either) then had to go on the punch which was fucking lethal.  Then Alan bought some champagne so that also went into the punch....  Yep I was more than little hammered. Of course I wasn't the only who was.  Matt collected all the balloons and decided that he was going to try and fly. So he's got maybe a hundred balloons and he's up on the table determined to try and jump off and fly (can't wait 'till we get the photos of that back)  At one point we got the Stewards radios and Chris and I are singing together from different parts of the room. I got some funny looks when I went to toilet and I'm reporting my progress on the radio.  Went to the George after that. Had a pint and then decided to go.  So I did.  Made it to the Arms for one. Don't know how though. I was absolutely wasted. Now I can get hammered but I've rarely been that drunk. I barely made it onto the train at Seven Sisters...and for that matter why the hell didn't I go from Liverpool Street.  I remember sitting on the bench at Seven Sisters and having to use all of my mental effort to get up and walk onto the train. Fucking world had decided to go all slanty on me.  I mean what the hell's all that about?  What I ever do to it?  It was a good night.  Oh and here's to Kate and Chris on their one year anniversary. Rock on guys     urlLink Email me you spanners! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not stopping.........perhaps i've just got more time on my hands than other folk? BB......... will Marco go?, i hope not, i think he's top.....he's a cross between MJW and Dirty Danny, i think Nadia should go, definitely not Michelle...she needs to stay and rape Stu (whether he likes it or not). Anyway i'm not watching it, i'm going out to get drunk as trousers...Yep i know, you're all shocked. Proper girly night out, no men allowed! Dean is on his hols, MJ is staying in and Steven no longer hangs out with us. So lipgloss, white wine, shrieking and going to the loo in 2's and 3's. Hmmmm.......  I love Fridays, i get really hyper about going out (coz we don't do exactly the same thing every week). I'm in a really good mood today, MD gone golfing, Paul went for his hair cut 2 hours ago, i'm listening to galaxy 105 and Leigh is dancing round the office in a ladies muscle vest (you think i'm joking?) i think he just needed a breather from Betfair...  Oh yeah Psycho Michael has been back in touch.......now he's a strange one! In comparison pot rat, is really quite normal.  See ya Monday with the weekends news..
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This heat is unreal, it's so muggy, it's not even nice warm, it's horrid!  I've consumed my recommended alcohol intake for a whole year in the last 3 days, good going i know, thank you........i take a bow.  Thursday virgin vie party........wrong! girly girls trying fizzing foot scrub and comparing tones of foundation, fuck that get me out of there! Ordered some perfume i hadn't even smelt, as long as it smells nothing like gravy i'm sure it will be fine!  Friday was top....eviction party, Katy,Spug,Hayley,Tina,Beth,Rach,Dean and me, lots of booze was drunk and 11.15pm two taxis to the regal please. Was quite enjoying myself, until i realised that Tina, Beth and Steven had disappeared probably to outbacks, Rach, Dean, Ruth and Mark had all left for food and Spug, Hayley and Katy had all pulled.  I was stood there on me tod like a right wally, can of redstripe in one hand and fag in the other, yep went for another lamb korma takeaway and put my can in the fridge for another day.   Saturday was a bit pants, Mad friend Helen came round Saturday afternoon for a few soft drinks and a natter. Town was dead Saturday night.......bag of shite, realised there would be no action so took myself off home at 10.30pm to watch Peter Kay.  Which was a master plan as i had plenty money left to play out yesterday, it was Katy and Claire's works BBQ down at the sports club, it was a scorching day which made us really thirsty, we sat in the sun with our pints of lager top, until 6.00pm then headed for Clecksville, Weatherspoons for a couple of hours, me, Katy and Spug.  Then round to the rose and crown, Ruth , Mark, Rach, Dean, Deans dad and Mandy then Phil turned up. Seemingly i thought i was the entertainment for the evening: Random comments i threw at people: 1.Who dares me to down a packet of peanuts? 2.Mark? do you want to swap shoes? 3.Shall i call Peter Stringfellow over? (random at the bar). 4.I need pizza.  Oh heck!!!!!!!!!! So that's the weekend wrapped up......over and out.  Question. How do you bath a cat that has weed himself in his cat carrier on the way to the vets? Answer. Run a bubble bath and submerge the cat carrier with cat inside, to just below chin level, hang out cat to dry!  GENIUS!!!!!!!  A special hello to Janet........you know who you are!       
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't think he'd go, but he took it on the chin........he even reckons him and Michelle definately have a future together bless him! the young fool...  Well i've had a busy week, not only the pressures of being in charge at my place of work, you can all stop laughing now!!  But i've been bang at it all week, mates phoning/calling round, Helen from Southampton, Kay from Leeds. Matt called round with a pink dressing gown he'd bought but didn't suit him, he wondered if it would fit me? Hmmmm  Lynn came round last night for BB eviction and vino. Claire's virgin vie party tonight, that's after i've taken Luther to the vets with his poorly toes...poor  Luth!!! i don't know what's worse squashing an animal the size of a donkey into a cat carrier or the car journey itself.  Tomorrow is BB Eviction party, followed by a trip to the regal bar afterwards, just to see what it's like. Maybe a curry afterwards??????  When will it all end? when i know i'll let you know!  Oh Yeah, i bought brand new pink stillettos, yep i was right i fucked the 1st pair up in the regal.......       
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tina's birthday night out was fine, all present and correct.....i few people cared about her that much, they took her for food to sober up before she went to outbacks!........no not me, i was snogging Alison Rhodes's brother who claimed to know me, i've since found out he's engaged to be married...knob!! Don't really know what happened, but everyone got split up..you know with the regal being the size it is, it's easy to lose your mates! I got a takeaway and went home on my tod, fortunately this time it was lamb.  Sat..only Tina, myself and Beth out.......still it was a very pleasant evening, nothing eventful happened.  Was beginning to think, i'd changed into a normal run of the mill, dull kind of 35yr old type person with no stories to tell........  Until SUNDAY........  Txt everyone in my phonebook, within a 3 mile radius ...  Anyone fancy beer and hotdogs in the garden 4.30ish? 12 attended.......not bad! Laugh? i think i did! a lot......  MJW refusing to take off my floor to neck cerise pink velour dressing gown, was last seen walking down Whitcliffe Road, heading for home in it, still claiming he was adamant we hadn't eaten any hotdogs???????????  Oh dear oh dear oh dear!  Mr.Stephenson's great news though!!!!!! HOORAY!!!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>