<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it's been a few days... Sue me. Here's the low down so far. Practical test on Friday, nervous as Terry Nichols at a Patriot Act Supporter Convention. To give people who may not know an idea of what's going on here, I'l explain it all. Now isn't that nice of me? No, I really want to tell this story using as much space as possible. See, now I'm a jerk.  Ok so this is a practical test, meaning there is no "When in doubt, choose C". I actually have to show some guy, or women that very well may not even be at the same EMT level that I'm testing for, that I can perform the skills required to be a paramedic. There are six stations, with six different examiners. If I do poorly on one station, I may retest on that station on the same day, this gives the state a cover for bad examiners. If I fail two or more, I have to try the next exam. The exam results will be mailed to me within three weeks, according to the powers that be. How they can tell  me that I've only failed one station that day and have me retest but can't tell us whether we passed or failed within, say a week, is greatly beyond me.  Just to give an idea of what kind of pressure we face for this  test, check this out: School price: $6000. Plus books, at $350. Plus  the cost of spending at least 20 hours a week sitting in a class room for 6 months. Now comes hospital internship time, 400+ hours of that, with a time limit. See, these classes run concurrently, and no course dirtector wants 30 students trying to get test dates while 30 more a starting up, creates chaos, you know. So after you finish practicing your skills in the hospital you move into the field internship part. Ride an ambulance for at least 100 hours and get 100 points. You get points by practicing skills like IV's and Medication administration in the ambulance. Of course this all well and good until you realize that you actually have to intubate and use electricity on a patient during this time to achieve 100 points. This means you have to "work a code" or "assist a patient who's chief complaint is cardiac arrest"... fun frigging shit, my man. Now, after completing this requirement, you can take your practical test. Pass that and you can move on to the written exam. Got it? Good.  My job depends on me passing this test. Enough pressure yet?  So now the test. My first station: IV, which includes starting an IV, adminstering a medication by syringe (Bolus), as well as mixing a bag of medication to "drip" in (Infusion). I started the IV quickly and easily. I was told to give the patient a bolus of a medication called Lidocaine (a heart medication, 0.5 - 1.0 mg per kg of patient weight), again, done without a problem. Finally I was told to infuse 2mg of Lidocaine per minute. I mixed the medication into my bag of saline and set the drip rate. I was so incredibly confident at this moment I could've told the examiner that I was setting my drip rate to "Plaid drops per minute" and I would've sounded correct. Instead I told the examiner I was setting the drip  rate to 15 drops per minute, which although it may have sounded reasonable, it's only 1mg, which makes it reasonably wrong. The examiner just said "OK, good," and made a notation on his little clipboard. He sounded impressed. As I left the room I thought to myself, "What the HELL was I thinking?!?!?" But the examiner sounded impressed, so I really couldn't tell if he was even listening to what I was saying.  Next station: Kendricks Extrication Device, or the KED vest. This is a Basic station, and it evaluates how well we can support the spine and neck of a seated patient. It went well, and I'm confident that I passed that station.  Next came the airway station. I've always been good at this, so I wasn't worried. As expected I handled the small issues that came up easily. Put that station on the "Probably Passed List" also.  Next was Random Basic Skill. Now this station should be a cake walk, but most paramedic failures come out of this station. We spend all of our time learning new paramedic skills that we forget to lose our bad habits that we get from working on the street. I sweated my balls off through this sation, not because it was difficult, but because the examiner had me putting a cute female in a traction splint. This means that my hands were in her crotch. Great fun, I'm trying not to eff this test up, now I'm trying not to eff up in front of an attractive woman, with my hands between her legs... What a frigging test. So I put her in the traction splint (curious about this? Break your femur, you'll learn ALL about traction splints), and then was told to place a patient on a long spine board. You've all seen this, it's the long board with the collar and head blocks you see people that have been in car accidents on. So I did this fine, or so I thought. I was completely done and told the examiner so. "You sure?" he replied, so I looked up and down the patient quickly and realized that I had forgotten the frigging HEAD BLOCKS!! The most obvious and maybe even important peice of this pie! I said as much and corrected my mistake. Check that off a "Passed, Barely".  Trauma Assessment. You get a guy lying on the floor in a rip-away shirt. You're given a scenario and are told to treat the patient. You do your exam and find the guy on the floor has injuries painted on him. Fun. No, really. I had a guy in his mid-thirties that rolled his ATV. Easy. Head injury: check, broken ribs affecting his lungs: check, did I mention massive head injury? Yeah, so his breathing sucked,and I never intubated him. I did, however secure his airway at the Basic level, and every time I reassesed it, i was told "Clear and secure". So passed? Who the hell knows. I did run into the victim a few days later, who informed me that not intubating the patient was not a automatic failure. Nice to know...  Cardiology. In the respect of your eyes, I won't describe this station, it would take forever. Either way, I was worried, but it was a cake walk. As I left, the examiner said "I can't tell you how you did, but if you look over my shoulder, you'll see which box I'm checking." It was the pass box. Put this station in the Pass Column.   Now it's been 6 days and I haven't heard anything yet. Just in case, the next practical is 3 weeks from the last test. Which is also the time we should be expecting our results... Great, this leaves no one any time to schedule a retest, which you can't do without your results... Frigging state.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, my first foray into this online diary stuff that everyone else has been doing. Why am I doing this? Two reasons. 1: Everyone else is and I am the least original person I know. And 2: I'm hoping that this will get me back into writing again.  Now I test for my Paramedic certificate on Friday. It's kind of a big deal, at least I think it is. Too big a deal to be told about it on Monday, anyway. And today, being Thursday, has been a day absolute torture... and it's only 3:00.  So this is what has been on my mind for the past week or so, thoughts that scare even me. First off, Static Cardiology. I have to sit across the table from a state examiner and just talk about what I'd do for patients in the scenarios he or she hands me. This sounds simple, I know, but think of all those cops films you see, the ones with the partners. One plays good cop, one plays bad cop. Now picture being in that interrogation room with only the bad cop. Sweating yet? Oh yeah, this guy has my career in his hands. That's right, I fail, I lose my job. Woo-freeking-hoo.  And lets not forget "Random Basic Skill". Yeah, basic, as in simple, as in I've been doing this for three years, I should know what I'm doing. Except that no one ever works the same way they were taught. KED vests? Never used it on the street. But I have to use it tomorrow, and I have to do it flawlessly, which isn't a problem, except with all the added pressure of the Airway, IV, Trauma Assessment, and Cardiology stations. Besides, KED and Random Basic are the most often failed stations in this test. Go figure. Come back tomorrow for an update on the torture... and they said the Iraqi prisons were bad.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here's the update from the last post  It turns out that my parents, who never showed much interest in the fact that I finally got my medic, have been planning a party. Now don't get me wrong, they were plenty excited when I passed the practical test... It just seems that they blew their celebrating load on the first half of the test... No stamina, those two.  The other surprise of the day, Lauren's also been planning a party, in fact, she has been planning the same party as my parents. It was SUPPOSED to be a surprise, but where Lauren was in charge of getting addresses of all my friends, she thought I'd figure it out.   And I'm not going to tell her otherwise. She put "No OT" on the calendar for the two days she expected the party to be on. Hmmmm... She also decided that once the Fire Department got their group invite, they'd let me in on it in the most inconspicuous way. Like: "Oh hey Matt, I got the email from the Chief about your party, and I'm sorry that I can't go, we're on that night, but have a great time..." Things like that...   So it's no longer a surprise. Wait until the invites come, Lauren did something pretty incredible. It's on July 9th... Watch your mailboxes.  Oh and the important part? It seems we're importing a liquor store to my parents' back yard. Quite literally.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All right here's the deal... In about a week I'll become a paramedic, because, that's right, I passed every station and will be taking the written exam on the 15th.  Of course, "you may fail this exam," you might say, and if you were to say this, I would first mushroom stamp your forehead, and then reitterate how I am most definitely NOT taking the paramedic class again. No way, no how. Torture? Abu- Gharid-fricking-blah prison has nothing on a paramedic course.  So what does this mean to you? Party. Huge party. If I were Will Ferrell I would say "Gi-normous" party. 'Cause this is as close to graduation college I'm ever going to come, in this life anyway.  Now this is not a "Happy Grad" party, where everyone dresses nicely and brings gifts and shite. No... this will be a return to my roots, if you will. My roots being in Amherst, Massachusetts, where parties last years, or until you graduate or, in my case get tossed out of, college.  Beer, loud music, live music, food if possible, who knows. All I know is that there will be beer. And music. And beer. And probably some Jim Beam and Jagermeister. And Smirnoff. And Captain's. 'Cause this'll probably be the last party of my unmarried life that I get to throw. So it'll be debaucherous.  Planning this will be an issue, for example: my apartment is out. First of all, I literally live in East Buttfuck, err... Eas Bridgewater. Besides that, I have somewhere between 6 and 8 cubic feet of living space. My porch is larger than most of the rooms in the apartment. My parent's place? Absu-fricken-lutely not.  Too much baggage. Lauren's parent's? Her dad will bogart the kegs. So will her brother, which isn't a REAL problem... Oh wait. It is.  Paul's place: Boston, better location, smaller apartment.  So, first step is finding a suitable location... Any ideas?  After this is solved, I'll tell you all about the next step... alcohol.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>