<Blog>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The objective of this blog is to create awareness of outsourcing as a practice and to share its benefits to individuals and organization across the globe  The debate surrounding IT outsourcing is heating up. To help provide an in-depth, real-world view of the issues and impacts of this phenomenon, I have decided to start this blog. This blog will now feature special coverage on offshoring, highlighting firsthand experiences and front line perspectives of people directly involved with outsourcing in one way or the other.  I would invite you to please help me share our collective knowledge with this world.  ----------------------Lets share the knowledge-------------------- 
    
    
</post>


<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dictionary Meaning  en·tre·pre·neur :A person who organizes, operates, and assumes the risk for a business venture  As the names suggests, the objective of the blog is to create an online exchange to share entrepreneurial information  The aim is to create a community comprising of individuals who thrive on the feeling of being an Entrepreneur. This blog will feature special coverage on entrepreneurship, highlighting firsthand experiences of being an entrepreneur and front line perspectives of individuals who have been , who are or who want to become what i call an "entrepneurholic"  This blog will help provide an in-depth, real-world view of the issues and impacts of this adrenalin pumping feeling, I have decided to start this blog.   I would invite you to please help share our collective knowledge  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The life of an entrepreneur is a confused one – full of choices to be made and paths to be taken (or not). Every day brings forth its own enigmas, leaving the entrepreneur is a perpetual state of being caught between multiple worlds. And, surprising though it may seem, it is the entrepreneur’s own making. It is a decision he has made of his own free will – a life of continuous flux, uncertainty and unpredictability...  urlLink More  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Passion:   An entrepreneur is fighting a war, a guerilla war. The enemies have more of everything: money, people and resources. They are the defenders. To stand a chance of winning, an entrepreneur needs the "Mother" of Business: Passion.   Passion is what comes from within, it is that fire and energy which can help the entrepreneur surmount even the most difficult of obstacles. Passion is perhaps the single biggest differentiator for an entrepreneur. In the words of Jack Welch, "If there's one characteristic all winners share, it's that they care more than anyone else. No detail is too small to sweat or too large to dream. It doesn't mean loud or flamboyant. It's something that comes from deep within."   Realistic Entrepreneurs? A euphemism? No. Entrepreneurs are not trying to do impossibilities. They have a dream of tomorrow, but one that is within the realms of possibility. Entrepreneurs see the same things that every one else sees, but based on their unique experiences and thinking, are able to put these together differently. Entrepreneurship is not about taking the greatest risk known to humanity, but about reducing risk in the endeavors to create what is within the bounds of mankind.    Innovation:   An entrepreneur's brain needs to be constantly active. Good ideas do not come between 9 am and 5 pm, Monday to Friday. For entrepreneurs, the conventional approaches don't exactly work. At the early stages when one in trying to build a business, few ideas from how large businesses go about doing things work. Talking to friends who work to the top-notch MNCs won't give a clue on how to fight the battle in the trenches. Putting up ads in newspapers are out of the question because they are way too expensive. This is where entrepreneurs need to think differently.   Innovation also means trying out many different things. Some will work, others will fail. But unless one tries out things, one will not know. More importantly, new doors only open when takes steps in different directions, and closes some others  Innovation also means trying out many different things. Some will work, others will fail. But unless one tries out things, one will not know. More importantly, new doors only open when takes steps in different directions, and closes some others. In IndiaWorld, we launched 13 sites. Only 4 of them worked well. But if we had hesitated from launching the new sites, we would not have know got those 4 winners. As an entrepreneur, one has to put away the fear of failure and think: what would you do if you were not afraid?    Choice:   We all have a choice: we can either accept the status quo or think like entrepreneurs. Whether we are working or running our own businesses, this is what can set us apart from the rest. In an entrepreneur's world, there is no room for mediocrity or petty politics.   There is no acceptance of underperformance or tolerance of exists. There is no room for losers. Entrepreneurs work to change the rules of the game, and play to win.  Entrepreneurial thinking is not only about the short-term or the long-term. It is about both. Therein lies the challenge. Anyone can do one or the other. To do both is what entrepreneurship is about. We not only need to build the strong foundation for the future, but also make sure that the salaries and bills for this month are taken care of it.    There is an opportunity for us all. To rise above the ordinary. To make a difference. To live a life. To bring out the entrepreneur within. The choice is for each us to make.  This wonderful quote from Dan Bricklin sums up that entrepreneurial feeling:    Being a successful entrepreneur is tricky. You have to live with having control and not having control at the same time. It's like this: In big business, when you need to cross a river, you simply design a bridge, build it, and march right across.  But in a small venture, you must climb the rocks. You don't know where each step will take you, but you do know the general direction you are moving in. If you make a mistake, you get wet. If your calculations are wrong, you have to inch your way back to safety and find a different route.   And, as you jump from rock to slippery rock, you have to like the feeling..    Cheers  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>