<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HEATHER MERCER OF FRANKTON HIGH SCHOOL! THE ANSWER WAS SEAN CONNERY.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHO WAS THE FIRST ACTOR TO PLAY 007. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DID YOU KNOW THAT BRITTNEY SPEARS MAY BE THE NEW BOND GIRL! DID YOU ALSO KNOW THAT PIERCE BROSNAN HASN'T BEEN SIGNED ON TO PLAY THE ROLE OF 007. WHEN WILL THE MOVIE COME OUT YOU ASK? WELL....I HAVEN'T FIGURED THAT OUT YET BUT I WILL LET YOU KNOW WHEN I DO FIND OUT.                                                                                                                  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHAT, OR WHO IS LITTLE NELLY. (YOU ONLY LIVE TWICE)
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      NAME THE HINCHMEN IN THE MAN WITH THE GOLDEN GUN & THE ACTOR THAT PLAYED 007 IN THE MAN WITH THE GOLDEN GUN. (to answer press comments for this page)
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you here of any James Bond news, LET US KNOW! We would like to post it on our web site if we LIKE IT. Not to mention give you credit for telling us about it. To let us know, click comments for this page.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have recently heard that there is a new James Bond game coming out, in which you are not playing the role of 007! The game will come out for all game systems sometime within the next year or so. Dylan and I will let you know ANY new details as soon as they are discovered. Let me know what you think. (to let me know, click comments)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHAT WAS THE VILLIANS NAME (full name) IN DIAMONDS ARE FOREVER? HINT(he is No.1)
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This Photo Is A Classic&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone, this is Dylan. I'll be helping to keep the blog going by doing some of my favorite things on the web like HTML editing. Give the site a week and it will be looking awsome. i'll get bond pics posted all over, and some other stuff. Im gonna see what i can do right now. Till Next Time 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tell me if you like my website (what I need to improve on or add). Also, tell me what you think about James Bond. Also, let me know your favorite Bond movies,characters,etc.. Place under comments
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      IF YOU HAVE ANY BOND QUESTIONS THAT YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND, OR HAVE A SUGGESTION FOR THE MONTHLY BOND QUESTION.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The new James Bond game is out, and it is fantastic! Everything or Nothing is a must have for every James Bond fan. This is by far the best one since Goldeneye. This game is in third-person view, and has some HOT bond girls! New gadgets, and exotic locations make this a great game. So, when you have an extra $50.00 laying around the house GET IT!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>