<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had another dream about whatsis-face, that guy I got hung up on in college, for reasons that baffled those nearest to me.  My sister was the only one who sort of got it.  She said, "you'd just never met anyone remotely like that before."  He had a murky mind.  His energy was a combination of Christian Slater's character in "Heathers," the raspy-voiced misfit who blows everything up, and a single scene in "The Unbearable Lightness of Being," where Daniel Day Lewis is confronted in his office by the KGB.  The KGB tells him, "Look, you're a doctor.  You're not political.  We know you didn't mean these things.  Just sign a little retraction, here on the dotted line, and you can keep your medical practice and everything will be fine."  Daniel Day Lewis leans back, smiles with an unearthly, casual radiance, and shakes his head, "no."  Cut to the next scene, of Daniel Day Lewis washing windows.  That was whatsis-face.    To this day, I have no idea of what whatsis-face thought of me.  I used to think that he just didn't, much.  (At least at first--after I went totally psycho on him, I was pretty hard to ignore.)  Then, much later, I thought that maybe I was simply Too Big.  Too tall, too visible, too much the kind of person who attracts circles of chanting people at parties when she starts spinning and doesn't stop, and ends up on stage with the band, and publishes fraught, obscure poetry in 'zines that twelve people read, and leaves puddles of dirty motor oil in the art department hallway.  I wouldn't have known what to do with me, either.  The woman he ended up with was much smaller.  She was famed for having size-five feet.  I have never been an overtly competitive female, preferring to withdraw with my wings folded rather than treat folks to the spectacle of two jealous harpies clawing each other's eyes out over some smug bastard, but she initally didn't even show up on my radar as a threat.  She whined, she manipulated, she wasn't very bright.  "Raaaaaaay," she would intone, toddling into the Salt Lick Cafe, "we're going on a daaaaaate this weekend.  I want to make whatsis-face jeeeaaaal-ous."  Please.  I would not STOOP to compete.  Which was fine with her, because she was a lot more highly sexed than I was, and that was all she needed.  Men are simple creatures, and I was, unfortunately, looking for complexity.  One afternoon in midsummer, whatsis-face got ideas about being a big cocky jerk, and decided to invite both me and Whiny Girl to lunch without telling us that the other one was coming.  I had a premonition about it when I saw her jump on her bike outside the art building and ride off with desperate purpose, so when I showed up to the assignation zone and found her already there, I sat down and made friendly conversation.  Whatsis-face strutted up a few minutes later, and plunked down between us with a bag full of plums.  He offered some to me; I drew myself up like an affronted Victorian nanny and refused.  He offered them to Whiny Girl; she extended her lower lip, gulped one directly from his hand, and sent him a look that at the time, I thought of as disgusting and Over The Top.  But even then I knew she'd won.  The events of the rest of that year are too tedious and gory to recount in their entirety.  Poor old whatsis-face ended up with a bruised jawbone (people were coming up to me for weeks and saying, "Serena!  I hear you beat up whatsis-face!  Congratulations!) and I ended up in therapy.  Whiny girl ended up with the guy, but only after using Ray and a number of his buddies with callous opportunism.  Turns out that whiny, manipulative and stupid was exactly what suited whatsis-face.  What can you do.  The thing that I felt horribly guilty about, for years and years afterwards, was not socking him in the jaw, but taking away his friends.  It was frighteningly easy to do.  His friends asked me, "why were you so mad at whatsis-face?" and I quoted him directly.  "It's not personal.  My feelings for all of my friends are pretty much apathy," and his friends didn't like this any better than I did.  I was witty and charming to his friends, and ignored him, and within a month or two nobody to speak of was speaking to him.    (A few years after this, I took one of those Meyers-Briggs personality tests, and scoffingly read my results to my roommate.   "ENFJ: it says, 'this type is exceptionally charismatic.'  What a crock," and she looked at me strangely and said, "you don't KNOW you're charismatic?"  I didn't know this, but I knew I was cruel.  It was my first experience of how, when you are hurting unbearably, the pain appears to stop when you hurt somebody else.  Only then it comes back again, and you have to keep hitting and hitting until it's way, way too much.)  I never went there again.  Eventually I apologized, and he got his friends back, and hopefully appreciated them a bit more.  In fact, being the Web-stalking psycho-bitch that I am, I know he appreciates his friends, and his wife the Whiny Girl, and is a nice upstanding member of the Sierra Club who volunteers for Children's Cancer and shit.  Maybe I knocked some sense into him.  But this doesn't explain why I dream about him.  Shame, I think, is why.  For a long time the dreams were the same; our friends were the same people, or our communities, and we were occupying parallel space without really interacting.  I didn't dare say anything, because I was that horrible psycho-bitch who socked him in the jaw and took away his friends, and thus was less than human.  Whiny girl generally appeared at some point, too, just there, not doing much of anything.    Lately the dreams have changed.  They're kinder.  Most recently, there was whatsis-face in a wheelchair, and I was helping him around, cleaning up bathrooms.  He got all happy and crazy and started drawing bright pastel patterns on the walls.  Whiny girl came along, and I said "I better be going."  Whatsis-face took my hand; I chatted with Whiny Girl.  He held her, and he held me.  I woke up happy.                            

						
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   are what I think they're called.  They look like tiny blue roses.  They don't smell, but they are profuse, and they dangle down.  I never heard of them before, but once I'd met them, ownership was mandatory.  And then I had to get a pot of pink-and-purple fuchsias to keep them company, and a little white cyclamen to replace the red one that died because the house-sitters didn't notice it, in the copper hanging basket, over Thanksgiving.  And then I had to re-pot everybody.    Okay, so I go on plant binges.  It's better than going on cocaine binges.  Cornelius says I'm not maternal, because when I have friends come to stay with me and they whine like spoiled four-year-olds for a week, I have hysterical breakdowns and don't get over it.  He says that if I had the Maternal Instinct and my friend acted like a four-year-old, and I realized that deep down she WAS a wounded four-year-old, all would be right with the world.    I don't know about this.  Maybe he's right.  Maybe I only have HALF a maternal instinct, and that's why I buy all these plants, and have a celebration every time the rubber plant unrolls a new leaf, and wring my hands when the china doll grows too near the stove burner and gets singed.  Maybe that's why I sit at breakfast every morning and encourage the ficus.    Then, of course, there are the cats.  I maintain that I don't really have three cats, because having three cats in a one-room apartment in Brooklyn would be crazy.  I just have one Cat, the Big Splendid Cat.  Then there is the Little Kitty, a different thing entirely, and utterly indispensable.  The Brat was an afterthought, and anyway he spends most of his time in the ceiling, above the acoustic tiles, which he figured out how to rearrange all by himself.    The Brat, however, is constantly warring for space with the orchid and the japanese fern, and I really don't know what to do about it. They all NEED to hang out in the bathroom window, and there's not room for all three of them there.  The plants get first dibs because they can't fight for themselves; they just sulk and languish for lack of humidity.  The Brat sends them tumbling onto the litter box, and everyone comes out with bruises, not to mention soil all over the bathroom.    Perhaps this is all just half-assed procrastination.  If I were serious about artistic procrastination I'd have a real baby, and put my art on hold for twenty years, and blame my frustration on the kid, and raise a serial killer and grow old and bitter.  As it is I just futz around with watering cans and cat brushes and vaccuum cleaners as an excuse for not painting.  That's what it seemed to be about on Friday, anyway, when I binged on campanulas after work, and then spent the next four hours watching Blind Date reruns, and went to bed excoriating myself for being lame and a failure and Not A Real Artist At All.  But then in the morning I realized that the reason I wasn't painting is that my studio was gunky.    It was full of cat hair and dead leaves and little flakes of scraped-off paint, and dirty rags, and seven unfinished paintings, all abandoned at Awkward Stages.  It was, simply, too disagreeable and overwhelming to contemplate, after massaging people all day, or before massaging people all day.  So I vaccuumed with the hose attachment, turned five of the paintings wall-wards, took out vats of garbage, did the dishes, re-potted some more plants, and voila!  I'm living in My Dream Life as an Artist.  With off-white walls, high windows, sun streaming in, and cellos playing constantly in the background.  I can't help it, I'm a romantic.  Today, though, instead of painting, I biked all the way uptown and saw the Whitney Biennial, which was actually worth the eight hours, the absence of bike lanes above 10th street, and the day out of the studio on one of the two precious days a week I'm not chained to the gallery.  Really, it ROCKED.  The last Biennial I had a revelation; that the Whitney wasn't the sole arbiter of What's Good In Modern Art, and thus I didn't need to take the Biennial personally and get really pissed off.  Instead, I took it as a "look at this, isn't that odd" sort of thing.  The years before that I DID get really pissed off, and competitive, and despairing.    This year, for the first time, I had an unequivocal blast.  I didn't walk up to each piece and think, "how cute," or "I can sort of see that," or "mmmmm."  I walked into the first room, which was full of big paintings by people who actually knew how to paint, and went "caramba!"  Then I went to the next room, which was full of complicated psychedelic images and videos and flashing lights in ever-changing colors, and went, "boop-be-doop-doop doop," and by the time I got to the sculptures of decaying werewolves in mirrored tombs with hummingbirds plucking jewels from their bones which were growing stalactites of quartz crystals, I was cackling and whooping unabashedly. I don't know how I would possibly write about this exhibition professionally--there was simply too much of it, and not enough for me to be ironic about.  I simply say, "Hiiiii-yah!  I salute you," plunk down my $40 for an artist membership at long last, and leave it at that.  On the bicycle I noticed that lately, the world is full of smells, and most of them are scrumptious, for some strange reason.  They are the kinds of redolent smells that imprint happy memories--baking cinnamon rolls, tobacco smoke, rain, herbal soap, indefinable green, floral things.  I don't know whether it's a sudden, miraculous respite of allergies, a random spiritual progression, or just spring.  Spring is a much, much, much bigger deal in a place where winter is constantly dark and full of piles of non-negotiable black icy sludge.  I used to think that people who fussed about Spring were about as fatuous as the curators of the Whitney Biennial.  Now I'm bouncing around telling people, "it's Spring!  it's Spring!" like a total idiot.  On the way home, after sitting in a burger joint having a celebratory Guinness and writing euphoric scribbles in my journal, I suddenly thought I'd start sculpting again, or making the sort of sculpture/painting/installation things I started making in art school, and stopped making for lack of encouragement.  I realized lately that you can KNOW that your instructors were jealous and screwed up and second-rate, and were being condescending and unsupportive out of ego and insecurity, and still internalize their attitude to such a degree that you stop making neat stuff.  I thought I'd make the towers again, little beautiful objects climbing up the wall or falling down the wall, and maybe this time the objects could be chakras.  Towers of seven chakras each, made of all sorts of lovely things.  Or I could do free-standing assemblage sculptures with the same theme, only then I'd have to get ten times as much space and a welding shop.  And I could use the plants in them, and call it art.                       

						
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I hate this show.  There, I've said it.  I hate the show that is hanging in my own personal gallery at the moment.  I want to burn every stupid ugly fatuous self-satisfied dorky piece of lame slacker art in it.  I can't afford to do this, because said lame slacker art carries price tags that only an idiot would take seriously, and I have signed pieces of paper taking responsibility for it.  Instead I will sit here, smile and endure for another week and a half, then I will take it carefully down, pack it responsibly, pay an art shipping company a ridiculous sum of money to take it back where it came from, and do a sage purification ritual in the gallery.  Ugh.  How did I get myself into this position?  I am now representing the kind of schlock that I officially declared war against, lo these many years since, and I have not changed my aesthetic agenda in the meantime.  The truth is, my attempt at playing Art World politics came and bit me in the butt.  I let somebody curate this show who was 1) an old friend of mine and 2) several rungs further up on the Art World hierarchy than I am.    This curator certainly didn't slack.  She included 22 artists, designed a web site with a page for every one, designed and printed postcards, wrote the press release, and hand-built a crate to get the art here on a plane.  I was thrilled.  I felt incredibly lucky to have such a person working so hard on the gallery's behalf.  When she pulled the first painting out of the crate and said, "Look, isn't this BEAUTIFUL," I took it as an intellectual exercise in restraining judgement, while expanding my aesthetic horizons.  You get good at that in art school.  Let me describe, at random, some of the "art" around me.  Hanging on the wall to my right, there is an object that looks to be a box lid made out of burlap.  The burlap is painted in what looks like cheap poster paint, with a splotch of burnt umber, some sienna, and some plain brown, in the shape of mountains, with blue sky above.  Three sea shells are carefully glued to the bottom, and brown yarn is wound around pins at the corners, framing the piece, and dangling down at the corners.  The whole thing is indistiguishable from an arts and crafts project perpetrated by a rather anal retentive and singularly unimaginative third grader. Price: $2300.00.    Or take the painting that was represented to me by the curator as being "like YOUR work"--a painting of a nineteenth-century marine battle scene, carefully traced from an actual copy of an actual bad painting, rendered bright with a hot pink background, lurid yellow and monkey-shit brown ships, and explosions rendered in Marx-a-Lot.  The artist claims to be "claiming the painting with individual color choice and mark-making."  Then there is the large pink painting with the stuffed arms hanging down, terminated by bloody detail brushes instead of hands; the orange-and-yellow pastel glorification of a piece of steel workout equipment; the "party zone" painting--oh, don't even ASK me to describe the "party zone" painting.  You don't want to know.  I took this in stride.  In courtesy to the curator, and as a junior member of the Art World, it was not my place to remonstrate or complain.  My love Cornelius told me, "It's like she's an Easter Bunny, creating an Easter egg with other people's work in your gallery.  It will be okay."  I was prepared for some craziness and conflict.  Over the years this artist/curator has manifested signs of nearly every diagnosable psychological disorder on the books, with creative mergers and variations.  In fact, she herself announced the latest theory, after having rejected "borderline," "bipolar," "obsessive-compulsive", "schizo-affective" and various others over the years.    "I think I'm a narcissist," she said.  "But my shrink says I'm a healthy narcissist."    "Oh no, you're not," I said.  This was early on in the visit.  The day she arrived, she wanted me to throw her a birthday party.  Which I did.  I picked her and her fiance up at the airport at the crack of dawn, unloaded the art, took her to breakfast, took them to my apartment (where they took naps), went back to the gallery where I worked on a client (I earn my living as a massage therapist, since "artist and gallerist and putz" doesn't earn much), went home, whipped up an elegant dinner of tortellini with marinara sauce from scratch, made elegant conversation till the small hours, supplied guests with clean sheets and towels and bed and groceries, and gracefully collapsed.  This was fine.  The next day she demanded the sewing machine, which belonged to a friend of mine.  I went to the store for breakfast food to feed my guests, fed them, went to my friend's house for the machine, took everybody to the gallery where they hung artwork and I worked on clients, fetched tools and supplies...this is getting tedious.  Suffice it to say that we were busy, and my personal space was swamped.  This was fine.  I had anticipated this.  I coped.    In fact, nothing really bothered me, not being the on-call 24-hour chauffeur, not staying up all hours, not continuously mopping up the chaos and trying to glean myself an oasis of peace amidst all of it.   My friend the artist/curator knew a handful of big-shot dealers and critics and collectors in New York, and she dragged them all through my gallery.  This was great, wonderful, fabulous.  It's really difficult to get big-shot dealers and critics and collectors into your gallery, if you are a junior member of the Art World in New York City.  The moment I hit the wall, however, was the moment when a big-shot dealer entered the gallery, my friend formally presented each and every piece of fatuous, juvenile art in the place, and let drop the enthusiastic recommendation, "You should give [lame slacker artist] a show!  He has a video about DANCING POO!"  After this it is history.  Toast.  I cannot stand to look at this person, cannot endure her ceaseless babbling, am no longer present in my own body.    There is a thin line between kitsch and shit, which all serious artists must negotiate.  Milan Kundera defines "kitsch" as "the pretense that shit does not exist," and I have never found a better definition.  To be accused of producing kitsch is one of the worst insults that can be hurled at an aspiring Art World artist.  To be accused of producing shit, well...evidently, that's okay.    At the back of the gallery is the "massage room."  Oh, humble name.  I designed it.  I work there.  I hang my paintings there, my beautiful, beautiful paintings, which are about light and love and grief, and the illusions of time, and the transcendence of spirit.  I've given up security to make those paintings; I've given up a lot of things.    To the back of the gallery was where the big-shot dealers, critics, and collectors never went, because the artist/curator never let them.  Literally.  "Don't go back there, that's not part of the show, go this way," she literally said, steering them physically by the arm.  She did the body-blocking thing, she did the talking-nonstop thing, she did the forget-to-introduce-the-owner thing.  She talked and talked and talked, about herself.  She stayed in the gallery all night before the opening, had a meeting with a dealer at 8 AM, and when I entered my healing space afterward, it had been turned, literally, into a junkroom.  My junkroom, with my art on the walls.  "WHY in the WORLD did you hook up with this ASSHOLE?" said Cornelius, never one to mince words.  "I was twenty-four and stupid," I answered.  And, twelve years later, I made the mistake of thinking that a certain amount of career success and years of therapy would mitigate a person's fundamental asshole-hood.  BLAAAAAAT!  Wrong.  During the opening, which I survived without having visible meltdowns or throttling anybody, I had a slow revelation.  That assholes attract their own kind, and the dealers, critics, and collectors that take this person seriously are few, and screwed up themselves.  That the fact that I'm a good listener who is actually interested in people beside myself is a great asset.  That really, the Art World doesn't matter all that much.  Just after the show opened, and I had gently confronted the artist/curator with her tacky behavior, and she had utterly failed to comprehend me, I got an offer for "gallery representation."  This gallery was "in the heart of Chelsea, the epicenter of the New York Art World."  I could join their "family of artists."  All it would cost me was $1750 in representation fees, payable in full by cash, check or charge, three months before my opening, date to be scheduled upon payment.    Of course, No Artist Should EVER Do This.  Real galleries do not charge representation fees.  If a gallery asks for money, they are a scam.  But I checked them out anyway, just to be absolutely sure.  They do exist, and they are located in Chelsea, in a cubicle at the end of the hall on the fourth floor of a building full of galleries.  They are never mentioned in Art in America, the New York Times, the New Yorker, or Art Forum.  I visited them; to be precise, I went to the door and peered round it.  Ugh.  It was a veritable Sea Of Kitsch.  We are talking reproductions of seventeenth-century petit-point furniture.  We are talking urns full of dried foliage.  We are talking wall relief sculptures of varnished driftwood.  We are talking doctor's office paintings.  I fled.  I wrote them a politely caustic letter declining their offer, and requesting the return of my portfolio.    When my portfolio arrived, to me it looked sadly diminished, tainted by its encounter with the kitsch-mongers.  I looked for telltale clues that might say "this one is a likely target."  Then I put it in a drawer, to be taken out upon a less vulnerable day.  "Be patient," says Cornelius.  "Don't let the bad art bite."  It's a thin line, but somebody's got to walk it.       

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   is standing in front of my gallery screaming at his girlfriend.  It's like watching the genetically mutated, white-trash versions of myself and C.--ourselves, bloated, drug-addled, miserable and graceless.   The girlfriend nearly had a show at my gallery last year.  She makes these amazing fantasy theme dolls; she takes old Barbies and other trashed goopy commercial dolls, strips them, paints them, dresses them, adds wings or model horse bodies to make mythical creatures out of them, turns them into little copies of celebrities or Pocohantas or the Spirit of Autumn or whatever.  She came shyly into the gallery, the first month it was open, and showed me some pictures.  She'd never had an art show, but had made a mint selling her creations on eBay.  It was quite a risk for me to say "yes, you can have a show," but wow, they were really neat.  They worked because they were completely naive and completely sincere.  "This might be considered almost 'folk art,'" I said, in my best impersonation of Sophisticated Gallerist.  I asked her if she could show in October, but she said no, that wasn't enough time.  I got some images on disk from her and started making her a web page.    She wasn't, then, the official girlfriend of C.'s crazy brother.  "Omen III--The Sibling," as C. calls him, is officially married to somebody else, with whom he was living across the street, along with their fifteen-year-old son.  C. has been The Omen's keeper for the last fifteen years.  The Omen has tried to kill him more than once, with a baseball bat, in the midst of crack fits.  He has wrecked C.'s car, threatened his tenants, tried to get a crooked cop friend to set him up for assault, broken into his bedroom in the dead of night and forced him to flee half-naked through the alley in below-freezing weather.  He has been beaten to within an inch of his life by drug lords to whom he owes money.  He vents his temper with a crowbar on parked cars.  He is one of the primary reasons C. was hospitalized a few years ago, with incipient heart failure.    Sometime round about last September, The Omen's son caught The Omen screwing the Doll Girl in the park, in broad daylight, under some bushes.  Much mayhem and legal hoopla ensued.  Tangled up in the hoopla were a number of property transactions, having to do with relatives who died inestate, or with estates which then had to be questioned because a primary beneficiary was having crack fits and beating up tenants.  It was all too complicated and too subtle to be explained here.  The only thing that amazed me was "why in the world would ANYBODY want to screw The Omen anywhere, let alone in broad daylight in the park?"  I had been in occasional contact with the Doll Girl, trying to arrange a date for her show.  I had the idea that she should show with another artist, preferably one with a standard "art world" resume, in order to boost her credentials by association, and to ensure a decent turnout at the opening.  I was getting a crash course in just how hard it is to run a gallery in New York City, even rent-free in the middle of the trendiest art neighborhood going.  Critical, financial, and social "success" really IS based on Who You Know, and I din't know nobody.  It is a bad idea to show artists from Out of Town, no matter how stunning their work, if you haven't already got a mailing list of over 1,000 loyal patrons; people come to the opening, and then possibly buy art, and have critics possibly write about it, only if they Know Somebody.  Meanwhile, printing cards, paying for light and heat and phone and booze at the opening, not to mention rent and groceries, gets expensive.    In other words, young artists, if a gallery gets interested in you, treat them nicely.    Anyway, about mid-October, as I was hanging our third major show at midnight, along with the current artist, the previous artist (a real doll, that girl) and C., my love, I got an email from the Doll Girl.  She wanted to know if I could guarantee the date of her show, since she was about to start work on it.    Now, to those of you not involved in the Art World, this may seem like a simple, innocent question, even a reasonable one.  But those of you not involved in the Art World have, ipso facto, never been an art student; you have never asked a gallery for a show; you have never entered juryings, applied for scholarships, grants, residencies, or teaching jobs.  You have never had the precious issue of your soul turned down and down and down until you were ready to dig a twelve-foot trench under the city, burrow into it, curl up at the bottom and stay there till your bones have turned to amethyst.  You do not know the Myth, which is that Real Artists Make Art, even if the show is not guaranteed, even if the show never happens in your lifetime, even if you never get paid, ha! even if you go hundreds of thousands of millions in debt to finance your Art.    And here, here! is an unknown, naive, uneducated Folk Artist with the NERVE to insist that I guarantee her a date before she sets brush to Barbie.  Steam gushed forth from my aural cavities.  I slammed the "Reply" button so hard the building shook in its foundations; my fingers flew over the keys like sharks dismembering a goat.  C. and the artists noticed something was going on.  "Whoa, Serena," they said.  "Disconnect the computer and slowly back away from the keyboard.  Do nothing at this time."  As C. pointed out, she's already screwing The Omen.  It would be excessively, even suicidally unwise to give her a show at this point, even if she lined 75 exotic Barbies up at the front door.  She has simply given me an ironclad excuse to dump her, and seem kind.  After about 48 hours, I wrote the Doll Girl a kind and apologetic letter.  Circumstances beyond my control, having to do with the curator for the April show and her dealer, rendered me unable to fix any dates at all at this moment; it would be unfair of me to ask her to start work at this point.  If she happened to produce any work she was particularly proud of, I'd love to take a look at it.  I think she is very gifted, and am very sorry.  Case closed.  All these many months later, I see the Doll Girl passing my door.  During the time that The Omen was trying to work things out with his wife, she looked tearful and despairing.  It was, still, difficult to believe that anybody could have genuine yearnings for The Omen on any level, but so it seemed to be.  Then The Omen finally left his wife, to the tune of much 5 AM screaming and dumping of furniture out windows.  He and the Doll Girl moved in together and commenced throwing one continuous crack and Bacardi party in the basement, along with all the small-time crooks in the neighborhood.  So perhaps they are happy.    I still expect to come across the Doll Girl's name in the police blotter section of The Post one of these days.  I could write an elegy about romance and trampled innocence and Barbie dolls, but I won't.  There's just no accounting for tastes.            

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Sooth, I know not why I am so tired. Slept 10 hours last night, after a bubble bath and a 45 minute meditation; got up, did yoga, poached an egg, wandered down to the beach and fell asleep on a rock for an hour.  Some doofus was using a table saw on the ridge behind me.  I drive all this way to get away from industrial noise, and there is a table saw at the beach.  Blarrrgh.    I really wonder if there's something wrong with me, that I sleep so much.  It weirds people out, but I've been like that since I was born.  Sleeping nine, or ten, or ten and a half hours a night is not unusual for me, and if I don't get enough sleep, trying to function like a normal human is physically painful.  Perhaps I should try some sort of cleanse, or fast, or exercise, or homeopathic something, but I don't know what, and I don't want to mortify the spirit to a greater extent than it has already been mortified, lately.  I am on vacation, dammit, I'll sleep if I want to.    Usually it seems to me that when I fancy myself in a desperate situation, and am clamoring to whatever powers that be that I need a little help, here, the powers that follow me are irritatingly smug and tight-lipped about it.  I remember in Mexico, when I had returned to find a psycho landlady who had not yet vacated my house and was demanding excessive money from me in payment of imaginary debts, and the former love of my life was living with somebody else, and I was melting down about all of it, K. told me that my guides were in the room.  One of them, she said, had his arm around my shoulders, and was patting my back and shaking his head. "He says that this is nothing at all compared to the battles you're GOING to fight," she said.  This was not entirely comforting.    This time I've been asking for advice, and they're actually being nice to me.  The night before last they didn't say anything, but gave me something blue to breathe in, which felt all nice and soothing and opened up the top of my head.  Last night it was orange, like coals--I don't know what effect that is supposed to have.  I don't feel fiery.  I just feel tired, and like writing and writing even though I don't have much to say.    Last night, brother-in-law and I were discussing the vagaries of my extremely conservative parents.  The last time I went to visit them with C., my mother had RENTED a cot and set it up in the office for me to sleep on, so that I didn't sin in her house.  She gave C. the best bedroom, with the Nantucket decor and the private bathroom.  At least he didn't have to sleep in the garage.  When Mom showed me the cot, I started laughing in incredulity, and even Dad joined in. "Your dad has a clue," said brother-in-law.  "Once we all went out without the two of you, and said we'd be back in two hours.  After about an hour and forty-five minutes we were ready to go, and I saw your dad checking his watch so that we didn't surprise you."  How sweet.  After all, I am THIRTY-SIX YEARS OLD.    The only thing worse than having your parents put you on a cot in the office, however, is suspecting that this is a relief to your boyfriend.  I mentioned this, and brother-in-law said, "Serena, you rock."  Do I rock?  I feel like I'm just perpetually messing up, because I sleep too much.   Sometimes I want to live the life of a character in a Robertson Davies novel--erudite, eccentric, argumentative, contextualized somewhere between great art, great scholarship, and academic uselessness.  This afternoon I picked up "Murther and Walking Spirits" and curled up on the big cuddly couch in the baroque, sage green reading room of the Belfast Public Library.  It's little short of a miracle that this library is here.  It's suspiciously brand-new, light-drenched, well-furnished, Internet-connected, and freshly painted in Martha Stewart shades of butternut, cream and sage for a public library in a town of 6300.  Maybe I actually did die, driving home last Tuesday.  Maybe I just went plowing through a red light and into a huge truck, and this is the Bardo.  I don't know what to do with myself.     

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   into Maine, the car suddenly started smelling like Deep Woods Off.  It kept smelling like that--I had the sun roof open, and I wondered if maybe the Maine government dusts the whole state with Deep Woods Off to keep down mosquitoes.  When I pulled up to my brother-in-law's apartment, it was still there.  I mentioned it to him, and he got a quizzical look on his face and said, "Maybe Deep Woods Off has a 'piney fresh scent.'  Oh.   Belfast has an organic foods co-op, and a big Victorian-ceilinged library with free Internet access, and a few too many galleries.  The chicken-processing plant closed last year, along with the fish-processing plant, and the harbor is full of yuppie sailboats. My brother-in-law is here designing high-end townhouses and condos for a new development.  My brother-in-law's business acumen is looking sharp to me.    Even the library smells like Deep Woods Off.    My brother-in-law has tactfully provided a piece of floor for me to crash on, and a very comfortable boat mattress, and a hand-me-down quilt from his mom.  I suddenly had a flashback to the month or so I crashed on the floor at B. and V.'s loft in Oakland, in 1996 I think, after getting smeared into the pavement in my SF ghetto, dumped by my then-partner and having nowhere else to go.  I wonder what happened to make me the sort of person who goes through periodic crises and ends up crashing on people's floors or couches or spare office bedrooms for longer than a week.  I suppose it's that persistent willingness to risk absolutely everything on an irrational compulsion.  I can understand why people try to dissuade me--too often, they're the ones who have to mop up the wreckage.    Then again, the time I got stranded in Austin and stayed with my friend Carlotta for a month or so, she invited me to go with her on road trips to her parents' vanity farm in Canton, and to her uncle's fiftieth birthday party, and out to poetry slams, and was sorry when I left again, so at least I'm not a terrible house guest.  Not the kind of house guest who complains that the couch makes her back hurt and the mayonnaise is all wrong and there isn't any sugar and she hates honey, and the cat is staring at her and she hasn't slept in four days.  And she forgot her toothpaste and she doesn't like mine.   (Do not compare yourself with others, lest you become vain and bitter, for always there will be greater and lesser persons than yourself...)     Had a Moment yesterday evening, after driving eight hours and walking around the waterfront at high tide, and meeting a couple of daddy long-legs which don't freak me out as much as they used to, and chatting neutrally with brother-in-law, when he said "...and I got some single-malt Scotch, thought you might need it" and I suddenly gasped as though I had been shot, and said no I wasn't okay, thank you.  There was a long silence, and brother-in-law said, "You don't have to have any Scotch if you don't want any."  I pulled myself together, and made both of us one of those fabulous salads with corn and tuna and artichokes and haricots verts that I learned to make from my French boyfriend.  It's one of those things that keeps my welcomes fresh.    My friend K. in Canada says, "You are mourning what you wanted, not what you had" but that's not true; I miss C.'s actual presence, his actual self, the actual intimacy built up over thousands of minutes together.  He once put a pill on his tongue, stuck it out and said "Say bye-bye," and I thought this was hysterically funny, even though I didn't think it was funny at all in first grade when boys did stupid things like that.  It came to me that having your skin ripped off isn't even the hard part--it's all those hundreds of thousands of minutes afterwards when every bit of your life is impregnated by absence.  I feel like a faded, childless widow, being dutifully cared for by a tired brother-in-law who has also got a business to run.    My actual lips taste like Deep Woods Off.  It's weird.    That vanity farm in Canton was slightly disturbing.  Carlotta's mother bought it with the proceeds of selling her clothing boutique in Dallas, and she decorated the main estate house and each of four smaller houses with antiques from the local flea market, each in a different theme.  I slept in the Hummingbird Bedroom in the Derby House.  When we arrived at 11 PM, all the lights were on in all the rooms of all the houses, and all the dining-room tables were set in matching service for twelve.  The living room of the Derby House was decorated with Kentcky Derby paraphernalia--riding crops and horse portraits and large tomes of racing statistics.  The back bedroom where Carlotta slept had an enormous mural of a desert painted on all four walls, with cacti and mountains in the distance, and a four-poster bed made of fence posts.  Little vignettes were set up in every corner--a place for young mothers to chitchat over tea and knitting, a place for a solitary writer to while away the afternoon with lemonade and a journal, an Irish Lodge for fourteen boisterous soccer players to sit up all night with Fritos and horror films, before crashing under matching plaid blankets in the bunk beds all round the room.  And as you explored the increasing detailed wonders of every room in every house, you realized that NOBODY LIVES HERE--all these rooms are set up for imaginary people who never come to stay. Carlotta said that when she and her siblings were little, her mother would follow around after them, putting all the cushions and lamps and charming arrangements of books and flowers and musical instruments Back In Place, in the elaborately casual way they had been before real live children messed them up.  Carlotta said, furthermore, that her mother periodically gets bored with the theme of each house, tears everything out and redecorates again. Her brother lived in the Derby House for awhile with his first wife, but they had to leave because his wife said it was like living in a museum.  They weren't allowed to have their own dishes or furniture or possessions or lives; they had to keep the tables set all the time.  Carlotta's mother said exactly one thing to me the whole time I was there; she said my hair ornament was "cuuuuute." And we all went shopping at the antique flea market.    I liked staying in the Hummingbird Bedroom, though.  It had an iron bedstead with hummingbirds on it, and a hummingbird bath with books about birds stacked up on it, under the hummingbird lamp, and antique white dresses hanging on the wall.  The mattress was all poufy and new, and there were about twelve pillows on the bed.  Carlotta said her mom bought all new mattresses after one of her mom's friends mentioned that the aesthetic details were perfect, but the mattresses were old and thin and scungy.  It was a lucky place for a tired gypsy to rest.  When we went to her uncle's fiftieth birthday party, Carlotta didn't even introduce me to anybody before she disappeared into the thicket.  She said later that she knew I'd be fine.  I was fine, but it wasn't easy.  For an itinerant artist I'm sort of shy.  Her uncle showed me his art collection and his wine collection, and I provided temporary Interesting Person conversational material to various stranded aunts and co-workers.  It was just after 9/11, and I was just about to move to New York.  I said, "New York could use some healing," and some pilot said, "You would make a profit on that?"  I forbore to ask him whether he'd fly a plane for free, camp out in Central Park and eat out of trash cans if flying planes would help the wounded, and said, "It's about survival."  My sister later said that the only proper response to that is to look the person in the eye and say, "Yes."       

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						        Biking around the pier in Red Hook last weekend I found another one.  It was almost a physical shock.  The last one I found I never photographed; I was driving, and literally slammed on the brakes and backed up to have a look at it, but I didn't have my camera on hand and was lazy.  There was a third, perhaps, practically a palimpsest of peeling paint in the shape of an intricate face, just around the corner from the gallery, which I passed every day and almost took for granted.  Then one day they started renovating the building, and before I knew it the entire wall was gone.    I had just been to have a look at the BWAC show, a pretty show, a nice show, of pretty nice art done by pretty nice people.  It was a very lovely day.  I was already, I know, bracing myself for the shock of breaking up with C.  Putting out roots, grounding in the world outside of us, outside of him.    Now, a gift.  My cup runneth over, and the memory card on my digital camera; when I came upon the next one, I was almost angry.  Now I had to erase something.       Paper.  They're made of paper, and ink, and pencil.  They're cut out with exacto knives, probably.  I guess they last a few months, depending upon the weather.  The weather in New York State will eradicate a stone building in twenty-five years, unmaintained.  They are not remotely like any other street art I've ever seen.  I don't think I want to know who does them.    If I weren't an artist, I might be a journalist.  There are interesting things literally around every corner, magical things, just waiting to be discovered.  It's only the Thing in me that won't be ignored or put aside, like carrying around a boulder in my gut, that makes me an artist first and an observer merely as a supplement to it.  It's not enough for me to just discover things; I have to chew them up and transform them.  Some days I wish I could put this boulder down.       The artist must be a man, I think; probably not an attractive one either, probably not a young one.  Some of the faces look sad, others more than sad; they are distraught, destroyed.  The one I didn't photograph was of a bride as a decaying corpse.  Immediately I thought of Mexico, of course, but the level of detail, creativity and artistic sophistication goes well beyond any iconic Katrinas.      Later in the day I called C., who had promised to invite me to a movie later, and didn't.  It is, of course, the Rule to never, never do that, but something in me needed to push it.  Lately he has been treating me like his paper-doll, junior-high-school girlfriend--holding my hand, taking me to movies, telling me he loves me, chatting about neutral things.  But he doesn't make love to me, he doesn't plan a life with me, he tries to separate out all the essential things and put them in boxes while waiting for a miracle, which he doesn't believe in, anyway.  And I was watching my dreams disintegrate like a paper woman on a fence.        So I went ahead and pushed it, and now I know, and now I can move on.  Yes, it was like having my skin ripped off.  No, I don't regret it.  I don't believe in settling for whatever you think you can get, instead of going full steam for what you want.  Settling just means that failure is assured.       I got to sleep the last two nights by creating a blue bubble all around me, an egg really, full of blue light with a golden shell.  The blue light was for healing, the shell was to keep out hostile things.  It's like the oxygen tent my daddy made for me when I was three and had come back from the hospital, after being treated for severe asthma.  I cried because I missed my tent, and instead of explaining that I didn't need it anymore, daddy the engineer solved the problem.  He strapped an umbrella to the back of an upright chair next to my bed, draped a sheet over it, and placed a humidifier on the seat of the chair underneath.  The sheet was over my whole bed, and the hum of the humidifier blanketed my world and let me sleep.    Next week I will go to Maine, I think, and visit my brother-in-law, and find a body of water, and sit next to it without moving for days and days.  Then I will come back to the city, and figure out how to get business loans, or artist grants, and maybe find a place where I can live and work at the same time, so that I don't have to pay two rents.  None of this will be easy.  I could fail horribly.  I could use up every cent of capital and go into terrible debt and be alone my whole life and die in the gutter.       Well, okay, then, here I go.                      

						
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   C. screamed at me.  He said, "I don't want you.  Go home."  This is what a nervous breakdown feels like.  When a truck makes a loud noise in the lane next to you, you start screaming, full throttle, the scream that you never scream unless you are physically assaulted by a stranger with a flamethrower.  When you have to stop at a red light in the middle of an intersection, you start crying and leaning on your horn.  When you go to the bank to deposit money, you can't add the numbers "55+55+55+60."  They just don't make sense, all those fives and then carry the one and you have to add it to another five and then there's that six in there, two sixes what is that? it doesn't make sense.  I have a problem, I have to get six big packages to FedEx and FedEx won't pick them up and they won't fit in my car.  I have to get a crate shipped to Los Angeles and the shipping companies haven't sent me the price quotes even though I've been calling and emailing.  I have a client booked at 4 PM and I have to cancel but I can't cancel because I need the money.  But I have to cancel because it is irresponsible and wrong of me to do any healing work on another person in my present condition.  And if I try to drive again there is a strong possibility I will end up in jail rather than at the shop.   I have a number for an Interfaith counselor but I'm not sure I can use the telephone properly or make it into Manhattan for any reason, let alone a counseling appointment.  I spent 81 minutes on the phone to Canada last night and 169 minutes on the phone to Austin, how many minutes total is that?  Does it work out to something even?  I called C. and he said I was drunk like his crazy brother.  I was drunk but saying I was like his crazy brother was going a little far.  If I put my head in the oven like Sylvia Plath the building might blow up and hurt the neighbors.  There would be no-one to take care of the cats.  If I put my hand on the cat while she is purring it sort of calms me down enough so that I can sort of sleep.  But when I was sleeping I dreamed that I had my best paintings in a gallery, in the window, and then someone pressed a button and the walls all shifted and big schlocky slick abstract paintings were there instead and mine were gone.  Then I woke up and had more ibuprofen and more water, and when I went back to sleep I was trying to get on a picnic table floating down a canal, but there were too many other people and when I stepped on the whole thing started to sink.    I used to think I was a strong person but I was evidently wrong.  People tell me "you are acting like a child."  All my nerve endings are on fire.  I'm doing the best I can.  This is evidently not good enough.  If I do something to get myself put into the hospital things will be worse in the hospital, they are not nice to you in hospitals, it's cold and it smells and they don't give you enough blankets and the lights are fluorescent, I had better avoid hospitals. I feel like I need to be in a hospital for people whose energy fields have been ripped up from top to bottom and they have no defenses left and are just wandering around tweaking and jangling like stun guns.  I need someone to put the psychic equivalent of a wet blanket on my energy field.    When my friends tell me things like "you will be okay, this is happening for a reason, you made yourself vulnerable, you are not crazy, I love you" this helps while they are saying it.  It continues to help for a little while and then the tweaking jangling thing comes back.  I can't have my friends around all the time constantly repeating these things, they have lives and responsibilities and I am being self-absorbed to be tweaking and jangling like that.    One of the neighbors down the street, an old guy who hangs out on the sidewalk drinking, asked to carry my bag when I got home and I walked past and he said, "Well, I tried" and I burst into tears and apologized and said I'd had a very bad day, and he carried the bag and said he feels like he doesn't want to get out of bed in the mornings and he just turned fifty and maybe we could be friends, and he held onto me until I stopped hyperventilating and sobbing uncontrollably, and told me his telephone number, and he did his best but it was still a drunk old guy using my hysteria as an excuse to put his hands on me and I put up with it because anything else would have been worse.  I read a girl's blog where her boyfriend broke up with her and she said she hated herself.  This was very difficult to read, it was like watching a train wreck, I am different from her but this doesn't mean I think I'm better.  I don't hate myself at all.  I did the absolute best I could.  I fell in love with someone and I loved him and loved him and loved him.  We would be together awake all night and he would rub his nose back and forth with mine.  He said he was happy and that he always wanted to be this happy and I thought this would be easy because I would always keep loving him like that.   

						
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   how I wish I could have given you a song without myself dropped it into your soul as a bird between two mountains bathing in the moment of tremor in your eyes  this noise, white noise, ecstasy in which to lose the poetry of an empty room how easy to be where no-one says goodbye  --fragment of crappy poem written in college, about which an ex-boyfriend said, "That line about 'the bird between two mountains' Has It--the rest is terrible."  The only thing was, I'd lifted the "bird between two mountains" schtick from the title of a Georgia O'Keefe print on the wall in front of me, and thus I thought of it as cheating.    The sentiment is still valid, if klunkily expressed.  The poem was, of course, as most of my poems then were, about some dude upon whom I had an unreciprocated crush.  I had enough wisdom to know that if a crush is unreciprocated, it's best not to push it (see "If I could only stay asleep," below).  I still wanted to give him something, but was hampered by living in a flawed vessel--me.  As I recall, I left him a funny note along with some money I owed him for an art project we collaborated on.  It gave the dictionary definition of the word "sport," complete with all the more esoteric, social and biological meanings of the word, and concluded, "Thanks for being such a sport."  I ran into him once afterward; his eyes lit up with what seemed to be genuine pleasure at seeing me, but I was way late for work and hurried on.  So go look up "sport" in the dictionary, if you want to know.    Things this week have been difficult.  C. and I need couples therapy, if we are to remain a couple at all, for a Big Huge Issue which will pretty much torpedo the relationship in nothing flat, if nothing else happens.  C. of course is highly resistant to couples therapy, so we are at an impasse.  I have considered:  -moving to Maine, crashing with my sister's in-laws and starting another massage therapy practice from scratch;  -going back to Mexico, although it's getting more expensive every day and most of my friends there have moved elsewhere;  -shutting up shop and signing up for the first temp agency which will have me;  -taking out another whopping student loan and going for another useless graduate degree;  -going to South America, what the hell, I have a couple of friends roaming around there, though I'm not at all sure where they are;  -killing myself.  None of these options are particularly practicable.  I'm stuck with what I got.  C. seems pretty hip on "maintaining the friendship, whatever happens," and I've nodded and listened sagely and so far refrained from saying, "Are you a COMPLETE IDIOT?  That's NOT POSSIBLE."  You don't have a heavy-duty, up-all-night-talking-and-snuggling-and-making-out kind of love affair, you don't have this state of affairs last for over a year, you don't go into business together, you don't walk all round your community holding hands and looking starry-eyed till the most cynical playboys are staring after you in awe, and then say, "Well, that didn't quite work out.  Let's still be best friends."  People don't DO that.  At least I don't.  C. thinks that when I point out this obvious fact, I'm "holding a gun to his head."  Whatever.  I have been discreetly researching good couple's therapists, so that if and when C. realizes that he is, indeed, a complete idiot and is about to lose the love of his life, I can whip the phone number out of my wallet and book us for Monday at 3 PM.  I have been setting up an account on ebay, and signing up for PayPal, so that I can start trying to unload cumbersome possessions and turning them into cold hard cash with which to run away.  I plan to start researching small business loans, so that I can move shop elsewhere and not have to temp for a living.  I should probably incorporate, so that if the sucky economy continues for the next five years, the corporation can go gracefully bankrupt and I'll still have enough capital to escape to South America.        It's hard to know what to do with yourself when you feel like a flawed vessel--like the person you want just doesn't want you, not in the package you're in.  This is why women go bulimic by the hundreds of thousands.  Somehow, men seem to be mostly immune to the feeling.  I've never known an ugly guy who seemed truly aware that he was ugly--they just think all women must be frigid bitches for not wanting to have sex with them.   I know this isn't about me at all, but it doesn't help much.  It doesn't change things.  When you're closely connected with someone, their problems become your problems; their blocks become obstacles to your freedom.  A good friend recently said, "Relationships aren't for people to achieve happiness; they are so we can become more conscious."  Consciousness is painful and we want to run away.  Ergo bourbon, tequila, oversleeping, going to the woods and not returning phone calls.  Usually when I feel like this I ought to go to Course in Miracles meetings and don't.  The last one I went to really annoyed me and I didn't go back--everybody in the room but me got connected with the inner oneness of everything, and got all touchy-feely and blissed out, and I sort of went along with it, and even did some break-dancing to entertain them.  But later all I could think about was a bunch of ugly guys putting their hands all over me, and stopped thinking of CIM meetings as safe havens.  Probably I should go back and bitch them out, to test the validity of their epiphanies.  They might even like it.    However, this evening good ol' David Duvall on WQXR quoted Alan Watts at the end of "Reflections from the Keyboard," and so CIM got through to me anyway.  The quote was something to the effect of, "We forget that the past and the future are abstract concepts, and the only thing that exists for us is the eternal present."  Presently I am on the couch with cats and computer, and the air-conditioning is on, and WXQR is playing something modern and dissonant, which I quite like.  I can deal with that.               

						
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What I did today was bitch out Planned Parenthood.  I felt much better afterward.  Gloria Feldt President, Planned Parenthood 434 West 33rd St. New York, NY 10001  Dear Ms. Feldt,  Recently, I received a letter from you, under the auspices of Planned Parenthood, which began, I am deeply troubled by your decision not to renew your annual membership to Planned Parenthood ...and I fear that I may not have adequately explained to you how much youre still needed.  The letter goes on to enumerate the many wonderful things Planned Parenthood does for the community, none of which I have any quarrel with whatsoever.  The problem I have, and the reason I am not sending you any money at this time, are your fundraising tactics.  Sometime late last year, not even a year ago by my count, I sent Planned Parenthood some money.  I am self-employed and I do not yet make enough from my work to cover my basic living expenses.  Having enough money to pay for even basic preventive healthcare for myself is still a distant dream.   After sending my check to Planned Parenthood, I received another request for money, practically in the return post.  I was irked.  The phrase annual membership  implies that funds will be requested, and donated, annually.  It might be permissible to send information updates every six months or so, but sending them more often is pushing it.    I continued to receive letters in the mail from Planned Parenthood at least once a month or more.  It became clear to me that every cent of my original check was being spent in dunning me for more money, and not on providing healthcare for needy women such as myself.  Not once did I receive a thank-you note, or any information which might be beneficial to me personally, such as a list of clinics in my area which provide affordable gynecological exams.   Other non-profit organizations to which I have sent money do not behave in this way.  Oxfam, for example, sent me a very nice postcard thanking me for my donation, and limits their repeat requests to once every six months or so.  In my opinion, this is the way civilized people and institutions behave.  I do not wish to support an institution which uses my money to harass me, however beneficial their purported purpose.  If Planned Parenthood cannot show more restraint in their requests, I must regretfully request that you take me off your mailing list entirely.  I know you need my money; please offer me something positive in return.    Sincerely,  me  

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   If anybody wants some schlumpy, formless summer clothes in natural-fiber fabrics, please inquire.  A large box of them is currently sitting outside my door, waiting for it to stop raining so I can put them on the street.  I've stopped dressing that way.  One of my college friends once mentioned that nobody back then knew what kind of a figure I had.  Well, it was better than I thought it was, better than it is now, but is not yet so far gone that I need to hold onto these clothes.  If I get pregnant in the next couple of years I may regret it, but I don't think so.    In addition to purging my closet, I got a haircut just slightly like Heather Locklear's.  I have not let a hairdresser layer my hair since I was about ten, because it is so very very straight that layers just lie there, balefully refusing to pouf out in the slightest.  But the girl who did it this time had a nice haircut herself, and a French accent, and I was at an emotional disadvantage in more than one way.  "Little sheggy layeurs," she said, pawing my head disdainfully.  I decided what the heck, if it looks horrible I can always go back to the chin-length blunt cut, staple of uptight classy girls, no-maintenance and boring.    The French chick actually did a good job.  I think I look sexy.  It doesn't feel "layered" at all, just like there's more hair there, and my face doesn't look so horsy.  I can slap it into a French twist and little tendrils hang down artfully at different levels.  I considered getting the "light irridescent blond" color kit at Pathmark and a set of rollers, so that I could manufacture a gigantic golden mop like Kate Hudson's, but decided to hold off.  I'm bleaching it slowly and cheaply with medicinal peroxide instead.  Of course, the day after I purge my closet, pack up all the winter clothes and winter blankets, the weather gets chilly again.  I have the windows open and it's almost uncomfortable.  I wanted to bike to Pearl Paint and pick up some tubes of white (NEVER buy white paint in a jar, it dries up on all the exposed surfaces and gets nasty and lumpy) but more rain is in the forecast.  I may do it anyway.    Working for BWAC was mildly frustrating.  Like with most collective organizations, management is erratic.  We sat around for an hour before anyone gave us a task, and then had to pack up about fifty paintings for shipping, with inadequate packing material.  This should have been done already, since we were the "site-prep" crew; the girl working with me complained all day about the lack of organization, and how last year was different, there was coffee and donuts and pizza, and paint and spackle all laid out, and she just spackled and rollered without talking to anyone and went home.  I would have liked to talk to more people, since networking is one of the major reasons I joined BWAC, but I was missing C. a whole lot that day and did not have sufficient energy surplus for gregariousness.  So I wrapped and taped and said "mmmmm" for eight hours and went home.      The BWAC girl reminded me somewhat of a friend of mine who came to visit me in Mexico, and complained for the entire three weeks of her stay.  After about ten days of it I let her know that respectfully, she was driving me crazy, and she didn't get it.  I realized that ritualized complaining is the only way some people know how to interact.  The underlying assumption, as near as I can figure, is that things SHOULD be a certain way, it's somebody else's stupid FAULT if they're not that way, there's nothing that can be done about it, and nothing more to be learned from the situation.  This strikes me as utterly pointless.  If you start from the assumption that there is a reason for everything, no matter how desperate and stupid it may appear, the world becomes a much more interesting and exciting place.  It becomes a dynamic mystery novel and four-dimensional jigsaw puzzle suspended all around you, daring you to assemble it.  Once you do, of course, it changes completely and you get to do it again, and again, and again.    It occurs to me that this underlying assumption of mine, that everything happens for a meaningful reason, may have been one of the factors contributing to the explosion of my friendship with L.  I made a few innocent, wondering comments like "Isn't it funny that you're meeting all these guys named Mark who aren't calling" and she abruptly disintegrated into hostile paranoia.  "I don't think it's FUNNY," she said, and proceeded to accuse me of taking "subtle pot-shots" at her.  Which could not have been further from my mind.  It WAS funny.  Why were they all named Mark?  What does "Mark" mean.  He's the mark, a marked man, on the mark, marked out?  Was she missing the mark?  Speculations were open-ended, and had nothing at all to do with her attractiveness or call-worthiness, which I took as given.    But in her mind, I had suddenly become a jealous bitch who was sniggering at her romantic failures, and nothing I could say or do would convince her otherwise.   Oh well.  Actually I dreamed about her last night.  We were both applying for a waitress job, sitting at a table drinking Coke and waiting for the manager, who looked a lot like Jim Carrey.  Nobody came over for an hour, and we couldn't even attract anyone's attention to pay for our Cokes.  She said something self-righteous, and I said, "you're the one who destroyed a friendship for something trivial in your head."  She went over to say goodbye, and I realized she'd already worked a five-hour shift with them.  I decided that waiting tables was the last thing I needed to be doing at the moment, and left.         

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   surprisingly feels pretty nice.  I even exchanged friendly words with my landlord, Phil the Neanderthal.  He did not make a fuss about the fact that my rent was a week late, or that my stairwell is a fire hazard, and inquired about the problem with my air conditioning.  He was here because the girls on the ground floor moved out.  I will miss them.  They threw away a ton of great stuff, which I recycled out of the garbage can--two silver-framed mirrors, three virgin stretched canvases, a brand-new mat cutter, a shower caddy with half a jar of lime-coconut sea-salt exfoliator, and a wool Army trench coat just my size.  Oh, to have a day job which allows me to think I can afford such luxuries.    Today I am doing a Master Cleanse fast, which makes me headachy, probably from caffeine withdrawal.  I decided that my ankle problem might have to do with toxicity of the liver (this is not insane, the massage therapist pointed out that my entire liver meridian is tender) and so I have quit alcohol for the time being.  Went for a bike ride round Prospect Park, which I must do more frequently so I don't go into tree withdrawal again, and did a very lazy, slap-happy, distracted yoga set, pausing every three minutes to snuggle with my Big Splendid Cat.  All of us missed one other.    Stopped by Barnes & Noble last night, in desperate search for the new Robin McKinley book, which I need so that I can escape my own brain for a couple more days.  Realized that during the last five years (FIVE years?  Five YEARS since I've had a steady job?  Ack!  Ack!  Ack!) since I worked in a library, and have been living in other countries and not browsing the new book shelf almost daily, all my favorite authors have been busy writing more books.  That's what authors do, right?  Whoopee!  Backlog!    Argh, I'm hungry.  You're not supposed to GET hungry doing Master Cleanse, but I always do.  Some people I know have done it for a month or more, but the longest I've managed is two days, in Mexico.  Then at the end of the second day I broke the fast with a Baratillo steak quesadilla with tons and tons of really hot salsa.  All my vegetarian friends were like, what?  You broke your fast with a TACO?  You're supposed to start with carrot juice, and work up to brown rice, or some such rot.  Sorry, I think I'm a different SPECIES from these people.  I think I've finished the painting for the BWAC show, which has to be delivered Saturday.  I don't like it too much, I don't think it's one of my best, but it's not bad enough to pull out of the show.  It is supposed to surge and glitter and sparkle, and it sort of does, but not to the extent that I envisioned, and now it's in danger of being completely overworked.  I need more space, so I can paint bigger and back up farther, and more time, and more money for huge canvases and brushes and paint.  Well, don't we all.  I should be all inspired and motivated, seeing as how I've got to go back to the shop pretty soon and start trying to earn my keep again, but all I want to do is lie on the couch and read my new Thomas Perry novel and make a bunch of macaroni and cheese.  God, I hate fasting.    I've given myself a one-year ultimatum for stabilizing my finances--if income does not equal or exceed expenditures by the time my lease expires next June, I think I have to move to Maine or Philadelphia, where the licensing laws are gentler and rents are much lower.  My friend Sasha vigorously tried to talk me out of this plan, over a way-too-expensive salad at the Brooklyn Diner yesterday evening.  It's true that I belong here, and I don't want to go anywhere else.  But I've been here two years and still am not breaking remotely even on rent and bills, let alone qualifying for a mortgage on a home of my own, even a stupid little condo which wouldn't be big enough to paint in anyway.    If I think of my current life as a one-year artist residency in New York City, maybe this will motivate me to use my time a little better, market my work a little more (I'm still terrified of gallery owners, even though I AM one) and get out of bed in the mornings.  Today I actually got up after eight and a half hours of sleep, hooray.  Quitting drinking is probably the secret, dammit.   

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Started running just a bit, just a wee small bit, yesterday and today. The problem isn't my aerobic condition; the problem is my left ankle, which tends to lock up, scream and collapse whenever I'm going through anguish in a primary sexual relationship.  I took the painful ankle to a local massage therapist yesterday, who specializes in trigger point therapy, horses, and old people.  She was frustratingly tentative and cerebral.  She kept poking me lightly and asking, 'there?'  It came to me that there are as many mediocre bodyworkers as there are mediocre painters; both are deceptively simple mediums with a nearly limitless range of potential lameness.  There are kitsch massages, all swoosh and no substance; aggressive, brutal carpenter massages, where the guy knows the anatomy but forgets there's a person in there; formless Abstract Expressionist bodywork; wispy drypoint doodling that is all theory and no affect.  Knowledge, coupled with humility, coupled with empathy and power is very, very rare.   A person's body is not a machine that rights itself when you press the right button.  It is an instrument that sings if you caress it with skill and with passion, warps if it is left out in the rain, sulks and decays if you put it in a box.  I want a bodyworker who goes straight to the sore places and sinks into them over and over, stretches out the kinks, unblocks the flow, kneads and swirls like a cat dancing on my spine.  I want someone who allows energy to flow through them like a cataract, who doesn't chatter or explain, who senses my body because they are in a body too, and they know what bodies feel like.  Someone who massages people just like *I* do, dammit.        Anyway.  This Sex thing.  I figured I'd just EXPLAIN, finally, instead of getting into all these confusing, cross-purposes tangles, tangles that have been happening to me now for nearly twenty years.  These scenarios are the stuff of farce.  For years I have been considering writing a comic novel that begins with me reading a Georgette Heyer Regency romance novel on my boyfriend's bed, while he quietly and elaborately ties himself up. Occasionally I prod his penis with my foot; he groans in ecstasy, and we pass the entire afternoon in parallel fetish harmony.  But if I started, the funny stories would not end, and not a jot of enlightenment would be obtained, for each story is a story of separation, confusion, isolation and miscommunication.  A friend of a friend of mine, bless her heart, recently attended a "sex workshop" in Manhattan, because she felt she needed some liberation.  The instructor used some sort of egg object to masturbate in front of the entire (co-ed) class, then the participants paired off to coach each other in the technique.  For other classes, an "intimate partner" was needed, but if you came to the class solo, they'd pair you up with someone.  Oh, blarrgh, horror of horrors.  It boggles.    Okay, so don't start getting upset and calling me a repressed fascist.  I didn't finish yet.  Learning the mechanics of sex is not bad, wrong or evil.  It's merely necessary.  It's also not sex; it's practicing scales.  I can't get that excited about scales.  For me, sex is intimate.  It is integrated.  And it is singular.    Arrgh, that doesn't work.  Let me try again.  Sex is the top of a fiddlehead fern thrusting through the earth.  It is rooted in a single place; it pulls the sun and the water and the soil through itself, it pokes, it springs, it releases lace and glory to the air.  It is concentrated creative potential, at one with its surroundings.    Intimate, what is that?  It means you know, and are known.    It has always baffled me when people talk about having 'great sex' with people they barely know and don't particularly like.  How is this possible?  Yes, you can have an intense physical release, made all the more intense by the mystery, the adrenalin, the danger of an animal encounter with another animal in the dark.  It's fine as far as it goes.  But it doesn't last, it goes nowhere, it isn't rooted in anything.  Non-intimate sex is lowest-common-denominator plumbing, snot-rag-for-the-lower-extremities, parts is parts.  How boring.  How depressing.    This is why, when all my college friends were blithely entering into polyamorous angst and telling me I was an uptight prude, I didn't get laid at all.  I danced instead.  Can we say, "sublimation?"  Freshman and sophomore year I went to parties and had five beers, and when Joe Jackson's 'Steppin' Out' came on I started whirling and didn't stop until the song was over, and only then did I notice the circle of gaping mouths around me.  Later on I discovered Austin's peerless live music scene, and for three dollars I could spend the whole evening doing interpretive movement, channelled straight from the source.  The musicians would ask me, 'how do you know what we're going to do before we do it?' and of course I didn't; I wasn't thinking at all, just entering the flow.  I was simply present.      I didn't want to sleep with anyone who wasn't interested in my soul, was all.  The boys who approached me seemed all about ego, and arrogance, and indifference.  They didn't give a hoot if I got pregnant, or herpes, or heartbroken.  So I kept dancing. Allowing the complexities of music to direct me was the closest I could find to an intimacy high.    Later on, I tried, I tried so hard to un-repress myself, to get it the way other people seemed to.  My first lover was simply awful in the sack, worse because he thought he was the greatest.  He'd slobber all over me, put his hands in the wrong places, and misinterpret me jerking my face away from his octopus tongue for thrashings of ecstasy.  The second was worse, a misogynistic narcissist who thought my body was disgusting.  On and on, an act which should have been about communication became an exercise in frustration and misunderstanding.  I tried to separate sex from relationship, from emotion, from partnership and communication, and failed completely.  My first instinct has always been to integrate, and I think it is a sound one.    Great sex, I think, is a poem about a person.  What I like is fine because I like it.  What you like is beautiful too.  How may these specifics work together to make art?    What interests me is tantric sex, which I haven't read much about because it is too damn frustrating to think about without an interested partner.  How about moving very, very slowly, just to see what it's like, or gazing into each other's eyes for twenty minutes?  What is there to discover?  Can our souls touch each other?  It takes an enormous amount of trust, strength, and good boundaries to embark on a project like this; also chemistry, community and committment. Which is why I've so rarely tried it.  I don't want to gaze into the eyes of someone who might suck me dry, or rip me to bits, or freak out and abandon me, or smell really bad and start to bore me.  So I apologize to all the people who might have felt rejected by me over the years.  What they didn't understand was that when they said, "hey baby, yer cute, why don't we get it on?" what I responded to was, "hey baby, how 'bout I suck up your soul and use it for Kleenex?"  Just my own freaky baggage.    

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   are what trigger the major meltdowns.  Yesterday was ripe.  It was Saturday night, which for me is Friday night, since I work Tuesdays through Saturdays.  But essentially it was Friday AND Saturday night combined, in my little psyche, and I have a thing about weekends stemming back from high school, when I spent them babysitting, without boyfriends, booze or cable, while my peers partied their carefree youth away.  So now that I am a glamourous artist in the big city instead of a dork in a suburb, I still freak out on Saturday nights when nobody is taking me to a fancy French restaurant and then to an off-Broadway production and then to drinks at the Algonquin to map out the film we're going to write and direct together.  I never consciously remember this, though, until it's too late to plan ahead.  My ex-boyfriend gave himself a cold in order to prevent himself from going rock-climbing upstate.  He thought he wanted to go, but his unconscious knew better.  When I arrived at work in the morning and saw his van in the same spot, I didn't even call or ask, just trundled off to the store for juice and Sprite and chicken soup, and dumped them outside his apartment.  Tactically this was a terrible idea, but I don't do tactics very well.  Tactically speaking, when someone breaks your heart and dumps you cruelly and throws you out of the gallery you have spent a year restoring lovingly by hand, the best thing to do is ignore him while he stews in his own miserable phlegm, the bastard.  Fetching Sprite and chicken soup is akin to lying prostrate in the gutter and begging him to wipe his feet on your face while his new girlfriends spit in your general direction.  It's just pathetic.  But I did it anyway, stupid me, because I love him and getting dumped didn't change that, and it hurts more to withhold love than to go ahead and get the groceries.  So ex-boyfriend swallowed his phlegm long enough to come down and try to pay me for the groceries, which was an insult, and sit around boring the hell out of me and my 6 PM client for an hour, with the result that we didn't get started till 7:30.  I noticed more strongly the way my ex-boyfriend talks AT people rather than WITH them, the way he tells the same angry stories over and over, the way he lets nothing and nobody in, but tries to manage and manipulate everything as though the world were his own personal Punch and Judy show.  I felt like I was floating unmoored in a sea of dirty cotton, and I wondered how I could have spent a year and a half of my life with someone so irremediably damaged, and whether I was every bit as damaged myself to even try.  I finished with my client at 9 PM; my ex-boyfriend had disappeared into his shop, I was tired, and dateless, and it was Saturday night.  I've been pretty good lately at avoiding numb-out tactics, but this was an emergency.  I fetched a bottle of wine and one of Jim Beam from Park Slope liquors, "Things you know just by looking at her" from Reel Life video, and went home for a zombie-a-thon.  To my credit I opened the wine and not the Jim Beam, steamed an artichoke and some Edamame instead of going for straight macaroni and cheese, and set my computer to upload a bunch of garantuan digital images to be made into slides.  Moderation in all things.  Then the VCR wouldn't work.  It would play properly for a minute or two, then the sound and the color would go out simultaneously.  I could get them back by stopping the tape and starting it again, but this never lasted.  I ate dinner sitting on the floor in front of the TV, my finger on the "stop" button, since I've lost the remote.  I tried to be patient, but it was a slow film anyhow, and it was a toss-up as to whether all this effort was even worth it.  I tried taking the tape out and blowing on the tape heads.  Nada.  I stopped and started for a good hour before I broke down and called the ex, who for all his faults, knows how to fix things.    "Is there some thing I can just jiggle?" I asked him.  He told me to insert another tape, press "play" and fast-forward simultaneously for a few minutes, till the schmutz came off the tape heads.  This I did; the other tape worked fine.  The tape of "Things you know just by looking at her" didn't.  Around 1 AM I was forced to conclude that it just wasn't happening.  Two hours of stopping and starting and drinking California Zin had frayed my nerves to irrational two-year-old hysterical hair-triggers.    I knew I shouldn't do it, I knew it knew it knew it, but I did it anyway.  I called the ex again.  "Dr. Video," he answered.  "It won't work," I sobbed. "I'm asleep," he anwered.  "Sorry," I said.  He hung up.  I might have called him back and had the kind of torrential psycho-stalker meltdown that gives emotionally stunted ex-boyfriends permanent ammunition for calling the psychiatric police and never ever dealing with their shit because obviously YOU'RE the one who's CRAZY, but thank God I'd opened the wine instead of, as I've mentioned, the Jim Beam.  I called my friend in Las Vegas instead.   She didn't pick up.  I tried her cell phone.  I tried her land line again.  I didn't leave a message, because by then I was in the kind of state that freaks people out unneccesarily when it's too late to call you back.  And it was way too late to call anybody who lived closer than Las Vegas.   Even in the depths of my despair, I set up the laptop to continue uploading on the land line.  Slide-quality files take a hell of a long time to transfer on a 56K modem.  Then I went into the studio with my Course in Miracles and my journal and proceeded to abandon myself to heaving tearing grief.  I grieved for the love of my life, who has turned on me as though I were his alcoholic abusive carping excuse for a dead mother, reincarnated.  I grieved for my former best friend, who stopped returning my phone calls on a major holiday, less than a month after I moved alone and jobless to New York City.  I grieved for all the ones I loved the most, who loved me for a little while and then fell into egoistic black holes and stopped trying.  I grieved for the fact that I fall in love repeatedly with damaged people who cannot love me back.  I grieved for all the times my heart has broken since ballet, at seventeen.  I think that love exists to break the soul.    At 1:31 AM, the phone rang.  This should not have been possible; the modem was still uploading.  I picked it up and nobody was there.  I started the modem again and continued cursing God.  I demanded answers, now, not in ten years when I see wisely how this was all for the best.  The files took two more hours to load; the answers did not come.    Just before folding up the computer and losing consciousness entirely, for some reason I checked voicemail.  "You have one new message, from an unknown caller, today at 1:31 AM," it chirped.  The voice of my long-lost lover burbled through the static.  "where are you fucking serena, calling you from mexico, I am really trying, where you going, are you out-side? sorry fucking english, I love you always, I miss you, beautiful blue-eyesss, mamacita, bonita, you are beautiful per-son, querida ojos azules, te llamo despues, why do you not write me fucking email, te quiero mucho, adios."  He could not have sounded more desperately urgent if I had sent him a telegram that read "DYING LUNG CANCER BORNEO TWO WEEKS STOP  DO NOT VISIT STOP LOVE ALWAYS."          Oh.  My.  I replayed the message five times before passing out.  Had a lot of bad dreams, woke up hung over, went to the beach.  Tried to calculate whether I can afford a week in Mexico this year.  Decided that maybe the interconnectedness of everything is not so theoretical.                        

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   came in a couple of Saturdays ago, and maybe brought a miracle with her.  I don't know.  Don't know which of my dreams are precognitive either, or just ambiguous dreck, or wishful thinking.  I wonder what good they are, then?  Sometimes I think all of it is just carrots on sticks, saying maybe, maybe, don't give up just yet.  Things with my now ex-boyfriend have been mainly horrible.  First he didn't speak to me at all for weeks, then he said things were OVER, GOT IT?!!! and threw me out of my beautiful beautiful gallery as of the end of August.  Then he called to apologize for being cruel.  As if.  One of my clients told me, "I slept with this guy last night by accident, it wasn't anything, and this morning he wanted to explain that he didn't want me getting ideas. I said, "kiss me good-bye. I don't have to listen to this shit."  All together, now.  AS IF.  So I spent obsessive hours job-hunting on the web, and grant-hunting, and round about midnight on a Friday I thought, "okay, now that all is lost, what do I REALLY want?"  And the answer came--"I want to live in a spiritual community with a lot of serious artists and writers and scientists and healers."  Not a monastery where everybody meditates all the time and gets in touch with their "inner artist" in the ceramics studio on weekends.  Not a graduate school with politics and competition and precious dysfunctions taken for genius.  I want to be around a lot of people who are looking seriously for the light, and coping gracefully with darkness.    About thirteen hours later, Grace walked in.  Usually I don't tell clients my troubles; that is definitely not what they pay me for.  I don't know why I broke this rule, except that it was a piece of relevant practical information; "I may not be in this space much longer."  Grace did not immediately recoil from failure and bad energy, strangely enough.  We got to talking; I told her my vision; she said, "That's my vision too!"   We got together on Wednesday.  I have had a picture floating in my head for months now, of how my gallery would be when it was all grown up.  She said, "Draw it."  As I drew, I realized how clear the structure was; high ceilings, high windows, white with silk jewel tones, flooded with light.  Galleries to the left, caf to the right, healing offices on the right mezzanine, studio spaces on the left.  Large multi-use event space to the back.  "That's exactly what I see," said Grace.  "My door is a bit different."    Grace likes to do publicity and financing; she plans big events and is part-owner of a bar.  Grace lives in a live/work loft three blocks away from my soon-to-be-former gallery, full of artists and healers, a Pilates studio, a dance company, a furniture maker.  Her roommate is leaving at the end of August.  She said maybe I could move in.  Meanwhile all the rsums and cover letters I have been obsessively sending out might as well have been flushed into outer space, for all the response I've gotten.  Meanwhile I had sixteen massage clients in one week, all sixteen of whom enthusiastically signed my mailing list, so I can let them know where I end up after August.  If I move in with Grace, I can keep my clients and have a studio in the same space.  I can roll out of bed, go to yoga up the street, breakfast in the Read caf, book a few clients, go home to massage and paint, go out to openings, go home without moving my car.  I can keep my community and build on all the energy I have nurtured over the last two years.  If I don't move in with Grace, I will probably end up checking out books at the Queens Public Library for nine dollars an hour, or moving to Jersey City.  It's not fun to want something so badly from someone you hardly know.  I have been dragging myself out to openings, parties and events, whenever someone invites me and I'm not totally exhausted from job-hunting and massaging and portfolio building and painting.  Which is not too often but happens now and then.  I got invited to an opening at an obscure gallery in Red Hook by two different people, one of them an awful poet who I have been steadily snubbing for two years and who does not take the hint, but continues writing awful poems about all my paintings and telling me he loves me.  The other was a promising artist who will now never have a show at my gallery.    I figured I'd better show up.  When I did I found I was a minor celebrity.  People I didn't know had heard of me, and babbled drunkenly about how I inspired them.  I was feeling like the old sponge that gets used to clean cat vomit off the kitchen floor, and was baffled.  A beautiful blonde girl started talking and talking about how we are all one in spirit, everything happens for a reason, there is no harm, there is nothing to fear, love is all there is, we just try to let it flow, we do not understand why, we must trust, we have faith...and I kept saying "uh-huh, uh-huh, yeah, right, you're absolutely right, I agree," and this did not help at all, in fact it got boring and annoying really quickly.  Particularly since she was too drunk to listen, or to impart illustrative details.    I discussed this problem with my sister--the fact that even though I believe in the mystical unity of the universe, I do not generally enjoy hanging out with people who talk constantly about the mystical unity of the universe.  She said, "I think that's the purpose of great art--to communicate things that are incredibly banal when expressed in words."  Thus my sister got to the nub of Why I Paint, and I was grateful.  She also pointed out that talking about the mystical unity of the universe, when someone you don't know very well is suffering, is not necessarily apt or kind.  "I'm so sorry" is more polite.  Last weekend I went to another party, given by someone I know slightly, to celebrate the completion of her five-years'-overdue MFA thesis.  Unlike the people at some other parties I've been to, her friends were kind and unpretentious and interested in meeting people.  They said simple things like "Hi, I'm Beverly, how do you know Harriet?"  Banal as this sort of conversation may be, it can lead to infinitely interesting places.  I stayed till 1 AM, and could have stayed longer.  One of the guests was a classics professor at an obscure college in Indiana; he was passionately interested in, and informed about, the Greek play that Harriet wants to direct.  She was thrilled to have met him, and he was thrilled to be a surprise celebrity at a party in New York.  I said, "Wait, you teach at Wabash College?  Do you know Stephen Forsythe?"  "Yeah, Stephen Forsythe interviewed me for my job."  Stephen Forsythe was one of my intimate friends in college.  Six degrees of separation, my foot.  Late in the evening, on the terrace strung with Christmas lights and ringed with planters, we got to asking the married people how they'd met.    "We were volunteering for Nader.  I mentioned I'd written my thesis about Samuel Beckett."    "You wrote a thesis about Samuel Beckett?!!!!  *I* wrote my thesis about Samuel Beckett!!  Oh my God, I don't talk like that, he must think I'm a dork..."    "Our wedding celebration was a week long.  She's worth it."   "I was running the lights for an obscure theatre production at Intersection for the Arts.  Every Tuesday through Saturday, for six weeks, I lit her spotlight while she did her monologue.  We became friends.  It's funny, how humans mate."  My ex-boyfriend thinks that commitment is the worst horror imaginable.  He thinks that independence and separation are goals for which to sacrifice everything.  I didn't cry among strangers.  I didn't have any more wine, and went home soon afterward.  I rode my bicycle in my white sundress through the dark city, and it was cooler after midnight.   

						
</post>


</Blog>