<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Heres a link to some lyrics I have recently written. I like writing. Review me please. It would be helpful. Thanks.   http://www.fictionpress.com/~benbowsher  There we go. Copyright and everything. Don't even bother trying to steal. Bastards. They will enforce copyright on ur ass. Criticism welcome. Don't be plain bitchy. I am trying to improve. Thankyou. I am an Art-eest you know.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Fat and egg like. Thats a saying. How's everyone? I'm Good. I've written a short story. Adam give me your email please. Thankyou. In advance. It is rather swell. ish. I have just finished listening to dashboard. Again. Some songs are good, On balance, Some smell like the bottom end of a skunk. The good ones are top notch. Download them. My my my. Thats a very good use of repitition. can't keep this up and stay funny. I apologise. It will gradually dissolve in funnyness. Like prozac in the bloodstream. Asparin in water. Urine on matresses and other such analogies. I apologise. The urine thing was not required. Unlucky is a key word here. A one word phrase if you will. A deep sea voyage of the english language. Exit.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well i'd just like to whine for a little about how annoyed I am. This is not a good life. Whatever people say currently it's no conselation. I will regret sayig this soon.  I can't take this happy happy life thats going on when not everything is going well. I'm sick of saying yes i'll listen. I have stuff to deal with as well. This isn't directed to anyone by the way. don't feel hated. just needed to get it off my chest for everyone inn the entire planet to see. This is lame. I'm going to stop now. Back to normality. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Good evening again. It has been raining. The sun has been doing a short peep show. Now and again that is. I really am not on top form. Feeling particularly sad about leaving currently. No matter. I shall be back to normal. Soon. Descent. Beginning to wonder whether I have the right spelling of the right word. Is descent as in it's good or falling? No matter. Zoom out Camera man. Listening to "am I missing" by dashboard, it is mighty good. Buy their album also. I do believe that this is not a good choice. Moving. Bullshit. I don't want to leave you all. Ever. Just written a pretty awesome set of lyrics. I don't think I'll ever get to use them. I'm always second rate. Or it feels that way. Back to masking the way I really feel by short sporadic sentences. I would share my lyrics. but you'd jip them you thiefing munchkins you. Umpa-lumpas even. With your orange skin and your green hair. You make me sick.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Band Practice was cancelled. fun fun fun fun fun. This was not a good move. Jo and squeet practically became comatosed looking at one another. Nathan if you ever read this. Thanks. Daytime television does smell awfully. Until the day I die is on my record player currently. Page avenue by story of the year. Purchase it quickly. I am supposed to write a short story. If I'm ok enough I may become rich. I am mentally blocked. Much like my nose and other orifices. Again my thanks go out to squeet. It is your fault. I love you for it. I can't fight my way out of a paper bag. I can talk it though. Any suggestions for plotline? comments welcome. I may sqaush them all together like a fine trifle. Maybe a jam roll. I'm now hungry. Ciao "buds". God bless your spoken english jason. Exit.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have a serious amount of flem. My throat hurts. I would like to thank the combined effort of squeet and Lulu of infecting me. thanks. Yesterday I stayed up an exceedingly long time and got up rather too early. My eyes hurt. I plain hurt. All over one might say.   I have practice today. I can barely stand up-right let alone jump around singing not so classic punk songs. Again thanks squeet. You are the worst in my bad books and have sunk. greatly. I have a calculator on my speaker. It is doing little good. Maths exam is a while off. It'll be ok. maybe. maybe not. Science is rather too soon to bare. God bless it. I shall soon attempt to eat breakfast. After that I shall attempt retaining it in my stomach. With little success I feel. My grammar is now on top form. which is rather bad as you can tell. Going to go peel the crust from the inside of my nostril. not really. I am blowing my nose. exit.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here again..me am..do not point out the very dubious grammer and dubious spelling of dubious. I am slapping some funk out on my bass again. It sounds broken. It is not. I cannot play. I lie. I can. Jaco eat your heart out. Dave, Rosie ...you two piss off; eventually i WILL BEAT YOUR ARSES. My bum hurts. I am covered in paint. I helped my mum do a poster. Whether I helped is as dubious as the spelling of it...I..T..take your time getting that one. No one is there to watch you fumble around desperatly trying to find it's meaning. thats the beauty of reading on your own rather than watching TV. tday was english literature, I'm all punctuated out, this is my excuse for my poor english and unlegibility for the time being. Next week I shall fake a sprained wrist to cover. Hollie if you ever view this; are you going out next friday; I may join you.        Currently I am listening to The Used. They are beyond a doubt pretty ok. Anyone who states otherwise smells like lucy's mum's collection of prehistorical cheese artifacts. Thats a mouthful.   Till next time. Exit stage trap door.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am depressive. I am again pretending to be emo. My eyes are watery. Avoid sticking orange segments in them. Plecs are so small. I loose most of mine. Theyre buggers. I prefer using my fingers to play bass. Squeet...Your not so nice now u n jo are an item..pretty damn mean infact. so thanks. I'm normally feeling rather cheery. today i feel lonely. it must be my odour. It's one of those things you can't shake. I will be cheerier tomorrow. Maybe I shall be more forgiving of squeet also. for now squeet..the bad books for you.   Bad books for lucy to. I like my women thankyou very much. Bad books for Jo also..he's as mean as squeet....good couple in a way.  bye.exit.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Squeet is here. hopefully Jo will get it over with and ask her out quickly.I hate being third wheel. This gave me time to write the latest entry though. this is rather helpful. I am listening to Ocean Avenue by yellow card. It is rather good. buy their album.   I tried self tattooing. It doesnt work very well. It hurts alot too. I need to go urinate. Have a good time doing whatever you're doing. Squeet..no love bites on jo please. he bruises like a peach. it's an emo kid thing. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Good evening one and all. me am writing again. today i had my listening exam. It was again rather easy. I hope you all did well. i ate an indescribable meal. It tasted much like the bottom end of a urinated carpet. Mr. T. Pratt. hav a kleenex you emo kid. You say you are not but you flick your hair and cry alot. hahaha. The end. exit.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here it is buoyo. You wanted an ode (however I don't know how to write an ode and so shall stick with a chunky paragraph or two.): Simon is rather cool. his wit is only exceeded by his skill with musical instruments such as guitar. He is without a doubt one of the funniest men alive and one of my bestest friends. He likes sumbreros. He likes sex with non gender specifified oranges.   When I go to Durham, he will be my legacy to bradford. he shall also stalk me in Durham. its a two position post really. He likes urinating in public places. He likes watching people urinating even more so. he doesnt like being kicked. handle with care.   He is good with english. He can even write monkey backwards. I will show you when I have a photo. His only downside is the tremendous amount of crabs. ahahaha. not really. he is rather genitally clean. I say crabs to often. I will try to stop. but this isn't about me. this is about simon. he says "Ben, I like to see you hurt" too much though.   I will always remember Simon for his massive burn on Ms Schhon in IT upon which she turned rather red. Thankyou for making life that bit better simon. You shall be missed early. better stalk me. get the site up and running. I will send you more drawings in the mail.                        Goodbye 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hullo again. it is rather soon since the klast one. I am rather bored. If anyone still visits this site... thanks. cheers for what you said adam by the by. I'd like to say your welcome for putting you onto Sarah. it is a shame things turned out like crabs on a stag night. Again I'd like to say crabs. It was rather fun. Crabs. Crabs. Right now I am listening to dashboard and pretending to be emo by poking my eyes till they water. I would like to give a round of applause to Hollie for punching someone called belly. I have no idea who he is. apparently he pissed her off much so. unfortunate I guess. I would also like to give abig round of applause to my brother for getting hit in the arse high speed by a frisbee without crying. at it boy. coming out of that emo phase. thank god. till next time. crabs.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hullo. Me am here. it is rather good a day today. IT was so easy. I thought i must have done it wrong. but i doubt it. I am feeling ill however. My throat is still soar. My eyes are feeling kinda fruity also. I'd like to apoloigise to all those I have confused over the years. many in count. It is rather windy. windig as the germans would say. listening exam tommorrow. i can't listen well. so it should go well. I was supposed to go to town, but i didn't. now i am bored. see you soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Me Am Here Again. Jo Is a failed astronaught. It is sunday. My life is rather boring as of today. I have revised for IT. It was rather spiffing. The sun is also up today. which is suprising. Sarcasm in writing shudnt be attempted. I just proved its unsuccess. Currently I am eating a yoghurt. I will then move onto a magnum before leaving to burn of the excess calories produced from eating such articles. I am writing lyics. they are reasonably good. I will not share. Sian, We will be good, inspite of our recent practice. before that, we were actually quite good. Juneau is currently in the record player. It is rather spiffy and really quite superb. I am revising again soon. I shall disappear. download juneau by funeral for a friend. legally please. otherwise i am in trouble.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Me Am Here Again. Last Week was good practice day. this week was not as glorious. Lack of sleep or a hangover plauged the ranks. We will rocketh next week. Boarding was the next on the list. I fell over alot. It was amusing. 180 Boneless being my curent trick. it looks impressive. I am covered in dirt. The sun is still up. I feel ill. My back is jarred. I am complaining. Exit stage left. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Two days it has been. Alex's Computer Smells. Not much has happened. I Have drank some alcohol since then. I have also eaten Cheese. It was a rather interesting experience. Emma S, you shall be missed alot too. Greenbelt was fun. My band is practicing for a gig soon. It will be tremendous. It may on the otherhand smell much like a collection of edam scrapings. My stomach is rumbling. I have had no Breakfast. Life is going swimmmingly...In Lava Rather Than water, no matter. We have found a house. I have already stated this. twice. I am not exited about leaving. It wouldn't be very good. All the people and more mentioned will be missed alot. Crabs. I have to go. My stomach really isnt too hot. Till another time when I have little to do.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Heres my goodbyes to all my friend soutside of school. this will be long and tearful. Lucy and Alyce..sorry i said my bye's already. Lets start with Alex, best mate since birth. You shall be missed so much little (not so much nemore) buddy hope ou and cat hav a good time. Cat, I havn't known you long. I have seen you barf however, which is more than alex. You are a good person. don't ever think otherwise. I'll miss you heaps also. Justine. I don't know you too well anymore, which is a shame. I will miss you alo and will forever remember when we used to hang out. Amy, don't see you alot at all anymore. You were a good experience for me, and on occasion a good friend..kidding..you were one of the coolest mates I had.. i miss you and will always. Tom Mitchell, you are a sorted guy. I will miss rolling in the clover with you...seriously though..you shall be missed alot much. Adam archer; you are the most amazing friend I have ever had (I'd like to take this point to allow everyone to know I am perfectly straight.) You shall be missed alot. Rob G..indeed my friend you are rather funny ands will be missed dearly, i will remember you and adam through the all nighter. Rob H..you are also a funny man and will be remembered much the same way..without an all nighter. Alan, mop head fo life. Have a good time in what ever you wish to do miss ya bud. Jonny, Quiet but cool. have a good one. Finally my band member and former band member.... Nathan, you rocketh buddy, you are wicked awesome. I will miss you and your guitar rocking, skateboard yielding ways. bye. Adam T, I havnt seen u 4 a while. I'm guessing that has much to do with emma, but i won't point the finger lol. I will miss you alot much. Goodbye friend. also special mention to dave, loui and tom, for you are the coolest. miss you all. goodbye.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Me am here again. It is a new day. well an old one. I spent much of it hoovering. Cheesy chips are good. Coca Cola knock-offs Are bad. I Sit here writing songs, becoming rather sentimental and slapping some funk out on my bass. I have an exam on monday. It will be good. Sarcasm Was intended. I doubt you can see that in the writing.We have found a house. It looks ugly on the outside. much like me thought. It is beautiful on the inside. i sound much like a drunken Re Or Philosophy teacher. I am not. being legally underqaulified and aged, that would be a mistake. Ashley, you are shoutuing at me, so here is my spot to you..goodbye ashley, you shall surely be missed. history with you was enjoyable. I will remember you and your sharp wit with Mr Midgley. Me am going now. Ben
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      soon I will say thanks to my friends outside of school. I will see them soon however.  I will not do it yet. In the meawhile, you sentimental types.... hurry up and cry. The sun has completely gone now. Time to go to bed with seven men..yes seven can't count it on one hand. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      varga..even though your probably too emo to go on this..stubborn get..im trying 2 say goodbye man. jonny..You are also cool..and not too emo. Abi und bex..ur gonna b missed. sara..you are uber cool and will be missed muchly to.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      sanna....you're cool and will also be missed alot too much. Sian (sorry dnt know how to do the whole accenty thing) you have been good to know, I will never forget you, we will rocketh at your do..promise. dave..better bassman...you have a good life. sorry folks, this may go on for a few weeks, so many people, they all deserve a mention. Seb...you are quite good at saxaphone, you shall be missed. Madeline..I don't know you at all, but I'm sure you are swell. Feather, you have been odd to know, but good to know also, how do you say it: "respect bud". Iverson, you have been a kool friend, and will also be missed, for your stupid stunts make me laugh.....Hollie again, coz you didnt think I'd miss you aha you were wrong.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Me Am Ben. I spend many hours a day sitting still. the sun is disappearing currently. I enjoy flashing my "not inverted" belly button. I have siblings of two in number, one being male and a twin, the other a smaller sister. The names of both children concerned is little business of yours. In other related articles (being about me)I am moving to durham soon. many people think it is good, on balance, many think it is bad. The change in scenary from the usual happenings of bradford may be refreshing. I hope it is. I wet the bed also.      I'd like to take this oppotunity to say goodbye to many of my friends properly: Booth...You large gay object you (its funny coz hes small and straight). Gornall...you've been a large factor in me coming out of school unscathed. Luke P, god bless you man...for you make me chuckle a wee bit. Tother luke, you make me chuckle slightly less, and you probably will never get to see this. Hollie, Goodbye, good luck next year, stay cool.Squeet, You are rather swell, I will miss you alot much. Simon, my bestest jazz loving beatle's playing "daddy". Lucy, you've been a rock, and although we lost touch, and only just got back in, i feel i can trust you, you shall be missed, you to alyce. Jade, what can be said, you are not so good at drawing, but the friend thing you have down. Lamis and Laura, you will probably never see this either, I hope you do, you have been kind to me, if we ignore the taunting, i love you both goodbye. Thanks to everyone who has touched my life at my school..that is most people. I Will never forget any of you. Stay cool. I will regularly keep this site updated with my ongoings life.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have justr spent the afternoon with jenny and sqeet. It's been a long afternoon. Full of talk of Eve, breeding and boxes. I am rather traumatised and do not wish to discuss further for fear of relapse.  Me an Jo are going for a midnight skate hopefully. If i can be arsed moving by then. I may not be able to for a fact. Greediness has overcome my tired, withered little body. Much like a shrimp eating lost of stuff. What's that thing shrimp eat? ermmm You know it...  I wish everyone I know all moved to Durham too. it would be good then. Not shit. Shit like it is now. Varga played well at the gig, as did rosie and andrew. Micky and kris did crap, coz they bitched and acted like it was a competition. I don't like them. they smell. Much like cabbage that is. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It was cool, because we did well. Many of the people there didn't get the music. Most were dance/pop fanatics, and thats crap. Dammit by Blink went well. Everyone knows that one. Always a plus.  I messed up a couple of times. Everyone messed up a couple of times. Hey well.  I'm too tired to put on this sarcastic outlook to life. It is 1.00PM GMT, and I have only just got up. woo. The buzz died pretty much as soon as we got home. Nathan is still asleep. Bless his little lead guitarist hands. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is ben again. Suprise suprise. It aint going to be anyone else is it. I come in here quite often, write something for you're entertainment and do nothing else till the time comes to write another post. To say I do all that, the commentage on this thing bites arse. Send a comment. Come on people.  Well, not alot has happened since my last entry. I've become overly infatuated with some one I shouldn't be, which is always a pleasure. never a chore. *shrugs and looks confused*.  It's been a long couple of weeks, and it's almost over. I feel like shit frankly. it's not the best time to leave. I love evryone so much that it's not funny. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Eating alot of sherbet (alot) after 24 hours without rest is not a goo idea. Eating burnt sherbet and the matchbox that it was burtn in is not a good idea either. Nor is eating semi digested sherbert.   I had my leaving party yesterday. It was good bar the drunk munchkin rodio clowns. Assholes. I have written some form the heart lyrics. They are good. I think. Not sure. Review, nudge.   My party was good. I'd like to say thanks to everyone who came. You all touched me alot (mentally, not physical touching). It was really good to say some goodbyes properly.   I love everyone who came and I hope they love me too. I am tired. I have had little sleep. 2 hours infact. Good news justine: The lump has gone down. Long story which needs no depth there.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello. It is my bbq tommorrow. Because I am leaving I have decided to throw one. Not me more than my family, including I. My head itches. I have been outside. I have froliced in the fields. I did not enjoy.     I am rather tired. I am going to rocksolid. Well everyone have fun. ciao.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My recycled fav song: she drove me to daytime tv. It is a good song. Bar all the killing it is good. Buy it.   I don't know why but I am getting rather bossy at the moment. Note to self: stop. I am hoping to get my lip ierced soon. I researched it. Sounds a bit yucky. If there's a will there's a way though. HAHA.   If people have a problem with piercing: piss off, I don't wnat to hear it on my comment thing. Mood has currently changed. I am now enraged. I love everyone currently.   I just went to town and got some rather nice cords. Rather splendid infact. Gooooo cords.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My new song, can be found in fictionpress. I like it. You probably won't. You know who you are. Screw you. Simon, I will get my lip pierced before I go. I will dammit.     I am looking forward to moving. I am also saddened about moving. A man of two boats really. Thats nice analogy work. I thought it was. Again who cares about you. 'Cept me; obviously. I love all. Orange and skunk alike.   Don't think I did too badly at my exams today. Hope I didn't. Who wants to do bad though I guess. Not me. Not many. English was rather good. It was the type of writing I like which was enjoyful much.  After tomoroow I have a week off, for lazing around. That should be fun. Might see if Adam is free a lunch time or two. I hope he is. Like simon, he is one of my bestest friends.   Till a later date when I have word upon which to say. Foundations for a conversation with myself. Bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is one of my favourate songs: from start to finish by the starting line, tis rather good. Buy stuff everywhere. I'm feeling a touch nostalgic. Cat's thrown up. Nostalgia gone. Bitter nausiea replaces it. Fabtastic.   Next week I have a history exam. Happy dance, happy dance. Maths, english and science. Makes it that much easier to feel at ease. Honest!  I got really fast at slap bassing recently, which I thought was quite cool. Superfast. Aeroplane fast.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hullo. I say I'm back. Havn't been anywhere. I'm just too damn lazy to care. That is right. Too lazy. I loathe some people right now. I will not name names. Someone's phone is not working either..ahem..mr. lloyd. nice one. Haha. I can't be bothered writing anymore, I'm in a real shitty mood. Real shitty.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was hot, really hot. It was not a good day for maths. It was neither that, nor a good day for my brain. It was also not a good day for sweaters.  it was a good day for ice cream. Woo, go ice cream. Apart from the chocolate ice cream, today did not go well. At all. I am talking german and listening to further seems forever. At the same time. Sounds weird, really isn't that more than boring. Further Forever are good, buy "How to start a fire" when it comes out.  it was good to see friends from school again. I miss them alot much. Simon and his glands. Luke and his beach boy hair. Sanna and her coolness. Sara and her incredibly small feet. There are more, but there isn't a comical feature ot match anymore. I could of made them up like simon's glands. I am too lazy. My back hurts. I played cricket very poorly for too long.  Well I'll be going now. I can hear my name being called in Peru. Also called in some parts of Uganda. It means something more offensive up there. Don't spend you're time looking that up. I made it up. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      HAHa. Maths test tomorrow. It's the one everyone dreads. Group dreading. Wow. I think I'm ready, but you never know, do you? Circle theorems are blurry, but thats life. Scuba diving sounds fun. Anyone for scuba diving? No. Just me.  I want to fall asleep and never have exams again. Thats a far away dream. I havn't much to say, it's study leave, i have done little bar revision.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had a long evening. I played with an inflated football till the early hours. It was fun. Got me too sleep quickly. Today is rather dull. Lacened with revison and none too pleasing at that. Science. Haha. What a thing. Science is much like Jo; It smells funny and makes me want to kick it. I like kicking things. If I could, I'd go pro. I cannot. The pay is quite frankly rather pantsy. "pantsy"-to be very much of a rather bad qaulity, see pants.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It has been a while. I have been sleeping alot. On holiday. I went to a party. It was good. Well done San. Not much has been happening over at Ol' fort Ben. Published more lyrics. I see no one has left reviews. nice guys. Nice. Seeta is here again. She mad me listen to killswitch engage. I think they're ok. Sorry Squeet. They aint the best. Sliced bread is still lookig sharp. Yellowcard are good though. Cheers for lending me the album. Thanks. You rocketh despite what you think I think. That made a whole load of sense. Don't pull me up on it. Well thats all fr today. Nothing new. As i said. Don't you listen. Honestly.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am moving on thursday. Finally it is over and done with. I'm not happy to go. It's a relief though: knowing where i'm coming and going etc.  Anyhoo. Sqeet was here earlier. I was in a bad mood. I apologise for the assholeage. I'm drawing again. Founbd my mood. woo.  Just went skating. No I am tired. Suprise suprise.  Pain. Tired. Goodbye.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>