<Blog>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude all i can say i wow.  Yesterday was super duper GREAT!  Me and Katlyn went over to their friends house for dinner and  got two presha warshin jobs lined up!  MUCHOS DINERO!  Then I went back to Katlyn's for an hour or so and we just chilled out.  We wrestled and i beat her bad!  It was fun though.  Chill and I'll tell you more later on.  I'm Out  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's summer and I'm lovin it.  This summer is going to include 2 major things.  Katlyn and Golf.  I'll be spending the whole with Katlyn or golfing, and maybe I can get her to come golfing with me so I can have the best of both worlds.  That would be neat.  Hopefully I'll lose some weight over the summer too so i can be skinny.  WooHoo!  Grandparents are leaving today so I can have my room back!   YAY!  I enjoyed having them here so it's all good.  I'll be glad to have my bed back so I can get off the floor.  That's all for now, posts may be few and far between during the summer, but I'll try to keep you updated.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My grandparents are coming into town.  Which can only mean one thing, I have to sleep on the air matress in the living room...  Oh Boy.  I love 'em and all I just hate sleeping in the living room.  We have to go to Kemah tomorrow, which I guess is ok but I'd rather spend the day at Katlyn's house.  But I can't, so I just gotta stick it out.  Oh Well.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OUtta middle school, yea baby!  Shit fool im so happy, bye bye ghetto QVMS!  YOWZA!  WEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from having dinner and a snack ;) at Katlyn's house.  It was yummy!  The dinner I mean.  We had chicken.  It was really good.  Then we went back upstairs for a while and just chilled out, it was cool.  Fun night tonight!  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was our last full day of middle school.  Three more half days we're out of the damn hell hole.  But, then we're into high school...  Oh Boy.  But anyhow.  That's all fer today.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, just to let you know, I'm a boy.  Today i purchased Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six:3 for my Xbox.  I must say it is a very good game.  I'm to head over to Zach's house today at 2:00 for band rehearsal.  I'd ditch it again to go to Katy's house, but I already told him I could make it.  DAMN!!!  Anywho, I'll have most of the summer to spend as much time as I want with Katlyn.  I say most because she's going out of town for a long while and I really can't spend time with her if she isn't here.  I'll find some way to keep myslef occupied until her return.  I guess.  Well I guess I'll catch you guys later on.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have nothing to do on the weekends!  I'd go over to Katlyn's but she's at a friend's little party thing.  So I'm forced to sit here for the whole day and do nothing!  Grrrrr.  I need more friends like me who have no other friends so neither of us will be busy.  Yes, that would solve everything... Well ok, enough of my whining.  Have a nice day.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from seeing Van Helsing, and it was super awesome.  The CG was indecipherible from liva action.  I can't even begin to explain.  Got some major cuddle time in with Katy too.  ;)  I'd definitely recommend you go see Van Helsing.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What's up everybody, I got church again tonight, except tonight we're just watching a movie. No lesson, thank god.  Doug's lessons are less than interesting.  Hopefully Doug'll let me bring the movie so we can watch Dickie Roberts: Former Child Star.  I love thatr movie!  I'll post again later.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from youth group and I feell better than usual.  I'd been thinking and I realized how much of a great person my Katlyn is.  I've been spending so much time with her and it just feels great.  She's the one for sure.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First post on my blog, this is exciting.  Nothing really went on at school otday, i got youth group at my church tonight but other than that today's just any other day.  I'll post later on with more news.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today hasn't been too eventful.  I bought new strings for my bass, but that's it.  I may be goin to a party, but I dono.  Catch Ya Later.  I'm Out.  I Love You Katlyn!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AudioBlogging is the coolest thing ever!  It's the wave of the future!  I love it!  Whilst I am in Alabama I will use that feature a lot.  Check you later.  I'm out!  I Love You Katy Bear!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My mommy made me stay home today because she says im spending too mucch time at katlyn's.  I feel like I've missed so much, but maybe it's good im not spending so much time over there.  She's probably getting pretty sick of having me around all the time, i know I would be.  Anyhow, I'm leaving for Alabama Thursday and I won't be back 'til Sunday so i wont be postin tween now and then.  Unless something big pops up.  I'll check ya later on.  I Love You Katy Bear!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
     

    
</post>


</Blog>