<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It is 6:50 in the AM on a Saturday morning and I am at work.  There are so many things wrong with that sentence...  But I gotta work.  What else is going to pay for my crack habit?  :)  Anyway, I had to wake up at 4:30 this morning to get into work on time.  Plus, I had to buy donuts for all my employees that also had to be here at the butt-crack of dawn.  'Cause that's what a good boss does.  He buys his employees breakfast that makes them FAT!   Back to my point...  I got up at 4:30 this morning.  That wouldn't have been so bad if I didn't go to bed at 3:30 this morning.  If I do the math correctly, that means I only got 1 hour of sleep.  Suprisingly enough, I'm not tired... yet.  Angela looks tired.  She is sitting at the desk next to me sleeping.  It's nice that she gets paid to work so hard!  JK...   That's all for today.  I'm going to Angela's house later 'cause Kathy is in town.  Should be fun!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hate the fact that my over-achieving friends make me feel like such a loser.  I have come to discover tonite that A BUNCH of my other friends also have their own blogs.  And you know what?  They're blogs are like 1,000 times better than mine.  They got pictures and different colors and SHIT!  It makes me feel like less of a man...  Well not really.  But it makes me wanna kick some ass! I'm going to figure out how to make my blog the shiz-nit!  I too will have pictures, and fuckin' bouncing monkeys, breakdancin' gorillas and NAKED, NAKED chicks just scattered all over the place.  It will be so ridiculously over the top.  SERIOUSLY!  (I only said that because Ang thinks I say "seriously" too much)  SERIOUSLY!  SERIOUSLY! SERIOUSLY! Alright, I gotta go.  I'm going to the gym and work out.  It case you wanna know, I like to work out in T-I-G-H-T spandex.  :)  Just kidding. I will see everyone later.  And to all my friends, this is Blog War.  I will take out my Blog Bazookas and Blog missiles and Blog Machine Guns and blast some holes in your mutha fuckin' asses!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I got a kink in my neck that just won't go away.  I swear I wake up every morning with a sore neck.  It feels like I've been karate kicked in the neck over and over and over again.  "Yeah, put him in a body bag!!!"  (That one was for Ang)  I have no remedies for the infidel that is my sore neck.  I'm just poppin' pills hoping this pain will go away.  People say that it's probably because of my bed or the way that I sleep.  But you know what, I've slept the same way for years...  I fall asleep crying in the fetal position.  That's normal right?    PEACE OUT MOTHER FUCKERS!   I love you!  P.S.  China, thanks for the voicemail this morning.  I know if I hit it once I can hit it twice!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So the posting continues...  I'm actually posting today later than I usually do, but that's only because I have been soooooooo busy all day today.  (Do you like how 7 extra o's to the word perfectly conveys that?)  It's ridiculous how much work I have on my desk today!  I don't know about everyone else, but I don't think working is part of my job description!  I guess I'll quit whining... Sorry but there's nothing interesting going on with me today.  I'll cross my fingers and maybe something cool will happen to me today.    T.T.F.N.!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This past weekend was/is a complete haze.  Let me start by saying to everyone out there in the world...  If I called you at any point between 11:00pm and 3:00am on Saturday, then I apologize for anything "inappropriate" that I may have said.  If anything, I guess I'm also sorry if I happened to wake you up.  But in my defense, WHAT WAS YOUR ASS DOING ASLEEP ON A SATURDAY NIGHT ANYWAY!?! Anyway, I'm pretty sure I had a good time on Saturday.  Me and my friend China, China, China, China, China (what do you think of that Queen Kate) went to a club.  We went ghetto style.    ghetto style:  ghetto style in this case is buying a bottle of vodka and making your own drinks before you even get to the spot.  it involves getting drunk before you even get there.  let's face it, my cheap ass is not paying $8 for a watered-down drink!  I spent all day Sunday being hungover.  I always recommend that!  (in a sarcastic tone)  We went to Sea World to check out the new water ride they got there.  So, we waited in line for about an hour before we finally get the news that the ride is "temporarily out of service."  FUCK THAT!  So, China, her sister Monica and I left and went to the Budweiser beer school.  We all graduated and got our Beer School Diplomas.  See Mom, I told you I would finish school!  Needless to say, I don't think drinking 6 glasses of beer superfast was the surefire cure for a hangover...  I guess I'll take off now, I feel myself rambling on...  Where the hell is that beer?
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am in quite a funk today and I can't seem to figure out why.  I just spent 10 minutes staring at my spaghetti trying to figure out what color it is...  It's not red and it's not orange.  I will call it "Sporangetti Red."  Maybe cause I woke up about an hour ago and went right into work...  Dunno. This funk is funking me out.  What the funk!?!  Or as my friend Angela would say, "I am in a mood today."  She is probably right.  I guess I can be pretty moody.  I need some sort of constant in my life I guess. Maybe this is partly because my friend is going to be gone all weekend and I don't know what I am going to do with myself.  Don't get me wrong, I have other plans this weekend too!  I am hanging out with my other best friend China on Saturday, so that will be cool.  I just don't hang out with China as much because the two of us have such opposing schedules.   Oh well!  It's not the end of the world.  I'm sure China and I will just drink all weekend until we're too drunk to stand or realize that what we're sitting on is not really a toilet, but the VIP booth of a club.  Alcohol solves all problems doesn't it?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Day #2 - I hope my posts aren't too boring for y'all.  Anyway, nothing special has happened since yesterday and today.  Just the monotonous existence that is my life.  I talked to my friend Steph last nite.  She made an interesting comment to me...   I guess she is having a birthday party at her house and she made reference to a place where the people can do the "boom boom."  A "boom boom room" if you will.  Rrrriggght...  I can't remember the last time I heard someone call it the "boom boom."  Except for the time I was in a Vietnamese village in east Saigon during the war.  "Me so horny!  Me love you long time!"  Damn Vietnamese prostitute!  That will be the third and final time that I get herpes!  Fool me once, shame on you.  Fool me twice, shame on me!  : ) Also, just wanted to say thanks to Queen Kate for giving me a link on her blog site.  Until I figure out how to put a special place on my site, you're just going to have to go to the following site:  www.katespurpose.blogspot.com  I highly recommend checking it out.  She is quite a cool lady with a much cooler blog site than me.  Smell ya later!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is the debut of my very own blogspot...  Although it could crash and burn terribly.  Oh well, as long as my mom visits then I guess I can live with myself.  My mom thinks I'm cool! I really have no fuckin' clue what I'm doing.  Obviously this will be a trial and error thing for me.  Please feel free to offer your contstructive criticism.  Unless it's hurtful.  Then keep that shit to yo-self!  : )   More to come as I learn to walk...
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For some reason today, I wish I was a mute.  That way I wouldn't have to talk to anyone ever again.  If people try to talk to me, I can just smile and nod.  Then make them feel stupid for trying to talk to someone that cannot talk back.  If I can't be mute, then I wish I was filthy rich.  Then I could walk around and not give a shit because I would be worth 1 BILLION DOLLARS!  Mwa ha ha ha!   Me and China would go around slapping people in the faces with stacks of hundred dollar bills.  Then, as these people look at us in shock and disbelief, we would hand them a $20 bill to shut up and leave us alone.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes it's fun to title a post with something that has nothing to do with what I'm talking about...  Sometimes it's better that I say nothing at all...
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today's post is inspired by lyrics to a Dashboard Confessional song, and also brought to you by the letters "F" and "T".  (Sesame Street kicks ass!)  I am vindicated I am selfish I am wrong I am right I swear I'm right I swear I knew it all along. And I am flawed But I am cleaning up so well. I am seeing in me now the things you swore you saw yourself.  I was going through my garage and found a box of old pictures and old poems and shit I wrote when I was younger.  Walking down memory lane told me one thing...  I was fucked up when I was a teenager!  I was imagining what my life would be like if I kept going down that path I was on.  Literally, I would probably be dead.  And it would probably be over a stupid reason too...  like a girl or something.         Thank God I was blessed with the ability to look at my life, see how much it sucks, and it turn laugh at it.  Otherwise, I would probably be in a gutter somewhere eating shit.  "I eat pieces of shit like you for breakfast!"  "You eat pieces of shit for breakfast?!?"  "What are you too good for your home?!?"  (Happy Gilmore)       Overall, the weekend was a good one.  I got to hang out with China on Sunday.  I hardly ever hang out with her on the weekend anymore because of her hectic schedule.  The best part about my weekend...  I got to see a bunch of old pictures of Ang and Kathy.  I laughed so hard that my contact came out of my eye!  Lookin' good ladies!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So sorry about the inconsistencies of my posts but the month of June for me has been such a whirlwind, hectic and out of control.  But as an answer to a request from my friend Angela, I thought I would go ahead and give you losers and update...  I saw Dodgeball last night.  All my friends have been hyping it up all week saying how funny it is.  So my review...  it was alright.  It was kinda funny.  I know I didn't hate it.  But I also wasn't busting up laughing and scratching Angela's arm.  If I was a movie critic, my tag line would be "Go see it if you want.  I don't care either way."  I also have had this weird twitchy thingee going on underneath my left eye for the last two days.  My boss said it was because I'm stressed.  I think I can agree with that.  Yesterday I had to work 11 fuckin' hours!  I hope I can use this weekend as a time to relax and drink beer and get fat!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey Kids!  Sorry it's been so long since I last posted.  You know how it is sometimes when you're wrapped up in a project at work.  I'm finally done though.  It was getting so bad that I barely had enough time to take a shit, let alone write up a new post.  Anyway, nothing is new with me.  I thought I would break the ice first with a little joke that my friend told me...  One day there were two peanuts walking down the street and one was assaulted.  Get it?!?  A-Salted.  Ha Ha Ha hm hm...  right...  um... anyway...  Saturday night I went to the Padre game and let me just say, that it was kick ass!  Normally I don't go to baseball games to watch baseball.  I usually just go to drink and eat nachos with my friends.  But this last time... damn!  The Padres were behind 1 point the whole game and managed to score 2 points in the 8th inning to take the lead.  It was awesome!  Last night I had an inspiration bug bite me on the scrotum and so this is what I came up with...  "The Story of My Life"  I've spent my whole life searching for you. There have been some close calls. But trying to find you is like trying to justify a mystery within a riddle based on a lie. I haven't got a clue.  The first time I found you I Am Young and naive. You were so quick  to make me believe the one thing wrong was me. The second time that you And I met I thought was as good as it gets. But you outgrew me, surrounded me with your lie. When you hid your sin in a look of surprise. Deep down wondering why I didn't die.  The third and fourth I couldn't make it right. You were my Sunshine when I couldn't see the light. Killed by the darkness As I chased you To a place where I didn't belong. Expecting to find you while surrounded  by a monster's arms.  The fifth time that we both crossed was the funniest  of them all. You were a joke that only now I get. Letting me hide my laughter within my regret.  The sixth time I went after you I thought I was done. This game was over and I thought that I won. My penalty was timing because you  had to leave. Fate took our lives in different directions. Why did she Step on me?  This last time I found you I saw you as  my savior. You were  An Angel and my devil on both of my shoulders. But you couldn't be what I wanted so much to see. Blind to the fact that your wings hold you up higher than I can ever reach.  So I'll spend more time searching for you. Searching for close calls as I try to grasp at these straws. Because all journeys are paved with pain. Each and every step is a step to be free. I know that  the last time  I find you I'll find the missing part of me.  China, since you have your degree already in Renan-losophy 101, then you should be able to follow this pretty well.  In fact, just as a test, can you find all of their names in each of the verses?   Well kiddies, that's it for now.  This post should keep you satisfied and fulfilled for all those other days I missed.  See ya later bitches! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I discovered today that my sweat glands are sooooo bass-akwards.  We are throwing a baby shower for our boss here at work and the gift we got her is a bassinet.  So because I possess a Y chromosome, I was charged with the duty of assembling the bassinet.    Mind you, assembling a bassinet is not physical work.  But for some God forsaken reason, I was sweating like a pig in a turtleneck.  You would think I was assembling this bassinet on the surface of the sun or in hell or something.  The weird thing is, whenever I work out, on hot summer days, whatever else it is, I NEVER SWEAT.  What is the deal with that?    Someone tell me that it's not just me.  Someone tell me that I don't need to go to the doctor.    By the way, for the nerds out there, I know that pigs do not sweat.  It was just an expression.  On a totally unrelated subject, let me tell you all about my weekend...  On Friday I saw Lit and Hoobastank in concert.  It was a FUCKIN' AWESOME SHOW!  I was goin' crazy that night.  By the way, I didn't sweat there either.  Even though there was like 10 people crammed into each square foot.  Saturday my friend Kathy had a party because she graduated from beautician school and it was our friend Ziggy's birthday.  So happy birthday to Zig and congrats Kathy.  Sunday was a day to be lazy.  I did go to the gym.  Here's a pop quiz to make sure you were paying attention:  Did I sweat?  Anyway, I'm done rambling.  Catch ya'll on the flipside!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I would be everything you'd want me to be if I were 30. I would spend 7 years learning to cook your favorite meals if I were 30. Taking those 7 years to make 7 figures to take care  of you and me if I were 30.  I would learn all about you if that person was me if I were 30. Most of all  the man I'd become would laugh at the boy I used to be when I'm 30. I would be everything you'd want me to be if I were 30.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have you ever been walking down a hall or on the sidewalk and notice that someone else is walking right towards you?  You are like 2 trains speeding towards an inevitable collision.  So, to avoid being embarrassed (because walking into someone and smacking faces is not cool) you do a little side-step to your right...  But then the idiot side-steps in the same direction.  The next thing that goes through your brain is to move the other direction.  But then the jackass does that too!   It seems so retarded that you are moving back and forth with each other.  It's like some impenetrable force field that you just cannot cross.  Finally after like 10 minutes, I smarten up and stop so the other person can cross.  What really burns me though, is right after that they say something stupid like "thanks for dancing with me" or "tango y tu?"  It makes me want to shove my fist in their mouth.  I want to stab them with my ball point pen in the ear.   And that is how I got my first restraining order...  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      3 more days until phalange Angie and I go to see Hoobastank!  I am Hooba-excited.  I'm about to blow a big Hooba-load because I am so excited.  It should be a good show.  Lit is opening for them too.  Lit rocks!   I am in the process of doing my homework for the concert.  I have been listening to Hoobastank and Lit non-stop.  Because you are not cool unless you can sing every single word to every single song at a concert.  You gotta sing as loud as you can too.  So loud that you ruin the concert for the people in front of you because you're singing is so terrible.  So bad that Hoobastank packs up all their shit and leaves! Oh yes, Angie and I plan to ruin the concert for everyone!  By the way Angela, don't forget to bring sunglasses for the Hoobastank guy.  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have nothing to say...  I've had nothing to say the last several days.  Sorry.    Hi.  Bye.    Don't you think it's funny that you wasted several minutes of your life to read this post about nothing?  I laugh at you!  Ha ha ha!    P.S.  Please come back and visit me again...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been bamboozled and had!  Do you see up there underneath the my blog title?  Up there in the description about my blog.  You see how the word "personal" looks so funny?  It has been turned into a link to another site!  A link to a singles lonely hearts site!  WASSUP WITH THAT!  I will admit that I have been unsuccessful with the ladies, but that's just sad.  You know what that tells the world?  It says "This is Ren.  He is sad.  He is lonely and needs to find a date through singles websites.  He goes on these sites so much that he is sponsored by them.  He even put a link on his own site for everyone else to enjoy!"  AAAAHHHHH!!!  Oh well, until I figure out how to fix it I guess there it will stay for now.  What's next?  If a link shows up to any gay/r kelly peeing on women/michael jackson and little boys/donkey  porn sites then I'm done!  I'm serious!  I will shut down this blog for good!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey folks!  Good to talk to you again.  I hope all you kiddies had a good 3-day weekend too!  I know I did.   Friday - My good friend Elliot is back in San Diego.  He was in Virginia for the past few years for school.  He graduated (consequently making me feel like a loser for not finishing school).  We hung out with my friends Anthony, China and Alex that night too.  T'was a good time!  Didn't get to bed until 3:30 in the AM... Saturday - Had to wake up at 4:30 = 1 hour of sleep.  Went to work from 6-10am.  Then went to Angela's mom's house to visit all the relatives from Wisconsin.  Cool people I must say!  Love the accents!  Sat around drinking beer and playing speed with Angela, Kathy and Danny.  According to Kathy, I guess I need a bib when I drink beer.  I do like to slobber!  : ) Sunday - Slept until about 3:30 in the afternoon.  Such a bum!  Then went and hung out with Angela. Monday - Went to Sea World with Angela and the kiddies.  Had a good time.  Got sunburned.  I was actually shocked that I did because I'm so freakin' dark.  Oh well...  Also got soaked on all the stupid water rides.  Who would have thought that you can get wet in a place like "Sea World."  Hmmph. The rest of the day today is going to be filled with work and working out at the gym.  My life is just one big party huh?
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    &nbsp; urlLink     China just sent this picture to me.&nbsp; Kind of a blast from the past.&nbsp; Sorry, but I was too stupid to figure out how to not make it sideways.&nbsp; So you get a sore neck from my blog.&nbsp; Big fuckin' deal!&nbsp; Anyway, it's just so shocking to see how we looked back then.&nbsp; This picture was taken the first time China and I ever spoke to each other.&nbsp; And look at us now...&nbsp; Awww...&nbsp; This picture was taken about 7 years ago.&nbsp; I was 16 and China was 15.&nbsp; Notice the lack of fatness in my face.&nbsp; Even more interesting, notice my hair!&nbsp; WOW!&nbsp; Now look out below:  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     urlLink     This is China and me now.&nbsp; Quite a difference I must say.&nbsp; Obviously this picture was taken at Disneyland.&nbsp; By the way, that really is Tinkerbell in our hands.&nbsp; We caught her in a net...&nbsp; It's amazing how much we have changed.&nbsp; I wonder how we will look 7 more years from now.&nbsp; That would make me 30.&nbsp; Hmmm...&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    &nbsp; urlLink     Today is my nephew Reed's 1st Birthday!&nbsp; Happy Birthday buddy!&nbsp; It's so wierd to think that he is already 1 year old.&nbsp; They really do grow up so fast (tear)!&nbsp; Pretty soon he will be digging thru all my shit and bugging me.&nbsp; For now, we will accept him as is because he is still cute and not a terror.&nbsp; Right now he is learning to walk.&nbsp; So he is taking steps in groups of 6-7 steps before he loses his balance and falls on his big fat butt.&nbsp; It is the funniest thing to watch!    &nbsp;  Anyway, Happy Birthday Reed!&nbsp; You are one of the best things that has hit this family since fried rice!  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Dear Angela, China & Queen Kate,     &nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; How are you all doing today?&nbsp; I am writing all three of you this letter to make sure that one thing is clear...&nbsp;  I would rather spend the rest of my life old and alone before I would trade our friendships over a girl .&nbsp; I know at one point or another, you all have questioned&nbsp;what I would do if a girl asked me to pick her over our friendship.&nbsp; I have never met 3 cooler females than the 3 of you.&nbsp; And I am so glad that I can call you my best friends.&nbsp; You are all so funny and constantly make me laugh (duh, what else would a funny person do?)&nbsp; Believe me when I say that I would never, ever, ever do that.&nbsp; Unless of course it was Kate Beckinsale who asked me to do so.&nbsp; Because  I know  that one day she will leave her husband for me.&nbsp; Then it would only be fair that I choose her over our friendships...&nbsp; :)&nbsp; Besides, would I really be the one to win if the choice was between myself and Justin Timberlake, David Beckham, or Douglas Robb?&nbsp; I didn't think so! &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Love you all, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Renan         
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Living your life    as a frog    looking for life's cure    can lead to    an interesting discovery.    Let me tell you    about the 2 princesses    that I was    able to meet.     &nbsp;   The first has been    royalty to me    for 8 years.    Always there to    make me laugh.&nbsp;    Always there to    dry my tears.    I spent one-third    of my life    trying to protect    her from pain.    I would rather die    than see her get    her feelings hurt again.     &nbsp;   The second highness    is as close    to perfection    as I can see.    And if you count    her sister then    princesses I know    will equal 3.    I won't allow myself    to be wrong    for as long    as she's around.    Because she gives    a friendship    that I know is right.    Picks me up    when I'm down.     &nbsp;   The most important    thing to know    about these future queens    is what makes them    princesses to me.    Because a princess    is full of class and dignity    whose beauty never ends.    Because with these 2,    No one is    good enough for them.    
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I feel like Michael Jackson in the "Thriller" video.&nbsp; I feel like a zombie.&nbsp; Also because I am wearing one white glove and a red leather jacket with zipper.&nbsp; I got red leather pants on to match.&nbsp; Hey Ang, Lobster Lady!   tic, tic, tic...&nbsp; 36 hours and 21 minutes I've been up.&nbsp; I don't know what to do with myself.   I went to check emails under my hotmail account earlier.&nbsp; I realized I must be tired because I proceeded to crack myself up for 20 minutes.&nbsp; I just realized that my email address is @hotmail.com.&nbsp; Or should I say hot male.com.&nbsp; Because that is what I am.&nbsp; One fuckin' hot male.&nbsp; I don't know why that was so funny.&nbsp; And now I feel stupid.&nbsp; Kathy, you know that gun you have in your picture?&nbsp; Will you shoot me with it?  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I was reading Kathy's post today and I saw that she mentioned that "they" added all kinds of new fonts and colors.&nbsp; It is so awesome!&nbsp; You can also put links too.&nbsp; See...        &nbsp;   urlLink http://twistofkate.blogspot.com   &nbsp;    I  love  it!        &nbsp;   Anyway, I am soooo tired right now.&nbsp; I went out last night with China and ended up not going to bed because I had to be at work at 6 this morning.&nbsp; I got home at 4 am and had to wake up at 5, so&nbsp;I figured "Why sleep?"&nbsp; So the countdown goes...     &nbsp;   25 hours and 8 minutes awake and counting...     &nbsp;   Last night was fun.&nbsp; We went out to Margarita Rocks, saw that it was too ghetto and a total Cholo / Sausage fest.&nbsp; So we went to Club Tremors.&nbsp; That was fun.&nbsp; We all got a little tipsy.&nbsp; By the way, China I am not mad at you and Angela we wish you were there.     &nbsp;   Have you ever been so tired that you hallucinate?&nbsp; I swear I am seeing things.&nbsp; These turtles next to me are telling me that they have the same problem.&nbsp; So I don't feel as bad. &nbsp;  &nbsp; I gotta go now though...&nbsp; the room is starting to fill up with cotton candy.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today is my little sister's birthday.  She is 15 years old.  I cannot fuckin' believe it.  It seems like only yesterday that she was just a little brat running around telling on me and getting me in trouble with my parents.  "Mom!  Renan didn't clean his room!" "Mom!  Renan is taking black-tar heroine!" "Mom!  Renan stabbed our neighbor!"  Such a brat...  Now she is 15 years old.  A little teenage girl.  Now I totally get to fuck with her boyfriends.  I am not in denial.  I know what it's like at that age.  She totally will have boyfriends.  If any of them touch or hurt her, I WILL KILL THEM!  KILL THEM DEAD!    I remember the days when I was 15.  Seems like so long ago.  I was such a nerd back then.  A little dorky kid with glasses in band.  Yeah I went to band camp too!  I stuck a flute in a girl's vagina!  So what!  And yes Angela and Kathy I'm still a nerd now too.  I beat you to the joke!  Anyway, Happy Birthday Sis!  I couldn't have asked for a better little sister!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, this lack of sleep that I have been having the past week or so has finally caught up to me.  I am SOOOOO sick right now.  Urp.  I think I threw up in my mouth a little bit.  The worst thing about it is that my dumbass is at work right now.  I woke up this morning at 5am feeling like shit, so I can go to work.  This illness has also affected my brain apparently.    Let's try to press on though...  I have been on several dates lately, which is partly what is also contributing to my lack of sleep.  I must say it is a strange feeling.  It has been such a long time since I have been on a real date.  Let me rephrase that, it has been such a long time since I have been on a second real date with someone.  But that is not my real concern right now...  My real concern is that I've noticed that all my friends lately have been on a sort of "relationship-envy" phase.  That is a phase that I understand very well.    What bothers me the most is that all my friends let these things bother them.  They are all SUCH BEAUTIFUL people.  You know who I'm talking to...  You will never, ever have a problem with attracting people.  And I know for a fact that you will find someone who will realize how special you are.  I think the real concern that you all should have is helping your friend Ren out over here.  I feel like Frankenstein sometimes when it comes to attracting women.  "WHY DOESN'T ANYONE WANT TO PLAY WITH ME?  Mwaah.  Urrgh."  It really doesn't help with the ladies that I am barfing up a storm right now.  "Oooh Ren, you look so sexy with your green complexion.  Did you just vomit up a hot dog?  That is SOOOO hot!"  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just realized this morning how long it has been since I posted.  Let me sum up these past 10 days in one phrase:  "Lack of sleep."  I have not been getting my daily dose of sleep lately.  It's making me very sleepy, cranky, dopey, bashful, sneezy, and any other dwarf I can't think of.  But it case you want a little more from me I can tell you that you haven't missed much.  I've been on a few dates lately...  I lot more than I am used to.  But so far, nothing to run and tell mom about.  I did see that Farenheit 9/11 movie the other day.  It was good.  Very interesting and very enlightening since I never really had a definite opinion about the whole Bush thing.  I recommend that everyone sees it whether you are a Bush supporter or not.  You at least walk out of there feeling smarter.  Definitely looking a lot smarter than the people walking out of "White Chicks."  Anyway, I promise to keep a better job of posting more frequently...  once I get more sleep.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't think I will be able to post this weekend, so I want to take the time to tell everyone HAPPY 4th of JULY!  I hope everyone has a good weekend.  I know I will.  I get to hang out w/ Angela and Kathy this weekend.  Speaking of the two of them, they actually inspired the rest of this post...  I realized this after my conversations with the both of them from last night and this morning.  I'm assuming everyone at one point or another has had a headache.  DUH.  Have you ever noticed that when you get a headache, something about it affects your brain.  This headache MAKES you want to tell EVERYONE that you have a headache.  Not only that, you have to use this exact phrase:  "I have SUCH a headache right now."  No exceptions...  Also, when you do have a headache, you have to make sure that you tell the other person at least 5 times in the conversation that you do have a headache.  Here is Kathy and my conversation last night as an example:  Renan : I rode an elephant today.  Kathy : I have SUCH a headache right now.  Renan : Really?  That sucks.  Kathy : I hate my kids!  Why don't they understand that I have SUCH a headache right now.  Renan : Why the hell hasn't Angela called me yet?  It's already 9!  Kathy :  I dunno.  Does she know I have SUCH a headache right now?  Renan : Probably not.  I need to get a haircut.  Kathy : Yeah, probably a cool, MIL-tary style haircut (in a southern accent)  God, I have SUCH a headache right now.  Renan : I know, you told me.  Cool, Angela's calling me right now, I gotta go.    Kathy : Tell her to call me back and that I have SUCH a headache right now!  I hope you all see now what I'm talking about.  I will be conducting further research on this.    HAPPY BIRTHDAY AMERICA!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I feel like a monster... I'm all bandaged up because there is a possibility that I suffered a mild concussion last night. Here's what happened... if you don't care, too bad. I'm gonna tell you anyway:   I had just finished visiting China last night for her lunch. I was on my way home and I decided to stop by Target because I needed some new hangers for all my damn shirts. I have too many shirts! Anyway, I was walking thru the parking lot up to the entrance when this crazy lady cuts thru the parking spaces next to me. You know how when you want to get to the next lane quickly in a parking lot, you cut thru spaces? That's what she did. Well she cut's out right next to me and I turn and see that's she's about to hit me. She slams on her brakes and I put my arms out to kind of brace the impact. Well, she didn't really hit me that hard, but the force knocked me down. I ended up spraining my wrist and hitting my head as I hit the ground.  So I'm lying there on the floor (by the way, you really do see stars floating around your head just like a cartoon). I guess I was knocked out for a few minutes. Next thing I know there are a bunch of people standing around me. The paramedics get there shortly and they ask me all kinds of questions. "What's your name?" "Do you know where you are?" Blah, blah, blah. At this point I feel OK but they insist on taking me to the ER.  I'm in the ER (which I hate by the way) and the doctor checks me out. At this point I feel fine, but the doctor insists I may have suffered a mild concussion. So I go home after about 2 hours. At this point it's about 1am. The doctor tells me not to go to sleep and that I have to come back the next day.  So flash back to the present day, I am exhausted from lack of sleep and looking like a moron with all my bandages. Somebody shoot me! The worst part about it, is now I have to explain the story 100 times today because it's only obvious something happened when you look at me. Oh well! Gotta go, talk to everyone later. Hopefully a blimp doesn't hit me when I try to go home later today. "It kills over 1 Americans a year!"   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I'm sure you all have been asking yourselves that question, and I'm sure that you have tossed and turned at night not knowing what my whereabouts were. Well, for the past week I have been in Pennsylvania. Scranton, Pennsylvania to be exact. I had to travel to Scranton on "business." I say "business" because how much work did I really do? Unless of course you classify "business" as drinking heavily in dive bars, then I have told you nothing but the truth.      There are couple things that I learned from this whole experience... First of all, I am a city boy. Not only that, I am a California boy too. It's just so amazing the differences between Scranton and San Diego. Granted, San Diego isn't exactly what you may call a "big city" if you compare it to New York or Los Angeles. But hell, it sure is compared to Scranton. I have never seen so much green in one place my whole fuckin' life! They say that Scranton is so backwards compared to San Diego.      This leads me to my number 2 discovery... I am not white! Don't think that I'm stupid. This was a fact that I was always aware of my whole life. But being in Scranton sure did beat that point into the ground. Good God did I stick out like a sore thumb. I felt like a movie star with so many people staring at me. So I did what any normal person would do... I told everyone that I was that Asian dude in American Pie. MILF! MILF! MILF!      I am pretty tired right now from the time difference and now I am about to go to the airport to fly back home. So I will talk to everyone later. Like I said, you all can breathe easy now... Ren has returned!  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>