<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      S is for seriously fun U is for united as friends to spend this time together M is for MAGNIFICENT M is for MARVELOUS E is for energy needed R is for Radiant   ok now when you put those together you get SUMMER! oh yeah today was our last day of JUNIOR HIGH and when i say our i mean you-jamie, you-ariel, you-sara, you-holly and all you other YOUS! yep ok well i got to tell mrs. burchett goodbye and Mrs. Bozman but i forgot to give mrs. burchett her gift so i have a reason to spend the night at your house, Jamie. i am gonna go isketch for now, bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yesterday sara had a terrible incident...she got her leg caught in her bike and she hurt herself....poor poor sara...ok now to new business i got my pictures from my camera YAY! they are so funny looking i havent got to view all of them cuz they are downloading at this very instint...yep (on the other computer) they are almost finished...dod dodododo i have some pictures of my cat Bob on them...he wass such a cute cat...but he is dead now, cuz some crazy drunk ran over him with his car...DANG HIM! ok well i have to go study for a spanish exam! wahoo not
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HEY! i havent "blogged" in a while cuz i have been hanging out with real ppl. yeah well I got to see Shrek 2 on Friday...it was so funny:     I am wearing women's underwear [nose doesn't move]    I am not! [nose grows]    I am not wearing women's underwear! [nose grows]     .....    .....        IT'S A THONG!!!  haha such a funny movie. but i must say, dont take the little ones to see it. yeah so umm hey what is up? I FOUND THE CUTEST swimsuit today. it is red and white and it is so cute take a look at it:  http://www.newport-news.com/shop/subcat_twelve.asp?gpcatid=2012&pacatid=2013&subcatid=3425&catid=4895&isfeature=    it is the last swimsuit on that page! it is awesome...and CHEAP!!! wahooooooo yeah...ok so down to business ummmmmm well the business of today is ummm I CAN STICK THREE FINGERS IN MY EYE! jamie tells me that one day i will get four finger in my eye, i just cant wait for the day..............ok now if you have read jamie's blog you now i eat glue. it is really good. and it is non-toxic!!! it is puzzle glue. yummm......dont tell anyone about it though.... you never know who is looking/listening/watching etc........hey today during  second period i saw a guy that i had seen before. i saw him at sara's neighbors house and i remember sara and i moved his rail around the street. yeah those were the days. lalalalla i think having an online diary is fun cuz i can just type and type and type and type.....so fun!! wahooo ok yeah katie dear i must tell you that you and trevor need to stop fighting over the lipgloss...better yet STOP WEARING THE LIPGLOSS! yeah that will work yup....................got to go so see yall later...wait i forgot to tell you about Cardies. ok well cardies (i think that is how you spell it) well it is really cool it is a bar palce wear heavy metal bands go and play. yeah well my brother played there last night. they did really good so umm yeah they rock....ok umm it is dark and stuff and it had the gothic look to it but i dont see it as gothic i see it as WOW so awesome! wahooo ok well see ya later
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i am really bored. i am doing my geometry formula sheet cuz i have to, well not really HAVE to but i want to so that i will pass geometry so umm yeah. today i got a trophy from theatre it is a star thespian award. it is really pretty. yep yep yep....today i learned something...someone who cant be named hurt me! she made me so upset she seems to want to go to a party which i know she is gonna have a sucky time instead of hanging out with me. and she PROMISED me that she would spend the night on friday i was so mad. so so so so mad....but i am ok now...hopefully well it is nearing my goodbye so i guess i will see yall later! oh and a few words of advice:  hi, how are you! hi! hi! how are you? are you, hi, how are you! hi! hi! how are you? are you hi!   SEE YA  oh wait before i forget, today at the thespian party, it was almost over and some of us were still there and well Mo was sitting on a table and Brittany runs and jumps on him and then me being my wacky self go and jump on Brittany and then Jacoment being her crazy self jumped on me! it was so funny cuz we were all holding on for dear life trying to stay on top of one another it was SO funny! and the great thing is...WE GOT A PICTURE! yes me tfne got a picture of it. i just so had my camera handy and Alex just so happened to take the picture for us!! it is great! i shall post it when i get it. but for safety reasons i shant show thou faces. :D cheerio!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i am oh so very bored. i am so bored i almost started to say hi, how are you, hi hi how are u? are you hi how are you hi hi how are etc...those are the good ol days. ariel we are genius!!!! hhahahahahah my head hurtz oh so very bad...it is just like about to EXPLODE!!!....Jamie you were a weird kid........really weird......i am oh so very bored and oh so very worn. i need to do my geometry but i am in much paine (yes with an 'e') of the head...got to eat my hotdogs with ketchup see ya!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Hello everyone! how are yall today? i am just fine and dandy. i decided to get back and post blogs again because i friends at Wrestle Mania Co. told me too. yes i am talking about you holly, oh and you sara. yall are genius ppl even though jamie started hers first....well anyways today at lunch to tables were going to fight but mrs. carlton had to be weird and like mess it up. it would of been really funny if something happened. our school has a lot of fights.... A LOT OF FIGHTS....i have never been it one so i am glad to say...WEEE!! WAHOOOIEE!! WEEE!!! ok i am good now. i am really bored and so i am gonna ummm gonna....gonna show you all the sites on my favorites list....or not..i looked at my list and there was like 800000000 million of them! really i promise. ok well there is some confrontation going on so i am gonna go and settle it.. haha not i am gonna go and watch it and LAUGH..like this hahahahha  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well....i am waiting for the fone to ring cuz ariel is gonna call before she comes over here. i guess that is ok, i mean i can wait, i guess.....well i have had a nice summer, its been filled with:   jamie spending the night, family reunion, family reunion, family reunion, Todd's graduation, some of the puppies going missing, i got an air fern, wal-mart, biglots, cell fone place, walmart, cell fone place, waking up early, secondhand lions, playing with pictures, spending the night at katies, hanging out with trevor and katie, wearing different color socks, having a cell fone "on" at walmart, thinking about working out, tearing part of my shoes, losing a tooth, making a comic book page thing, wearing different color socks, talking on the fone, sleeping at night, making a newspaper thing, Billy running from Cops, Big Bird sighted, troy, virus on my computer, getting a fish for my aunt, going grocery shopping, messing up my fone   i cant remember what else right now i shall get back to ya! tata
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Now it is a new month. And what a great month it has been! i got a cell phone! which i can only use with other cingular customers oh and i can talk on nights and weekends for free. and and and well i already screwed the freakin' fone up. yep i was trying to get the stupid pin number fixed and it just felt like blocking my stupid card! GRRRR! it should be beaten.....yeah well i spent the night at katie's house a while back. and trevor spent the night too. it was fun. ok we slept upstairs(katie and myself) and trevor slept downstairs with a baby monitor i might add. ok well i wanna do something but i dont know what, maybe ariel wants to do something tonight...hmmm i am gonna go see tata for now!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>