<Blog>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It was a great day today!!! Got up, got the kids off to school then came home and played EQ for a bit, then just did some wonderful playing around! ;)  Think I liked that the best about today.  Long and slow, made me tingle all over.  I love that feeling, that and knowing that I made him feel satisified.  Then we did some running around, then back to the kids; but before I went to see the kids I started dinner (spareribs).  He loved them!!  I love knowing that I have completed the day with a dinner that satisified as well.  Tomorrow is movie day so I'm told.  We'll have to see about that.  I talked to a new friend today from AFF (Tom).  He'd like to meet, maybe tomorrow evening; we'll see - I have learned not to jump into anything at this point.  Dan talked to his attorny friend today and has a really good feeling about it - I am hoping for the best to come of it.  He (dan) is due for some good luck to come his way!!! He also got to talk to his kids tonight.  I could see and hear how much it ment to him.  He really misses them and I know how he must feel.  I miss not being with my kids and they just live a few miles away from me.  His are several states away.  I wish nothing but the best for him, I can think of no one that deserves it more.  Well, I think that's about it for one night. Off to bed, and hopefully no strange dreams tonight. I'll let you know tomorrow. 

						
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well thanks to a call to his attorny, we didn't have to go to court today.  But the worry is still there!! What next, we have to decide what our daughter will be doing this summer.    We have to sit down together soon and make some decissions in the divorce.  I'm not looking forward to it, but it has to be done.  The faster it's done the sooner it will end.  That's what I want is for it to be over with soon. 

						
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well today wasn't too bad, didn't do much of anything.  Didn't want to go out, but was told I had to go.  Went to friends of theirs for a birthday party >  don't really know them but really like their youngest daughter (smart cookie).  She and I had a good talk so the I wasn't bored stiff.  She's a very likeable  kid, has a good heart!  I guess I must do as everyone keeps telling me > take it one day @ a time and minute by minute; don't look to far ahead cause you might not get there!  Enjoy yourself and live each day as though it might be your last!!  

						
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This week has been rough, I didn't think that I would be like this!  I don't like the way that I feel and I'm so ashamed of myself for being like this.  I care so much for him and all I really want is for him to be happy - something I know he hasn't been in a long time!   First of all I want, no I need to remain his friend, and he mine.  If we're lovers then so be it, but he can not be expected to just be mine!  I won't do that to him, I have no right.  He is and shall always be his own person, to come and go as he pleases and with whom ever he pleases.  This is his life style and I must respect that and I must learn to deal with it or loose him!  That is what I am most afraid of is loosing him, loosing a true friend.  Someone I can talk to when everything is going wrong and I can find no where else to turn. When the world is crashing in on me, and I just want to give up.  To know that he's there cheering me on. That is what I'm really afraid of loosing.  I sit here typing this and I wonder if he knows how much he has changed my life.  If he can even begin to know, how frightened I am! How the thought of waking up and finding that I am again alone scares the hell out of me.  To be out in the world alone, maybe in a place of my own alone; I don't know if I can do it.  I know I have others counting on me and I know I have lots of other friends out there.  But the fact remains, I have know him before, and have lost him before.  And that fact haunts me every minute of every day - the not knowing when it will happen again and will I be able to show him just what he means to me.  Just how much and in how many ways he has changed my life?  I can't begin to imagine my life without him in it in some way, shape, or form!  To make him mad at me, cuts into my very soul.  And yet he encourages me to explore. To explore everything and everyone around me; how this must hurt him and yet it seems to excite him.  To see me going to meet someone else, he smiles, but what does that smile hide?  I wish that we could talk openly, without fear of her hearing and coming ungluded and being involved at all with us.  Would it be easier if we had a place of our own?  I don't know - I think yes because then we could do things together if we wanted, there would be no fear.  How I long for that day to come when she won't be here and we will have a place of our own.  If I can hold it together until then and not drive him away from me with this silly childishness!  I am trying so hard not to be jelious of him when he is with someone else.  I didn't think I would be like this - all I want is for him to be happy - it's just so hard when I know he is in the next room and I wonder how she is kissing him, touching him - does she make him feel things that I can't?!  Should I be doing something differently to please him? Is she a better lover than I am??  Can she complete him in ways I never thought of ?  I may never know the answers to any of these questions; what I do know is that I have to be honest with myself and with him - YES, I AM JELIOUS!  and it's stupid to be this way!!!  So it stops here tonight, as I write these words - I end that feeling and will talk of it no more.  D - YOU ARE FREE TO LIVE YOUR LIFE, BE HAPPY AND LIVE LONG MY FRIEND!!!  I SHALL NOT STAND IN THE WAY OF YOUR HAPPINESS - I WILL NOT BE THE ROCK THAT TAKES YOU UNDER.  I HAVE NO RIGHT TO PUT UP WALLS AROUND A FREE SPIRIT!  YOU CAME INTO MY LIFE FREELY AND YOU WILL LEAVE IT THAT WAY.  LIVE LONG AND WELL AND KNOW THAT I WILL TREASURE YOU FOREVER AS A TRUE FRIEND! 

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I don't know if I can describe it this feeling that I have been having for a while now > a feeling of not belonging!  Not really sure what it is, don't think it has anything to do with being on or off my meds; it's just really strange.  A feeling of having over stayed my welcome, of being somewhere that I'm not suppose to be!  Very errie and ominous; like the next step I take will cause something terrible to happen.  I hate the not knowing and the feeling of dread that I have.  I can't explain it; although everyone around me thinks it's because of the new job, I don't think that's it at all.  I think it's something bigger, I just don't know what or when this thing will happen.  I hate the waiting, the not knowing what is going to happen.  I'm trying hard to keep my mind clear and not think about it but like a bad dream it keeps coming back to haunt me and it keeps getting stronger and more ominous.  Well I guess I'll just have to let it happen and deal with it at that time.  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well I just got my notice and I got certified!!!  So I guess it's ok; although I'm still not sure about this, but I guess I have to try this.  But I'm still thinking about moving out.  I'm just not sure about this working and living together; I not sure about a lot of things right now.  I'll give it a couple of weeks but I don't know if I can handle it for long.  

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Just waiting to see if I passed my certification and it's killing me!!! My stomach is killing me and my nerves are shot!  I feel like I need to do something but not sure what or with who.  Not that there's anyone who would want to do anything with me.  I have that lost feeling again > not knowing what to do or where to go.  Thinking about moving again not sure that this is really the right place for me any more.  Now with what's happening with D.  I think he needs more space and with me here all the time; I just think it's cramping his style.  I think that if I don't get this job I will be moving. I'm just not sure where I'll go yet; I just don't think I can handle it here.  I'm  feeling so boxed in and so alone!  I feel like I have lost my best friend.  So close and yet so very far away.  BUT THERE AGAIN THAT OR SHOULD I SAY THIS IS MY LIFE!!  come what may I guess I have to take what comes my way.  

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well not much happened today, sleep for most of it.  Back on my meds, so didn't really feel like doing a lot.  I don't think I'd have felt like doing much weather I was on my meds or not > just haven't wanted to do much or be around anyone.  Not sleeping well, keep having this dream that really boths me.   Tomorrow starts another week of trainning and I'm a bit worried about that too.  Everyone tells me I'll do fine, but I'm not so sure.  This is different from anything I've ever done before, as far as work is concerened.  Not sure where this will lead, but that's life I guess.  The unknown, day to day.  

						
</post>


</Blog>