<Blog>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Germs         What are germs?    Germs are tiny organisms that creep into our bodies and attack our immune system.  Unable to live on their own, germs invade our bodies and steal the nutrients and energy that our bodies produce. After gobbling up all of our nutrients and vitamins the germs leave behind their own harmful wastes called toxins. These toxins are the sources of our runny noses, high fevers, diarrhea and hoarse coughs.  Think back to the last time you were sick. Did you have a fever, runny nose, stomach ache, or throw-up often? Did you have to visit your doctor? Did you need medicine to help you get better.  Well… did you ever wonder why or how you became sick? Chances are that germs were the source of your illness.  There are many different kinds of germs, but the four most common are: bacteria, viruses, fungi and protozoa. Each of these types of germs cause different symptoms or illnesses. For instance, while bacteria germs cause minor illnesses such as ear infections, sore throats and cavities, viruses cause more serious diseases such as chicken pox, measles and the flu.  Although germs are everywhere, most of the time we don't realize that we have germs because they are so small that you need a microscope to see them. Germs spread through the air when someone coughs or sneezes. Or germs can also appear in bodily fluids like saliva, sweat and blood. The best way to avoid getting germs is stay away from these areas where germs spread. But the most easiest way to protect yourself from germs is to wash your hands with soap and water frequently. You should always soap up your hands with suds after using the bathroom, after touching money, after playing outside or after visiting a sick      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday the 13th         Why is Friday the 13th considered unlucky?   One of the most commonly held superstitions in our so-called civilized, educated society is that Friday the 13th is an unlucky day, and since, in this equation, each is held to be unlucky, added together, their sum can only equal double trouble.  The modern basis for the aura that surrounds Friday the 13th stems from Friday October the 13th, 1307. On this date, the Pope of the church in Rome in Conjunction with the King of France, carried out a secret death warrant Against "the Knights Templar". The Templars were terminated as heretics, never again to hold the power that they had held for so long. There Grand Master, Jacques DeMolay, was arrested and before he was killed, was tortured and crucified.  Superstitions swirling around Friday as being lucky or unlucky have existed since ancient times, beginning with the northern nations. Ancient Romans dedicated the sixth day of the week to their beautiful, but vain, goddess Venus, so, when the Norsemen adopted the Roman method of naming days, they naturally adopted Venus as their name for the sixth day of the week. Their closest translation for Venus, Frigg, or Freya, eventually evolved into Friday, a day they considered to be the luckiest day of the week.  From a religious standpoint, Muslims tout Friday as the day Allah created Adam, legend has it that Adam and Eve ate the forbidden fruit, the apple, on a Friday, and later died on a Friday, and Christians consider Friday as the day on which Christ was crucified by the Romans.  The Scandinavian belief that the number 13 signified bad luck sprang from their mythological 12 demigods, who were joined by a 13th demigod, Loki, an evil cruel one, who brought upon humans great misfortune. The number 13, in the Christian faith, is the number of parties at the Last Supper, with the 13th guest at the table being the traitor, Judas. When Christians combine this day and number, the combination can only hold special significance.  Whether or not a person considers Friday the 13th as unlucky, he or she must understand that this superstition, as well as others, merely stem from beliefs or practices man used, and continues to use, to explain, and to protect himself, from events beyond his control in his complicated world. He worked, and works only with the bag of knowledge he has on hand.  Only when factual, scientific bases for these beliefs are unearthed, and people do not dispel the beliefs, but instead cling to them, the beliefs become superstitions. Today's beliefs may very well be tomorrows superstitions.      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday the 13th         Why is Friday the 13th considered unlucky?   One of the most commonly held superstitions in our so-called civilized, educated society is that Friday the 13th is an unlucky day, and since, in this equation, each is held to be unlucky, added together, their sum can only equal double trouble.  The modern basis for the aura that surrounds Friday the 13th stems from Friday October the 13th, 1307. On this date, the Pope of the church in Rome in Conjunction with the King of France, carried out a secret death warrant Against "the Knights Templar". The Templars were terminated as heretics, never again to hold the power that they had held for so long. There Grand Master, Jacques DeMolay, was arrested and before he was killed, was tortured and crucified.  Superstitions swirling around Friday as being lucky or unlucky have existed since ancient times, beginning with the northern nations. Ancient Romans dedicated the sixth day of the week to their beautiful, but vain, goddess Venus, so, when the Norsemen adopted the Roman method of naming days, they naturally adopted Venus as their name for the sixth day of the week. Their closest translation for Venus, Frigg, or Freya, eventually evolved into Friday, a day they considered to be the luckiest day of the week.  From a religious standpoint, Muslims tout Friday as the day Allah created Adam, legend has it that Adam and Eve ate the forbidden fruit, the apple, on a Friday, and later died on a Friday, and Christians consider Friday as the day on which Christ was crucified by the Romans.  The Scandinavian belief that the number 13 signified bad luck sprang from their mythological 12 demigods, who were joined by a 13th demigod, Loki, an evil cruel one, who brought upon humans great misfortune. The number 13, in the Christian faith, is the number of parties at the Last Supper, with the 13th guest at the table being the traitor, Judas. When Christians combine this day and number, the combination can only hold special significance.  Whether or not a person considers Friday the 13th as unlucky, he or she must understand that this superstition, as well as others, merely stem from beliefs or practices man used, and continues to use, to explain, and to protect himself, from events beyond his control in his complicated world. He worked, and works only with the bag of knowledge he has on hand.  Only when factual, scientific bases for these beliefs are unearthed, and people do not dispel the beliefs, but instead cling to them, the beliefs become superstitions. Today's beliefs may very well be tomorrows superstitions.      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rubber         What is Rubber?   Rubber is a sticky, elastic solid produced from a milky liquid called "latex," which has different properties than the sap found in trees. Although latex is found in the bark, roots, and stems, branches, leaves, and fruit of over 400 different plants and trees, the bulk is found, and extracted, from the inner bark of the branches, and from the trunk, of the rubber tree. Quite simply, it would not be cost-effective to extract the latex from rubber producing plants, such as the dandelion, the milkweed, and the sagebrush. Just visualize some poor soul laboring over one of these with a syringe!  Rubber, derived from the gum of a tree, has existed since prehistoric times. For example, fossils of rubber-producing plants date back almost 3,000,000 years. Crude rubber balls, discovered in ruins of ancient Incan and Mayan civilizations in Central and in South America, are, at very least, 900 years old. Natives of Southeastern Asia used rubber, prepared from the "juice" of trees to waterproof their baskets and jars. Even Columbus, on his second voyage to the New World, observed Haitian natives playing with balls made from "the gum of a tree."  Latex consists of tiny particles of liquid, solid, or semi-fluid material, that appears in the form of a watery liquor, not to be drunk! The breakdown on this watery liquid is only about 33% rubber, with the remainder being, not surprisingly, water! When the rubber particles in the latex join together, they form a ball of rubber.  Rubber producing plants grow best within 10 degrees of the Equator, where the climate is hot and moist, and the soil is deep and rich. For this reason, the area of about 700 miles on each side of the Equator is known as the "Rubber Belt." Brazil, from whence the best, and top-producing rubber tree hails, is firmly planted within the Rubber Belt. This Latino tree with a Latin name, Hevea brasiliensis, produces approximately 96% of the world's supply of natural rubber, and now is cultivated in other Rubber Belt countries.  Most likely, the French, prior to the 1800s, were the first white men to take advantage of rubbers' elasticity. They manufactured "rubber bands" for use with their garters and their suspenders, to help to keep their pants up. Rubber belts did not exist at that time.     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The smallest country         What is the smallest country?   Size is not a criterion in our definition of what constitutes a country. A country need only be an independent state, with distinct territorial boundaries, and its own government. This is a true blessing for Vatican City, as, weighing in at a mere 0.17 miles, it holds the title of being the smallest country in the world.  Prior to 1870, however, political control by papal governments in central Italy spanned approximately 16.000 square miles. In 1870, the Kingdom of Italy, in a shift of political power, established Rome as the national capital of Italy, wrested political power from the papal governments, and absorbed the so-called "Papal States" into its territory.   A 1929 Agreement hammered out by the Italian government and the Pope, established Vatican City as a country... all 0.17 square miles of it! Gradually the country has gained recognition as such, by establishing diplomatic ties with other countries, and by receiving dignitaries from other nations.  Vatican City is the official seat of the Catholic Church, and its head, the Pope, rules through a civil governor. As with any other country, this miniature country sports its own flag, coins its own coins, runs its own postal, transportation, telephone systems, and radio broadcasting station. Vatican City is all grown up.  This pint-size powerhouse of a country primarily supports itself through contributions from Catholics around the world, and through tourism. Safely ensconced within Vatican City lie some of the worlds' most precious of treasures; the Gardens, St. Peter's Basilica, and the Vatican Palace, which houses the Vatican Library, and...the Pope himself.     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      US national emblem         Why is the Eagle the national emblem of the United States?   In 1782, US Congress selected the bald eagle as the emblem of the newly formed United States, because it symbolized courage and might, and because it was indigenous only to the United States and to Canada.  The national seal depicts the bald eagle with its wings spread, with one claw clutching an olive branch, and the other claw grasping arrows. The eagle, however, strikes different poses on other national depictions.  The bald eagle owes its name to the early American colonists, and is bald in name only. As the white-headed American eagle differed from the European gray eagle, the colonists used their word for white, which translated into bald, in describing it. Unfortunately for the eagle, the literal translation, bald-headed, stuck like a toupee.  Since ancient times, men have identified themselves with the eagle, because it creates an impression of majesty and of power while in flight. As early as 5,000 years ago, ancient Sumerians chose the eagle, in spread eagle form, as their emblem symbolizing their power. Ancient Romans followed suit, as did Emperor Charlemagne, and finally Napoleon. No doubt, Congress considered the eagle's historical pedigree as being the animal representing a nation's power, when selecting it to be the national emblem of the United States.     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hot dogs          What are hot dogs made of?   Are hot dogs really made from pigs' snouts and unused meat scraps? Contrary to popular belief, hot dogs are not made from left-over meat laying around on the floors of meat-packing houses. Whether it is pork or beef that is stuffed into a hot dog, the meat trimmings are carefully selected just like the meat you buy in your grocer's coolers.  Most recipes for hot dogs combine together a tasty blend of favorite meats (pork, beef, chicken, or turkey), meat fat, a cereal filler which could be either bread crumbs, flour, or oatmeal, a little bit of egg white, and a mouth-watering array of herbs and seasonings including garlic, pepper, ground mustard, nutmeg, salt, and onion.   Once these ingredients are grinded together, the stuffing is squeezed into sausage casings. Many of the hot dogs sold in stores are enclosed in synthetic cellulose casings, but most home-made hot dogs are made out of natural animal intestines.   Following the stuffing process is the pre-cooking cycle in which the hot dog links are tossed into boiling water for approximately 15 minutes. Finally, the dogs are packaged, loaded on delivery trucks, and sent off to food markets.  Hot dogs are popular among Americans because they are easy to make, inexpensive, and delicious.   What is your favorite type of hot dog? - a chili dog, a cheese dog, or a foot-long dog? A multitude of toppings can enhance the flavor of your hot dog. Common toppings used on hot dogs include ketchup, mustard, onions, relish, chili, cheese, and sauerkraut.      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blue Jeans         Why are Blue Jeans traditionally sewn with Orange thread?   The orange thread traditionally used to sew Levi Strauss blue jeans was intentionally selected to match the copper rivets that doubled the durability of the jeans.  Levi Strauss, however, neither envisioned this particular use for copper riveting, which the orange thread complemented, nor the unique stitching on the rear pockets of the jeans.   Jacob Davis, a Russian immigrant, and a tailor, who plied his trade in Reno, Nevada, formulated the idea for the riveted seam, an idea that would vastly extend the life of the jeans, and would revolutionize the garment industry. Alas, due to financial constraints, Jacob could neither afford to obtain a patent for his invention, nor to produce the new garment.  Out of necessity, Jacob approached the wholesaler he purchased his denim from with a proposal that he sell him the West Coast rights to the riveted blue jeans, in exchange for the $68 required to obtain a patent for them. The wholesaler whom accepted Jacob's proposition was none other than Levi Strauss.  Levi gave Jacob a position with his Company in 1873 and, during his tenure, Jacob ensured that the orange thread be used in all stitching on the jeans, and that the curved, formally named "arcuate," stitches adorn the     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Dizzy         What makes people dizzy when they spin?   Rolling down a hill or spinning around in endless circles causes dizziness or vertigo because hair-like sensory nerve cells in our ears send wrong messages to our brain.  The motions of our bodies are detected by the vestibular system found in the upper part of our inner ear. The vestibular system senses whether we are standing up or lying down.  When we spin in circles or get up too fast from the couch, we feel dizzy and lightheaded due to the vestibular system's nerve reactions to these unusual motions.   Here's how our vestibular system reacts to a slight change in direction when we bend our heads: The vestibular system senses motion through three semicircular canals that are at right angles to one another. Not only do these canals have hair-like sensory nerve cells, but they also contain a fluid called endolymph.  Following the principle of inertia, endolymph resists changes in motion. As a result of this resistance, the endolymph lags behind and stimulates hair cells to send nerve signals to the brain. Our brain interprets the nerve messages and knows which direction the head moved.  However, when we spin, our brain receives mixed messages. The endolymph slowly begins to move in the same direction we are spinning. As time goes by, the endolymph catches up to the rate of speed we are spinning and no longer stimulates the hair-like nerve cells. This causes our brain to quickly adapt to the nerve signals. However, when we stop spinning, the endolymph continues to move and stimulates hair cells in the opposite direction.  These hair cells send wrong messages to the brain making it think that the head is still spinning although it actually has stopped. As a result of this inaccurate signal, we experience dizziness. Eventually, the endolymph stops moving and no more signals are sent to the brain. The brain interprets that the spinning motion has ceased and the dizziness disappears.     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gray hair          Why does hair turn gray?   Hair goes gray because pigment cells in the hair base at the roots of the hair stop producing melanin.  It doesn't matter if you are fair-haired or dark-haired you have the same chances of getting gray hair. However, it is more noticeable in darker haired people.  Graying of the hair generally starts at the age of around 30 for males and 35 for females however since the onset of this phenomena varies greatly from person to person, age is not the most accurate indicator.  The graying of hair appears to be genetically determined but the connection isn't at all clear.  So for now, your hair turning gray is just one of those mysteries of science that we have yet to solve. But salt and pepper hair always did look distinguish     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yawn         Why do we yawn?   The truth is that we don't completely understand why people, or animals for that matter, yawn.  It's widely assumed that yawning occurs because we are tired or bored or because we see someone else doing it, but there isn't any hard evidence to support these beliefs.  Scientists do not purport to know all of the biological mechanisms of the yawn, but tend to agree that a yawn is an involuntary respiratory reflex, which regulates the carbon dioxide and oxygen levels in the blood.  Technically, a yawn is the reflex opening of the mouth followed by the deep inhalation and slow exhalation of oxygen.  The very act of yawning is but one of a number of involuntary reflexes controlled by the spinal and nerve centers.  Scientists speculate that the onset of a yawn is triggered either by fatigue, or by sheer boredom as, at those times, breathing is shallow, and little oxygen is carried to the lungs by the oxygen-toting cardiovascular system.  When one yawns, his or her alertness is heightened, as the sudden intake of oxygen increases the heart rate, rids the lungs and the bloodstream of the carbon dioxide buildup, and forces oxygen through blood vessels in the brain, while restoring normal breathing and ventilating the lungs.  This quite plausible theory of yawning falls short of explaining many aspects of yawning. Scientists explain away the "contagious" nature of yawning, that is when one person's yawn triggers another nearby to yawn, as due to the power of suggestion, but are at a loss when attempting to explain why yawning occurs excessively in patients with lower brainstem damage or with multiple sclerosis.      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Helium balloon         How does a helium balloon float?   Helium is lighter than air and just as the heaviest things will tend to fall to the bottom, the lightest things will rise to the top.  Helium weighs 0.1785 grams per liter. Nitrogen, which makes up 80% of the air we breathe, weighs 1.2506 grams per liter.  Basically, if you were to fill a soda bottle with helium and another with air, the one filled with helium would weigh a gram less than the bottle with air. It doesn't sound like a lot, but that's usually why balloons are usually really big, the one-gram difference really adds up in large volumes. Helium balloons follow the same principle as you do when you float in the water; the law of buoyancy. If the water you displace weighs more than you do, you will float.   Helium isn't the lightest element, hydrogen, weighing a mere 0.08988 grams per liter, is.  Wondering why we don't use that instead of helium?  Well, hydrogen balloons used to be really popular, but it is extremely flammable. The slightest spark will set off a huge explosion.   Did you know?   Helium is a colorless, odorless, tasteless inert gas at room temperature and makes up about 0.0005% of the air we breathe.   Helium's principal source is natural gas wells where it is extracted from the crude natural gas stream and purified and that it can be stored and shipped either as a gas or a cryogenic liquid.     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why do halogen light bulbs last longer?   Hot-burning "halogen bulbs" can last two or three times longer than regular bulbs because they are filled with chemically active halogen gases that preserve the filament.  The filament of an ordinary light bulb burns out because atoms of tungsten evaporate from its surface, so that it becomes thinner and thinner until it breaks. The evaporated tungsten is deposited on the inside surface of the bulb, where it forms a dark deposit.  The gas inside a halogen bulb combines with the tungsten atoms that condense on the glass, removing the deposit. When the combined molecules touch the hot filament, the tungsten is redeposited there, and the gas is released to do the same trick again.  A halogen bulb is often 10 to 20 percent more efficient than an ordinary incandescent bulb of similar voltage, wattage, and life expectancy. Halogen bulbs may also have two to three times as long a lifetime as ordinary bulbs, sometimes also with an improvement in efficiency of up to 10 percent.      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why doesn't an igloo melt inside?   The igloo, a temporary winter hunting shelter to the Alaskan Eskimo does, in fact, melt inside, but not to a great extent.  The snowflakes falling outside of the igloo, in the harsh Alaskan winter, quickly melt when they land on its roof, and provide a replacement layer of insulation for the igloo. The ongoing freezing and re-freezing of the igloo, hardens it, and transforms the blocks of snow the Eskimos used in the construction process into a solid, icy, domed refuge. The igloo can now withstand the weight of a massive polar bear, should one happen along and have the urge to play "king of the mountain."  The initial freezing and re-freezing of the igloo takes place at end of the igloo's construction. First, the men must dig a trench into a fresh snow- drift, and, using their knives, cut blocks of snow from it that are specifically shaped to face inward when fully laid out. They then lay the blocks on their edges to form a circle, cutting them to size as they go, so that the end result will be a narrowing spiral. They cap the igloo by dropping a keystone, or block with edges cut wider above than below, into the remaining gap in the roof, and "grout" the gaps between blocks of snow with additional snow.  The men then call in the resident expert, the Eskimo woman, to put the finishing touches on the igloo. Armed with her whale blubber lamp, she enters the structure, lights her lamp to the highest possible setting, beats a hasty retreat, and seals the entrance with a block of ice. Inside the igloo, the snow on the roof begins to melt but, because of its domed design, the water melts down the sides of the igloo, and soaks the blocks of snow. When the blocks are almost completely saturated with water, the Eskimo woman returns, douses her blubber lamp, and allows the frigid outside air to rush in, transforming the fragile snow structure into one of hard, solid ice.  The igloo is now prepared for its temporary tenants, whose body heat, combined with the warmth of one to two blubber lamps, maintain its interior at approximately 55°F. Not until the winter ends, and the exterior temperature rises, does the igloo begin to melt.      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bananas         Why do bananas get bruised as they age?     Liken the black spots on bananas to the liver spots on mature adult, they appear with age, even if they go untouched. The hormone ethylene, a ripening agent found in the skin of the banana, transforms a green banana into the appealing yellow fruit we purchase at the market.  Ethylene, however, continues the ripening process, which gives the banana a "bruised" appearance, and eventually turns the banana black in color. There is no switch to turn off this process, but by placing the banana in a cool place, one can slow the process. The refrigerator is no place for a banana, because this is certain to blacken it prematurely. The cold air, to which the banana is exposed, causes the production of blackening compounds known as polyphenols.  Did you know?   In North America more bananas are eaten every day than any other fruit.   Bananas aren't grown on trees. They're part of the lily family, a cousin of the orchid, nothing but a very yellow and plump member of the herb family. With stalks 25 feet high, they're the largest plant on earth without a woody stem.   The word banana is African, though, a word carried to the New World by Portuguese slave traders. In Alexander the Great's time, bananas were called "pala" in Athens.   North America got its first taste of the tropical fruit in 1876 at the Philadelphia Centennial Exhibition. Each banana was wrapped in foil and sold for 10 cents.    note:   hormone: 荷尔蒙 ethylene: 乙烯 ripening agent: 催熟剂               polyphenol: 多酚         lily family: 百合科 orchid: 兰花       
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Halogen light bulbs         Why do halogen light bulbs last longer?   Hot-burning "halogen bulbs" can last two or three times longer than regular bulbs because they are filled with chemically active halogen gases that preserve the filament.  The filament of an ordinary light bulb burns out because atoms of tungsten evaporate from its surface, so that it becomes thinner and thinner until it breaks. The evaporated tungsten is deposited on the inside surface of the bulb, where it forms a dark deposit.  The gas inside a halogen bulb combines with the tungsten atoms that condense on the glass, removing the deposit. When the combined molecules touch the hot filament, the tungsten is redeposited there, and the gas is released to do the same trick again.  A halogen bulb is often 10 to 20 percent more efficient than an ordinary incandescent bulb of similar voltage, wattage, and life expectancy. Halogen bulbs may also have two to three times as long a lifetime as ordinary bulbs, sometimes also with an improvement in efficiency of up to 10 percent.      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahmed Chalabi         U.S. Aids Raid on Home of Chalabi   Iraqi police backed by U.S. soldiers on Thursday raided the home of Ahmed Chalabi, a Governing Council member who was once the Pentagon's pick to run postwar Iraq. Officials later said they were seeking 15 people, including at least one member of Chalabi's Iraqi National Congress, on charges including fraud and kidnapping.  In coordinated searches, U.S. troops seized computers, files and dozens of rifles from two offices of the Iraqi National Congress, a coalition of political parties that opposed former president Saddam Hussein. Boot prints marked several doors kicked down in the raids, which included a top-to-bottom search of the INC intelligence center that U.S. authorities once turned to for help in searching for former top Hussein officials and weapons of mass destruction.  A visibly agitated Chalabi told reporters after the raids that they were retribution for his increasingly strident criticism of the American management of post-Hussein Iraq. "I call to liberate the Iraqi people and get back our complete sovereignty," he said, speaking in English, "and I am raising these issues in a way that the Americans don't like."  But Hussein Muathin, a judge with the Central Criminal Court of Iraq, said the raids were part of an investigation into such crimes as the detaining and torturing of people, theft of government cars and illegal seizure of government facilities. Eight people, including Aras Habib, Chalabi's security and intelligence chief, have been declared fugitives. Chalabi was not charged.  U.S. and Iraqi officials said that the arrest orders originated in the Iraqi justice system, and that senior U.S. occupation officials did not know about the warrants until they were served.  The raids appeared to complete Chalabi's fall from grace in the eyes of U.S. officials over the last difficult year of the occupation. In recent weeks, occupation authorities have cut off a $335,000 monthly subsidy to the INC's intelligence arm and have pursued an investigation focusing on alleged fraud against government agencies by Sabah Nouri, a Chalabi aide who served as the anti-corruption chief at the Ministry of Finance.  This pressure comes as occupation officials are preparing to hand limited authority to Iraqis on June 30 and oppose a government role for such former allies as Chalabi.   The raids alarmed other members of the U.S.-appointed Governing Council, several of whom called on the United States to apologize to Chalabi immediately. "Doing such a thing to a Governing Council member proves that they do not acknowledge this council, which they formed and appointed," said Songul Chapouk, a council member and women's rights activist. "This is an insult to this council."       
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It turned out that the sourcing was inaccurate and wrong and, in some cases, deliberately misleading," Powell said on NBC's "Meet the Press" program. "And for that I am disappointed, and I regret it."    Powell made the US case against Iraq in a February 3, 2003, presentation to the UN Security Council in which he highlighted an Iraqi defectors "firsthand descriptions" of mobile biological weapons factories.    Although never publicly named, the defector has been identified in US press reports as the brother of one of Chalabi's top aides.  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       AFP Photo   GIs, Iraq Police Raid Home of Former Ally  (AP) - Iraqi police backed by American soldiers raided the home and offices Thursday of Ahmad Chalabi, a prominent Iraqi politician and a Pentagon favorite once groomed as a possible replacement for Saddam Hussein. Authorities made several arrests and seized documents and computers. Reporters who visited the offices of Chalabi's political organization saw scattered documents on the marble floors, ripped-off cables and overturned furniture. A portrait of Chalabi hanging on the wall in his home had a bullet hole in the forehead. More... 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      我又看见出国的丁丁和小胡在加拿大校园里绿绿的草坪上和朋友烧烤的照片。或许，他们的生活尚有许多艰难，但是他们靠在一起的笑容，那么放松，那么坦然。   我看见新婚的大学同学写的留言。他们只是普通得不能再普通的一对新人——不太穷也不太富有，两个人工作着，生活着，安安静静的度过着。   我看着曾经不被我们看好的他和她走过红地毯有了自己的家，不管他们的未来是不是被看好，他们总算走出第一步，而且，现在，他们过得很好。   我看着曾经不被你看好的另一对他和她同样尘埃落定，开始踏踏实实的经营起以后的日子。   我看见各种各样的幸福，只没有我们的。   难道真的，幸福总是可望不可及吗？  如果爱情只有折磨才美，我宁愿不要了。我只想要属于我的，只属于我自己的幸福生活啊。  可是幸福的定义又是什么呢？没有爱情会有幸福吗？没有你会有爱情吗？有了你就会有幸福吗？   齐豫的歌又在耳边：放弃多少才算贤淑？保留多少才算让步？迷人的是忠诚还是背叛？幸福是自由还是牵绊？  那么多的问题，谁来解呢？  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      猪肉忌荞麦、鸽肉、鲫鱼、黄豆； 羊肉忌醋； 狗肉忌蒜； 鲫鱼忌芥菜、猪肝； 猪血忌黄豆； 猪肝忌荞麦、豆酱、鲤鱼肠子、鱼肉； 鲤鱼忌狗肉； 龟肉忌苋菜、酒、果； 鳝鱼忌狗肉、狗血； 雀肉忌猪肝； 鸭蛋忌桑椹子、李子； 鸡肉忌芥末、糯米、李子； 鳖肉忌猪肉、兔肉、鸭肉、苋菜、鸡蛋。   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      夏季“无病三分虚”补养身体正当时              　　越胖越怕热，动一动就汗湿全身。虽有空调，但到了夏天还是热得喘气，浑身无力；为消暑解渴，大量冰镇食物下肚后，胃难受、拉肚子；而心脑血管病人在夏季闷热潮湿的气候常感憋气、胸闷、疲乏无力、头痛……怎样才能消除上述夏季征候群？专业人士认为，注意调补正气，改善体质，就能有效截断夏季病乘体虚而入的途径。    　　夏季是人体出汗多，体力消耗最大的一个季节。为消暑解热，人们在夏季里会有一些特定的饮食、生活习惯，容易导致各种暑病的发生。除日长夜短、天气炎热的诱因外，人体自身的抵抗力下降也是很重要的因素。  　　临床资料证明，夏季由于饮食不当、劳累过度等很容易引发各种暑病，导致体质下降而无法适应炎热天气，严重的会影响到心脑血管功能。可见，体虚为夏病之本。体虚了就应调养和滋补，中医理论认为，在各种生命活动较为亢进、能量与营养物质被大量消耗的夏季，人体更需因时清补。  　　少吃冰食保肠胃  　　为在夏天避暑解热，冷饮、凉拌菜成了人们最喜爱的夏季食物，但很多人在吃了这些冷菜后，出现呕吐、腹胀、饱满等症状。市二医院消化内科蹇贻副主任医师介绍，无论是冰镇的饮料还是啤酒，过多饮用不但会损伤脾胃，还会诱发腹痛、腹泻等疾患，引起胃肠道炎症，饮用应适量。  　　为防止夏季胃肠道疾患的发生，炎热季节必须讲究饮食调节，养成良好、卫生的饮食习惯：膳食最好现做现吃，生吃瓜果要洗净消毒；在做凉拌菜时，应加蒜泥和醋，既可调味，又能杀菌，且增进食欲。饮食不可过度贪凉，以防病原微生物趁虚而入。此外，亦可进食一些绿豆粥、荷叶粥等有一定驱暑生津功效的“解暑药粥”；还应多喝水，注意盐分和维生素的补充。  　　养心安神防“内火”  　　人体在夏季高温的环境中，特别容易疲倦，尤其是大汗后多有四肢软弱、神疲无力、胸闷气急、能量不足等感觉。此外，夏季高温时人的某些神经机能，如机体的注意力、运动协调能力、判断反应速度会明显降低，经常出现夜寐不安、头重足轻、心烦意躁、智力减退等神经系统功能紊乱的症状。  　　“空调病”、作息时间的改变等都是导致人体神经系统功能紊乱从而产生心火、肺火、胃火、肝火和肾火的“内火”原因。在温度降低、湿度增高、传热加快的空调环境里，人体体温调节和免疫功能会失常。此外，由于夏季日长夜短，很多人因乘凉或其它原因而改变了以往的作息时间，使体内原有的正常代谢节律受到干扰，因疲劳而“内火旺盛”。中医认为，除对症服用一些“消火”药物外，人自身调节作息、休养身心也是防“内火”的有效措施。  　　心脑血管病人喝点“酒”  　　虽然心脑血管疾病在冬季发病率最高，但夏季大量的出汗会使血液浓缩，血液粘稠，流速减慢，心脑内已狭窄的动脉更容易发生缺血。因此，在夏季防治心脑血管疾病也是非常重要的。据成都市青羊区人民医院脑血管科主任周世喜介绍，五一大假期间，为期七天的“免费检测心脑血管疾病暨喝‘酒’”活动在该院举行。  　　数百名市民参加了这次活动，其中年龄最大的 87岁，最小的 24岁，这表明心脑血管疾病患者增长速度加快，并且有年轻化的趋势，必须引起人们的高度重视。然而目前治疗心脑血管疾病的方法大多很单一，一般是输血液，扩张一下血管，疏通一下血脉就完事，治标不治本。直到近年，医学界将治疗“心脑血管系统”与“肾系统”结合起来，进行同步修复和双向激活，开创了心脑血管疾病与补肾同治、互治的全新模式，实现了异病同治。  　　心脑血管疾病的病人能否喝酒一直广受争议。越来越多的专家经过研究后发现，适量喝一些低浓度的酒，有活血、通脉的作用。北京一教授也说过，“少量的酒是朋友，过量的酒是罪魁祸首”。正因如此，传统中医在治疗心脑血管疾病上引进了这一先进的理念，将中药制成酒剂型，这样一来，不但能活血化瘀，同时也达到强肾、通脉的功效，使心脑血管疾病的治疗收到事半功倍的效果。  　　目前走俏市场的通脉强肾酒正是采用这一原理，集通脉、强肾于一身，治疗心脑血管疾病收到良好的效果。日前从成都市第一人民医院传来消息， 5月 13日晚上，医院接到 3名突发心肌梗塞的病人，并连夜为患者做了手术。市一医院提醒广大市民：在夏季一定要注意心脑血管疾病的预防和治疗，特别是中老年人，在盛夏湿热季节更要注重防暑除湿、饮食起居，并及时补充水分，减少心脑血管病的猝发率。   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sss上班族运动“悠着点”      HEALTH.SOHU.COM  2004年5月20日10:11  作者: 邹宁 彭炜  来源: 新华网           　　有关专家提醒上班族，偶尔运动要谨防身体损害。  　　李平是一名公务员，上周末，他与老同学相约去打篮球。在大学时，作为系篮球队主力队员的他，毕业后因为工作关系再也没有参加过任何运动。上场后没过多久，他就被跳起的同学踩伤了脚，不能动弹。经医生检查，他由于长期不运动，突然剧烈运动后遭撞击，造成跟腱断裂。  　　贵阳医学院附属医院骨科主任唐本森介绍说，对于上班族来说，一般不经常运动，但是偶尔出去“活动”一下，往往会造成一些类似跟腱断裂、韧带断裂等身体损伤。对于这些偶尔参加大剂量运动的上班族来说，应该随时留心自己身体的状况。  　　在运动之前，必须做一些相关的舒展运动，向身体的肌肉和关节   
     
    
</post>



</Blog>