<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Give me ambiguity or give me something else instead.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      sometimes it seems as though chocolate is my only true and constant friend. which might explain my severe obesity.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      sometimes late at night i realize that i wouldn't be in school if it weren't for that chipmunk.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      One of the best tricks ever is having a fake garage sale at someone else's house. Only you don't tell them. That way, they get confused. Also, if you do this, make sure you put in ad in the paper and hang up signs. Mischief is fun! (thanks to Matt S. of California for this one!)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sometimes I wonder if roller coasters would be more fun without those wussy restraints. That way, it'd be a thrilling battle to survive.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There were some robins living in my porch and they decided to raise their young there. One day while mowing the lawn I stopped for a minute and looked up at the baby robins in the nest. One of them started to edge out of the nest and I got really excited because I thought that it was ready to leave the nest. I was still looking at the bird and something flew out of the nest. And it hit my eye. And it wasn't a bird. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A great man once said, "Give me all your money, or I'll snap your neck." This man was my great-grandfather. I would like to continue our family tradition, so fork it over, or I'll be forced to take action.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      no matetr waht oredr the lteetrs are in you can siltl raed tihs bcuease you see the wrod as a hloe, not as speretae lteetrs. Wreid, is it not?
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      someone once told me that fighting never solved anything. this person obviously never won a fight.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i got in a sun-staring contest the other day. i bet a kid that i could stare at the sun longer than he could. he quit very quickly to avoid eye damage and got attention from a group of girls who said that he was smart for not staring at a giant nuclear furnace, whereas all i got was permanently damaged cataracts and a lousy fifty cents.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yesterday i got a fortune cookie that said that i "show people that there is more than one kind of beauty". i can't believe that a cookie told me i was ugly.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i hate it when you trip in front of a bunch of people in a public place and fall and then try to pretend like it never happened. so when the person starts acting like it never happened, i trip them again.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      One time during lunch at my school, my friend said "woah!" and pointed towards the stage. obviously distracted, the kid sitting next to my friend look at the stage for several seconds while my friend took the kid's ice pop. My friend ate the pop in front of the kid all during lunch and the kid never found out what happened to his ice pop.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      surprisingly, pointing at something far away and saying, "Oh, my God! Look at the size of that distraction!" will distract your friends long enough for you to punch them.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Everything in the world is easier said than done, with the possible exception of "Systematically assisting Sally's sly, silly sister, Sue," which is easier done than said.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      violence is not the answer, because if it was, i wouldn't be in so much trouble.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      don't case squirrels. they can climb walls and chances are that you can't.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      if you can't say anything nice about someone...they obviously have personal attitude deficiencies and it is in no way your fault.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      speak soft and...drive a german tank.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      the best defense is a good...laser cannon.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i saw a shark today. i named him Jeffrey. then he swam away from. he didn't like being called Jeffrey.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      perro is spanish for dog and a perrito is spanish for puppy, and gato means cat and a gatito is a kitten. a donkey or mule is a burro. so what am i ordering if a ask for a burrito? gross.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so, i'm not supposed to drink mountain dew because it makes me all hyper and i drink it on this extra-curricular field trip to a college and i start freaking out. i'm hypnotizing people, talking to some kids i hardly even knew and sharing some candy. that's when the girl hit her head on the book shelf and we had to go back to the bus. but on the bus, they gave us ice cream and it looked like i threw something out the window, but i didn't, and i got yelled at for throwing stuff out he window. they gave me 3 detentions for it and now i can't go on the whale watch trip. then again, i see quite a few whales at school every day anyway. Heyoo! (thanx to Chris Riley of CA for this one! long time no see, mein fruend)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      a guy walks into a bar and begins complaining about his wife. there's a guy in the bar. for the purpose of the story we'll call him Arty.&nbsp;Arty is a hitman.&nbsp;he offers to kill the other man's wife for 500 dollars. the man says i don't have the money, but my wife has a huge life insurance policy.&nbsp;once you kill her&nbsp;i'll pay you with the insurance, but i'll give you this dollar as a down payment. arty agrees. the next day the man's wife is grocery&nbsp;shopping and arty chokes her in the produce section.&nbsp;however the&nbsp;produce manager sees him and arty chokes him too. by then the police have surrounded the store and arty is arrested. the headline in the local newspaper the next day was  ARTY CHOKES TWO FOR A DOLLAR AT&nbsp;THE GROCERY STORE IN THE PRODUCE&nbsp;AISLE&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;     
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i know a kid who says, "jeremy thinx that's terrifying," and the sentence, no matter what you tell him. so one day i decided to punch jeremy every time he referred to himself in the third person. and the moral of the story is: referring to yourself in the third person makes people want to punch you, and it's terrifying. and that's all alastor has to say about that. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>