<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
          I went for a drive with Robyn, the pilot whos working for the dropzone for $50/week to get his hours, to Dorrigo national park air walk.  The air walk itself is about 30 metres long, but theres a walk that took us a few hours through the rainforrest.  Its very much a family/touristy track - the walkway is bitumen the whole way.  It was nice though, and the coffee at the coffee house there was good.  I took some pictures (of course).. theres a link to the right.  I also managed in my cleaverness to delete my Documents directory.  Doh.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Perfect weather today.. blue skies and almost no wind.  Only problem is that no one wanted to do a tandem, which means I couldn't go up (they need the numbers, otherwise they loose money - the price of petrol these days is criminal :P).  So instead of spending money on jumping, I spent it on shoes and stuff.  They look kinda dagy really, and aren't particularly comfortable... they were just the best I could find.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       This is part of my world.  Post jump relaxing... post food relaxing... procrastination relaxing...          
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       green chicken curry.. or is that Thai green curry chicken?... anyway, its good, even if I can't talk properly afterwards..               
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Although I know next to no HTML, but thanks to the uber clear layout of the blog template, I managed to relatively easily add a links section and move my profile.  I am now happy.  I managed to get a website that doesn't suck (no comments thanks) without actually learning HTML.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I did the second jump for the day about an hour and a bit ago.  I was passed for the stage, but it wasn't as good this time.  I didn't stop my 180 turn, so I did a 360 during deployment, which put twists in my lines - something easily dealt with but not exactly graceful.  Now I'm okayed for Stage 7 - BACK LOOPS (otherwise known as back flips).  I'm also ok for solo jumps.  I think I'll do some solo ones just to practice the turning, tracking (forward movement ala James Bond) and stable pulls.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I woke up today more nervous than I've been before any of my other skydives (for this course anyway).  I was shivering and went to the loo rather frequently.  It was a bit overcast, with fog in some places, but I was detirmined not to chicken out.  I'm pretty comfortable with the jumping out of the plane thing now - its just that today was the 360 degree turns and forward movement (stage 5) and I wasn't confident I'd be able to do the turns consistently.  I was just thinking "what the hell.. we'll see what happens".   We took off about 8:15am and on the way up the instructor was telling me to make sure I push off the strut, otherwise my face might hit the step!  Anyway, exit was good and he followed me - it was uber cool to look up at the plane and see him dive out after me.  I drifted to the left a bit and attempted a turn to face him again (this was when it would be a success or I'd fall into a heap of spinning craziness) - and it worked!  Wicked... in no time I was back facing him.  He indicated for me to do a right 360 and I did.. my legs were a bit wobbly but I corrected (apparently... I can't see them from my point of view).  I then did a forward movement towards Mark (my instructor) - which involves straightening the legs and bringing your arms back a bit - to dock and was close enough to head butt him.  I then did a left hand 360.. and we were still at 7k.. still 3k feet to go and enjoy the ride!  woohoo.  It was great....  I can hear the jump plane now .. a couple of English backpackers are doing a tandem each... bloody tandems.. taking up good jump spots on the plane.  I'm hoping to go again today if the weather holds.  OK for Stage 6 (which is almost exactly the same).  After Stage 6 I can go alone! (to practice and prepare for the backloop and shit). In less important news, it looks as though I'll be staying on up here to 'run' the chemotherapy department (I'll be a rubber stamp for a while I think).
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I wanted to go out last night to the Plantation, but didn't so I'd have a good sleep before jumping this morning.  However, I got up this morning at 6:45 to see that the sky was overcast and the air was chilly... after all the perfect days when i was working.  Apparently it was fine for jumping, but I cancelled and went back to bed.   I'm booked in for tomorrow at 8am.  I'll probably go even if it is cold.  360 turn here I come.. I hope.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have recently discovered the joy of beef penang.. it looks ok but the taste is a wonderful contradiction.. creamy, chilli, light, and sweet and .. corriander.  And beef.  And rice.  Its good.  hhmm.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If you wanna see some pictures of coffs, of the spirit and of.. boats and stuff, have a look at:   urlLink  Coffs pics and stuff 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'd like to use ftp to publish.. shame I have to have such a sucky URL.  I suppose I could register www.robphukinrocks.net or something.. hhmm.  At least I could get rid of that bloody add.                         urlLink                             View of the hills to the west from my balcony               
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm in Coffs working at the hospital. Its cruisey and cool and I'm skydiving, which is hard.  I've been making progress and will be attempting stage 5 on Saturday.. takeoff 8:20am! Its about 20 degrees or so cooler where I jump out... so its frequently minus something up there.  A good way to wake yourself up is to get a blast of minus 2 degrees air and then climb out of a plane.  I hope to have some photos and shit from the whole process soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It was perfect weather  today (about 22 degrees, not a cloud about and negligible wind).  I did my stage 7 and went well, then did my stage 8, which also went well.  I won't bore you with the specifics, but I will say that I didn't really expect anything... I didn't expect to pass or to fail, which isn't the same as giving up or being unsure, its just that I was going to try and see how I went.  I had just a little bit of addrenalin, wasn't nervous and enjoyed the experience - a state I've been looking forward to.  The best bits were exiting the plane and looking up to see my instructor exit and do a head down dive to catch up... very cool.  Its good to be up there with someone else.  My instructor was happy with how I went, which I could tell from him sticking his toungue out and giving me a bit grin and thumbs up while we just enjoyed the ride to pull altitude (after completing the requirements of the stage - turns, fast and slow falls, S-turns, tracks, backloops).   There was a guy doing a tandem when I was doing my stage 8.  He was grinning all the time even before he left, and on the video hes is so happy he looks like he took a truck load of ecstasy or something.  He was swearing and yoohooing... the most I've seen anyone, and he seemed to pretty much lose control of himself when he landed from excitement.  He was constantly swearing and saying how it was better than getting laid and how he'd be back in a couple of weeks.  Most peopel are excited after doing a tandem, but he was the most extreme example I've seen so far.  I don't think it would be possible to be more excited.  Work is better now.  I'm in charge of the chemotherapy pharmacy in the cancer services area of the hospital.  Its just me and a very sweet and competent assistant.  I can listen to music, boss her about and if I wanted to, totally slack off.  We usually finish our stuff by early afternoon, when I go accross to the main pharmacy and help out till knock off time, except for Wednesdays because we're busy till the end of the day in the chemo department.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is the second weekend that has followed a week of great weather with cold front passing over the coast.  I can see the high that is going to be over the mainland for the comming working week, and the low following behind it..it should come over the coast around friday or saturday... dammit.  As a result there was no jumping last weekend, this weekend and probably next weekend.  I'm going to have to get some kind of life beyond skydiving and work.   I will need to think on this.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm being moved into another place half an hour from work and the airport!  and I may not have a phone line!  So much for bitching that I don't have broadband... I might have no access at all.  Crap.   I am soon to be the proud owner of a base station extreme with a modem, thanks to ebay.  Might get a express as well.. dunno.  Might have to wait.  Anyway... it was 27 degrees today.  Winter sux :P
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Went scuba diving with about 20 sharks cruising around the bottom.  They were very handsome and unphased.  We were basically in a school of them.  Then we did another dive, just looking at fish and sponges, which was better in a way, because on the first dive with the sharks I didn't put on enough weight, so I had to pull myself down to the bottom, where I was ok, but my mask had fogged up, so to see the sharks I had to be really close to them (one side wasn't fogged up to badly), and towards the end of the dive (with the increased boyancy of being at 15m - neoprene expands at lower pressure and makes you more boyant - and the less compressed air in the tank) I had to hang on to something to do my safety stop.  It was rather stressful.  I also got very low on air (at about 8 metres) and lost my buddy.  Not what you'd call a successful dive.  The next one was better with an extra 3lb of weight, but I could have done with even more.  We had perfect weather though... the other divers were complaining about the cold.. it was 22 degrees in the water and we had wetsuits on!  I didn't want to overplay the "In tassie... blah blah 12 degrees blah blah", but thats pretty wussy.  I saw some very pretty fishies and some really nice underwater landscapes.... the underwater swell was strongish, so the schools of fish all got together and swayed about together in the 'valleys'.. it was cool to just hang in the water and be taken along with the school.   We also saw a huge turtle, and some crazy fish.. it was very nice.  The first dive site was in pretty bad swell, and I was very close to vomiting, just when they brought out the food.. so close my bottom lip did the 'pre-vomit wobble' regularly.  I was contemplating how much I'd get for my scuba gear, but once we got into the calm, both my stomach had settled and the food gone.  At least the setup was good and the boat was easy to get into.  I'm still feeling the sway of the boat.. it quite nice.  I'll probably go again in a month or so.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes.  I did another jump today.  Pretty average, but I did get the backloop this time, and went over a couple of times.  Apparently that happens when you do it correctly.. it happens quite fast.  Lots of things to work on.  Last week some guy did the whole course in four days!  Bastard.  It was perfect weather until friday, when I had the morning off.  Friday was to windy for jumping.  Hopefully I'll be doing my stage 7, 8 and 9 next weekend. I've added a link to a decent sized map of Coffs Harbour.  I doubt it'll be of any use, except to see the relationship between where  I live (Victoria St, next to the (old) hospital), the airport and the harbour.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Clouds smell cool.  This is something I didn't expect to learn in my aeronautical pursuits.  When I say cool, I mean it in both senses of the word.  They smell both cool as in good, nice, appealing, agreeable, and also cool as in low in temperature.  The crampness of the plane full of bodies and the ever present, though diminishing, nerves are gone and replaced with eager excitement only when the door is open and the clouds can be smelled.  I suppose its really just the air up there at smells, because its present if there are clouds or not.  Its just that its so much how you'd expect clouds to smell. I'm going to be doing my stage 7 tomorrow morning.  After my last two solos I'm confident I'll stuff it up, but not so much as to fail.  I succeeded in doing a back-loop the first time I tried, but later on in that day I tried twice more (in a single jump), only to kind of roll sideways the first time, and the second time I brought my knees to my chest, my arms to my sides and my head back in a dynamic movement as I was told, but I just ended up dropping like someone doing a very long 'bomb' dive.. i.e. bum to earth and looking up at the sky.  It was cool in its own right, or would have been if I'd been a bit higher.  As it stood I was at around 6500 feet and didn't want to stuff about for to long.  I hope to get it tomorrow, otherwise its $242 down the toilet.. well, not entirely, but a pretty bloody expensive 40 seconds of fun.. think of the other forms of fun you could have if you were willing to pay that kind of rate!   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This morning I did a dive exit! woohoo... In other words rather than hanging off the strut and pushing off, I dived out head first (pushing off with my feet).  It was (predictably enough) excellent.  I also landed in the 'intermediate' area (instead of the beginners' area) and did some tracking for about five seconds (where you aim to assume an inverted arch, shaping your body like a wing, in order to transfer as much energy you can into forward movement.  Its used to separate from other jumpers prior to parachute deployment). During my second jump this afternoon I was going to do a backflip, but just as we were taking off there were reports of gusts to 16 knotts (or is it notts?  I'll go with knotts), and my legal limit is 15 knotts ground wind (even though I'd been in 25 knotts ok... damnit).  Regulations are regulations.  I'm hoping tomorrow is better and that I get a jump.  Two jumps is a good number.. one is enough to get you into it, then you spend the rest of the time crossing your fingers for another one.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went skydiving today.  My first solo (technically not really, but for this course) from 12,000 feet.  It went super.. I was the last one out of the plane (after a tandem) and when I exited the plane I was facing it for ages (one of the aims of my jump was to keep my heading on the plane).. it felt so right.  I had tonnes of time after I did my turns and stuff.. it was awsome.  I felt more in control than ever before (which is a good thing).  There was so much wind (the maximum I'm alowed to jump it) that when I was facing into wind under canopy I had no drive at all (i.e. the forward speed of the paracute (around 20 knotts) was the same as the wind I was facing into), and when I turned off wind I was passing rather quickly over the landing area... in other words its lucky the landing area is so big!  Its odd being pretty well dead still relative to the ground below.  Then I went to work.  I wish every work day started like that!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been told off for using the shit word to much, so I'll try to use it less from now on. I took this morning off work (yes, this morning.. I still have to go back in the afternoon), but its windy... to windy for jumping.. aarrrgh.  This is mildly frustrating.  It'll probably calm down this afternoon, so when its time for work it'll be good weather, so the ppl booked in for a jump will go and there won't be anyone to go up with on the weekend... bugger. Its sunny at least.  I had a dream last night that I spoke with some tassie ppl from 'under the mountain'  and they'd complained about how cold it was and all I ever said was "its 22 in Coffs most of the time".  Anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My hair simply MUST have product... 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This time I dived after my instructor.  It was cool, looking into Brad's eyes (about 1m away) as we both fell away (eye contact is essential in relative work).  I tracked towards him once we were pretty much level, as we'd separated 'on the hill'.  It was quite surprising how quickly we came together.  I had all the typical problems of a beginner .. either falling to fast, to slow, slipping back and combinations thereof.  We were supposed to do a few manoeuvres (Stage 2 B-rel), but I couldn't do a basic comfortable pin (front link up).  The exit was similar to the exit in this picture, except we weren't actually holding on to one another, and we were facing each other directly.   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      [The folloing is an overly detailed account, more for me than anyone else.  Just skip the details if they bore and go straigt to my conclusion paragraph :P]  Todays foray was rather eventful.  I turned up at the DZ thinking I'd just do another solo - so I was there with 5 minutes to get ready.  However, Steven Hill (Hilly) told me I could do a B-rel with him, because his tandem hadn't turned up.  B-rel is the next 'course', or series of jumps that you have to pass to do jumps with other people (which is lots o fun).  The thing is, you're supposed to have about a 30 minute briefing.  That didn't happen... I got a about 3 minutes on spotting (directing the plane to the right position for exit - you need to take into account winds at different altitudes and the effect they have on where you open and how you get to the landing area).  Todays winds were all over the place, and on the limit as far as jumping goes.  I then got a 90 second briefing on the jump itself - a different exit position than I'm used to, and I had to do a fast fall down to the instructor then some docks.   The exit went much smoother than I expected, and was quite snug - we were both on the step facing opposite directions, left shoulder to left shoulder, so when we fell away we fell close and facing one another.  We got level, and I starting 'half' tracking towards Hilly just to make sure we didn't drift to far apart, and was waiting for him to 'drop out' so I could follow him down with a fast fall.  However, he didn't, and gestured for me to continue towards him.  He docked with me first, then I docked with him (a dock is where two skydivers are falling betty to earth (BTE) and one person flys forward to 'take a grip' with the other guy, either face to face on the arms, or to the side on the hip or from behind sometimes).  I was supposed to do another dock, but this time I stopped to soon, so I had to have another go.  That was when my dytter went off (very soon.. way to high), so I thought I was lower than I was and that I was running out of altitude to pass the stage, so I put in a aggressive movement towards Hilly and basically crashed into him and over him (he had said earlier that that wouldn't be a problem.  Passing the stage required a touch, not a perfect dock).  The problem with being directly over another skydiver is that over their back is a low pressure area (called a burble), which is what I fell into, and as a result we (according to hilly) both dropped about 400 feet in a second or two.  I continued over hilly into a head first dive, when my dytter started screaming in my ear (the tone for YOU ARE REALLY LOW), so I pulled my parachute.  The thing is, I had actually pulled at close to 4000 feet, which is 500 feet or so above my planned deployment altitude.  My dytter had thought that I was at 1000 feet when I deployed (very low).  I was supposed to track for a few seconds to get separation from my instructor.  As it was, that didn't happen, which is risky, because collisions on opening or during opening due to close opening heights can cause real problems (e.g. somone falling into your parachute while they're still deploying). The spot was good and I was just where I wanted to be on opening, which was fortunate because there appeared to be a 20 knott or so WNW, judging by the fact that when I faced into wind I had no ground speed, and at times I was going backwards, which isn't good as a rule, and when I turned downwind I was motoring (about 40 knotts).  The idea in these situations is that you position yourself to turn into wind as soon as you get downwind of target.  I ended up landing about 15m from my target, which is really good, especially whith the winds as they were.  My last couple landings have been 100m from my target in good winds, so I'm very happy with my landing.  Also, to get my A license I need ten landings within 25metres, and I now have eight.  Woohoo.  I think I was lucky in a way though, because about 100 feet from the ground the wind was quite bumpy, and at about 20 feet the headwind died, giving me more forward speed and getting me that bit closer to the target.  Now I need to be a bit more consistant.   Would you say that was a good jump?  It was good in that I learned a bit, and that it was fun with hilly, who is a bit of a dude, and that I had a good landing, but I didn't expect to pass the stage, but Hilly thought it was good and okayed me for stage two, but he says I owe him a Corona (top beer) for kicking him in the head on my way over him.  I actually hit him in the forhead with some metal rings on my shoulder, then kicked in the back or something (well, I shinned him actually.. I can still feel it were I hit him).  It didn't seem to phase him at all.  The problem with my dytter had been my fault.  I turned it on in the plane after take off.  I thought it was already on, but it had gone into power save mode becuase I hadn't used it for a while (I left it at home yesterday), so it thought that 2500 feet was ground level, so when it though I was at 1500 feet and started screaming, I was actually at 4000 feet. Something that I've realised is that my favourite jumps are those that don't go to plan, where I have to react to something unexpected.  There is something gratifying about being in a situation where I could have panicked, but didn't (much) and dealt with it.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've got a flatmate now.  His name is Errol and hes a psych registrar, and is saving up to do a mountineering course in NZ, which won't take him long at $680 a day!  Bastard.  Thats the real reason people do medicine.   Yes, I went for a jump today.  This time I went on my bum (i.e. 'sit flying'.. with my arse towards the ground in a kind of sitting position).  It was pretty cool, but I started turning soon and didn't know how to stop it (well, I didn't really have time to work it out at the time), so I went back the familiar belly to earth position and did some turns using my legs rather than my upper body, with a view to combine both the lower and upper body turning soon to make a fast turn on the spot (i.e. turn left with my feet and right with my arms/chest - similar to rowing in different directions to turn rather than using just one oar).    Nothing much else happening, except that I'm getting more pimples up here for some reason... maybe its my diet.. who knows.  I've been playing a few new games I hired.  Ninja gaiden is good but hard, and Munch's Oddysee is fun, as is a rally car game I've been playing, RallySport Challenge.  Thats it.  No more.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I completed the last stage of my AFF (skydiving course) today.  It was a jump from a low altitude (4k').  I did a poised exit, and to pass I had to watch the instructor in the door of the plane for a few seconds, and tell them what hand signal they used (to check I could keep my eye on the door after exit).  I pushed off the strut quite hard, and fell away almost on my back (ie about 30 degrees off horizontal, feet lower than head facing the sky), which meant that I could easily see the instructor in the door.  It also meant I had to get back on my belly in a few seconds.  I opened with line twists, which doesn't happen often with me.  The difference this time was that the lines were 'asymetrical' and 'locked' in the twists (I couldn't use the brake lines with the twists in the lines).  In these situations, sometimes you need to cut away (i.e. deploy the reserve after releasing the main canopy) because the canopy starts spinning slowly, but kaccelerates, and to get the twists out you have to 'kick' them out.  Only problem is that the spinnning canopy can add twists faster than you can get rid of them, turning you into a spinning disaster area.  So, this was going through my mind as I found myself spinning faster and faster, and watching the twits to see if they were getting less or more.  If I'd been any later or slower getting the twists out, I'd have had to use the reserve.  It was all rather exciting.  I thought I'd be in trouble for not using the reserve, but I don't think my instructors saw it properly (they were still in the plane) - they seemed to think it was all quite normal.  Its common to get twists, but not spinning canopies!  Anyway, my landing was pretty crappy... safe, but about 36 metres away... I'm aiming for a maximum of 25m from the target.  I also went to the chilli festival in Sawtell with Robyn, which was pretty cool.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>