<Blog>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
          That's Jenny, me, Elissa, then Amina. Man I'm pale. You can't really see my dress because it's a dark picture. But doesn't Elissa look hot?! Haha. We all said she was one sexy mama but she denied it. }=p  Just finished baking banana nut muffins. Yum. =) I'll post some of the NY pictures later. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Song:  Go Mad (Original Mix) -  Yoji Biomehanika   Now I have Power Puff Girls stuck in my head... If you don't know why, listen to the first few seconds of this song. It sounds like the Power Puff Girl's theme. Haha.  Anyways, yea, I think I lost my job. But I'm not too sure. This Sunday, I went to service apon Gina's insisting, and later when the guy who pays me gave me my pay, I told him that I didn't baby sit today and that I should get only $50. So he comes back later with $50 and tells me, "Well, I guess I won't see you next week then?" I kind of just stood back. I explained that I wasn't quitting, but if they didn't need me then I won't come. He said he'll need to talk to someone about that. I don't think he wants me around.  Oh well. There goes my easy source of money. Except the screaming baby girl who is such a spoiled brat. =)  Talked to Kelly today. She said that some people remember me from middle school. Which is strange because one of them I don't even know, and another one of the guys I never talked to. Except the exception where he insulted me once.   I am known in San Francisco merely as "AJ's girlfriend from 7th grade". Come on! It's been what, 4 years since that? Just drop the subject! People insist that we were each others "first loves" but who the hell heard of a middle school "couple" who went out for a MONTH and fell in love? Oh please.  He has his girlfriend for what, 3 years? She's really cute and very nice from what I heard. Why do people need to bring up this bull shit? Great, so when I moved back to SF, am I going to be known as "AJ's ex from 7th grade" forever? Psh, I think I'll avoid the people that went to Presidio thank you.   - s i m o n e -  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Song:  Cube -  Gackt   Lonely~ I didn't think I would say this, but I actually miss my sister.. and she's only been gone two days!!!  Usual day. My mom spends all of it on her computer... While I stand in the back and yell at her to get off and go exercise. Haha.  Started a weight losing challenge. Fifteen pounds by August. Crazy? No. I should lose some flab. Haha. That way, I'm not a fat depressed girl, I'm a .. not-so-fat depressed girl. Hahahahaha~  I wonder if people read this? I really doubt it. But, hey~ I can vent things I can't on Xanga, because my dad reads my Xanga. O_o  Should I call up Gina?   (...)  No. I haven't seen her in about... a week. And haven't talked to her in a week. Everytime I call her she's not home or sleeping. Avoiding me? That's a possibility. I shall find out tomorrow. That would be hella sad if that were true. Holy shit.   - s i m o n e -  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Song:  Condition Of My Heart -  Fly To The Sky   Ok, I didn't really bother to look at my transcript before, but, HOLY CRAP, I am hella far behind in credits! This really depresses me. I used to think that independent study was all great, now I see it screws you up! My sophomore year was totally messed up. And I screwed up on my Junior year. My dad is pissed off like crazy about this.  Yea, ok, so I'm taking the CHSPE test and I will get out of high school, but my dad is making me very unsure of myself. He keeps saying, "IF you pass the test." Does he really think I'm some grade-A idiot? From what I hear, Academy of Art is all bullshit with an expensive tuition, but you know what, I am NOT going to get into any other art college that I know of so I really want to at least try out the summer course there. I don't think my dad approves of the art profession so it's not happening. He calls me an "artist wanna-be". Man, this is really ticking me off.  I am spoiled. I know I am. I've been slacking off for the past year and a half. I know I don't really deserve anything special. Korea, you shall have to wait until I can EARN my way to you. Jiyeun should really go to Korea without me.   This isn't even cool. I see how stupid I really am now. And it depresses me. When your own FATHER tells you to just drop out of school and get a job because he doesn't think you can make it in college, you know you are messed up.  My mom could care less how I am doing. As long as I don't give her a bad reputation or cost her money, it's all good for her. Which is probably why she's been stalling on taking me to a doctor.   Ok, now I seem like an ungrateful brat. This is not a good post. This post makes me sad and mad. Now it will give you all a bad view on me.  - s i m o n e - 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Song:  Uhjjuhmyun (Maybe) -  BUZZ   hello. it's 2:19 am and i'm still up doing homework for my psych class.  why does it take so long, you ask?  i hate memorizing the doctors, their theories, their contributions to psychology,and what books they've written. boo.  why did i start blog, you ask?  xanga seemed to be the breeding grounds for e-pimps and e-whores so i just decided to put random posts there and write about my daily life here. ^-^  talking to sato... but he's not really talking... rawr~  i'll fix this layout up later... when i get access to a computer that CAN run photoshop. haha~ my computer is getting crappier by the second. i need to save all my files on CDs and reformat. how is that done?  man, do i have to bring my compy to the computer place to get reformatted? someone just teach me so i don't have to pay for it. -_-^   - s i m o n e -  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Songs:  Why Be Normal -  G-Dragon Feat. Taekwon   So... I got bored last night... saw hair cutting scissors... .... *snip snip snip* I meant to only trim my bangs.. but I ended up cutting all over... so my hair is SHORT now. slightly uneven too.  >. but its ok. ill just wait till it grows a bit then go to the salon to trim it. man... why do i do these things when i get bored?!?!?   - s i m o n e -  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>