<Blog>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So yeah. I hate nights like this...Where your so damn exhausted, you cant fall asleep. The yawns are abundant, but for the life of one, you cant seem to find that comfortable nook in your bed, where you can nestle in, and pass out into the unconcious. (trust me, ive already tried)           Breif Recap Of My Weekend So Far Thursday-school/work Friday-school/work Saturday-Work/party Tomorrow-Party/Movies/Swim.  I swear to god..this thursday couldnt come any sooner. Im dying over here. Today i went to work from 11-4. lets just say that it sucked ass in there. It was completly dead, but hopefully in the comming saturdays, it will pick up. I waitress, so its sorta hard to keep busy, after you've already done things. Lack of customers are not my fault. I was also horridly unmotivated, due to the friday night rush the previous night. I got to leave there arround 4, and pick up a present for my buddy Jonathan, cause today was his graduation.(I also got a Black Lable Society CD...I saw it, and it reminded me of My Jae..so i had to pick it up. Plus, the song "Blessed Hellride" is cool..so what the hell?) As luck would have it, i missed the ceremony..i couldnt take off. But i got to go see him afterwards. It was fun...I watched "not another teen movie..(it was gay)..We ate cheese cake and just hung out. I always like going to go see Jonathan. Then after that, i came home....and didnt do jack shit. Tried to sleep, but obviously it was a failed attempt. And now im rambling...ramble ramble ramble.....Shit.  Im gone- 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Brandon Lee...*sigh*&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah...a new web journal thing. score..I guess. anywho..I realy dont know what to say, im just sitting in the library waiting for the time to pass. I had the most awesome nap in 5th period. we were watching an old movie...one that they're currently remaking..but i didnt take the time to watch most of it. I needed that nap. right now ive got a type o negative song stuck in my head..thats probably why i titled this blog "type o negative" ....go figure. So yeah..im gunna let a bunch of little meaningless words waste space on the internet. Dang. I have a 6 weeks test next period. US History. gotta love it. anywho. *yawn* ..I miss Jae. I wonder what hes up to. I cant wait to go see him in June. anyway..i think this is where i stop posting, and i check out all the neat little things i can do with this gadget..to see if i really want to keep it or not.   -Cheers-
     
    
</post>


</Blog>