<Blog>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It was inevitable.  The  Hollando Blog  has now arrived.  What form will it take?  I have not decided.  Perhaps I will begin with little blurbs about my day.  My source material, though, promises to be more entertaining than case law.  As I wrap up law school, I now have time to read the stack of  Foreign Affairs  and  Political Science Quarterly  books on my shelf...  ...and the  ABA Journal ... the  Texas Bar Journal ... the  Baylor Law Review ...  ... and issues of  The Economist ...  The New Yorker ...  The Atlantic ... the  Harvard Business Review ...  Legal Affairs ...  ... and back copies of the  MIT Technology Review ...  Wired Magazine ...  PC World ...   Digital Videomaker ...  ... and of course the  Yale Alumni Magazine ... the  NYC Yale Club Newsletter ... the  Dallas Yale Club Newsletter ... the  Mory's Newsletter ...  Baylor Magazine ...  Docket Call ...  ... and others that slip my mind.  These readings have been awaiting me.  Perhaps my plan to pursue all six concentrations at Baylor Law was ill-advised.  The logic has been to delay other indulgences in favor of attaining my education now.  The magazines will be available for quite some time, but I have only one chance to pursue a formal legal education.  So the magazines taunted me.  But no longer...  I have to include a bit of variety, so I may reference the occasional video game magazine.  Matthew Alexander's work at  American Thunder , and my resulting subscription, will lead to some interesting observations.  My steady stream of  National Geographic  issues may yield random ramblings, as will the endless reams of junk mail.  Despite all the magazines to which I subscribe, I do intend to spark discussion of meaningful literature.  John Irving, Jack Kerouac, and their ilk glare at me from another bookshelf in my spare bedroom.  I expect much ribbing about my subscription to the  Harvard Classics  series from the Easton Press.  Yet for all this reading, I hope to promote discussions among friends and to enjoy the fellowship I discovered in college.  With distance and varying schedules conspiring to separate us, I think this may be the best method of staying close with one another.  This site is meant to supplement Hollando.com, which serves as a collection of photographs and blurbs about the people, places, and events I encounter in my life.  The Hollando Blog treats a different set of meetings... meetings for which there will not be photographs... meetings with the great writers, the hack journalists, the parade of authors who offer glimpses into the world around us.  Hollando.com is a self-mocking, jubilant jaunt through my life, always tinged with irony.  The Hollando Blog will be a chance to offer more than mockery.  I will need your help to make this endeavor worthwhile.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday was the planned slaughter that we call a practice Multistate Bar Exam (MBE).  I call it a farce.  Several folks opted out of taking the exam once they received a book with the questions, answers, and explanations.  An even greater number of students began to walk out of today's post-exam review as it moved into its sixth hour.  We have seven hours or so scheduled for tomorrow.  After all this sound and fury, the test and explanation sessions' real benefits appear to be (1) inspiration of fear and (2) concept review.  We have had true success as to benefit number one.  Number two remains elusive.  To break the montony of our daily lectures, some of us have taken to examining each lecturer's appearance and mannerisms.  Rarely do we view professors in our videos; we are too busy filling in blanks and wrestling with faded memories.  Yet there are brief glimpses.  We have a small collection of celebrities, or at least their clones.  Steve Buscemi tought us negotiable instruments and secured transactions.  Tim Allen attempted to provide a post-MBE property review.  He failed.  In the nerdy world of law students, Erwin Chermerinsky's actual appearance in our Con Law review video was a something of a celebrity event.  Yes, we crave for something to add levity to our daily three-and-a-half hour review sessions.  Now I attempt to finish all of life's "little projects" in time for my target date of July 5, 2004.  All other work must end by that time.  The Bar draws near.  Still those books from the Easton Press taunt me.  Plato... Carlyle... Homer... and what must I read?  BarBri...
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jim Dedman, a friend and mentor from Baylor Law, has once again offered me sage advice.  He told me to blog despite my protests that all I have been reading is BarBri material.  My logic is that the old saw "you are what you eat" applies to how you consume items of thought as well.  If a child reads more challenging material, then he will outperform the child who consumes information from television and junk magazines (I recall the old Wall Street Journal advertisement.)  "You are what you eat."  I started the South Beach Diet three days ago, so if I am what I eat, then I am doing better than I ever have.  But if I am what I read, then... BarBri?  So the first posting of substance on Hollando's Blogspot is a dull protein performance drink.  Though I have had no time to read for pleasure, I have been reading.  I have been pouring over two of  nine  books that have been sold to me as part of my review for the Texas Bar Exam.  BarBri, the most commonly chosen review course at Baylor, is a master of overkill.  These nine books together weigh thirty seven pounds.  Everyone tells me with great confidence that I need not read all the materials provided.  With the Bar just a month and a half away, I lack that confidence.  But my de facto reading amounts to some smattering of pages from the day's assignment and my reading of lecture materials while I fill in blanks.  Taking law school courses during BarBri was not a wise decision.  Nor have I been successful in juggling four capstone projects and an externship at the local District Attorney's office (arguably a fifth capstone).  I graduate on July 31.  How will I complete all of this work?  My plan of attack is to read the full assignments going forward and to review the lectures we covered.  Then, if time allows [insert laugh track], I will read those seventy-page daily outlines from the last two weeks.  As MBE practice test approaches on July 26, I will try my hand at a few practice tests.  What do my readers think?  Post a few comments and advise me.  I am the first lawyer in my family, and I am flying blindly.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today I managed to study for the better part of&nbsp;twenty hours, covering about five outlines for the first time and working through&nbsp;some practice essays.&nbsp; I went to bed early yesterday at 8:00 pm because I was too tired to be productive, and I awoke today at 3:30 am.&nbsp; Somehow, the fear of the Bar kept me working all day today.&nbsp; I did nap for an hour, but rarely have had such a burst of productivity as I did today.&nbsp; The Bar Exam&nbsp;is an amazing motivator. &nbsp; I will pay tomorrow, no doubt.&nbsp; I will not even start until about 7:30 am thanks to the need for a full night's sleep.&nbsp; Yet one&nbsp;story gives me hope... &nbsp; The legend of Ryan Squires is alive and strong in the memories of Baylor Law students.&nbsp; After competing in traveling Mock Trial team competitions, Squires returned to Waco and had only eight days in which to prepare for the Bar.&nbsp; He passed.&nbsp;&nbsp;A few&nbsp;say his success was proof of&nbsp;the&nbsp;proposition that&nbsp;the Bar is merely "a test of minimal competency."&nbsp;&nbsp;Most (including me) suggest that what Squires did was amazing.&nbsp; His accomplishment&nbsp;will&nbsp;not be repeated easily. &nbsp; One thing is certain... I have only seven days until the Bar Exam.&nbsp;&nbsp;Until now, this quarter's work&nbsp;has not left me with much time to prepare for the Bar.&nbsp; Two of those remaining days involve my last two Baylor Law School final exams.&nbsp; I have reviewed for the MBE, but I have hardly studied the essays.&nbsp; I must survive this Exam.&nbsp; But how? 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had bombed my BarBri practice MBE test recently, but now the PMBR's MBE practice test (rumored to be harder) gave me the opportunity to redeem myself.  I moved up an additional 30% in my percentile ranking after just a week or two of less-than-regular study.  I was able to improve despite the fact that I still haven't read property or criminal procedure, either!  So room for improvement remains, in addition to some needed review of torts, evidence, contracts, constitutional law, and criminal law.  I now view the chance to review as an opportunity for hope!  Now I can begin to fear the essay section as well.  Gulp...
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      George Foreman markets a grill.  I bought that grill.  What a happy man I am!  I had left this grill sitting unused next to my stove for two weeks.  This morning, I decided I did not want to buy any more fast food, and I took a small risk.  I plugged in the machine, pulled a burger patty out of my freezer, and slapped it down on the grill.  I was certain nothing could be so foolproof, let alone Hollando-proof.  How wrong I was!  Three grilled meals later, I am in full pseudo-Atkins mode, with nothing but meat, cheese, and spinach salads in my immediate future.  I say "pseudo-Atkins" because I have no idea what constitutes an acceptable meal plan under the late doctor's regimen.  Like the majority of other shoppers, I flip packages around to see which products have the fewest carbohydrates.  I hope to do some research on the South Beach Diet after the Bar Exam.  For now, though, this quaint little gadget is saving me from spending the same time, more money, and far more patience in the pursuit of not-so-fast food.  Some would say it's healthier, too.  Here is something my friends never thought I would say: "Do you have any recipe ideas?"  Well, do you?  Let me know...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      No matter how much I try to resist, I am doomed to wake up every morning at 7:30 am, even if I stay up to study past midnight.  The days have become a blur.  I move through life in a zombie-like state.  I have only studied for the MBE so far.  I still have DA's office hours to complete on Tuesday through Friday of this week.. exams on Saturday and the following Wednesday and Thursday... a paper and will to draft for Featherston... about 20 or so topics to study for the essay portion... and I still haven't finished reading Property for the MBE.  Of course, today I devote to practice questions--for the first time.  I can sense I have fallen behind.  Arguably, only six days are left completely free for bar study.  Time is in short supply.  After a mandatory grocery run this morning, I intend to hole up in my apartment for as much of the time as possible.  In a strange way, I enjoy this socially-sanctioned opportunity to review all the law I have learned over the last three years.  I just hope enough time remains.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This afternoon, as I closed my book upon completing the final BarBri review lecture, an incredible thought occurred to me.  I have finished attending law school classes.  Because I will attend PMBR's MBE review on Monday, Tuesday, and Wednesday of next week, I will miss the last three school days of the quarter.  This quarter is my last.  I have no classes tomorrow.  Without realizing it, I completed my law school career at 2:03 pm today in Professor Whitaker's Securities Regulation class.  Today was my last day as a student in a classroom.  After attending law school for twelve quarters over three years... after taking the maximum allowed course load every quarter... after completing all six concentrations... after seven-and-a-half uninterrupted quarters on law review... after a year of Student Bar Association work... after clerking for Professors Guinn and Powell... after six Moot Court competitions... after Practice Court...  ... it all ended today.  I have capstone work left to finish.  I need a few more hours at the DA's office (Criminal Practice), I have a research paper and a will to draft (Estate Planning), and after graduation I have nonprofit bylaws to draft (Business Transactions.)  Of course, one more round of exams looms in the distance.  Yet none of these tasks seem quite so daunting now.  More than 170 quarter hours of classes are behind me.  The Texas Bar Exam stands as guardian between my student life and my graduation ceremony.  College friends will arrive from Cambridge, New York, and San Francisco.  My parents will drive down from Plano.  I will walk across a stage and into my new life.  The excitement and anticipation of that moment propel me through this hellish month.  I intend to become a financial planner.  I will sit for Certified Financial Planner (CFP) exam in November, the Certified Financial Analyst (CFA) Level I exam in December, and the Series 7 (broker) test in early January.  Considering the self-study in my near future, perhaps the finality I appreciate this evening is an illusion.  Life is always a balance between learning and doing.  Today, though, marks the end of twenty years of formal schooling (kindergarten, grades 1-12, four years at Yale, and three years at law school.)  The future beckons.  But now is not a time for reflection.  The greatest battle awaits me at the end of the month.  One beast remains for me to slay.  After two months of fear and trembling, I face that Bar Exam with an intensity I have not had until this moment.  Off I go to study.   I prepare for the coming battle.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My friend Rusty Adams now holds a unique place in Baylor Law School history: he has participated in what may be the shortest and the longest trials in Practice Court.  Last January, Rusty was a defense attorney who received a directed verdict in his favor.  In that case, certain of the plaintiff's witnesses did not appear on time and therefore failed to help plaintiff establish his cause of action's essential elements.  Now as a witness in July, Rusty played the part of a cardiologist for a plaintiff whose three-party trial began at 2:15 pm and ended at 2:30 am.  Although two-day cases have lasted for a greater total number of hours, I am hard-pressed to think of Big Trial case that lasted for a longer   continuous   time.  Do any Practice Court alumni recall longer stretches?
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Fourth of July is traditionally the time at which "applicants" become nervous.  "Applicant" is the Bar Examiners' term for one of those poor souls hoping to survive the onslaught approaching at month's end.  Applicants endure tests for three long July days and then wait for results... which arrive in November, rumor has it.  So during these final, balmy days before the Bar, tension becomes palpable.  Like a tropical malady, Bar Fever sweeps law schools.  The afflicted are in plain sight... gaunt, bloodshot, unshaven, reeking with foul odor, clutching a thousand-page review book that maps the path to salvation.  Even the lower quarter students sense the unease.  A lazy summer pace abruptly reaches a point of inflection after which no one is quite happy.  I struggle with a paper, an externship, three classes, and residual work on another project.  As the Bar approaches, nothing but Bar preparation seems relevant.  I see others studying while I attempt to wrap up school.  I feel as though a hurricane is churning its way toward us, and as my friends finish boarding up their homes in anticipation of the storm's wrath, I am arriving only now with planks.  My magazines taunt me.  National Geographic offers a wonderful survey on the study of our Sun.  But I have no use for the Sun.  I am a creature of the indoors until July 29...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Bar Exam was every bit the challenge I expected. In the end, the Exam was less a test of knowledge than it was a test of your desire to be an attorney. First, the Exam itself spans three days. Second, the testing time ranges from three to six hours each day. Third, the Bar rewards those who steadily work practice MBE problems. Finally, and most important of all to me, students often master certain subjects only days (or hours) before the exam begins.  Though I concentrated in six areas of law, I never had courses in Civil Liberties, Secured Transactions, Commercial Paper (a.k.a. Negotiable Instruments), or Oil & Gas. The Exam covered all of these areas heavily, including the first  entire  Oil &amp; Gas question in five years. I had not read any of the BarBri reviews for essays until about one week before the exam (a mistake). Thus, I learned the basics of Secured Transactions and Commercial Paper during the all-nighter study-fest before Day 3 began.  I was woefully unprepared in certain respects. Though I took BarBri and PMBR's practice MBE's, I  never  worked a single practice problem outside of those practice exams. My MBE score was last measured (scaled) around 131, and given the lapse of time between practice and test time, the score may have dropped. As for Civil and Criminal Procedure, another all-nighter produced a remarkable performance on the Day 1 Procedure & Evidence portion of the Bar. I realized the advantage of Baylor when I zoomed through that exam, though I would have failed without the all-nighter. The Multistate Performance Test hardly merits mention. One confession: I never read Oil &amp; Gas, never attended its BarBri course, never read its Conviser portion, never read the long form outline, and never took the class. I have never prepared more with less time for such an important test. I only can hope I passed.  Now I enjoy a road trip across Texas with my friends from college. Matt from San Francisco, Will from Cambridge, and David from New York all flew into Texas for my Baylor Law graduation. I wake to a wonderful view from the Hilton in downtown Austin. My friends tell me to quit blogging, shower, and hit the road. I am off to complete our journey.
     

    
</post>


<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ha!&nbsp; Progress is made!&nbsp; My consumption of half a pizza and cheesesticks for dinner, my lunchtime pillage of the Chinese buffet line, and my inhalation of a greasy barbacoa burrito for breakfast&nbsp;ALL failed to stop the downward trend.&nbsp; I thumb my nose at you, oh diet gurus!   
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, it was so very, very wrong... but I gave into temptation and&nbsp;chose Red Lobster for dinner Saturday evening.&nbsp; What better way to innaugurate a new diet era than to break the diet immediately?&nbsp; Hence, I rocket upward to 176 on Sunday before gently landing at a 174 benchmark this morning.&nbsp; Now to be well-behaved... 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I was up working on a capstone course project until 3:30 am on Friday morning, woke up at 8:45 am, and handed in my project an hour later. Without an appetite, I hardly ate yesterday.&nbsp; I slept from 8:00 pm until 6:30 am this morning and then jogged for the first time in at least a month.&nbsp; So this weight is the absolute lowest weight with which I could hope to begin.&nbsp; I expect it will go up before it goes down.&nbsp; But at least I have the supplies for my Insane Hollando Diet: two burgers in the morning, spinach chicken salad for lunch, and shrimp or chicken for dinner.&nbsp; That's the plan over the next week as I take my last law school exams and then the Bar exam on Tuesday-Thursday, July 27-29. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Morning snack*: 1 part-skim mozzarella cheese stick, 8 oz. glass of skim milk  At the office: 6 oz. can of V8  Lunch: 1  urlLink Subway Chicken Ranch Atkins Wrap  (hold the bacon).  6:30pm: 2 more 6 oz. V8s  Supper: 1 homemade 2 egg omelet with part-skim mozzarella cheese, roasted peppers, and garlic powder -- prepared in olive oil with salt &amp; pepper to taste.  Dessert: Roasted peppers  Miscellaneous: countless Diet Cokes, Diet Pepsis, and water bottles (sparkling and still) throughout the day.   And the scale says: 174 pounds.   *South Beach doesn't recommend skipping breakfast, but I'm not a breakfast person, never have been. Instead I choose to eat something light, but filling, to forestall real hunger later in the day. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is something about software engineering that is simply not conducive to a healthy lifestyle. Of, certainly, there are plenty of counterexamples, but I should face facts: we are not, as a group, a particularly healthy lot. I'm sure it has something to do with sitting around at desks all day, staring at screens and tapping away at keyboards. If I hadn't switched to Diet Coke several years ago I highly doubt that I would be able to squeeze myself into my chair at this point. Allow me to introduce myself:  urlLink William Crawford , out of shape software developer, author and technology strategist, as well as college buddy of these other three.  At 5 feet and eleven inches, I fall between Matthew and Holland on the height scale. Mr. Hughes is somewhat taller, but as his post below amply indicates, his role in this blog is primarily to mock the rest of us, at least until he turns 30 at which point he has promised that genetics will kick in and add fifty more pounds. This morning I topped 182 pounds in stocking feet, which has been about average over the last few years, although the proportion of muscle to blubber has varied a bit. Since I think Holland and I are about equal in volume, I can only suspect that I'm either guilty of wishful thinking in that observation, or, alternately, am substantially denser than he is.  Like Matthew, I felt much better when I weighed in at 165. And that's a reasonable goal, although I've decided to shoot for 162 to make it an even twenty pounds off, as I certainly have it to spare. My strategy is fairly simple: eating in as sensible and balanced a manner as possible, and doing at least fifty minutes of intense cardiovascular exercise at leave five days a week. To this end, I've acquired my very own elliptical training machine, which is now located equidistant from my bed and my shower, with the dresser on one leg of the triangle and the clothes hamper on the other. No possible excuses remain.  And we're off.   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had lunch this afternoon with a colleague in Stamford. We went to a new place on the corner of Main Street and Summer Street Extension; I believe it's called the Black Bear Grill. Only opened two weeks ago. I highly recommend it to those travelling the Northeast Corridor.  I mention this merely because my lunch consisted of a  one-pound  hamburger. With onions, mushrooms, and cheese.  Doesn't look so big side to side, but it certainly sinks well into the lower bun. (Oh dear--no pun intended.) This was followed, of course, by some warm, rich chocolate dessert that only a Jansenist or an Atkinite would term sinful. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I live in San Francisco, a great place to eat and drink. Italian, French, Indian, even classic American, you name it we do it, and do it well.  San Francisco is also, however, a very image-conscious town.  Obviously, these two attributes can conflict, as the effects of the first influence the second. This has been a--pun very much intended--growing concern to me for much of this year. Finally, a little over two weeks ago I stepped on the ol' bathroom scale and confronted a number only five pounds shy of my highest recorded weight ever, registered back in December 2001. It was time for  urlLink South Beach . More on that presently.  I am six-feet tall in thick socks. I felt best freshman year, seven years ago, at the slightly underweight (I think) tonnage of 150 pounds. Of course, I was also training daily as a Division 1 varsity athlete and subsisting on college dining-hall food, which never gave anyone an appetite. These might have had something to do with it.  I quit the team and, later, moved off-campus, events that roughly correlated with the onset of the dreaded late-sophomore fifteen, just a little behind schedule. Since then my weight has fluctuated, but, net, mostly in the wrong direction: up.  Enter South Beach. It worked well for my parents, so I decided to give it a shot--slightly modified. I'm paying more attention to calories than is perhaps strictly necessary, but I'm not going dry. (Sorry,  urlLink Dr Agatston , that's just no fun.) I am, however, endeavoring to drink less. Cheers.  The biggest hang-up for me going in was my Italian heritage: bread, pasta, pizza, and wine are dearer to me than life. I should sooner go hungry than forsake these friends, or so I thought. But it transpires that the good doctor was absolutely right: the cravings, and the munchies, go away as one regularizes the swings in one's blood sugar. I now swear by the  urlLink Glycemic Index . Low-GI foods simply keep you full longer. Also helping was Dr Agatston's constant praise of  urlLink olive oil  (a "good fat," one of the category distinctions that separates South Beach from Atkins). So one could, after all, be Italian and on South Beach at the same time.  So far, I'm down 10 pounds from 185 at the outset to 175 this morning. That's about where I was at the beginning of last week, when I should have finished Phase 1. But then I went on the road with the other blokes on this blog. Texas Barbecue and Irish Car Bombs are part of no reputable diet. Add back five pounds. Now with more diligent effort, and more time on Phase 1, I've taken those off again and the clothes are loosening up every day. The key will be to keep the net downward momentum going, although I imagine the graph will look something like the market during a recession: generally down, but with small spikes along the way. My new four food groups are dairy (eggs, cheese, and skim milk), salad, chicken, and the occasional Atkins wrap from Subway. Soon I will branch out into my mother's more daring array of South Beach-compatible recipes.  What are my goals? Well, as college bulks so large (another dreadful pun, I know) in the story of my stature, I've chosen to frame them in terms of applications and admissions. I'd love to get back to 150. But as our bodies are arguably somewhat different at 25 than they were at 18, this is my "reach." (The lowest I've been in the modern era was 156, two summers ago during a calorie-cutting and exercise jihad.) It will also, almost certainly, require me to  go  to the gym for which I registered. My "likely" or "target" goal is 160, and my "safety" is 165.  These days, however, admissions are so competitive that rarely is a safety truly "safe." The same applies here. Ten more pounds will require discipline, 25 at least 2.5 times the discipline. I shall rely on your support, encouragement, and, doubtless, continual mockery to keep me motivated.  Oh, and if you want another cardiologist's endorsement of the South Beach Diet, just ask my dad.   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have not weighed myself in ages, so it was a rare treat to use Hollando's digital scale, albeit weighted down with clothes and shoes, as I am wont to be. I have no idea what my ideal weight is, so I went  urlLink here  and entered in my known height and that dubious, shoeful weight. The algorithm spat back a 22.5. Does that automatically qualify me for Hollando's promised cigar? 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Behold!  Now the Diet Blog has new members!  They will, no doubt, introduce themselves over the next day or two.  Ah, and now for the scale's verdict... 178.  That's about two or three pounds off of yesterday's weight.  Of course, I haven't eaten today.  We shall see how this progresses...  
    
</post>


</Blog>