<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I heard a girl today say, "...but there's no point in doing it. I mean, there's no reward so why should we do it?"  There's something seriously wrong with this way of thinking. Why do you need a reward in order to do something? This is very selfish and indicates a lack of responsibility and self-motivation. Unfortunately, this is a very easy trap to fall into. Just be careful to catch yourself when you do. (I'm guilty of it too!)  Jonathan 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone seems to agree that distance relationships just don't work out.  I disagree.  I have been dating the same girl for over four years. Of those four years we have only been physically present in the same city or area approximately 9 months. And it never fails that either or both of us is asked, "How do you do it?"  I always answer the same way, "Love, Trust, Self-Control". That's all it takes. If you or someone you know doesn't seem to be able to handle long distance relationships, then you (or him/her) is missing one of these elements. It's as simple as that.  Do I miss my girlfriend when we're not together? Definately, more than you can imagine. Do I trust her not to mess around with other guys? Absolutely. Does she trust me? Absolutely. Does it take a massive amount of self-control to resist the temptation of talking to other girls/guys whatever your case may be? You bet.  Is it worth it?  You have no idea...  I realized that the friends of mine who couldn't stick it out were, basically, wimps. They didn't want to do what it took to actually keep the relationship strong and growing. In other words, they didn't really care for the other person, were unwilling to committ to them or afraid of getting hurt - either way it amounts to the same thing.  Does that mean Long Distance Love doesn't work? No. It means those people were lazy and selfish. That's the hard, cold truth people. I'm sorry if you don't like it.  Jonathan  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a question for all of you out there.  If you make a mistake doing something, isn't is safe to say that you will know the next time not to make that same mistake, and thus have learned something from the experience?  If this is the case, why are we raised in an educational system that punishes you for making mistakes? If that's one of the best ways to learn and grow, you'd think our teachers and elders would take advantage of this to facilitate our development as individuals...  Just a suggestion to all those teachers out there - Give two tests to your students, and use the second one as the grade. This will be a much better representation of what your students are learning.  No one has gone through life making no mistakes, so don't contribute to the problem by pushing this thought process that 'mistakes are bad' onto others.  Just my two cents worth-  Jonathan
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the first time since news of Michael Moore's  propaganda docufictionary Fahrenheit 9/11 first surfaced, I have come across an  article written by someone who actually has some common sense. Here's the url:   urlLink about the docufictionary   I can't put it better than it already has been  said, so just read&nbsp;it for yourself. Even if you disagree, it's a well  written and captivating article.  Jonathan
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder sometimes what would happen if people just  sat back and relaxed for a bit. In our microwave society, we want everything  right now and God Forbid if we have to wait even a few minutes for it.    I remember once I was at a McDonald's, waiting in  line to order. This black lady was waiting at the counter looking very  impatient. Within a minute she called one of the employees over and verbally  barraged them with demands on where the heck her food was. About 30 seconds  after that she got her food, but looked very disgruntled. She flung open the  bag, inspected the contents and then went on a tirade.  "I can't believe this! I have been waiting for FIVE  minutes to get my food. FIVE minutes! And then you bring me this crap? I don't want this, gimme my money back  Whoah. Five minutes for food. Five. As in less time  than it takes most of us to fill up our cars with gas. And certainly less time  than it takes to fix your own food  The next time you're in an unbelievable rush with  the patience of a gnat, ask yourself this question: In five years, how important  is this event going to be in my life? Chances are the answer will be "not very  much
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever heard anybody say, "I wish I had more time?"  This makes me wonder, what does that person actually do with the time they have? Time is definately more important than money, but you see most people squander it as if they have an endless supply.  Why is it that some people are more effective and get more done in their life than others?   Simple, they take responsibility for their life and don't accept the excuses most people do.   If the first thing you do when someone asks you why you didn't do something you said you would, or were supposed to do, is give an excuse or reason why -- you are not taking responsibility for your life.  Big problem...  If you blame other things, situations, circumstances or people for what goes on in your life - you are giving up control of your life, saying that you had no choice but to do what you did. That makes you a slave, and I'm pretty sure you are not a slave.  Jonathan
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hear a lot of stuff about how Americans are opposed to this conflict in Iraq. It seems to me that the majority of these people are speaking from a position of selfishness. They think our prescense in Iraq is wrong, or they don't want anymore US soldiers killed, or they may think that our government isn't really concerned with the war on terror so much as other things.  But what about the people who this affects the most? The soldiers fighting the war, and the people of Iraq?   The soldiers almost unanimously agree that being there is the right thing to do. If that is what they believe, that is good enough for me. They are the ones doing the dirty work, risking injury or death and all in the name of protecting and preserving the rights and freedoms that we enjoy and usually take for granted. By protesting our armed forces presence in Iraq, we undermine their efforts. We need to Unify and support them and not erode the very foundation beneath them.  How about the Iraqi people? Well, I wish I could ask them - because the Media is doing a really crappy job of informing us about them and what they think, the really important stuff. Not the blood and violence, not the "if it bleeds, it leads", not all the conjecture and allegations and accusations that have no proof.  To all you media moguls, don't tell us what you think is important. Just tell us what's going on and we'll decide if it's important or not. If I want to be entertained I'll go to the movies or watch a sitcom.  Jonathan
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have any of you guys heard of Michael Moore? Is there anyone else  besides me who think this guy is a complete idiot? It seems to me that if you are looking for a posterchild of the Cronic Blameplacer I can think of no better man. For those of you who saw Bowling for Columbine, I'm sure you know what I mean.  Take for example, a scene near the end, where for some unknown reason Mr. Moore mysteriously connects Charleton Heston to the death of a little girl who was shot, simply because he is was doing a rally for the NRA in the same city shortly after she died.  Is it tragic the girl died? Certainly. Is it Charleton Heston's fault? I can think of nothing farther than the truth, but that is what Michael Moore led the viewers of his film to believe.   How about the time when Mr. Moore dragged a paralyzed teenager to the Kmart corporate headquarters, somehow claiming that because Kmart sold bullets they were somehow responsible for this paralyzed young man. Does that boggle anyone else's mind besides mine? Since when did Kmart, or any other business for that matter, become responsible for the actions of its customer's personal lives?  Better yet, how about the time Mr. Moore walked into a complete stranger's house in Canada simply because the door was unlocked, trying to prove some obscure point. Umm, in America that's called Breaking and Entering and its not only illegal, its a Felony.  I think it is safe to say that these are the same kind of crass, tasteless, twisted and completely unfounded allegations that are present in all Michael Moore's work.  If this is the kind of man that most Americans see as a hero, then this country, as marvelous as it is, is going to the dogs.  Jonathan  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the first of many postings introducing the problem of, what essentially boils down to, a phobia of taking responsibility. By helping others to be aware of this problem, and how serious it is, I hope to counteract and stifle the spreading of this epidemic.  If you have a particular situation to share, have comments of this topic or just think I am totally off the wall (that's okay - it won't be the first time you've been wrong) then let us all know by posting here.  I hope to hear from you!;)  Jonathan
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The divorce rate in America is over 50%.  Wow.  The problem more disturbing than that though, is that people think divorce is okay.  Huh?  Yeah, exactly what I said. But it's a common occurance nowadays and I'm sure all of us know somebody who has divorced. So, what's are the most common reasons?  We're not in love anymore. We're too different. The other person won't change.  Okay, response one. Um, you are never in love. That euphoric feeling you have when you first date somebody is called Limerance and usually lasts anywhere from a few months to 2 years. So what happens after that? You CHOOSE to continue loving that person. So that's not an excuse. (See the book  The Five Love Languages  by Gary Chapman)  Response two. Too different? Why didn't you think about that before you got married? I'll tell you why, you were in Limerance and were blind to/ignored your mate's many 'flaws'.  Response three. Other person won't change. Although this is actually can be true *rarely*, in most cases this is an indication that you are the person unwilling to change. If you are honest with yourself, anyway.  Any other reason is most often connected to the above three, unless it has to do with physical abuse, but that is another matter entirely.  The solution? Don't get married while you're 'in Love'. Be a bit more patient to make sure you know enough about yourself and your partner. This is very big decision to make.  Don't believe me? Ask any divorcee and the legal proceedings that are a part of divorce.  That old adage,  Patience is a virtue , is true...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a conversation yesterday with a friend of mine from Finland. He mentioned Michael Moore (it was all over then, as you well know if you've read the micael moore post) and the 'gun problem' in the U.S.  Now, I have to admit that my friend had a valid point - take the guns away or outlaw them, and deaths attributed to guns should go down. Granted - however, Americans have this little thing called individual freedom and even if they don't ever want a gun, they like the idea they can buy one if they feel it's necessary or decide they do want one.  That being said, assume we outlaw guns and take them away from all American citizens - what have we actually done? We've fixed a side effect to the actual problem. Let's remember that guns don't pick themselves up and shoot somebody randomly. The responsibility lies with the person who shot the weapon.  Okay, you say, what if it was a kid and they didn't know better? Good question, but I have a better one. What was a little kid doing with a gun? If they are in an environment (I'm assuming their home) and they find a gun, geez - all I can say is that the parents themselves (or whoever brought the gun in the home) should be shot. *that was a pun by the way*  Whoever buys and brings a gun into a household has the responsibility to make sure that any children in the house either:    a)Have no possible way of getting ahold of that gun.    b)Are educated on what a gun is exactly and the seriousness of it AND putting it away so that they have no possible way of getting ahold of it.  If you don't do this, you are responsible for what happens.  But wait! you exclaim, what about what you said about how each person is responsible for their own actions??!  A kid doesn't know that fire burns until he/she touches the flame. Likewise a kid doesn't know a gun kills unless you tell them (even then they might not understand) or he/she has the unfortunate experience of using it to kill someone.  But wait! you exclaim again, how do you know when a kid becomes 'responsible'??   That's the million dollar question. I know teenagers that are more mature and responsible than some 40 year olds, and vice versa. I think this is dependant on the person and there is no perfect age or solution to discover when a person is responsible or not unless you really know them.  Of course, if each person in the world took true responsibility for all their actions, this would be a mute point - but no such utopia exists yet...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever heard anyone talk about something they know absolutely nothing about? I'm sure you have, and it's probably as amusing (possibly frustrating) to you as it is to me.  I'm of the opinion that if you don't know [much] about a subject, it's probably best to keep from voicing your views on the matter to others. Take for example, the average American, and the many different views on how money should be handled. This is just me, but unless you are financially so well off that you don't have to work, you shouldn't be telling anyone how they should handle their money. Especially since most Americans spend more than they make in a month, and the average debt for every man, woman and child in America is over $5000.  I'm sure there must be millions of little kids running around, but I also know they don't have credit cards. So for every man, woman and CHILD to have that much debt -- the actual average amount of debt for those who can have debt is significantly higher. (Just a side note, this is unsecured debt [e.g. credit cards] and doesn't include mortgages or car loans.)  But back to the point in question.  Would you take tennis lessons from a brain surgeon? Not a chance. Would you ask Pete Sampras to take out the possible cancerous lump in your brain? Again, no way.  So why is it that people feel so free to talk about what they know nothing about? Sure, its a free country...You can say what you want, free speech and all -- but that doesn't mean you are right, and to someone who actually does know -- you sound like a complete idiot.  And I'm fairly certain that no one intentially wants to look like an idiot.  Just a thought...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those of you who don't know, I am currently studying in Japan at Waseda University. I was in class recently and the teacher mentioned that we would be having a quiz. One of the students spoke up and said that he didn't know about the quiz. The teacher said that it was on the schedule that was handed out to everyone in a previous class. The student said he didn't know that (and very obviously implied that other people didn't either) so nothing could be done and there shouldn't be a quiz.  I was flabbergasted. How is it that a student can tell the teacher what is acceptable in the teacher's class? I couldn't believe the audacity of this guy. He showed absolutely no respect whatsover for this Professor!  Since all this happened in Japanese, there are certain nuances that just don't get translated, but what this guy said and how he said it is like an American saying, "What the fuck? How the hell can we have a quiz? Some of us didn't know about it so it's really pointless to have one." The exact phrase he used, "Shigata ga nai" implies a sense of the decision having already been made and there's nothing [the teacher] could do about it.  That really pissed me off. This guy was trying to bully the professor into not giving us the quiz simply because he didn't want to take responsibility for the fact that he didn't check the schedule beforehand and prepare for class.   Glad nobody checked my blood pressure that day, otherwise I would have been hospitalized.  Now, before any of you people try to assume that I'm a teacher's pet let's get one thing straight. I'm not. In fact I really disliked this teacher, however that is no excuse to disrespect his/her position and the authority he/she holds.  It's time to wake up people. Don't be such a wuss, stand up and just accept the fact you might have made a mistake.  Revolutions of the Mind
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is kind of related to my last post, but thought this was interesting, so here goes...  There was a Harvard University study done on some healthy, independent seniors on what kind of effect positive/negative words had on their physical state of being.  They were tested with some sort of video game where positive or negetive words were flashed on the screen for a predetermined amount of time, but not long enough for it to register consciously.  The result?  The seniors exposed to positive words walked an average of 10% faster than their regular speed.  Huh...amazing...  Oh yeah, the senior exposed to negative words saw no change at all. I wondered at this, but the researcher said this was probably attributable to the fact that most seniors have a negative view of old age in general and are therefore less affected by the negative input.  Just thought that was interesting...  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have any of you ever said a sentence like, "I can't..." or "I must..." perhaps "I have to..."?  Hrm, not a good idea guys. Why not? Well, let's look at what actually happens when you say something.  Wouldn't you agree that how your voice sounds to you is different from how it actually sounds to someone else? I'm sure you know exactly what I mean, especially if you've ever heard your own voice on a recording. The reason for this is that when you hear yourself say something, you hear it with two ears, the inner and outer (not left and right :P ). The effect these words have on you is, basically, to influence your subconcious mind.  I'm sure you can see what I'm driving at now.  By saying, "I can't..." you are sending a message to your subconcious mind that you are unable to do whatever it is that you said. As a result, the next time you try to do something, you have a lack of confidence and if you fail, the experience confirms what you 'knew' to be true already. However, the inverse is also true. By saying, "How can I...?" you send a message that is a catalyst for your subconcious mind to figure out a way to do it.  I think we'd all agree, it's much better to be able to do something and choose not to, that to not be able to do it at all.  So what about the "I must..." or "I have to..."? This goes back to that sense of Responsibility that is lacking from modern society. By saying either of these two phrases (or something similar) you are programming your subconcious to beleive that you have no choice in the matter and therefore no responsibility in the decision.  Not good.  Life doesn't just happen to you. You are where you are in life because of the decisions you made in the past. If you do some serious and honest soul searching you'll realize that this is true, and you have at least some portion of responsibility for what's "happened to you".  So what do you do? Simple...   carpe diem   Jonathan
     
    
</post>


</Blog>