<Blog>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ave,   Well nothing really going on here except me trying to finish everything needed for the German Trip as quickly as possible while listening to classical music!  Check out  urlLink Penny Arcade's take on "Troy"  if you're bored and would like to laugh ^_^.  Ah well, preparation beckons me!  -Aryan
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hail,   Last night I attended a concert at the local youth centre, there were 5 bands playing(all 'punk'). What can I say about this type of music? All I can think of is that it really isn't my type, the instrumental was great, but the vocals...agh..the vocals were screaming, except one band which you couldn't really hear the singer most of the time! Being as my favourite bands(Einherjer, Rammstein, Cake, L'ame Immortelle) the vocals are at least understandable, screaming bands are *not* my favourite.    Well, today we rented "The Last Samurai" as well as "Star Trek: Nemesis". "The Last Samurai" was *great* I mean, really *great*! The movie emphasized Japanese values such as Boshidu, very well in my opinion; very touching as well. "Star Trek: Nemesis" absoulutely the *best* Star Trek movie I have ever seen! It really gets the viewer into the whole experiance; and the ending *OH* the ending... so tragic... I almost cried(looks embaressed)!    Well, time to go visit some message boards! Until next time! -Aryan
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hail.   I've just created this blog after deciding that it'd be best to leave my  urlLink News Page  uncontaminated. I may begin publishing my Commu-Capitalist manifesto using Blogger... it all depends on how well I like using a third-party site to publish my works onto the www... we shall see.    Today I went to a picnic and met with the people responsible for funding my upcoming trip to Germany! Being around those people just reaffirmed my love of Germans! We have finals next week, and that weekend we're leaving for Deutschland, I am *so* excited!! I just hope the guy I'll be living with isn't a dyke.    Well, it's late and I have my hard classes tommarow, so until next blog!(hopefully a little interesting!)                                                                                        -Aryan    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ave,   My mother has finally decided that the windows box's payments are "too much" and so I may not have it too much longer.    At least I have my beloved linux box... Of course I feel bad for my brother who will lose his gaming box, indefinitely.  -Peace for now
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ave,   I am back from Germany..and let me just leave it at it isn't what i expected, and I have canceled my plans to move there; in fact to move anywhere outside of the USA, unless I have a dramatic change of opinion about the people, and their constant anti-americanism mixed with american-wannabeism.    One good thing that came from the trip: Some of my mythology came to me; unfortunately(or not) after talking to Maylilly about it I've realised that it sounds a lot like Genesis. I'll post a copy of it once I am able to express it in a more eloquent form, either that or I'll publish it on my website at least. More good from the trip is, I've evidentally gained a few fishy(freshman) friends..lol...    OH, I also got my OWN(thats right, its just mine) bank account finally, this one my mom can't mess with! On top of this I got Condition Zero! It is a lot better than the constant complaining from some people would have led me to believe, in fact I prefer it over plain CS(1.5 or 1.6).  -Aryan
     
    
</post>


</Blog>