<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So I read a little new article about this rance guy who's got himself a blog and portrays himself as a celebrity of some sort posting incognito.  Good on him, I guess, for creating a little shitstorm of publicity around his site and a little cult around his blog.  I wish I had a cult...heh...  This situation forces me to think a bit about celebrity and why people are so enamored of it.  We love the mystique and the aura that surrounds our famous people, and as a society we need them.  We love to make fun of them, to watch them fall, to adore them and help them rise.  Some people love to walk around feeling superior to them and look down at them past their own insecurities... "Well my life may suck but at least I'm not a nutbag like michael/a cradle robber like demi/a bad actor like so and so".  We also just love to see someone we consider "just a normal person" make good and become bigger than themselves.    The thing society seems to forget is that these people are ALL just normal people, and that we turn them into the things they become.  I have to wonder...would Michael Jackson be the freak that he is if he hadn't spent the majority of his life being surrounded by people who never said "boo" to him?  If someone had pulled him aside when he was like 17 and starting to get a little odd and said "Hey Mike...your cool enough now dude, don't fuck with your face, and by the way...sleeping with children is not cool man.  And hey...instead of buying the elephant man's remains why don't you start a little foundation for people who's daddy's are assholes and treat them like shit, much like happened to you.  And one last thing...here's 450 bucks...go live for a month in some little fleabag rental unit and see how the rest of us have to exist...not only will it ground you again, but it will probably give you some kick ass songwriting material."  Back to Rance... Good on this guy regardless of who he is.  Whether he (she?) truly is some famous or moderately famous actor or just some humorist with a brilliant concept or even, as one person suggested, a writer using his blog as grounds for a book...none of that really matters.  His blog has now become bigger than he is just because of that mystery.  Regardless of who he was before, he is now a famous person; a celebrity and we all will fill with glee at the thought of seeing him rise or fall.  His 15 minutes is here as a blog writer, regardless of whether or not he has another 15 minutes in another guise, and thus he has achieved his goal with the blog.  So everyone who reads this (both of you) go check out his blog and add your little piece of DNA to the organism he has created.  Props to this guy.  My thoughts on who he is (heh...me adding MY DNA to the organism):  IF he is truly an actor my money is on some Canadian expatriot...he writes like a Canadian, or should I rather say he does not write like an American who isn't a writer.  Not that there aren't any American writer/actors, just that there aren't that many and I don't know that any would have the time or need to come up with this little publicity machine.  But...having said that I don't know that I believe he is an actor.  Or she.  I suspect it may be someone who is somehow involved in the entertainment industry, but more as someone in the wings, not one of the front and centers.  But then what the hell do I know.  Heh  Here's his website: http://captainhoof.tripod.com/blog/ 

						
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The smoke billows out from my cigarette, making amorphous shapes that dissipate just shy of making a recognizable shape.  I can imagine the shapes they are going to make, but never get to see them realized.  It always interests me to see how they seem to meet a wall and stop moving where the air pressure and currents change due to the shape of the balcony.  That's where the shapes begin to get interesting, and I toy with it with every puff, trying to invent something new.  The smoke flows in a dirty grey with a tinge of yellow, a color that just screams UNHEALTHY, with little cobwebs trailing off from the boundaries.  The motion sensor light goes out and that poisonous little cloud shape seems much less malignant in the dark.  The deck itself always evinces the thought of brown in my head when I think of it.  The brown leatherette cover over the barbeque, glistening in the rain, the brown deck door and the brown railings.  The brown flower pot with a tinge of green and more brown inside of it, and the brown shingles on the rooflet below my bedroom window.  Even the siding on the apartment is brown, although it's a greying wood brown, and the gutters are brown too.  The gutters are actually the exact same color as the barbeque cover, and even glisten the same way in the humidity.  The only things that aren't brown are the aforementioned plants and the greyish, dirty white flooring (soft in places, and probably not very safe as the brown wood underneath it slowly rots away).  The air smells fresh from the recent rain, and the city is fairly quiet tonite.  I can hear Solitation rustling about in the distance, but I know it isn't me she's coming to visit tonite; she's just letting me know she's there.  The neighbourhood is mostly asleep, having had a good weekend and now getting ready to go back to the grind tomorrow.  I breathe out slowly, the smoke evacuating from my lungs to create more shapes on the air currents.  A slight breeze starts our little wind chime to singing it's melancholy little tune, and I pause to listen.  I breathe the fresh air in, leaving the cigarette in the resting position.  As I breathe out I can see just the slightest tinge of steam forming, but it's no where near as interesting or as  organic as the cigarette smoke.  I step out into the range of the motion sensor light to activate it again, take another puff of my deathstick, and try to form some new shapes. 

						
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It seems that my two days in a row off have turned into two days in a row called into work.  That would be ok, except getting called into work when I'm planning on a day off always puts me in a crappy mood.  That would also be ok, except that on Thursday my girlfriend got a new job.  So she's been in the mood to celebrate.  I'm extremely happy for her, and proud of her cuz it's a booty kicking job, but being called and guilted into working for the 13th and 14th day in a row put me in such a foul mood that I completely rained on her parade.  So now I'm a tired, bummed out assmonkey.  But what are you gonna do?  Tomorrow I will do something nice for her and maybe things will be all kopasetic again.  However I do feel pretty shitty for pissing on her great news.  I didn't mean to, but I did it.    Hey about the word Kopasetic...wtf does it mean?  Where did it come from?  Why do I care?  And speaking of words, I was watching a program just now about purely Canadian words.  I didn't know that Butter Tarts are a purely Canadian thing.  And so is the colloquialism "Shit end of the stick".  A few others struck me as well.  Course I can't remember what they were now...hehe. Ummm...twofour is a canadian term (as in a 2-4 of beer), and so is dipsy-doodle.  Not that I use either of those a whole lot.       Uhhh that's all I got tonite.  RT I await your comments... Oh yeah...i'm still waiting for the word too...  

						
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My head hurts.  I'm not really sure why it hurts, but it hurts.  I spent an hour checking out all the job boards and companies i have bookmarked to check frequently, and then 3 and a half hours sitting on the couch watching Return of the King.  Maybe that's why.  Stress plus sitting in my twisty computer chair plus sitting on my lumpy couch plus 210 minutes of the most amazing cinematography ever equals sore brain pan.  I should be a doctor or something.   I forgot how long Return of the King is.  And how amazingly good.  And how sexually suspect frodo is in the movies (and all this time I thought gandalf was the gay oine).  The same thing bugged me in this movie that bugged me in the books: after all the fighting and the good stuff, there is still like 25 minutes of movie or a hundred and fifty pages of book!  I mean, I understand why, and I am glad that I get to find out something about what happens to the characters after (which is something I  always  think about when I read a book, actually), but come on!  The one thing I always want to know after I read a book, and this one gives it to me and it bugs me.  Wierd, huh?  Having said that tho, it's a pretty small bug.  Actually Frodo's girlishness bugs me more, but I can get past that too.  Not that it's bad to be girlish, just that I always pictured frodo as a kinda rock and roll pot smoker dude.  Like Merry and Pippin only a little more mature.  He is, after all, 33 in the books.  But I digress.  The point I was starting to make before I went off on the Frodo tangent is that in my opinion, the Lord of the Rings trilogy is as close to cinematic nirvana as we've ever seen.    IF   you buy the special extended editions, that is.  Which is the only way to go with these (tonites movie was a rental...i'll wait til the spec ed before I actually buy it).  The direction, the art, the effects, the cinematography, the music...it's all pretty well done.  And to top it all off, it's entertaining too.  And not even all "Hollywooded" down to a 2 hour package.  Back to the special edition vs the normal one... I always wonder about these people who pissed and moaned when they bought the Fellowship disc then had to buy the special edition too cuz they bought too soon.   That alone doesn't make me scratch my head so much as the fact that they DID THE SAME THING WITH THE SECOND ONE (Dumbasses) and bitched about that.  And THEN they bought this one on Tuesday when it came out.  Seriously WTF are you thinking people?  And then there's this guy...comes into the store today and buys RotK on both DVD and VHS, because he was gonna watch the VHS and keep the DVD in it's wrapping until it goes up in value.  I didn't have the heart to tell him that they produce 3394883920284387329209 copies of this all on dvd, and it's gonna take a LOOONNNGGGGG time for all of them to deteriorate enough for his copy to be worth anything.  But whatever floats your boat I guess.  My head hurts lots so I'm gonna stop here.  Kinda sucks too cuz I was on a roll.  

						
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As I was looking into the dark gray abyss of a switched off plasma screen today, a thought occured to me.  For hundreds of years the seller really did make all the rules in the exchange of money for goods or services.  We did what we had to as consumers because that was the way it was.  Don't like your bank's interest rate? Too bad, so sad.  Electronics cost alot? Well that's just what they cost.  The seller had a product, and really the only differentiator between his and someone else's was how long it lasted.  You paid more for a longer life one, but that's just the way it worked.  You always knew that more money=lasts longer and better quality.  Of course you had to rely on the seller's integrity to know that you were getting a good product; one just couldn't know lots about everything you may have to buy.  The information age has changed all that.  Need a new widget?  Google it!  See what the best one is.  See what the best price is on the best one.  See what other consumers think about it.  See what kind of service vendor A gives vs. vendor B.  Woohoo... all that knowledge in 10 minutes!  As consumer's our education level is exponentially higher in every purchase than it was 20 years ago.  Not only has our education level increased, but so have our expectations.  The great differentiator is now "how much bang do I get for my buck?".  We all know the rules have changed, and not only that, but the rule  maker   has changed.  No longer does the vendor say how it's gonna be and we as consumer sheep just go along with it.  Now  WE  make the rules up, and we decide who gets our business.  The products are all made pretty much the same.  There is very little difference in quality between a Sony, Toshiba, Panasonic or Hitachi DVD player nowadays.  There is also not much difference in price.  But at what cost does this newfound power come?  It occurs to me that besides education the other thing the information age has given us is the twitch factor.  What is the Twitch Factor?  It is the decline of our attention span and our need to flit from idea to idea; instant gratification is no longer something cool, but a demanded normalcy of modern life in the western world.  We twitch all the time...when we're gaming, when we're driving, when we're flicking thru 300 channels of shit on the TV, when we choose and design our living space.  We twitch all the time, and between that and our newfound power over the vendor we haven't noticed that they are  still setting the rules !    Think about it.  My last TV was a 1200 dollar, 250 pound monster console television from about 1980 with a 30 inch screen.  It lasted until 2003 and would have lasted another 5 years if I wanted it to.  I replaced it with a 50" 180 pound 2500 dollar wide screen high definition CRT projection TV that will last me maybe 10 years if I'm lucky.  Of course, I'll replace it with a flat panel of some kind within 5, and the vendor knows this.  He KNOWS I will twitch again in 5 years and replace my beautiful-massive-panoramic-high-resolution-that-cost-as-much-as-a-house-50-years-ago television with a Beautiful-thin-panoramic-high-resolution-that-cost-as-much-as-a-house-30-years-ago television.  So he built it to HIS specs, not mine.  He built it to start to look bad in a few years.  He built in obsolescence.  He changed the rules on broadcast itself. And then he changed those rules again.  I am now a corporate shill for the television manufacturers and the broadcasters, and my twitch factor will only increase.  And the vendor knows this too.  Remember your first VCR?  You paid 800 dollars for it and it lasted you like 15 years.  Buy a DVD player today, it will cost you 100 dollars and wear out in 4 years.  Not that it matters, because with BluRay and other new media formats in the pipe it will be obsolete in 2.  And you can't record with it.  Of course, you could buy a DVD Recorder for 500 bux that is pretty cool (probably my next purchase...).  The Recorder will also need replacing in a few years.  Back to the basic DVD player.  Suppose this is your first DVD player.  You're gonna take it home, go rent Return of the King and be UTTERLY FUCKING AMAZED at how good DVD looks.  But now your fucked and our good ol' vendor knows this.   (twitch)  ...what the hell are those black bars on the top and bottom of the TV.  What? Oh I need a widescreen TV?  Ok.  Well since it's gonna be widescreen I may as well get it HiDef ready too...  (twitch)  ...well DVD sure looks and sounds awesome on my new TV, but everyone says it's better in 5.1 surround.  I best get one of those....  (twitch)  ...WHAT? Movies are in 6.1 and 7.1 now?  And on this new format that looks even better?  Now I need a new DVD player, new speakers for sure and probably a new reciever, and what's that you say?  Broadcast is no longer limited to 720p lines of resolution so I need a HIGHER definition TV?  Well Hot Damn! Sign me UP! Let me just google it first to see which one is the best...  So there you go.  This is just one industry, one example.  I could give others too.  The rules have changed alright.  Now instead of the Vendor making all the rules for buying stuff, the vendor makes all the rules for buying stuff and you  think  you're the one making the rules.  Kinda like my g/f (lol).  Well Twitch away people.  It makes the world go on.  The only concern is the waste all this short term obsolescence creates.  But I'm not an environmentalist, per se, so I'm not gonna bother about blogging about that.   

						
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I forgot to post a blog last night.  Damn I suck.  Guess I get to do a double long one tonite then.     

						
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I seem to have nothing of import to say tonite.  Even freefalling my brain is numb.  GG MacDonald's for lunch!  See kids...this is what eating crap food does for you...makes u stupid and uncreative.  Maybe a bowl of branflakes will help...  I often wonder how some people get their jobs.  You get these guys in the sales world who's only method of selling stuff is to dump the price below cost...seems like a pretty sad way to do business to me.  I mean...I guess if you can look in the mirror and be ok with yourself having no skillz at all in your job, well then good on you.  Me, I need to feel good about what I do.  Damn integrity... life would be a heck of a lot easier if I just didn't give a shit; if people could be like tools to me and I could use them for my ends and not worry two squirts about whether or not their interests are being looked after as well.    Then there are the people who do fuck all except write a good report and make a good presentation to the boss.  I get these reps all the time who don't know shit, rarely show up, and never tell me anything to help me sell their product.  Now I was a rep for a long time, and a damn good one at that.  I never kissed the bosses ass or played the politics game, but my customers loved me and learned from me and developed huge loyalty to the product I sold.  And it got me laid off.  The guy who took over my position has never been seen by my former customers... go figure.  Nice to know that slackery will get you everywhere.  Having said all that, in the end of it all I know that I will come out ahead of these tools, if not financially at least when the balance sheet is measured at the end of it all.  Which may be sooner rather than later with Nikita Bush and Adolf Rumsfeld in charge of the US of A.  But that's a whole 'nother blogg... 

						
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's that time of the night where the city is all but silent, except for that low rumble that is consistent and omnipresent.  It permeates everything, the very air, and it almost seems offended when some jackass interrupts it's conversation to shout or whoop or scream obscenities or sing drunken songs.  Every city I've ever been to, big or small, has a point in the night like this.  It is both melancholy, yet strangely warming and soothing at the same time.  A car hisses by on the street and it seems like it is trying desparately not to disturb the city's chant.  Deep in the distance a train or a boat sounds it's horn, but the city doesn't seem to mind too much.  This is the hour of which songs are written and stories begun.  This is the hour where in the movies some sad saxophonist or harmonica player starts to blow some incredibly soulful and beautiful piece and the movie watcher is able to completely feel every note ripped from his or her heart.  It is "Solitation time" as in solitary meditation.  I feel the pulse of this organism when this point of night hits, and it's one of my favorite times to think or stand out on the balcony and smoke.  Wrapped completely in solitation, I can absorb the heartbeat of the city and let it's blood and smog scrape away my frustration and loneliness, giddiness and exhaustion, happiness and bliss, leaving my core open to rebirth itself with all the previous day's (week's? month's?) shit whisked between the buildings and down the streets.  The catharsis of this cleansing usually can last me weeks, but unfortunately it's often longer than weeks between the times when Solitation's people and my people can arrange a meeting.    I can NOT seek solitation, because to do so would be to destroy the magic it gives me...ask the above mentioned sax or harp player, they'll tell you.  If you seek this muse, you will be disappointed, and the promised cleansing and creative flow will just not happen.  Should you catch up with her she'll kick u in the nuts, usually in the form of a siren or car accident a block away.  But most likely you just won't catch her at all.  Solitation just comes, often when you desparately need it, but sometimes just when it misses you and feels the need to see you.  Think of her as a slut, and you as her booty call.  But there is no way you could ever turn her down.  Nor would you want to...she gives the best loving you can imagine and you know it.  Solitation came to visit me a bit ago, but I was too agressive with her and she has left now.  She may come back tonight, but I doubt it.   More than likely we are just plain done now, until her next visit.  The brief cleansing I recieved will last me a day or two and it is up to me to get the most out of that; to let the residue of the city's soap last as long as I can.  Until her next visit.      

						
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...begins again.  I get the unparalleled joy of 7 days in a row working for near slave wages now.  ARGH WTF is wrong with me?  I can't get outta this cycle of negativity that's been sucking the life outta me for like 2 years.  I don't see any future past the next paycheck, and that's not a good place to be in.  I mean I see a future, I just don't see any details.  I've always had this feeling I was destined for something better than this... but what that something is is completely beyond my site.    Watched big fish tonite... See in my head i'm a big fish...and yet...my head is a pretty small pond, if u know what i mean.  Wait...that kinda sounds like I think I'm stupid...not quite what I meant.  Oh well.  Did I ever tell you about the time...   

						
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   First Saturday off in a long while.  Today was a bit of a crappy day weather wise, but I had an ok day, I guess.  Other than the fact that I found out the job I thought I would get with Bell was filled by someone else, and that my backup plan at the same company, a Mat leave fill in for a year or so, is gonna be filled internally.  Which kinda put me in a pisser.  This whole getting my career back on track thing really is starting to feel like swimming through peanut butter, but without the yummy fat and the peanut buttery taste.  I decided to check out the website of a wireless company that will be launching in Canada soon, but they have no Canadian site yet.  So that's on the back burner.  Do I make a move to Calgary for a job?  I don't really want to, but I may have to.  I have some contacts, and Calgary is where all the action is happening these days.  But man...winter...yech.  I mean I dig winter, but only if I can drive away from it at the end of the day.  And prairie dry air.  Goodbye perfectly coiffed hair (HAH! Like that ever actually happens).  Goodbye sparkling singing voice.   The other downer about moving to alberta would be the end of the band...not that we're going anywhere quickly, but it is the one consistent bit of joy I get in my somewhat stressful life of late.    So I guess it's time to actually start weighing all these cons with the pros and start sending rezzies to Calgary companies anyways.  I guess if I get a job offer I can always make the move decision then...   

						
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...the job search SUX ASS!  There is just nothing out there that fits my profile these days.  Fourteen gazillion job sites and they all have the same six jobs that I'm either: A) unqualified for, B)Over qualified for C)Not the least interested in.  I seem to have this problem where I know what kind of career I DON'T want more than I know what I DO want.  Oh well...the shizzle falls where it's pooped, I guess.  I guess I oughtta get my ass ready for my lame McJob now, so I can make my 10.50 an hour by being treated like scum by junkies and skids.  Yay for downtown Vancouver!    Damn I'm negative today...sheesh... Snap outta it.  

						
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yeah...just what it says.  It's 12:31 AM and thus i blog.  Perhaps tomorrow will be a better day than today.  Not that today was bad...   

						
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...somewhere along the line here I haven't lost my nut completely.  Like...has my mental health deteriorated enough for people to think I'm crazy?  Because sometimes I sure feel like I'm crazy.  I've gone a long long time without alot of good things happening and without getting a lot of the necessary things for good mental health.  So I sometimes wonder if I've approached and perhaps crossed that line.  Of course, now I'm taking the necessary steps to alleviate some of that, starting with my diet and moving on through getting excercise and all that.    But still I wonder.  I was watching "The Next Action Star" last night (yeah, yeah I know...reality tv...what can I say, I'm sucked in), and a couple of things occured to me.  First of all, during their acting class they all had to discuss an object that holds sentimental value to them, and go deep into the memory of it.  Well I don't even HAVE such an object.  I really don't feel sentimental attachment to anything, and own nothing that signals strong growth in my life.  Isn't that kind of wierd?  I have no talisman. Hrmm.    The other thing that occured to me as I watched this lame reality show is that the psycho chick Viviana is not so different from me.  Much as I loved to hate her, she reacts to situations very similar to the way I do, although much much MUCH more exaggerated.  I thought of this moments after it hit me that she was a total nutcase and not in control of her mental situation at all.  So that made me wonder about MY mental situation.  Now I am concerned.  I guess in the end all I can do is do what I do and do it til it's done.  But it certainly is time for me to keep a watch on where my head is at, especially if I want to make myself a niche somewhere that allows me to succeed.  Pretty hard to succeed anywhere when everyone notices that you're a nutbag...  

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I didn't go to the gym.  I woke up with another freakin migraine, and have stayed at home being lame all day.  I don't work til later tomorrow tho, so I'll go tomorrow to make up for it.    Went to some blog site this morning and he spent the whole blog explaining how Michael Moore made everything up in Fahrenheit 9/11.  Now, it seems to me that this guy should pull his head out of his ass and do a little research.  First of all, Moore has never hidden from the fact that this is purely and op/ed piece.  So of course the facts in it are contexted to his side of the story.  Second of all, this bonehead on the blog goes on to talk about how Bush didn't stay reading to kids for 7 minutes or whatever it is after he got the news, and how Bush didn't welcome in al qaida members to texas and how Bush doesn't have relationships with the Bin Laden family.  Uhhh...dumbfuck...it's all available to you if you look, and everything you contested you're wrong about.    I almost commented to this guy that he's an idiot, but I thought 'Nah...let him think what he thinks.'  It's not my job to go around correcting people, and frankly if this guy is that brainwashed by republican propaganda, all my comments are going to do is piss him off.  So I didn't bother.    Now, I'm not saying that I believe every word Michael Moore says like it's gospel or something...I know he edits things to get his point across.  But I am smart enough to do the research and figure out the wheat from the chaff.  I totally agree with Michael Moore's way of thinking, just not always his defense of his arguments.  Regardless of whether you believe everything Moore tells you or not, George Bush is the biggest threat to world peace since Adolf Hitler.  And that's just commonly available facts telling me this.    Having said all that, I haven't actually seen Fahrenheit yet...I'm gonna wait for the video, cuz why bother paying 25 bux to see a documentary?  So...having not seen the movie who's to say that I have the slightest clue of what I speak? Hehe 

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, I did make it to the gym today; I was going to post right when I got home but I ended up doing other important stuff (looking at porn, playing counterstrike, you know...).  I didn't make my 40 minutes on cardio like i had said, but did 35 so that's pretty close.  And I did the circuit as well, and my muscles are nicely exhausted now.  I tried not to go too hard and make myself in pain tomorrow...we'll see.  I did get a very good stretch in, so that's good.  We had our national election today, and I guess I'm happy with the results.  The party I did NOT want to win didn't; the Conservatives winning the election here would have been tantamount to electing a puppet for bush only one more dangerous to Canada's way of life.   I feel Canada does need a change in government, however, so I was a little dissappointed that the Liberals won.  The good thing is that it was a Liberal minority, so the checks and balances that our system of government is supposed to offer by nature will actually be there.  Unlike our provincial government which has such a huge majority they've become like dictators.    Although I don't disagree too much with the provincial Liberals goals, their methods seem counter productive to me.  I quite strongly believe that cutting social programs, arts and education to balance the budget makes for short term gain but long term hurt.  If you remove the future, the safety net, and the entertainment from a society you have not much left but a mad scramble for the crumbs dropped our way, and no way for people to forget about it or things to look forward to.  In the near term we may have a strong provincial economy, but ten years from now we will be royally fooged.  We will have a half assed american style education system churning out automatons with no skills or abilities, we will have huge burdens on the already stressed health care system, and we will have no way for people in trouble to get out of trouble.  Not that we ever really had an effective example of that last one there.  But there should be ways to creatively solve some of the problems present in our province now, without slashing and burning the shit out of everything.    Ah well...in the end I am no politician, and don't really have a corner on the knowledge market as far as the subtleties of how our province is run.  Shit I can't even balance my own budget...heh.  Tomorrow I go to the gym again...tonight i eat chips. :D  

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   In keeping with my plan to rejoin the world of non-unsuccessful people, it occurs to me that a big part of moving forward is getting the mind into good health.  A huge part of getting the mind into good health includes getting the body into good health.  So I'm going back on a workout regimen.  For years and years I was quite serious about fitness in general, and body building specifically.  I was never aiming to be a competitive muscle head or anything, but I thoroughly enjoyed a good sweat at the gym and pumping a bit of iron.  I hurt my shoulder on an inclined bench press, and just never got back into it again after that.  So now it's time to start that up again.  I'm about 15 pounds overweight right now, and completely weak.  So it's back to a gym mentality for me.  Perhaps yoga too, eventually; Sylvie loves yoga and maybe it's something we can do together.  Of course I got to get a bit of dough before I can do that.  But the Gym rat thing I can do, as I have a membership I've never cancelled.  Today, once I finish this post, I'm going to go start my laundry and then head down to the gym.  I'm going to spend 40 minutes on a cardio machine and then do the little circuit training dealio.  I won't push it too hard, as I don't want to just make myself extremely sore for tomorrow, but I will try and get a good sweat on and maybe move some muscles other than my jaw for a bit.  I will then do a good 20 minute stretch and walk back home.  I'll post on here after about how I did.  Tomorrow, I will do the same thing, and then Wednesday, Thursday I work.  Next Monday I start my new job on Monday, so I'm going to get up early and go to the gym before hand.  And Tuesday and Wednesday.  After that point I will endeavor to go to the gym before work every Monday Tuesday and Wednesday.  I will leave Thursday, Friday, Saturday and Sunday for the time being.  If I can get in that habit for 3 days a week, it can only be a good thing.  We'll see...  

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So this damn holy war is gonna be the end of humanity if something doesn't cause some peace soon.  The Jews and the Muslims kick the shit out of each other, and the Christians stick their nose in (just like they have for thousands of years)making everyone even madder.  The Buddhists sit on mountains and watch and pray for peace, but don't really accomplish much else.  And although this war is supposedly based on religion, we all know in the end it's actually based on land rights.    So I have a solution.  Let's wall off Saskatchewan and Northern Quebec.  We give the Palestines Saskatchewan and the Jews Northern Quebec (or the other way around...).  Nobody lives in those two places anymore anyways, so why the hell not?  Not only that, if Quebec starts talking about separation again, we just tell the Moslems that the Quebecois are defiling their god, and they go in and kick some butt.  I think this is a fair solution for everybody.  The 25 or so Canadians that get displaced we just give them a nice home wherever else they want in Canada, along with a big tax break.  Maybe a hundred litres of free gas too.  And a case of Molson's.    Obviously some ground work would have to be laid first.  We would have to completely dismantle all the holy buildings and reinstall them in their new home.  The buildings that both the Arabs and the Jews feel are theirs we just split in half.  That way the people who are fighting now get MORE land than they had before, the freedom to do with it as they will, way better natural resources to work with, their holy places, and no contact with their sworn enemy.  The plus side to all this is that the Americans can go and secure the damn pipelines which are so fucking precious to Mr. Bush and his robber baron buddies.  We then turn all of the holy land into a completely off limits shrine, where Jews can visit some days and Moslems on other days.  You wanna go sit on the sacred soil, get a pass, a flight from regina, a battery of shots and go nuts.  Your pass will tell u what days u can go visit, and if you go on other days, well...you may face some nastiness.    I don't think it would take much of a buyout to convince the saskatchewan government of the validity of this plan, and the northern quebecers wouldn't be able to read the contract properly so we can pull one over on them pretty easily.  As far as the Jews and the Palestinians are concerned, we don't even have to tell them...just put them all to sleep or something and when they wake up in their new home with the wailing wall right there, away they go.  Or, we could use Uncle Sam's might to go in and say this is the way it is, and if you don't like it we're gonna Bertuzzi you like we did to Iraq.  Although, that may just incite more violence against westerners.  Perhaps it would be better to just draw up the plans and then ask them nicely if they'll agree.  If they won't agree, demand to know what they need to make this work.  It could happen... 

						
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's election time in Canada.  The Corpocracy must do it's thing and elect the next government here based solely on who had the most money to spend.  As we near the end of the world of democracy and closer to a total corporate governance, many people wonder why the hell we even bother to vote.  We who do vote end up voting for the guy we fear or hate the least.  None of them do anything for ME as a person, so I have to choose who works with the corporate entities who I align with best.  And who has the least offensive platform.  Sad, really.    So, politics in the western world face two downfalls: Corporate control and lack of concern for citizens.  They all say they worry about Canada, but they worry about THEIR Canada.  Not the Canada the rest of us live in, those of us who don't take corporate handouts and have to keep big business happy so they stay here.  "Tax cuts for big business! Lower health care to pay for the deficit! Destroy arts programs so the next big nuclear power co. can get the funding needed to build it's facility!  Who gives a rats ass about the middle income and lower income working stiffs?  Yeah, they are the majority of voters, but it's easy...we just disallow any parties who would work for them from being in any media, and then buy all the advertising we can knocking the other guys who advertise.  We're a shoo in to win!"   Sigh...as you can see I'm somewhat tired of the way politics happen and the amount of crap i'm hearing from all the parties vying for the big chair.  Yes, I am oversimplifying things, and yes I am aware that political leadership does require pandering to many different interests...doesn't mean I have to like it or agree with it.  I am a Utopianist, indeed.  But I wish to maintain that utopic view because I truly believe at my deepest core that governments CAN find a way to look after both their people and their business.  Not to mention foreign affairs, which is a whole 'nother ball of bees.  I hope that on Monday Canada does not allow the bad guys to win the election, but it's kind of hard for me to pick out the good guys.  For the first time in my life, I'm probably going to vote for the far left just because the present far right scares the hell out of me about the future of human rights and foreign policy in this country, and the middle have proven themselves to be pretty bad managers with loads of fiscal irresponsibility.    In my particular corner of the world, I happen to quite like our incumbent MP Hedy Fry, but she's aligned with the bad manager group, and I gotta vote for the country not just my neighbourhood.  Hrmm...does that last statement invalidate the rest of this post about how they don't govern for me??   

						
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, it's done.  After 7 years of being associated with Microcell in one way or another I have left now.  It is certainly a weight off my shoulders, what with all the issues I've been having there of late.  On July 5 I start my new job at Roger's part time, and I'm kind of excited about it.  It's been many many years since I was in a direct B2B type of sales role, and I welcome the challenge.  I don't know that this is my career bliss, but I also don't know that it isn't.  So we'll see.  I'll take a couple of months and explore it, see how I dig it and if I can make any scratch doing it.  One thing that kind of shook me yesterday when I went in to do all the paperwork is that two of the people who worked at a previous gig I had are there.  Tina and Bruce I worked with both at the furniture place, and they're ok people I guess.  I was just surprised to see Tina there yesterday in charge of all the commissions and paperwork stuffs.  She says the professionalism of this company is miles beyond the last one we worked together at, so that's a good thing.  Now just to kick some ass and make some headway so I can completely quit my sucky retail job.  That would be a very much good thing.  I have never worked in a purely commission environment before, so this will be a gas to see how much I make when I write my own paycheques.  The only concern is where my head is at these days, and if I can bring it on or not.  The idea of working with Bruce and Tina again makes me think of how everything tends to be circular.  For 7 or 8 years I've been going in various circles; working at a place, moving up, moving up, moving on, turning around and going back in an entry level position.  And here I am again in another circle, although a smaller one.  I worked with those two people 18 months ago, left, did a little loop-dee-loop and here we are again.  Hopefully it will work out better than it did last time.  Alls I know for sure about the future is that leaving fido has lifted a bit of a weight off, and I feel somewhat free.  Perhaps I've put a new weight back on, but perhaps not.  We shall see.   

						
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As I was sitting on a patio today drinking a frosty beverage and watching the denman street beach crowd walk by, it occured to me that virtually everyone who passed us had a bottle of water.  Now, they didn't all have the same kind of water, but they all had water.  Well, not all of them, but most of them.  As the world's population grows and the fresh water supply dwindles in both supply and quality, bottled water has become a mega industry.  Most every corner store sells some form of it, as do drug stores, coffee shops, etc.  So... why not open a water bar?  You could have all the different brands at reasonable prices, to go or to drink inside.  It could be set up like a wine tasting place, with different comments for the different brands and genres of water; kind of a water conneusuer joint.  Obviously, you would also need to make it a place where people want to go for their water all year round, not just on hot days, so your selection would have to include specialties as well.    If one set such a business up in the proper place (I'm thinking some place full of both yuppies and beaches/outdoor activities), it would be a winner for a period of time.  HEck, you might even create a trend...   something to think about...  

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It is sooo hot here right now...like 30 degrees, which for june in Vancouver is uber hot.  It's like old people dying heat.  Not that I'm complaining...it's all good.  Well, not the people dying bit, but the walking around in shorts and a t-shirt bit and going to the beach and seeing beautiful babes in abundance.    So today I will call and quit my fido job and accept the job I was offered last week.  I don't know if it's the right decision or not, but hey...life begins when you jump off the cliff, right?  I've been reacting miserably for so long career wise that it's time to get my booty bouncing and take control of the situation.  So I may be taking a pay cut for a couple weeks, but at my low pay that's not all that painful anyways.  For the amount I was working at the job i'm quitting, I only need to sell 2 pieces a month to make it up...that's not so bad or difficult.    I haven't been getting my one post per night here lately...for whatever reason I think of cool things to write all day while i'm out and about and then I get home and I blank.  So I've got to get that creative ball rolling again as well.  There's a point one reaches when you're doing something creative (be it music, writing, art, whatever) where a burst of clarity hits and things make sense.  Problems can be solved and stress can be relieved, and it is that same feeling that one should strive for at all times in your life.  My whole point in writing this blog was to have an outlet to access that, to reach that point quickly and consistently and maintain it for long enough to ease the stresses of everyday life.  Hmmm...Perhaps I've been having trouble because I spend too much time trying to think of witty and intelligent things to write and not thinking about the free association flow that I originally meant this to be.    This issue gets back to my post about success and uberness and the part about having a vision and then maintaining it.  I seem to have lost some of the vision I had for this little endeavour, and I need to regain that now.  Which is, I guess, what I am doing in this particular post.  Now to keep this vision consistent and ongoing.  That's the hard part.  I don't know why I worry about what I write or how it's written; it's not like ANYBODY reads this stuff except me... and yet I do worry about it, and the result of that is that I lose the path.  Well, I'm gonna strive to not do that any more.  /me puts his foot down!  Back to the heat...time for me to put on my shorts and go out and find some foodage.  Maybe i'll see some pretty girls half naked too... don't tell my girlfriend...  

						
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Wow it's been hot the past couple of days here.  It feels like old-people-and-sick-people-dying-and-people-getting-heat-rage-and-flipping-out heat.  It's probably not that hot but it's felt it to me.  Yesterday we went out and did a little walking around Granville St and then West 10th ave just for fun.  By the time we got home later in the evening I was in the throes of full blown heat stroke; headache, nausea, everything sore, and constant lightheadedness.  Now personally, I think heat stroke is worth it; I usually get it the first uber hot day that I get to play each years, and it signals the start of the summer for me.  I did indeed drink about 3 litres of water, so I didn't dehydrate, and I did have my hat on, so I took my precautions.  But still I got uncomfortably warm.  No biggie, cuz I probably won't get that again this year.  A hot summer day in Vancouver is a beautiful thing for people watching.  Everyone is feeling groovy and happy and walking with a smile on their face.  The beaches are jam packed with beautiful people wearing small amounts of clothing, and the parks are full of people having fun.  The buildings and colors of the city are all fantastic too.  Everywhere u go you see people having fun, and even the streetskids seem to be in a better mood.  I dig it.    I don't seem to have anywhere to go with this little bit of writing, so I'll stop here I guess.  Gotta get ready for work anyways.  

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   OMG I'm tired.  This is two days in a row I've had trouble sleeping at night and had to get up at like 6 AM for work.  And then tonite right after work I must drive out to New Westminster for some recording.  I'm stoked about it, except I just hope I have the energy to kick ass.  As I said...I'm tired.  Got a job offer yesterday...sort of.  It's a company who I had turned down an offer from about 18 months ago.  Now I remember why I turned them down: they seem reluctant to take any accountability for my income.  Purely commission outside sales just doesn't appeal to me all that much.  They have presented it in such a way that it allows me to keep my already part time job pretty much the same as it is now tho, so I may say yes.  I figure it can't hurt, except for loss of some free time which I don't particularly need right now anyways.  If I can make a bit of cash I come out ahead.  If I don't dig it, it's easy to quit.  So I'll quit the job at fido with the racist boss which only gives me 8 hours a month (much as I enjoy that job and that company, I can't stay in the location I'm in anyways).  And set some hours ground rules at LD and then kickus bootayus selling b2b wireless data solutions.  Or fail miserably.  Whichever.  Man it's hard to think coherently when you're this tired...day off tomorrow thank christ...  

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I put a couple of links on my Blog site that I thought were worthy.  The first one is my band's website.  Although we don't have jack shit for content yet, we will, and when we do it will be the boomba.  Check out and see if you can guess which cat is I.  If your curious about the music (since we don't have any up at this point), we do original hard rock...two guitars, bass, drums.  Our influences are vast and many, seeing as we're all dudes in our mid thirties.  I don't know that you could come up with a sound reference; at times we are mellowish southern rock kinda sound and at other times we are hardcore heavy like tool.  We like to experiment with sounds and alternative structures etc, but through it all we strive to maintain a good song structure that will get the people up on the dance floor shaking their booties.  So check it out, but don't expect a lot yet.  The second is my King's of Chaos army recruiting page.  KoC is an online turn based game that I play just to kill time sometimes.  Check it out, join my army and kill bad guys.  This game requires absolutely no effort, except to go to the site and spend the money you've earned and attack people if you want to.  You don't actually do anything except tell it to attack the player you chose, and it's all text based.  So if you need a way to kill a minute or more, sign up and go.  I'll add more relevant links as they come up.   

						
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As I was walking across Burrard bridge today, it occured to me that one of my favorite things about spring and summer is bikeboobs.  You know...girls bicycling wearing a normally sedate and conservative top, but because they're bent over their handlebars everyone they pass gets a full on downblouse shot.  I dig that.  Alot.  Does that make me pervy?  If so, I guess I'm pervy.  But I believe every guy out there loves the chance at a sneaky glance at something they aren't supposed to see.  It gives our girlfriends and wives endless hours of joy to have a reason to punch us in the shoulder or squirt lime in our eye.  It also gives us a little heartrate increase, and that can only be good.  Unless your near dead with heart problems i guess.  Speaking of squirting lime in the eye, I got that little bit from that corona commercial.  The couple is sitting on the beach, a hottie walks by and the guy's head follows her.  After a second or two the girl reaches in and pulls the lime outta his corona bottle and squirts him in the eye.  I love that commercial; it is SO me and my girlfriend.  Except I'd probably drool too.  Cuz I'm pervy, as we determined one paragraph up.  Uh...yeah that's all I got tonite.  Sorry.   

						
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "Looking for Pootie?"  That was the title of some spam e-mail I got today and I thought it was pretty funny.  Pootie is a very funny word, I think, and deserves some recognition.  We're all quick to dismiss pootie as just another laughable slang, but really, it's much more powerful than that.  So long live the Pootie Power.    Im gonna start using pootie as a word when I can't think of any other words.  Like when your fixing something and u can't find that tool u can never think of the name of:  "Hey have u seen my pootie?"   Or when you're running late and forgot one thing and you shout to the person behind you:  "Hey...grab my pootie will you?"  Or even when your dinner tastes like something you can't place: "That tastes like pootie!"  Seriously, though, I never actually opened my pootie spam.  I get like 10-20 spam e-mails a day...man if I answered them all, by now i'd be rich, incredibly sexed up, and have the biggest weewee ever.  Not only big, but it could stay hard all year long with all the cheap and free V1@gr@.  And why the heck do they use the netspeak for viagra all the time?  It's obvious the spam filters don't work so well, so just spell it proper you spammers.  Do you think you're intelligent or sneaky by changing the text?  Does it make me more inclined to open your bandwidth wasting tripe? NO!  So just stop it.    If I was king of the world (see my post on the Samurai Pharmacist for my methods of attaining that position), I would pass a law that would force all spam companies to buy squippy new computers for everyone they spammed.  At least until they run out of money.  Then I'd make the lame ass bastards wash my car.  And my dishes.  Yeah!   Yeah, OK it was a bit of a lame blog, but what are you gonna do?  Go have a bowl of pootie and get over it.   

						
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It occurs to me that part of my problem in my job hunt has been that i've kind of been waiting for something to come to me; for someone to bring me the position I'm looking for.  Yeah, sure, I've made some half assed efforts to grab something unique and awesome, but for the most part I've been waiting for someone to say "Here...take this ball and run with it.  It's the ball you've been kinda hoping you'd get, and I want you to have your opportunity with it."  Of course, real life doesn't actually work that way; if I want to play with that ball, I best intercept the pass next time it's thrown.  See, I've spent some time thinking about the difference between the ultra successful and the not so successful.  What makes one person in "x" industry worth tons of money and incredibly happy, while another makes a mediocre salary or wage and goes to "work" to collect a paycheck?  The easy answer is doing what you love makes everything else gravy.  But there's more to it than just that.  What is that extra little something that separates the Gates', Trump's, Bezos' of the world from a 50 grand a year employee in their company? The employee may very well love his/her job just as much.  They may be just as bright, creative, skilled and with similar leadership qualities.  So what is the X factor that makes the difference?  Well, if I had that answer, my name would be in that list as well.    I think one factor that plays here is vision.  One thing the best people at anything have in common is that they are visionaries; they think completely outside the box, come up with a masterful vision and then (and this is where I start to differ) they stick to that vision thru it's completion.  Which is the second factor I can determine:  Focus.  While I've spent the last couple of years waiting for someone to hand me a mondo groovy career and pining and whining for the last one, I've completely lost my focus.  I haven't got a clue what my career goals were five years ago (or my life goals for that matter) I only know that I haven't attained them.  So, before I can reach the success I've always known I'm destined for (this is not arrogance, btw, this is just something I've known since I had conscious thought...)I must address this cancerous laziness that's been feeding on itself in my head.  This blog is part of that, although I kind of made the decision subconsciously.  I have, however, now vocalized my goals with this blog and the role it will play in my hunt for success.  OK, so let's see here.  I've determined that success needs the following ingredients (in no particular order as they're all inter-related): 1) Love what you do--I've always had this; I've quit many a job because I didn't love the industry or the job. 2) Be intelligent--I feel I have a certain amount of this. 3) Be creative-- well, I am a musician, and I have my blog, so that's got to be an inate ability of mine (not because of the blog, but because I've always done creative things) 4) Have a vision -- Ok I need to work on this...I got to find my vision--see need #3. 5) Focus -- My big weakness right now...perhaps this blog will help with this one... 6) Stop waiting to react and start forcing a reaction.  This one is KEY to my happiness in my career right now I believe.  So I need to determine the steps to begin this process.   7) Look forwards, not backwards -- This has been a bit of a problem for me the past 8 months or so...time to stop that little self destructiveness...  So now I have to start applying these known needs...if anyone out there reads this (like that happens...) and can think of some other needs, please post them in a comment, will ya?  Thanks...  This will be a continuing thread for a bit, methinks... though not necessarily all at once...I have other thoughts to write as well...  

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well tomorrow is day 3 of my three days in a row off, and it's time to get back to the job hunt.  I've enjoyed slacking yesterday and today, but I really really REALLY need to find myself a good job in my field.  Failing that, just a good job that works monday to friday and pays well will make me happy.  So my plan tomorrow is to call the dude who offered me a job like 18 months ago that I turned down for a different job (one of the biggest mistakes I've made in the past 2 years), surf my job sites for new openings, and send off a total of 6 resume's and cover letters.  Perhaps tomorrow is the day that something clicks.  Fingers crossed.  How come no one comments on my blogs???  :(   

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   On a sunny day, downtown Vancouver is the most beautiful place in the world...at least that I've been.  The Wall Center practically glows in this fantastic indigo blue when the light hits it correctly, and it makes a brilliant contrast to the lighter blue in the sky.  A jet's passing has left some fluffy white contrails, parallel lines floating in an east/west direction from the airport towards the mountains.  As I walk through the West End, there are still some cherry blossoms left; stragglers who have resisted the urge to fall to the ground below to become food for the incredibly green grass.  The heritage houses along Bute street stand at attention, various colors trying to stick out from the pack.  Yellow, green, blue, white, natural wood grain...they are like pageant contestants, all wearing the white sash of a low picket fence, strutting their stuff for me.  Some have had enhancements; tall flowers, the fragrance somewhat sweet against the smell of the grass.  The road itself stands out in stark contrast; a black band thru a sea of color, it's honor guard of spruce, fir, cherry and nut trees standing at attention, swords raised.  As I reach the hill above Robson street, the various less organic colors and sounds there start to show.  The orange of steamrollers' awning, the blue London Drugs sign with the dark green Earl's roof.  A boom car goes by, some silly little ricer thing...12000 dollars of bright red honda with 14000 dollars of ground effects and muffler, the subwoofer working hard as this small person overcompensates.  The crowds are relatively light this time of day, but I decide to just cross robson anyways, heading down towards Coal Harbour.  As I near Georgia, the blue green pastel of the Hotel Vancouver's multi turreted copper roof comes into view.  The gargoyls all salute me as I walk past, wishing they could un-entrench themselves from their guard posts.  The roar of Georgia's traffic, across the street I see that one old apartment building standing out like a rebel amongst all the monster condo hi-rises.  One piece of organic brown and rust, this little 5 floor building defies all the black and blue glass of the expensive condo's around it, daring them to try and move him.    Beyond, as the hill moves down, I see coal harbor.  The esso boat gas station guarding the harbor against invaders.  A float plane takes off, roaring past the end of the park to fly over Lions Gate bridge, astounding the drivers with how close it seems to the suspension wires.  I cross Hastings and decide to turn left, walk towards the park and back up denman.  The condo's here are a different sort than the ones on georgia...less spartan, more green comes out here.  Not just the greenish tint to the glass, but the large lawn area's and the greenery on the tiers of some buildings.  To my right, I pass the little harbour with the big boats; quarter million dollar and up yachts of the ultra rich mixed with the small pleasure craft or the somewhat less rich.  The Coal Harbor community center pops up like a periscope; the round roof just slightly above the ground level from this side of it. Some kids on BMX bikes are working on their skillz, curb hopping and wheely-ing away.  The cannon sits sheltered in it's cage, a monster waiting for it's time to shine at 9 o'clock.  The Vancouver Rowing Club building is its usual bustle of activity; some event seems to be happening on the deck and if I was going that way I may try and crash and munch on a barbequed burger.  But I'm not.  I reach the start of Stanley Park and turn left again, through the tunnel under Georgia St.  Roller bladers whizz by, some skilled, some looking dangerously precarious.  Up the hill past Lost Lagoon, the fountain is off right now.  The geese are about, though, and that white bird way over there might be one of the swans.  Of course, it might also be a seagull...it's hard to tell from this distance and he's cleaning his wings so his neck isn't up.  It's always a treat to see the swans; their graceful lines and movement a nice change from the gawkiness of the geese.  I stay on the path for a bit so I don't have to worry about crunching on goose shit, then decide to head out of the forest up to denman street.   I leave the shade of the trees, the smell of the fir needles, the crunch of the red gravel path for the smoothness and fragrant air of the west of denman area.  The nicer part of the west end, I tend to think of this area as low-rises and medium rises guarded by tons of flora.  The building managers around here must all be gardeners, because flowers are king in this neighbourhood.  The holly branches abound, the bigger flowers stand at attention.  A few bees buzz around, and one can hear the birds singing softly here.  I reach Denman streets bustle; on a hot day like today denman is busier than robson.  I walk towards second beach and the other entrance to Stanley Park, and the crowds get bigger.  The Bread Garden patio is packed, as is Death By Chocolate's.  The Denman Place Mall seems to be a hub of action right now, people running into Shopper's Drug Mart to pick up sunscreen and an icy drink.  The bikini store has a few people inside, and I ponder how busy that store can actually get.  Do people actually go to the beach very often without a bathing suit and then decide they need one?    The water on English Bay is a slightly different color than that of Coal Harbour.  A tinge lighter, with more whitecaps as it's less sheltered.  There are a surprising number of freighters parked out there today, and a surprisingly small number of sailboats.  The freighters seem to be at attention, the cranes all pointing the same way and in the same stance.  Most of them are riding high, so they are probably waiting for approval to go into the port and load up with stuff to take back to Japan, Hong Kong, San Francisco.  The few sailboats out strut their plumage like mating peacocks, flitting around looking for the best wind.  In the distance I see a kite surfer (I gotta try that some day) jumping waves along spanish banks.  Burrard Bridge stands majestic, it's yellowed sides and rounded girders a classy piece of engineering history.  I've always found burrard bridge to be sexier than Lion's Gate because it looks so classic.  Plus it's a heck of a lot easier to get across.  Back up Davie St, towards my house, the uphill climb begins.  The crowds down this far are all heading somewhere; some to the beach, some home like me, some just down here to do their shopping at the safeway or the LD.  The macaroni grill sits serenely, this magnificent stone building with it's fantastic lawn seating.  A few couples are having a romantic lunch on the lawn, I'm sure the building is pretty busy inside as well.  I turn down Nicola st and go up one block there, then walk the final two blocks home up that street.  I pass the movie star rental place and glance at the windows, wondering if i'll see any famous people today.  No...it almost looks empty actually.  Often when people are filming in town they will rent a suite in that building; perhaps no one is filming right now.  Or their filming and at work right now, which is very probable.  I go through the back door to my complex, check the mail and head home, another nice walk on another nice day in my city.  

						
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I spend a certain amount of time thinking about the ebb and flow of traffic (generally when I'm sitting in a gridlock wondering why we're stopped).  Often, a slow traffic situation is caused simply by some scaredy cat going 10 or 15% below the flow of traffic.  Obviously, an accident is a whole different story, but theoretically those could be avoided too.  As the population increases and the auto driving population increases with it, congestion becomes a more and more serious issue, and just the volume of traffic forced more and more of these stop and go driving stretches.  About 5 years ago I could drive from downtown Vancouver to Langley in about 35 minutes.  Now it takes 35 minutes to get out of the city and another 30 on the highway to get there.  So what causes the problem and how can we fix it?  As I said at the start, often the slowdown to halt of traffic on a busy highway or freeway is caused simply by some bonehead with a confidence issue, or just plain bad driving skills.  I've always been of the mindset that the safest and most efficient way to drive in traffic is to go at the pace of the other traffic.  Even if the speed limit is 60, if everyone is driving 80, you should drive 80 because if you don't, you become the biggest hazard on the road.  The other big issue is people who go slow in the fast lane (nothing brings me closer to road rage than this...except maybe non shoulder checkers).  So my utopian plan has a couple solves for this.  First...it has to be legislated that speeders aren't the only people getting tickets.  Yes, speeding can be dangerous (again...flow of traffic...if you're going twenty percent faster than everybody, you are a hazard), but slow drivers are just as dangerous.  So the police speed traps should include ticketing those that don't go fast enough as well.  Re-configure the traffic laws so that the posted speed limit is a guideline that should be followed, but not a set in stone ceiling.  If a person is holding up traffic, give them a ticket.  Enough tickets and maybe these people will learn.  Second, ticket ANYONE who goes in the passing lane and gets passed on the right.  This is possibly the most dangerous thing, especially on a 110km/h highway.  These idiots not only cause a hazard for the person right behind them (since they may have to slow down in a hurry), but far behind them they create very serious hazards as people jockey to pass others.   How many times i've driven down the highway and some buttmunch 20 cars ahead slows down enough that the cars a ways back have to slow down even more...  The guy coming up to the tail of this little train comes around a corner and has to nail the brakes, or pull into the other lane which is also congested.  This is a very very dangerous situation, and I believe that more rush hour accidents are caused by this than anything else.  Even the classic rear ender because of a lapse of attention is ultimately caused by that retard 60 cars ahead that forced EVERYONE to slow down.  So how else to fix this besides ticketing everyone??  We all know our police are definitely busy enough as it is, and sitting on a highway stopping the intellectually lightweights doesn't do the guy getting robbed any good... Well I've come up with a system.  What if we had a two tiered licensing system?  People who are capable of passing a much more intensive driving test and who are willing to pay a higher insurance and licensing fee structure get a different color license plate or something.  The people with this plate get right of way, and on a three lane road one lane is only for them.  These higher tiered drivers would also be given a 20% speed cushion, but only when they are in their lane.  Any non high tier driver gets a massive fine if they go into the high speed lane, and if they don't give right of way they get a fine as well.  The test could include defensive driving skills, emotional stability levels, willingness to let people pass, all those things.  Oh, and a car that meets slightly higher maintenance requirements.  This could not only work very well, but it would be a massive revenue generator for the governments that adopted it.  Make just taking this elite test a certain expense, and it becomes even more of a financial bonus to the government.  The only downside is the added policing costs...but we have the technology to deal with that as well.  With todays "smart highways" one could quite easily work out a sensor system.  When a person gets licensed, a small electronic box could go in the car much like toll paying devices that are available now for people who regularly use toll highways.  Sensors inside the road at the lane crossover (just one sensor wire would be plenty) would read these sensors as cars crossed the line.  If a car sent the wrong signal, a redflag goes up in the computer locked to the subscriber code in that cars electronic box.  Obviously, the subscriber code is linked to the car's owner, and a  ticket gets sent if that car does not leave the high speed lane within a certain distance (say 400 meters...that's plenty of time for someone who needs to pass or something).  This system could be a relatively inexpensive solution that would probably pay for itself quite quickly.  Remember most city's don't have a huge overabundance of 6 lane roads, and this would only be needed in those places.  The cost of the box could be built into cars price or insurance prices and it could be  a requirement for getting insured.  The next logical step to this would be speed control via the smart highway.  If a person goes a certain speed for a certain distance (again based on the flow of traffic around them), tickets could be sent for this as well.  Obviously, more technology would be needed than just the line sensor, but it could be built in.  This would eventually save municipalities money due to lower policing needs on those roads.  Obviously, you still need some police presence just to chase down dangerous drivers, drunks, etc (another related thing would be to have breath analysis in all cars so that someone who's drunk would not be able to start their car at all.  That would be cool).  The next step past the velocity monitoring would be velocity control...if a vehicle is moving at a speed that's too much of a variance over or under the general flow, a system will increase or decrease that car's speed remotely.  This would obviously take substantially more technology than we presently have to be made safe.  Wouldn't it be cool tho...the highway sets your cruise control automatically...woooooo.  I'm sure that eventually the car itself will do most of the driving based on mapping, GPS, proximity sensors and other future tech, but these solutions will help in the meantime.  Of course, it probably would never happen; too many people would complain about this or that aspect of it.  Hence the title of this post.   

						
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It occurs to me that sometimes things actually ARE what they seem.  I have a boss at one of my two lameduck jobs that I'm having a problem with.  Anni is a little Vietnamese lady who i've known for years.  When I first met her I figured she didn't like caucasians because of a couple of comments she made.  She was a customer of mine, and we dealth with each other lots on a professional level, and soon became friends.  I completely forgot about my original misgivings, and we socialized lots; camping trips, birthday parties, drink fests...we were part of the same social circle among which everyone respected everyone else and we all got along smashingly.  When I got laid off a couple years ago, I maintained contact with many of these people.  As my situation grew worse, someone else in Anni's company offered me a job there.  I took it...a part time job, few hours a week, perfect supplement to my teensy little income.  After the end of last year, they transferred me to anni's store because it's closer to my home.  Now for as long as I've known her and she was in management, Anni has had a grand total of 4 white males who worked for her, me being the fourth.  The first one, Ron, was a nice young kid, flaming gay but a nice guy and pretty good at his job.  Within a week of him starting I started hearing from Anni about what a poor worker he was, and how he didn't follow her lead etc etc.  I believed her...figured he was a bad employee with discipline problems.  After 2 years of this from her he quit this company.  The second one was a guy named Steve, who was in a position similar to what I am in.  I heard quite often how he wasn't a good hire, how he probably shouldn't still be in the company, etc etc etc.  Steve was transferred to a different store (ironically, to the store I left after christmas).  Next, Cory.  Cory is a sharp guy with a sharp tongue.  Very good employee, fun to work with, good sales skills, good product knowlege...all in all a guy I would hire.  Cory's been there for a while now, and he's good friends with Anni's boss.  Before I started, I heard second hand stories of how awful a person cory was for anni to work with, how he had her near tears with his horrible disrespect and lack of dedication and how he goes over her head all the time.  Now, I've worked with cory for 4 months now, and that's BS pure and simple...he's a good guy and a good employee.  So now me.  I've been given a letter from management about unprofessional things i've done, and they've been told I stink.  Now, anyone who knows me is well aware of the fact that I have an extremely sensitive olfactory system...I can smell BO 300 meters away and it makes me ill.  I have since asked everyone I know if I've ever stunk and every last one of them has said they've NEVER known me to smell bad.  It's something I'm a little obsessive about.  Now when this was first told to me I asked if it was smoke from taking a cigarette break (I smoke), but I was told no it wasn't that.  So what the hell?  That one just about made me fall of my chair.  I even asked all the other co-workers about that, and they said they've never noticed anything like that.    Also, she knows I have two jobs, yet every week she changes the schedule to try and screw me.  Without telling me.  And then tells me the previous schedule wasn't the real one and that it's my responsibility to keep on top of it.  Well, no it is NOT my responsibility, it's hers.  Last week my schedule said I was working next tuesday.  So I switched my schedule at the other job to accomodate her, and they scheduled me on Thursday.  Now all of a sudden she has me working Thursday.  So now I'm hooped.  I either skip a shift at the one job, or the other.  I desparately need every hour I can get right now.  So this sucks.  So how is all this racism?  Well, every other person she's worked with is asian, and she NEVER says boo about her asian co-workers.  Now I've been in telecom a LONNGGG time and have tons of Asian friends from it, and I know that they will always give the business to another Asian first; it's a cultural thing, and that's fine.  It's not conscious discrimination, and it is easy enough to get around (just be better at it than your asian competition), but none of my Asian friends actually generate ire towards caucasians (although a lot of them don't really like most east Indian's...).  I'm mostly caucasian, sorta brown cuz there's a bit of East Indian in there, but mainly seen as white.  I've wracked my brain to come up with why she is doing this to me (she's even attempted to poison me with some of our other mutual friends, and THAT crosses the line), and the only thing I can come up with is a subconscious dislike of caucasians.  I've asked her what her expectations are and done everything in my power to meet those, but it is not enough for her.  So, I think I must quit that job.  Her boss is away right now, and I can't go to him for a transfer or something, and this needs to be sorted out this week because of the double shift.  I would report her to HR, but I don't have any actually proof of this, only my feeling and past knowlege which is all just hearsay.  I sooo need both jobs right now, and it's crushing me to quit, but what the hell am I supposed to do?  Stick it out til she fires me?   Continue along with this scheduling nightmare and avoid her?  Try and get all the other guys she's tried to screw together and bust her for discrimination?  That's just not in my nature; I would like it on record that I feel discriminated against so she can't do it to the next guy, but that just makes me look bad to the company.  Which I guess doesn't really matter if I quit, but it kind of matters to me since I have so many friends in the company.  Sigh.    

						
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was linked to a website the other day of this dude who predicts that the world will end on June 24th of this year.  He has proven this by researching the Bible, cuz we all know a 2000 year old book has a pretty good handle on where things are going.  Now this guy predicts that on June 6th a cloud will form over the earth, and that on June 11, 21 and 24 ELE sized asteroids will strike the planet.  How the cloud relates is beyond me; I would think the cloud would form AFTER the Extinction Level Event.  Anyways he did indeed say that there would be an major sighting of an earthbound asteroid on June 3rd, and that did happen.  Of course, that happens somewhere in the world pretty much any day.    But just to be safe, I will spend the next two weeks amassing huge debt loads, tasting all the foods I've never tried, and having unprotected sex.  Cuz if the end does come, I wanna be able to say I enjoyed my last hours to the max.  Maybe I'll book a flight to Thailand and do all three in one stop.  Tomorrow it's buy buy buy. Sunday I'm going to sample heroin, just to say I did.  Monday, flip off a cop.  Tuesday steal a gangsta's sport utility.  Wednesday, the aforementioned flight to Thailand for sexual tourism, new food, and to get away from the gangsta.  Then whatever happens, I can't say I didn't experience stuff.  And hey, the heroin thing...I know I'll be able to kick when the nuclear winter hits for 3 or 4 years.  Poppies don't grow in the snow.  Seriously though, who gives these doomsayers oxygen to breathe and teaches them how to read and write?  Some poor sap is probably seriously screwed up right now due this guy's website, and how many people who went there are now gonna breathe a sigh of relief on June 25th when they wake up in their comfy old bed with a blue sky and the flowers still there?  I don't understand it; people who make claims like this are just wak; they see no future so they douse everyone they see with their gasoline of negativity and then throw a match at them.  Lit.  Maybe there should be some legislation.  Make a doomsday prediction once and be mistaken, you are forced into positive mental attitude training.  Do it twice and you go to a psychiatric hospital.  Three times and you go to jail for being an emotional vandal and just general shit disturber and menace to society.  The comedic value from these guys shouldn't be relevant in their sentencing because it would be even funnier to see them have to live a couple months with Bubba, the homosexual convict.    Well, not really...I wish no ill will on anyone.  But let's say doomsday does come this month.  Who will be the king in the new reality afterwards?  My guess it will be the best swordsman and pharmacist.  See, all the rednecks will shoot each other lots in the first days after.  And shoot others, I guess.  Eventually they'll run outta bullets, and with total destruction about it may be difficult to find a sporting goods store to buy more at.  The militia freaks will all go hide in the mountains somewhere and wait for orders.  Killing anyone who trespasses.  Eventually they'll run out of bullets too.  The common folk will be dying from things such as paper cuts and the common cold because all the little medicines and such we've used for a hundred years will be hidden; infections will abound.  Of course the hunger won't help their immune systems.    So the person who is king (or queen) will be the guy who knows how to use and maintain his sword best, and who has the foresight to rob every pharmacy he sees of any kind of infection killing drug such as penicillin and all that.  Plus aspirin for the aches and pains of formerly lazy desk and couch potatoes forced to work for their food, and other drugs while he's there.  Of course while he's robbing the pharmacy he can stock up on chips and twinkies and canned goods, so he'll have food for a long time too.  As the rednecks run out of bullets and dwindle due to attrition and the militia guys hide and await orders, this samurai pharmacist will attract a very loyal group of followers.  He can teach some of them how to battle with swords as well, and maybe even make some swords for them; i don't imagine we'll instantly forget how to make fires and forges.  Of course, he'll have the only really good sword since he was the only one with the foresight and vision to grab one.  After a few roving bands of marauders get schooled by this guy and his cold steel blade, the word will spread not to mess with him.  And as we move forward he will just naturally become king.  He will have little bands of jr. pharmacists who will go raid drug stores everywhere, supplying his people with aspirin, band-aids, chips and Gatorade.  He will have a defensive core of jr. samurais with slightly edged metal clubs who will do his bidding.  And eventually he can order the militia guys to come out of the mountains and join his little commune.  Of course shortly after that total chaos will break out as militia men are notoriously bad and dealing with undisciplined behavior, and of course there will be lots of that.  Also, the militia colonel will think HE deserves to be king, so the Samurai Pharmacist will have to lay down the law, probably in battle.  He'll win, of course, cuz he's been working on his swordsmanship since the meteor's hit.     Well, enough for tonite...got to go research swords now.    

						
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As I was flipping around the blog sites today I came across a couple that made me want to comment.  First was this guy who wrote about his adventures in a used bookstore.  Now, that's all well and good and all, but this guy sounded like a third year arts student in university.  "I was pleasantly surprised to come across a lugubrious tome by nietzsche, as well as one of my favorites, Tolstoys extemporily well written War and Peace".  Come on dude...stop with the pretentious pedanticism and just be yourself.  NOBODY reads War and Peace for entertainment; it's perhaps the second most boring peace of literature ever, right behind the Time magazine.  No, I like Time sometimes, so I am kidding there.  But seriously...Nietzsche and Tolstoy and Frost's poems...these are english class homework assignments, not something anyone really wants to buy for enjoyment.  Unless, of course, they get enjoyment out of showing everyone how intelligent they are.  But, then, the only people impressed by display books are morons who wish they had enough brains to understand those books, right?    Anyways, I wrote out a comment somewhat to that affect, only nicer, but then I thought "What am I accomplishing by sending this?"  Nothing other than showing myself to be as pretentious as this git was.  I was brilliant in my comments, going so far as to suggest he try some authors from this century such as Neal Stephenson and Michael Odjaante and Yann Martel...suggesting that a piece of literature's primary duty is to ENTERTAIN, and all the dark philosophical meanderings he mentioned aren't even entertaining to philosophy students.  But, when I looked at these comments before I sent them it struck me as very hypocritical to say such things to someone.  He was doing it his way, and who's to know...maybe this guy really did get enjoyment out of self torture.  I doubt it, but it's not my thing to judge, is it?  So...if anyone else reads this and wants to read something highly entertaining AND educational AND a bit philosophical, I suggest Neal Stephenson's "Cryptonomicon".  It's a honking big book with all kinds of mathematical equations and shit in it, but in the end it's just a great story.  If science and math makes you itch, try out something by Yann Martel (heavy on the philosophy and theology, light on the math) or anything by John Irving (just plain entertaining, but written in a classic prose style).  The second blogg I wanted to comment to was this American dude who wrote that "American media only shows us the worst of what our troops are doing over there.  Don't you think the Iraqi's are doing worse things to their prisoners of war?  And CNN is the worst."  Well, this guy I wanted to tell that, as an outsider who watches non-American news, trust me...you are not seeing only the worst.  CNN is owned by the republicans...it is the most biased, right wing, pro-Bush news broadcast there is.  They had to run the prison beatings to be competitive, but there is much worse stuff your troops have done (under orders yet!@).  I watched a documentary on the CBC some time ago about the experiences of reporters over there during the war.  One very moving scene was a reporter talking about a van that stalled on the road.  The iraqi driving it with his wife, sister, 2 daughters, a niece and a nephew begged the americans for help; they were fleeing the battle ground.  The American radio'd for advice, and the order came down...destroy it and kill them as terrorists.  They showed this on the broadcast! This is not a second hand story; I watched it unfold (well, on TV mind you, and it could have been staged I guess, but why would they?  Canada is a US ally, and has no intention of pissing them off with false propaganda...hell the US would just take us over if we did that)!   Anyways... I'm getting a little worked up cuz watching that story really really affected me.  It was a horrible thing to see.  Anyways the guy's other comment about the captured Americans...2 things here.  First: Any American who has been captured then released or escaped who I've seen a press conference from has said they were treated very well.  Obviously the head chopping guy is a different story, but that one leads me to my second point: The American's are not fighting a legitimate army who is held to the Geneva Conventions.  They are fighting a bunch of people who just had their homes and lives taken from them by an invading army...of course they're over the edge.  Don't get me wrong here...I totally do not support any terrorists or acts of such.  This whole war sickens me almost as much as the act that ultimately started it 2 and half years ago.    Well, there you go.  Two blogs that made me want to comment today.  And I didn't comment to either of them in the end. 

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Is it just me, or do people seem to have lost a bit of compassion over the last little while?  My neighbourhood has become a freaky, often scary place.  It used to be we had our little group of alcoholic guys in the park, the odd street kid panhandling for pot money, dumpster divers recycling their loot on the streetcorner.  All comfy and safe, and this neighbourhood truly was a safe place to be at any time of day or night.  The community I live in is basically made up of a few generally tight groups of fringe dwellers who all look out for each other.    But lately things have changed.  The bums in the park are no longer alcoholics, they're crack and motorheads, the streetkids are all psychotic meth junkies and the dumpster divers are heroin addicts who have been rousted from the downtown east side.  What's worse, is now we have dealers and hookers plying their trade on my street.  Recently two people were shot outside my back gate; I even heard the gunfire and thought "That can't be gunfire around here can it?".  The dealers are verbally abusive to everyone but their customers, and it is actually quite frightening to walk around down here at night.  Now, I'm not a guy who's ever been afraid of crowds or groups of people, not even of little gangs of ruffians; for the most part trouble can be easily avoided in those situations.  But now...damn these guys kick the crap outta people just cuz it's fun.  And where do their morals kick in?  Do they have any, or has the meth completely wiped out their conscience?  Cuz these guys don't just punch people out; they stomp, run over, stab, shoot, blunt object beat and other fun games to their victims.  And they don't stop when the person's down...they stop when the authorities show up or they realize they just went too far and someone is SERIOUSLY hurt or worse.  Every day I read in the paper about some horrible beating, stabbing, shooting...all very close to my home, and it's messing with me.  When i'm afraid to leave my house after 10PM there's a problem.  So what's the answer here?  The cops do nothing...they tried to do something but the rich people on the West Side got their panties in a knot about the police tearing a little strip off some chronic offenders that the court system lets run wild.  So the community in the downtown Eastside said "We've had enough" and pushed them out right into my little neighbourhood, the Davie Village.  There was some talk awhile back about a little community action to clean stuff up but I think they got threatened away from doing it.    I have thought of a solution, but I don't know if it would catch on.  I figure if everyone in our neighbourhood whenever they saw a pimp or a dealer or an aggressive panhandler hit the motherfucker upside the head with a blunt object, eventually these skids would get the hint and move on.  The police do jack for us, cuz they can't, so let's show the scumsuckers who's neighbourhood this really is.  Of course this does nothing to cure the problem, but my personal belief is that the only thing that will actually cure the problem is get the warmongers outta office in the US and other parts of the world.  Seriously...this shit started to escalate right after Bush bought his illegal victory down there...not just the shit in my part of the world, but the whole fucking planet.  I view my neighbourhood as a little microcosm of what's going on out there, and it's a pretty accurate gauge.  I digress a bit...Yeah kick the shit out of these assmonkeys and eventually they'll realize they aren't so welcome here.  Tough to do business if your customers are afraid to come to you, but hey...that's exactly what these little fucks did to the local legit businesses...let's get them back with their own medicine.    Sadly, these guys are completely above the law because the system doesn't work as a deterrant or a recovery for people with now conscience.  Of course myself and my neighbours won't go around bootfucking every pimp or dealer we see; if that was in our nature we would be working with them, no?  So it appears that in reality the only choices real working people have in my neighbourhood are "Deal" or "Leave".  And that sucks.  I firmly do believe that when bush and his war criminal cronies get their asses evicted from the white house, the world will breathe a collective sigh of relief and maybe people will chill out a bit.  One can dream...  

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I went out to the Keg for dinner tonight.  If you don't live in a place with a Keg, basically it's a fairly high end but not stuffy steak joint; fantastic food and cool ambience...great place for a date, although dinner for two will cost the better part of 100 bux with drinks added.  The dining room is very dark with fireplaces going and somewhat private booths.  Dark wood paneling, dark leather seats, black painted walls and dim lights all add to the feeling of being alone in a crowd in The Keg.  I ordered a 12 oz. New York Peppercorn steak cooked medium with garlic mashed potatos, and it was near perfect.  I ordered a bottle of Australian red (um...shoot can't remember the name right now cuz i'm bloated and full and thinking slowly...but the yellow label one...they make a black and red label too) that was fantastic; nice nose, dry but with a peppery slightly fruity taste.  One of my favorite wines, and I order it often.  You can buy the red and black labels in the local liquor stores, but the yellow u can only find in wine stores or restaurants.  Shame, cuz it is by far the best of them all.  We finished our dinner off with a Keg Billy Miner Pie... basically a half liter of coffee flavoured ice cream covered in hot fudge sauce, caramel sauce, and sliced pecans on a sugar crust and in a 6 inch high wedge shape.  I always get that at the keg because it is one of the most incredible and decadent desserts around and I much love it.  And it was as good as always... :D  Anyways, we walked home after dinner, and right outside the back door to our apartment complex there was a squirrel sitting on the sidewalk.  At first I was all like "awww look at the little squirrel doorman come to greet us" but then I noticed that he (she?) didn't skitter away as I approached.  And if you have squirrels in your neighbourhood you know that they always skitter away...hence the term "squirrely".  The poor little guy was definitely alive, but he was obviously in distress.  My first thought was that he'd been hit by a car, but there was no blood or anything, no leaky bits at all.  He seemed to be trying to hide behind his tail.  As he watched me with grave interest I got a little closer to see if I could discern what was wrong.  It made him a little jumpy, and he tried again to hide under his bushy little tail, nearly falling over in the process.    This little grey squirrel was breathing quite quickly and shallowly, and I just didn't know what to do.  Does one call the SPCA in this kind of case?  I mean, seriously in the grand scheme of things a squirrel is considered vermin in the city; would they just tell me to bonk him on the head and put him out of his misery or kick him to the curb for the garbage man to collect when he finally jumped off this realm?  My heart really went out to him; he was hurting, he was alone, and it was starting to rain a bit.  I thought maybe i should grab a box and put some peanut butter in it and take him inside...but if he has a back injury am I doing more harm than good? Also, wouldn't our two cats just eat him?  Cuz really, that's what cats do with rodents that are smaller than them.  What what what??  So I left him there.  With a somewhat heavy heart I opened the door and went into the complex, and left him there.  I started to think about what may be wrong with him; did he get bit by a coyote? Partially run over?  Did he crawl into some junkie's hole and get punted out?  Was he poisoned by some nasty ass person with a garden and no sense of fairness to nature?  And then it hit me...maybe he isn't a he...maybe he's a she and about to have more little squirrels.  Now, one thing we don't particularly need in downtown vancouver is more squirrels, but it was a much more positive spin on the situation.  After a little while I couldn't deal with the curiosity and the sympathy I had for this small wild creature any more...I went back out to check on him.  This was probably 45 minutes later.  Well...sadly, he was gone.  Not gone as in dead, but gone as in no longer in that place.  I looked around and didn't see him anywhere, didn't see any tracks or anything (yeah, that's me, the great hunter tracker...), no smushed grass where he may have dragged his weary carcass...no sign at all.  Now, my apartment is right close to that back door, and if anyone had come in there I would have heard it...and no one did.  So I'm gonna assume it was a momma squirrel on her way to a nest to give birth or something.  That's less depressing than thinking he got grabbed by a hawk as he was helpless there.  I wonder why he chose my doorway at that particular time to have his situation, whatever it was.  Was it an omen?  A sign?  A sad coincidence?  A reminder from the powers that be that my trivial little issues are pretty tame in comparison to the struggles of living in the wild?  A test of some kind?  I don't know...perhaps I am reading too much into it.  All I know for sure is that little squirrel spoke to me quite loudly in the moment or two we shared looking into each other's eyes.  Be well, little grey squirrel, wherever tonights journey took you.   

						
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Uploading music is a difficult thing if you don't have a website with tons of room on it.&nbsp; I've been trying all morning to upload an MP3 of my band to various places...of course it's to big to post anywhere and for whatever reason I can't edit it.&nbsp; So now i'm a little frustrated with the whole dealio.&nbsp; I even went to audioblogger to try that...I should have read it more carefully...I didn't know that it had to be sent from a telephone there.&nbsp; Sigh...&nbsp; I suppose I could call it in and then play the mp3 real close to my phone... &nbsp; Ahhh the joys of technology.&nbsp; I'm sure this stuff is all real easy but I'm just too much of a luddite to get it sussed out properly.&nbsp; Sigh.  

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As I was sitting in that wierd little gourmet hot dog place in Langley on Saturday, an idea hit me.  What if a there was a restaurant that only served food your mom made on days she felt lazy.  Not burgers and fries, not ethnic food, not steaks etc, but comfort food.  They could serve things like Kraft Dinner(tm), grill cheese sandwiches with cheez whiz, wieners and beans...uh...spam even.  All those bizarre little meals that aren't really healthy but aren't as bad for you as MacDonald's burger with supersize fries.    It could be profitable; all that stuff has real low costs associated with it; a case of mac and cheese is like 5 bucks...you could probably get 30 or 40 servings out of that.  Even if you went cheap and only charged 2 bux a pop, you just made 80 dollars by spending 5...that's a pretty good margin.  You could sell popcorn as well.  Wieners and beans would be like 2.50 and cost you maybe 45 cents.  And spam...well spam is uber cheap.    The key to place like this would be location.  Now location is always important, but for this kind of place it would be even more so.  You would have to be near a large supply of people who want quick easy eats but don't want to eat another meal at the local choke and puke grease bar.  Perhaps a mall or something with a built in supply of lower income employees.  Another good spot would be near a hostel or similar backpackers type lodge; the kids there never have much money, and tend to be the types to love comfort food.  Heck you could even expand it to include comfort foods from around the world to entice the world traveller in.  Everybody likes to grab a little taste of home once in a while when they're travelling.  The other benefit to having comfort foods from around the world is that will bring in locals who want to sample it a bit.  Not a true ethnic restaurant where they sell the best food from "x" country, but one that sells the stuff college kids eat in said place.  The other key would be to make it a real comfortable environment; people need to want to hang out there. Maybe a couple TV's and couches, like a coffee lounge.  Internet access would be important in the hostel area location.  Cheap internet access.  Maybe a few board games and books to make people want to chill for a bit.  In the end it will all come down to three things: Location, Good Food, and Cozy Hangin Spot.    

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So...to continue last nights post... Friday we went out to record vocals on the demo.  I called drummer Greg up and he said he was gonna be there, kids and wife in toe (lol WE ARE SOOOO ROCK AND ROLL!!!), so I invited Sylvie to come to and hang with the kids.  Poor Engineer Greg probably felt like the circus invaded or something.  Anyways, I picked Sylvie up from her work and off we went out to New West.  It was Sylvie's birthday today, so I knew that clan G (greg's family) had a prezzy for her and a card.  After the recording we had plans to go out and see a friend of Sylvie's friend's band play.  At the studio, I was the first one there, other than engineer Greg.  We listened to the songs a bit and picked the best take of each one to work with.  We decided to focus on Bus Stop since I had to leave early anyways.  That way we could spend more time on one song and do it right rather than less time on both songs and do them half assed.  Darren went out and did a vocal take.  He was having a bit of a challenge with the chorus, but he was singing the shit out of it.  We decided that we would use his track and I would record my BG's and that would help with his chorus.  It took me 3 or 4 takes, but I finally got a kick ass one down.  Darren went out and nailed the leads in 4 tries and he sang that shit HARD.  And it was good.  Sheldon went out to do his BG's and had a bit of a challenge nailing the harmony, but that's ok cuz he was more prepared to do the other song.  He got a pretty good take tho, and we kept that.  Then Greg went out to put some percussion on...and Sylvie and I had to leave.  We said our goodbyes and headed out.  Darren told me today that Greg did a rockin tambourine and shaker bit, so I look forward to hearing that...it might add some cool dimension to an otherwise straight ahead hard rock tune.  We had an uneventful drive home, and Sylvie changed to head out to the bar.  She wore some awesome tight ass jeans (woot sexy) and a little tee.  She stuffed her little bar wallet in the back pocket and off we went.  We just missed the bus by our house so we figured we'd catch it at granville.  We set a very brisk pace (we were on the verge of being a bit late) and kinda half walked, half ran to granville street (about 6 blocks).  We got there as a bus was pulling up and as Sylvie grabbed for her bus ticket, she realized she had dropped her wallet en-route. SHIT!  Her drivers license, bank card, and about 40 bucks cash.  Good bye that...Davie st is littered with junkies and street kids, and it was, after all, Friday night.  We headed back up Davie looking for it, not much hope.  Sylvie was some kinda bummed (no doubt).  Nice birthday present that...   I personally just figured she had taken it out for some reason before we left and forgot it.  So off we went up Davie at an even brisker pace than we went down it, scanning for her little flat wallet.  As we crossed Burrard, a woman came up behind us and tapped Sylvie on the shoulder.  She asked if we had lost something, and of course we said yes.  She said she had been looking for us and Sylvie looked like the person on the driver's license.  Holy shit!  There are still some good people out there.  So thanks, lady, whoever you are, for helping a good night not turn into a bad night.  Props to you, and extra special thanks for not taking any of the dough in the wallet.  Good karma coming your way.  It's about time something good happened to us after the shitty couple of years we had, and I personally take this as a big sign that (at least for Sylvie) things are turning around.  So...thanks again.  Not that anyone reads this blog, but if you do...thanks.  So we finally got to the Railway and the band was just about to go on.  The Railway Club is an odd little room...very intimate, with the stage right at the front group of 8 or so tables.  It's narrow and long with kitschy 70's rumpus room kind of panelling and accents.  The room is bisected by the bar about halfway down.  For the length of the bar, it is basically a hallway to get to the back half of the room where there are a few more tables and the bathrooms and a pool table.  We were sitting at the front table, as the piano player in the band is best buds with the dude we were there with.  The cheesy orange/brown carpet smells slightly musty, and the carved up tables are somewhat uneven.  The lights are flourescent and synthetic feeling, but cool because you feel like the band is in your living room.  All in all a great venue to see bands in, and a long standing Vancouver live music watering hole.  The band got up on stage and were all old guys.  Well, 5 old guys and one old girl.  The make up of the band was singer, 2 guitar, chick bassist, drummer, piano and percussion.  Everyone but the piano player sang too.  The main singer guy was hilarious looking.  He had on a pink shirt with a logo that said "Dicks...where  taste IS the difference".  He was an older bald fellow with a really odd shaped skull.  It had some kind of extra bone in the front giving him the appearance of some wierd bastard child of a Diploducus (er...that's a dinosaur with a lumpy head) and a really skinny, short Klingon.  They launched into their set with a bizarre 5 part harmony barbershop kinda thing that was really cool, and man could the singer dude sing.  Well, they all had serious vocal chops, but I guess this is what 30 years of playing clubs gets you...either serious chops or a serious addiction.  Anyways they rocked the joint with a bunch of bizarre cover tunes (mainly song's I'd never heard before with a few exceptions, but all cover tunes).  Now, normally cover bands bore the shit out of me...if I want to hear a band's song I'll listen to their album, ya know?  But these guys COOKED!  Not only were they exceptionally good and fluid players, but they were having a  blast  up there.  Which is what rock and roll is all about really, having fun.  They all played well, but not like schooled arrogant college music playing.  They were just good cuz they do it lots and have done it a long time.  The only way to get truly good is to play the shit out of your weapon for a long long time.  And that's what old guys bring to the table I guess.  We watched two sets of the band and had a really good time and few beers, then decided to head home.  Had a fine walk home and went to bed a bit tipsy but not slammed.  I havent drank that many beers in a long long time tho, so I did feel more drunk than I should have.  I didn't want to stay up too late cuz today is Sylvie's birthday as I mentioned earlier.  And we had plans.  We got up slowly this morning, and left the house around 12:30.  We decided to drive out to fort langley just cuz we hadn't been there for a long long time.  Walked around there for a bit, ate a gourmet hotdog, looked at some antiques and just enjoyed being out of the city for the afternoon.  We were gonna get together with Darren and Diane tonight to play x-box and eat unhealthy food, so we headed back home after a couple hours.  We stopped at Coquitlam center to pick up the Hobbit on x-box and ended up picking up another game as well.  We almost picked up two other games, but one of them was the game that I knew Darren and Diane had bought her for her birthday so I told her two were enough.  Came home and prepared the house then I went and got D and D.  We picked up some mix and some birthday cupcakes and then went to Memphis Blues for some BBQ take out.  If you ever come to Vancouver, eat at this place.  It is THE shit.  Huge assed portions of wonderfully tender and utterly decadent BBQ pork, beef, chicken etc etc.  And the ribs...omg the ribs...like beef candy man.  Completely melts in your mouth.   And fantastic fries too.    So we ate our anti-vegan meal and watched "The Story Of... Metallica's Black album" on DVD.  It was a cool video, and the place where our band rehearses is where they recorded alot of that album so we got to see our room lots.  After dinner we proceeded with the mass killing of monsters in our new game "Hunter-the Reckoning -Redeemer".  Great game for four player...no split screen, all cooperative play and just plain fun.  Pure destructorama with lots of animated bloody bits.    Holy shit this has been a long post...full of nothing too...lol  Oh well time to stop I guess.  

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   And then I went to a bar to see a pretty cool band...pretty cool for a cover band that is.  Bunch of old guys looking kinda not so rock and roll, but man they cooked on their gear.  More on that tomorrow tho...tonite I'm a bit drunk, a lot tired, and a tad bit not feeling well.  So...this great post in my head will have to wait.  Hope I don't forget it all...  

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It was kind of creepy walking home from work tonite for some reason.  I'm not sure why but I felt an unusual sense of anxiety this evening, to the point where at one point I noticed my heart was beating like 130-140 bpm...pretty high for a nice leisurely walk.    It was the usual crowd of skaters and urchins on granville, all the non conformists non-conforming together in the same way.  There were a few people begging, nothing unusual there.  It was grey and cool, comfortable temperature, and the reddish concrete of granville mall felt like drying blood.  As I crossed Smythe street into the cold concrete of the driving part of Granville, the urchins and skate punks turned into grumpy looking guys of unknown racial descent wearing headbands and facial hair, a permanent scowl etched into their frustrated looking faces.  I passed Tom Lee music and the guitars in the window called to me to go in and look, play.  But I ignored them and moved on.    At Nelson I turned North and headed up the hill.  I saw one rather incongruous gang banger wannabe who kind of made me chuckle.  He had the regular scowl, ultra short hair, some attempt at a goatee and the head band.  He appeared to be native or south american.  He was a little chunky, but not fat...just...soft in the middle.  The thing that was unusual is he was wearing a very effeminate pink sweater preppy style over his shoulders and tied in front by the sleeves.  I wanted to say something to him, but he had that angry look to him that I see more and more these days.  So I smiled inwardly and walked on.  I passed a couple of quebecois squeegee kids, laughing about some person who cursed them out for not taking no for an answer.  I thought about it a bit, and this is part of the problem today...people just don't want to accept responsibility for their actions.  It was all the fault of the person in the car that they got mad, of course not theirs.  They were just trying to make a buck.  I wanted to tell them it's pretty hard to make a sale when you intimidate the customer, and most people aren't necessarily going to buy anyways.  I also wanted to tell them that if life is soooo difficult for them here, they should get back on the greyhound and get their separatist asses back to Quebec.  But then I realized that the first would just insult them and the second would insult them and be an incredibly racist thing to say.  At this point I thought about the difference between Tourettes sufferers and the rest of us: we all have thoughts that are harsh or even downright mean, and mainly out of character, but the Tourettes person doesn't have the ability to stop those thoughts at the mind.  They travel down the various ganglia and medullas and shit until they end up at the mouth and come out, usually causing embarassment, anger, or sadness.    I digress...back to my walk.  I crossed Burrard street and a car ran the light, almost hitting a couple of pedestrians (me being one of them).  The classic styled stone walls of the two big old churches stood majestically, ignoring all the noise and bottled up frustration around it.  Behind me, now, the cool blue super tower of the Wall Center(tallest building in the city right now)looked on somewhat arrogantly; expressing it's superiority (hence it's inferiority) like a small guy with a BMW.  The guy who ran the light got honked at by the people in cars who he ended up blocking, being stuck in the intersection.  More than one Trudeau Salute was offered to him, and I was strongly thinking about offering my allegiance as well.  Up to Thurlow, everyone I passed looked pissed off or sad...I hope I didn't as well.  I entered Nelson Park just as some girl was complaining to her boyfriend about all the junkies and hookers hanging out in that park these days.  I agreed with her completely and wanted to say something, perhaps form some kind of vigilante allegiance with them to rid our neighbourhood of these scum.  But, that doesn't solve the problem it just moves it.  And besides...it's a fantasy I have, not a reality that could ever happen.  Throughout the park, the aforementioned junkies were sprawled out in various poses of undeniable uselessness, just waiting for someone to come and end their miserable lives or change it in some way.  Of course, they will never do that for themselves, and societal thinking (mine included) doesn't help their case at all.  I had a brief fantasy of going up to one and coercing him to reveal who his pusher was, then finding the pusher and kicking the living shit out of him telling him to never return to this neighbourhood on pain of death...but in reality I'm a coward and a wimp so that would never happen.  It saddens me a lot to see Nelson park so full of such dirty garbage; it truly is a beautiful piece of green in the downtown core, the bike path crunching under your feet as you walk thru it, the dogs playing at certain times of day (it's an off-leash park).  It would be nice to see our fair city fathers do something to clean up this particular bastion of west end life, but it's going to take something serious to happen before they do that.  I got to Bute St and still, no one was smiling.  By now everyone I saw was either intimidating me or angering me; I was in no state to be in public, and it was making me feel pretty crappy; mad at myself for having such dark emotions.  I got home and felt like shit; I called Sylvie to tell her I wasn't going to go to walk her home from work, but she didn't answer.  I went out on the balcony to have a smoke (my heart rate seemed normal again), and promptly fell into a bizarre sneezing fit; I must have sneezed 8 or 9 times.  After that was done, I felt fantastic, so I decided to go walk Sylvie home after all.    All in all it was a wierd walk home from my work today; it started to hurl me down the steps of depression, but I sneezed my way out of it.  Go figure.  

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I don't know why but I get belly button lint.  Like every day.  My girlfriend never gets belly lint.  What the hell is causing this?  Am I dusty?  Do I need to start vacuuming my chest?  Why do men get belly lint and women don't?  Is it related to the balls and testosterone?  These are important questions and people deserve to know the answers dammit!  I also get sock lint.  No ass lint tho, thank goodness.  I'd hate to have to pick my ass to remove lint.  One day I'm gonna start saving all my belly lint, and when I get enough weave it into fabric and make a sweater or something.  I could walk around in my belly lint sweater with pride, knowing that in the most basic, lowest production level I produced this thing from scratch.  Me me me.  Shit, even the farmer can't say he did as much to produce his wool sweater, cuz the sheep grew the wool, not him.  Everybody's got to have a goal in life, a dream to fulfil.  Mine may well be the famous belly lint sweater.  I wonder where I'd store it all...have to find a shoebox or something I guess. 

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   OK so this one may never happen, at least not as long as the US market controls the entertainment industry.  I know that broadcasters must aim their programming at the lowest common denominator, and that people as a rule are afraid of change.  Hence, a unique and creative show gets popular, and then gets followed by tons and tons of clones, each one dumbed down a bit more than the last.  Until finally, from starting with the Eco Challenge and you end up with The Simple Life and Wife Swap.  But what about all the other programming out there.  There are...what...800 channels broadcasting in North America?  And a lot of them put out the same 20 shows.  But there are also diamonds in that rough.  With the advent of digital broadcasting, satellite reception and the continued development and enhancement of storage technologies, why could we not have a pool of all broadcast to work with?  The consumer could select the type and or level of intelligence/humour/acting/reality and get a list of programming that fits their need.  None of this "100 channels of shit and 4 good tv shows that aren't movies, time your life around the tv guide" stuff.  TiVo has already put little tendrils of thought into this, and most of the cable and satellite companies are putting similar ideas to work for them with PVR's.  But the problem here is we still are subject to the whims of the provider as far as programming goes.  Why should I be forced to have 7 different channels showing some stupid shit like Nick and Jessica or else a bunch of crap that doesn't interest me at a given time?    So here's my idea.  Take the TiVo model and expand on it.  Have the providers work together to offer ALL broadcast in digital format, and the consumer picks their watching choices.  Not just the 150 channels we can choose from now, but ALL channels.  You could set up a rating system with different ratings for things like intellectual content, creativity (ie: is it a new idea or another survivor clone?), dramatic skill, music skill, action skill, pace, budget, "Hollywood" level, obviously sex/violence/language ratings like we have now, etc etc.  You could even set it up so that one station on your reciever only shows new shows, so you could sample what you want to watch from the bi-annual crop of new blood.  Some of those stupid shows are interesting to people who wouldn't normally watch such crap...for example I totally dig "Next Action Star".  So I could choose to look at new shows as they come out and see if there are other ones that appeal to me on a similar base level.  Obviously, the major challenge in this system would be the ratings system:  how do you make them accurate and usable?  In a perfect world, the consumers would set the ratings; either net based or remote control based, after a show a little survey comes up and the viewer ticks off the appropriate boxes to give an accurate rating.  The problem with this is that there could be payola and cheating from the big networks and producers to skew the results.  So how could it possibly be done accurately?  Perhaps a limit on the ratings each source could do for each show...one rating per week per show per cable box.  Again there could be flaws in that, but if the proper checks and balances are installed those flaws could be minimized.  It would take a bit of time to work out the logistics of such a plan, but theoretically it  could  be done.    I guess we approach these abilities now with computer viewing and downloading.  The biggest problem with the current system, however, is how does the user find the program that  THEY  want?  If you've ever tried to search out a TV show or movie on the web, you know that it's difficult to find non pirate downloads of something.  So the producers, broadcasters, networks would have to get on-board and help out with that.  Instead of commercials on their shows they could have banner ads etc.  Although that may screw up the revenue streams.  Ahhh I don't know how to make this work.  But that's why it's a  Utopian  idea and not a plan of action.   

						
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well the first day of my new gig has come and gone.  I'm not decided yet whether I dig this job or not; it will take a bit to get the groove and all that.  Today I spent alot of time sweating and looking for something to do.  The crew I work with is pretty cool, but they seemed a tad unprepared for me.    I got in this morning at 9 and was the first one there.  I couldn't do much, cuz I didn't have access to the computers or know where anything was.  Once some people showed up they gave me some files to read, but still no computer access.  I got a phone and a data device to noodle on, but those are things I know inside and out.  I asked the IT guy to get me set up on the network so I could do a bit of web study on the Roger's plans and pricing and what have you.  He got that done by about 2:30... Of course I don't have any customers yet, but that will come.  I did call Sheldon today (the band's bass player) as he owns a towing company and I may be able to save him a few bucks in wireless charges.  He will fax me his bills tomorrow and I can see what I can find for him based on his usage and needs.  And other than that...more study is all I have to do tomorrow.  All in all it looks like I'll enjoy the environment, as everyone seems pretty groovy and the atmosphere is pretty laid back.  Now the only thing is to see if I can make any dough doing it.  I did apply again at Bell: they're posting once again for a retail account manager...obviously the guy they hired over me last time didn't work out. Or maybe it's expansion...who knows.  I have set my alarm for 6 AM tomorrow...gonna hit the gym in the morning before work if I can get out of bed.  Sound body =  sound mind... I gotta keep this fact in the front of my thought pattern when I sleep tonite.   

						
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My new gig starts today.  Outside sales, for the first time in my life.  Should be interesting and exciting.  I may crash and burn completely or I may kick ass at this, but whichever way it turns out, I'm learning a new skill.  So that's good.  And I'm working for a new company with completely different philosophy's than what I'm used to.  So that's good too.  I had a heck of a time getting to bed early enough last night.  The original plan was to be up at 6 this morning and off to the gym before work, but when I looked at the clock and saw 1:15 am I thought that might be a bad idea.  So I changed the alarm to 6:45 for that extra bit of sleepypooh.  Didn't help much so far...I can barely keep my eyes open right now.  Man...what happened to my innate ability to run on 3 or 4 hours sleep?  Stupid maturity! >:(  I will write some about the job tonight...how it went and all that. 

						
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The band went into the studio on Friday night, and it was good.  I was a little late because I had to work until 7 (we were booked at 6...), but it worked out ok because it gave the rest of the guys the opportunity to start setting stuff up.  I arrived right around 8 and I was charged to go.  After a day of working my shitty little job and trying to get into my zone, it arrived about the time I showed up to the studio.  I slugged my amp and guitar and gear bag into the place, and saw that the room where my amp sits was all wired; I just had to plonk it down and plug it in.  The mics were all set up, including the plethora used for the drum set, and everybody else's gear was all hooked up and ready to go.  I figured "Yeah...we're gonna have a poopload of time to just get stuff down now".  But it was not to be.  Greg (the guy who was recording us) is taking a recording arts in school, and we are two of his projects: a three piece rock recording we did a couple weeks ago without Darren, and a four piece we were doing this night.  On the three piece there were some wierdnesses in the kick drum sound, so we decided to spend a little extra time and get it right for this one.  Now, it can be fixed, the stuff on the last recording, but it's much easier for Greg the engineer if it records well off the start.    So I hooked up my gear, did a little warm up noodling, and waited. And waited. And waited.  After about 35 minutes it was time to start setting the levels.  So that started with the drums...takes about 45 minutes to do it right slowly.  Then the bass, then bass and drums, then darren's guitar, then my guitar.  It was 10:30 before we were ready to start recording.  I could see that Greg the drummer was already starting to get the go jones on.  Then Darren and Sheldon went to grab sandwiches, Greg the drummer went to call the wife, and Greg the engineer wanted to play my guitar a bit.  So I went out and had a smoke.  And got locked out of the building :/  I tried calling Greg the engineer...no good; his phone doesn't work to well in the studio.  I tried calling Sheldon...no good; his phone works, but was sitting in his gear bag in the studio so even if someone was right beside it they wouldn't hear it.  I tried calling Greg the drummer, but his phone lost signal after 2 rings.  I kicked the door a few times...no one could hear.  Sheldon and Darren showed up with the remains of a tasty looking subway meal, and I decided to try greg the engineer's phone again...got him this time.  So we were ready to go.  The wait wasn't that big of a deal...a big part of recording is spent waiting for set up, and theoretically the longer it takes to set up the better it will be.  So I didn't mind all the waiting that much...other than the fact I was totally itching to play.  We got all tuned up again and launched into Bus Stop.  Greg the drummer was ON FIRE, and rocked totally.  Unfortunately the rest of us were pretty flaccid...no performance.  But it was the first run, and that's ok.  So we did another one.  All in all it was pretty rockin, but Sheldon didn't have his best run on the bass.  Greg was still on fire, and Darren and I were rocking pretty hard.  So was Sheldon, but he did make a couple of boobups...nothing major tho.  We went in and listened and it sounded fucking HUGE! We almost decided to stop after that one, but I suggested we do one more just in case we hit the zone on it, as we were pretty close on that second take.  The third take was pretty hot too...almost identically played to the second one, but with two of them Greg the engineer will be able to take the best overall one and make something pretty cool.  We chilled for a bit and then launched into Control.  The first take I played pretty well, but no one was totally happy with it.  Again, it lacked a bit of enthusiasm.  On the second take we all played pretty well, except I did a brutally awful solo at the start, and sheldon completely missed the ending...that's ok; that ending was only 3 days old.  We were getting set to go again when the security guards came in and said we had to shut down...it was after midnight and they had expected us out by 10 (!!!!).  The said it was ok to rip off one more take so we did.  And I think we just about nailed it.  Even my solo bit was pretty good (a nice change from the previous version we had played).  The drums were definitely there, we were definitely tight and the performance was pretty rocking.  Sheldon missed the ending bit again, but that's easy enough for him to do over.  So then we helped Engineer greg tear down the gear, loaded up our stuff and went home.  I look forward to hearing what we did in a mixed version, but it will be a couple weeks.  Actually we still have to go in next week and do the vocals too.  I'm stoked about that.  

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The song of my various fans in my computer and the ones just for keeping cool, various pitches and velocities forming their own little symphony.  The metallic creak of my chair as I turn this way or that, the odd thunk as it passes a particular stressor point form their own percussion.  I take a drink from my bottle of diet coke, it hisses quickly as I open it then sputters briefly as I set it down and the carbonated goop gets angry at the motion.  My fingers beat out a somewhat irregular rythm on the keyboard, similar sounding clicks of a sort that if you'd never heard it before, you'd still know that it could only be a manmade sound.    One of the cats run past my doorway, making that sound that only running cats on carpet can make, and my lady Solitation hangs out just past the glass of my window.  It's eerily quiet on Davie st right now considering that it's Canada Day and all the partiers have been drinking since noon...perhaps they've all passed out already.  The heat is somewhat stifling and a thin sheen of sticky sweat covers my entire body; even sitting infront of the fan only brings a temporary reprieve.  I sway between sickly hot and a wierd chill from the sweat evaporating under the fan's spinning eye, and long for a nice cool shower...soon...soon...  In the apartment above me a certain amount of thumping is going on; this happens every night and it's like whoever lives up there has to redecorate their apartment before they go to bed.  That deadened bang that rattles in the walls but has no echo; a symptom of a carpeted apartment.  It always startles me when it first happens and I wonder if someone's getting pushed around.  But then I realize it's probably just a futon being unfolded, somewhat ungracefully, and my mind always strays to that old joke about throwing peanuts on the floor.  "Hi...I'm Peanuts..."  My hard drive spits out it's thinking rap, a new virus or spyware installing itself in a warm and cozy place...probably not actually...my protection systems work as well as they should.  It's just the everyday constant processes that need to be run, the subconscious and unconscious things the computer needs to survive, like breathing and pumping the heart and farting.   I hear the tinkling of breaking glass somewhere off in the distance, someone has dropped or thrown a beer bottle onto pavement.    And Solitation runs away for the time being.  I wonder when she'll be back...  

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...is paved with good intentions.  So much for three days of gym bliss this week... Yesterday the headache, this morning I had to drive Sylvie to work after an interview she had, and then had to rush my own ass to work...sigh... oh well.  Tomorrow is Canada Day, and I have to work.  That sucks ass, cuz normally we do something groovy on Canada Day.  I do get off at 5:30, but for whatever lame reason there is exactly sweet fuck all going on in Vancouver for Canada day night.  We don't even get any fireworks this year, ffs... "Too many safety concerns..." Bah on that...the only safety concerns are the dumbass loogans from Surrey who come into town specifically to ruin people's evenings...real life griefers.  They are all a common profile too...they are 18-25, male, matching wanna be eminem haircuts, and they swagger like wanna be rap stars.  Their only strength is in numbers, cuz solo they're to the last a bunch of pansy assed wimps, but they swarm.  So thanks, Surrey Loogans, for destroying Canada day for the good people around.  Of course, I generalize...they aren't really all from Surrey, but it's fun to pick on Surrey.  If you don't live in this neck of the woods, you wouldn't have experienced the big cliche that is Surrey, but every city in the world has a suburb like it...in Toronto it's Scarborough, in Edmonton it's St. Albert, Calgary it's Airdrie...a suburb where everyone seems stuck at least one decade back, where the mullet is king and the hair sail is queen, and acid wash denim reigns supreme in the fashion magazines.  A suburb where it's considered fun to drive stupidly fast in your (stolen) pickup or rice-racer and hurl insults and worse at people you pass.  A suburb where racism is the norm, not the exception, and it's not just the white nazi's prevacating it.  Uh...I lost my train of thought completely...time to go to bed I guess.  

						
</post>


</Blog>