<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I previously wrote a fairly scathing vent about my husband here. I have decided to take it off because it is not really a fair thing to do. I am a pretty fiery person at times and I am a bit too quick to judge. Mind you he is a lazy bastard at times and I do get very pissed off at him when he appears not to think of things that seem fairly obvious to me like don't pee in the shower. It is a disgusting habit and I don't know anyone who thinks it's a treat to clean urinals. But I do love him a lot and I cannot bring myself to imagine life without him. Sounds really sucky I know but I don't care.  What is it in this life that makes it hard for people to see the good in others? Is it that we are forced to become so fast paced now? That we have barely enough time for ourselves that we can't seem to find time to invest in others? I find it hard these days to find time even to catch up with old friends let alone make new ones. Maybe i should stop blogging. But I don't think that would help either. Before I started I had the same problem.  Everyone I talk to seems rushed off their feet, constantly time-challenged. All these gadgets are supposed to make life easier. I think it is all a farce. It just makes it different. There is now more to do and not as many excuses for when it doesn't get done.   Kids these days seem to grow up right before your eyes. I don't think I had even heard of the internet until I started work. My son (aged 4) now searches it for spider-man sites and robots dancing to cool music. I don't want him to loose his thirst for nature and going for walks along the local creek. Finding spiders and getting his clothes dirty from head to toe. The dirtier the clothes I think the more fun he has had.  I don't believe there are still 24 hours in a day. Maybe I have really terrible time management. Or maybe it is all part of getting older.   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes I sit at my desk and watch my boss,P, walk by and I think he would look not so bad as a drag queen. He is quite lithe with a slender face and high cheek bones. On the other hand if you saw my boss you would probably think that I was being quite insulting of the drag queen community. I guess that it all depends on your tastes.  P thinks that our office handles quite a lot of sensitive information. Well we do but I keep pointing out that I have worked in this industry for 7 years and the stuff I have seen would curl his teeth. Especially if he thinks what he has on his desk would end up on the front of the news papers.  He is constantly paranoid that someone will break into work a steal our files. His words not mine: "I have stuff that people would kill for." Well they haven't yet, maybe soon though. I might be singing from a different mountain if he is ever found in a gutter.  I might come back to this my son wants to show me something and he needs my full attention...  It is really good. His dad bought him one of those expandable balls. It is made of hundreds of coloured plastic joiny things. Really fun. I also saw a membrane. He is very fascinated with it. We are in the middle of re-tiling the shower. We had to paint a white membrane to water-proof it. Anyway you've probably been there before so I won't go there again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love the sound of my daughter laughing. Doesn't matter what mood I am in, I melt when I hear that sound. I will be sad if her laugh changes. My son had a really funny laugh as well. Sometimes when he wants attention or wants me to laugh he will force it but it never sounds the same as when you chuck him on the bed and just tickle him into laughing paralysis.  I think I am on a bliss plan at the moment. I hate the thought of it, but there always seems to be some darkness waiting not too far off into the future. I hope the bliss lasts for a while yet. These periods seem to be getting longer though. Doesn't matter anyway, I'm happy right now.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My boss has a fairly painful ability to swoop from on high, shit all over a project and fly off again.  As I have previously alluded to, he is paranoid. If I was game enough to reveal where I work I think you would have a pretty good cackle. But alas his paranoia has infected me to some extent and I fear that he would find out what I have said. May sound stupid but I don't care.  I don't think I have ever met someone in a position with so much financial responsibility who knows so little about money and budgeting. I don't know that much myself but at least I know enough to know that we should right now be working on the budget for 2005/06... and we're not.  Hmmm. Could this mean yet another year without proper budget? I also know that in October we will be required to present our annual report including financial statements to parliament. And no-one is working on it yet. Though I am sure that I will be one little bunny that will be.  Always at the last minute. What are they? Masochists?! Why can’t management manage?! I swear the P word is a swear word in our office! (P= Planning by the way)  Thank you, I needed to vent.   I get really depressed when I see such wastefulness. We have such a good dynamic in our office. All the staff work so well together. It breaks my heart to think that it has all been such a waste. You just don’t get this kind of dynamic in government.   My boss seems to occupy himself with silly things that just shouldn’t even be on his radar. I think this is in a effort to ignore the really big important issues that pile up, you know those issues that CEO’s are paid the big bucks to pay attention to.  I have worked in the past with management who don’t know much - but this is ridiculous. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My stomach is my worst enemy right now. I don't even know if I can stay at the computer long enough to finish this enrty. I have to keep getting up and running to the toilet. God I hate being ill. The really, really shitty (not pun intended) thing is I really, really have to go to work tomorrow.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>