<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      right today  we had the french oral exam. eeeeeeeeep! i totally screwed it up, i couldnt remember words and shit, i really messed it up i think the examiner felt sorry for me, it sucked big time.  oh well it's a giant weight off my shoulders and now i can get on properly with life and the rest of the exams :)  anyways i havent written in like 2 days :O hehehe but yeah tuesday night i ran off to Briston with Nathan :) ended up sleeping on marc's pull out sofa bed with him, no nothing naughty happened but no 1 believes me when i say that, even though it's true, seeing as it was the wrong time of the month. stupid body. but it was lush to wake up next to him in the morning and be showered with kisses :) mmm was sweet :) *blushes*  yesterday i stressed about french by watching videos and reading clothes catolougues hehe so not classed as revising. but oh well :)  yey camping tomorrow :D it's gonna be so great!!!! seeing all the old crew again :D like Naomi Holly Adam and Dan it'll be so cool, yet so odd, i'm scared i'll have nothing to say to Dan or Holly or Adam i havent seen them since i was 14, especially Dan with all that's happened since i last saw him it's difficult enough online to speak to him let alone what to say in person, coz i had such a majour crush on him from when i was like 11 to just recently, he knows that but i dont particularly care. i just want things to be ok, after the whole photographs ordeal, that was harsh but i think we r ok, well i hope we r. he means alot to me, they all do.  :) i get to see Nathan on friday 4th :) and stay over for one of marc's fab partay's :D woo woo and on the saturday after it's daniel's gig so it's a must :) have to support my freidns in things like that coz it's a kewl thing to do :)  ohh yeah i pinched daniel's lip ring today too, i well want my lip pierced now, it looks so fuckin lush!i want al ip ring in the middle of my bottom lip and a nose ring, a small nose ring on the right side of my nose, it would b such an improvement to my face, which is rank, than to finish off my loverly transformation, i would like my dragonfly tatoo on my back almost at the bottom of my left shoulder blade but a lil bit higher :) then i would b supreme sexiness, possibly get my right eyebrow done too but i think that might be a bit too much. ok i'm gonna scrounge money off momma tomorrow for a hair cut, my hair is really pissing me off so bad i want it cut and straightened and made to look sexy ;) hehe then just to be naughty i might take in the digital camera with my prom dress and shoes steal the lip ring again and get someone to take pics of me lookin drop dead sexy. modest i know hehehehehehe :D but it is all loverly :D hehe i'm way too excited about all of this hehe and now i'm rambling so best be off.  toodles xxxx
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yes this would be titled by lyrics of avril lavigne, that would be because i bought her new album today along with soil's new album and i got a free playlist cd too :) so it's all good!  i had to go to the dentist this morning for the first time in like a year :S it was scarey as hell. i found out the fillings my last dentist had done have "buckled" and need replacing, what a fucktard, aren't fillings supposed to last for forever? plus i had to have my teeth scaled, that fucking hurt. but it'll fo me good in the long run :)   back to work again for training on the new till system, it'll b well scarey when i come back in 2 weeks time to that new system :(  watched empire records again on dvd but fell sleep in the middle woke up and watched the end then watched the bits i missed in french with french subs so it classed as revision, then i watched mulan in french with french subs, so yeah french revison done yeah? hehehe!!!  i cant believe Amba said that to Brian last night, i really think he was offended but just covering it up. i did have a go but then she got uber upset so i had to take it back, i still totaly luv amba she's a fantastic mate, but she shouldnt have said that to Brian no matter what we were talking about, coz he means alot to me and i dont want to lose him as a friend again ever. *huggles Brian* *huggles Amba so she doesnt feel left out or like anything is her fault coz it isnt* right now i've sorted that out in my head it's all kewl i just hope he's ok.  :-D i can't wait to see Nathan tomorrow, i've missed him like crazy, spoke to him on fone coz he pranked me, and *sigh* he's just excelent and i love him, heart body mind and soul. sounds cheesey doesn't it, but i do, i just need to state it out loud coz i truely realised it the other day. i dont care that i'll have to share him with every one else tomorrow, i'll just love being with him, because when i am with him, it's like there is only me and him in the whole world and like nothing else matters at all except us being together. it's a most fantastic feeling *blushes* there's nothing else like it :)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so up early again coz of stupid staff meeting, it bored me to death, plus ryan showed up i wanted to smack him well bad, coz of the mess he got me in last week.  oh yeah by the way i now have super sexy black hair! ;) yeah baby! i look good! ;)  hehe!ok now all sleepy due to my munching on bread pate and cheese, it wasn't supposed to be like a meal but i'm now full so i think my diet is going to pot. daniel called me classy totty coz of what i was eating, silly boy.  i went to real dad's after work meeting, was ok watched pocohontas2 and lion king (that film fricking rules!) and then fell asleep watching snow dogs then got woken up and made chocolate shapes with my youngest half sister, that was kewl though!   now i'm home feeling fat from the munch and i'm craving Nathan. i miss him so much, yet i know he doesnt miss me, coz he has loads on at the moment. just un-nerves me that i actually know he doesn't miss me. i dunno what to do. i want to see him yet i dont think he minds that i probably only see him once every 2 weeks. never mind, i just don't want to lose him, he's everything to me.  i need to write my french oral and learn it for thursday. i am so screwed. i am gonna fail coz i am shit at writing about single parent families in france in french! o why did i chose to do this subject? ok so i do know why i chose french but that's not the point. i just wish all my exams were over so i could get on with re-takes, if i have to take them, which i probably will.  oh well, i wish i hadnt eaten that pate tastes rank in my throat now.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok weekend, should be a day of rest and fun but no i have to get up super early for the music lesson then off to worksky.  got to work after nearly falling asleep in the car again only to have to beg Jane for the day off next weekend to go to whit camp (woo!) she gave me evils and finally gave in after i begged some more, evil woman. she then packed me off to the bank, but on the way i turned on my fone only to recieve a text off the one and only Nathan, love him way too much, made my day and put me in a superb mood all day :)  plus new guy Ross is now a permanent member of the so-called "team" of Cafe Rouge Norwich. he's a dude we get on really well which is well kewl, a new and proper friend in the work place :)  am possibly going to dye my hair black tonight if i can pull myself off of my pc, hope i do.  and i want to kill my pc as i'm on mum's coz i've had to re-boot it twice and i can no longer be bothered with it and it's 20 second delay factor. long live mum's pc!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok note to self never tell boyfriend you are wearing your ex's trousers, he'll think you've been up to no good but will then tell u he trusts you more than that. so if u do have a guilty conscience u feel like shite but if you have a clean one you feel all special inside, like you are truely loved.  today was, well , an experience. watched the crow and beetlegeuse round daniel's house and yes i am wearing his trousers but for a very good reason *pokes the stomach* if you are a girl you'll understand, if you are a boy we hope you understand and just move on, which is what i'm gonna do. anyways watched the dvd's coz french tape and blank tape got mangled up in tape deck when tried to copy french tape to a blank *yawns* it was a messy day but as usual i'll pull through it all, talked to daniel about the day and we r all cool, not that there was a problem.  brandon lee is tres sexual! hehe it had to be said! am currently re finding my love of Aqualung and the cute lil music he makes. so if there are anymore references to his lyrics in my blog that's why. :)  i may add more to this later as have now run out of things to say and the night is still young and i could get enourmously (dont care that that is spelt wrong i can't spell it any ways) bored and write some more random stuffs.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i saw nathan on friday, he looks better than my idiot mind had made him out to look after last weekend but he has to go back to hospital again so they can replace his cheek bone with a plate instead. poor baby, mum says she'll take me to see him in hospital when it all happens.  i didnt get much sleep though on friday night but hey it was worth it :) plus i have to say a big thanks to Kiddo for letting me and Nathan sleep in his bed.he's a top quality dude :)  saturday was rank. no Ryan, he was so loverly last week, it made a change but he was feeling down coz him and Candy have split up, i just so want to hug  him and tell him if he needs someone to talk to or what ever, i'm always there for him. *hugs ryan*  sunday i lounged around and did diddly all day hehe  today was super cool at school all my lil mates from C&A were at induction, and i havent seen them all for ages. Rob still looks as bloody cute as ever, but he has a girlfriend who is also very beautiful in that goth way :) but it was just a cool day :) then it all has to go pear shaped when mum makes me help her to book my flight to Paris for 2 weeks this thursday, am well scared of flying by myself, and of spending 2 weeks with a family i don't know. plus i'll miss Nathan like crazy so am gonna have to have like a billion pounds on my fone so i can text him whilst i'm in france. right now i really dont want to go, i feel like a small child that's lost it's parent in the airport, but i'm too old to have an air hostess look after me :(   i wish it wa sover already so i could be back with all my friends and back with Nathan.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok it may have to be a case of one word descriptions, or not how ever the case may be.  nathan rang me sunday when i was round my dad's, god i love him so much, he talked to me about what he could remember about saturday. i ended up in tears again after the conversation finished. :( i seem to nearly be crying at loads of things lately, and i dont cry, i hardly ever cry. hmm *sighs* who knows.  i may phone him later, or rather i want to fone him but dont know if he'll be up coz his pain killers dont seem to be working, and he's resting loads, supposedly. i can't wait to see him on friday night, i just want to hold him and give him the most gentlest kisses just to make sure i dont hurt him.  going to notre dame, my old school tomorrow, i miss all the old school peeps.  i'm regressing to childhood. i'm reading books i read when i was 12 and younger and watching kids movies, oh well.  right now i feel so drained and so tired, yet when i go to bed i wont be able to sleep and i'll feel really ruff when i get up again. i was nearly majourly sick this morning, and was nearly sick yesterday too outside drama. i hope i aint coming down with anything.  i want to curl up with a duvet and not have to face the world right now, it'd be so simple, but i couldnt live without him in my life.  gig tomorrow night, teen spirit, should be a blast.  hmm have lost my track of thought  mom says nathan can stay over on saturday night if he wants, but he either has to come to the city or stay round my house all day by himself if he doesnt want to stay in city. hmmm tough choice. i just wanna see him, but if he doesnt want to come i'm cool with that.  love him so much, i've never been so frightened in my life for some one else that i care about. sounds weird but i cant explain how i feel now and how i felt then, it's all a blur, like the days are. i though tomorrow was friday but it's tuesday today.  i think i'm loseing it.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      was at nathan's over friday and hannah and amba and rachel are all round tonight everything would be all cool but i can't seem to think happy like.  i found out from a random prerson that i met today who knew kel and doz that nathan had just been taken to hospital, because he had been beaten up by townies, who had broken his nose and some other shit. i didn't know what to think or say or feel, i just had to pretty much power walk with amba to sunrise to see hannah, on whom i burst into tears on, she's never seen me cry ever, coz i dont cry easily. i just want him to be ok. i saw the reflection of the flashing lights of the ambulance in the shops windows, i could have been there for him, and i wasn't, when he needed me most i didnt know and i wanst there for him. right now i just wish i was with him in the hospital, if he's still there, i think he is kirsty his brother's fiance rang me from nathan's mobile to tell me what had happened, they said they'd keep me posted, but i just wish i could be by his side holding his hand, i just wish i was with him. *sighs* i can't explain it it's too hard i can't put how i feel into words and i feel speechless because i just can't talk or know what to say or do. it's like i'm powerless and mute and numb. numb with fear for him and if he'll be ok and all that and i can't express this it's too hard and i don't know how to, i could be here for forever if i tried i feel so many different emotions yet i cant say what.  i saw jonny for like the first time in ages today, man i've missed him, he's great. :) ok so i've changed the subject but i can't talk about it, it's too much. oo ooo oo i got a ticket to see HIM when they come to norwich!!!!!!! VILLE!!!!!! SEXAY MOFO!!!!!!!!  god i hope he's ok and that he knows i'm thinking of him, and i hope the fuckers that did this to him fucking get the same treatment, the bastards. argh!!! i want to be with him.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ---------- Original Message ----------  Hey there! I'm Sarah, Nathan's wifey...lol! I read the stuff on your website, it sounds so bad. I know u probably don't want me commenting, but I just wanna let u know that Nathan loves you, so so so much! Last night, he went offline saying, "I know what I have 2 do, I have 2 go tell her I love her" I hope you 2 are ok! U r a realy gr8 couple! But sorry, i'm sure you don't care what his wife says! Well, catch ya arnd! xx  my reply:  hey hunny bean, it's probably not as bad as it seems i just get way too paranoid about everything, plus i think the stress of exams and stuff was getting to me coz now that i've had my last exam i feel really good about everything. but hey thanks for telling me what i needed to hear, i'd just forgotten the important things about me and him, that he loves me loads and that i love him loads. yeah i think we r ok now after my destructive rants, and i do appreciate you saying all this to me, kinda like a smack in the face whilst saying "hey stupid woman wake up, everything is ok" hehe, so yeah i have alot to thank you for, you've put a smile on my face and also made me realise how much of a bitch i've been, thinking the way i was. soo muchos de love and thanks and huggles to you my lovely. mwah! xxxxxx     ok so i have been a moody winey wingey bitch to him, i'm really sorry and i feel really bad for putting him through it all so when i go round on friday i have to tell him i'm sorry for putting him through hell this past 2 weeks. mmm yey am happier yey! and slightly hyper, lol! i finished my last exam today woohoo!!!! and i get to see my hunny on friday and hannah and rach are staying over on saturday night coz it's hannah's birthday on monday the 21st!  love him loads and loads and loads and loads and loads and more than all that but i would probably never stop typing hehe.  hehe Grant wants hannah coz he is gagin for it the poor boy plus he found out i have loads of bisexual friends so he's like bisexual girls :O *drool* gimme gimme gimme!!! hehe poor love that he is with his shexayfull black hair courtesy of amy :) m cant wait to see him feels like i havent seen him in weeks rather than just days. :) oh his momma says she'll kick him out if he doesnt get a proper job pronto so he may end up living with grant for a while. he knows he can stay with me if he wants but grants is closer to home and to his friends so i can understand why :) which is dandy :)  marc is still being a cunt, they evicted him from the briston posse :O duh duh duh duh "certain death" hehehe oooh that reminds me, must watch that film again soon  i watched sleeping beauty and 5th element yesterday. god i love 5th element it's a perfect film, i love it so much and would gladly watch it again right now :) oh the loverly bruce willis and milla jovovich teamed with chris tucker lol too funny and sweet and beautifull, but not as beautiful as my baby, he's the most shexayfullist guy :D mwah! but............he wont believe me when i tell him he's beautiful, he so should listen to me. hehehe  mmmmm i love the way everything is good now. :)  :O TRAMPOLINE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and in my opinion, i'm the fat lady.  The Reason by Hoobastank  I'm not a perfect person, There are many things i wish i didn't do But i continue learning, I never ment to hurt you, And so i have to say before i go, That i just want you to know  I've found a reason for me, To change who i used to be A reason to start over new, And the reason is you  I'm sorry that i hurt you, It's something i must live with everyday And all the pain i put you you through, I wish that i could take it all away And be the one who catches all your tears, That's why i need you to hear  I've found a reason for me, To change who i used to be A reason to start over new, And the reason is you, And the reason is you, And the reason is you, And the reason is you  I'm not a perfect person, I never ment to do those things to you And so i have to say before i go, That i just want you to know  I've found a reason for me, To change who i used to be A reason to start over new, And the reason is you I've found a reason to show, A side of me you didn't know A reason for all that i do, And the reason is you.    ok so it may be weird to write out a whole song, but it's a beautiful song, and i can't help but listen to it when i feel like this. i feel like i'm being cut up inside and the blade is burning hot yet blunt so it hurts even more.  you talk to your friends about things for support and advice, right? and your best friend tells you that maybe you and your boyfriend aren't working out by the sounds of things. not helpfull, makes me feel extreamly shitty, then when i explain this to another one of my good friends she doesnt understand either and says "fuck him, some men just don't understand women" but then some sense when she asks have i tried talking to him, i tried ages ok but he doesnt talk to me about us he talks to hannah about us. rach thinks i should confront him and ask him to speak to me but i dunno if there is even a point anymore. would he even speak to me about it any way? ok so there is a point i love him, that is the point, and another point is that i want to be with him. but right now it feels like he doesnt care wether we stay together or not, and i really love him and want to be with him, and i really dont want to lose him.    ok it's now midnight so it's probably the 16th now so i have an exam later today, i now feel loads better than i did before, who ever said chocolate makes you happy was so right. coz i feel so much btter yet fat but screw the fat i feel good. and if things aint great between me and Nathan then i'm sure we can work it out and it'll all be ok again :) and if it's me being stupid, i'm sure he'll tell me i'm being stupid and that things are great and all that :) so i just need to chill out a bit more and not get so paranoid and upset about it all.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      meh is how i feel along with pft and naff off.  ok so i havent been about for a couple of days, pretty much like last weekend but when i went to see nathan, i felt alot happier, he seemed happy to see me so i thought things were ok, went to his brother's engagement party but went for a walk and got lost under a tree on the way back hehehe ;) but yeah that was a good weekend, work can kiss my ass though Ross wasn't there and  so i had no one nice to talk to and had to put up with Ryan by myself. i got so angry i've decided that i am going to quit after summer but it'll probably end up being after christmas so i'll have been there for 2 years, it sucks.  i got so angry i made up a lil song, well i started to, i dunno what to call it and i got stuck after the 3rd line.  it goes:  Ryan is a twat Who thinks he's all that He never takes off his skanky townie baseball cap  it works better if you rap it for some reason lol.  found out today he spoke to my best friend instead of me, about us and all that happened this week that i have been tearing myself up over. why didnt he speak to me? i could have given him the answers. she says that maybe he wanted things confirmed from someone who i confide in. maybe. maybe he just doesnt belive me or the text i sent him. FUCK i need to stop being so paranoid.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ned baby i know you will probably never read this but you are an absolute star and the army should consider themselves damn lucky to have you, coz they have taken you away from me :( *sniffles* miss you loads, hope you had a good birthday.  i know this is going to sound really stupid, but i feel like i have screwed up my relationship with nathan to the point that he no longer loves me anymore.  dammit, i'm so stupid for the things i say and do.  in the words of the wonderous Matt "stupid fucking insecurity"
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so i didnt exactly make muffins today but the recipe said american muffins but they aint huge enoughto be muffins they are nice ickle cakes :) am well proud of them coz they taste lush! ok think i might go sneak another one!!!  ok so i ate another 2 i feel super fat now, but i had no lunch!!! lame excuse i know.  ok so i slept half the day away and made cakes when i was gonna tan up in the garden but it was too hot, i was melting inside the house let alone wanting to go outside. plus i was trying not to think about last night and lying in the sun only leaves you to think about things.  he doesnt want to talk about last night.he's been and gonne on the net twice and he doesnt talk about it, when i start to talk about it he just ups and leaves. i dunno. i did ask him if we were ok and he said yes. maybe i should just accept that and think everything is ok. but he doesn't know if he got my text. i hope he understands my text, i don't often bear my utmost feelings, but for him i have, and i hope he understands it, my text i mean.   oh before i forget big shout out and hugs and kisses to Matt and Daniel for getting me through my utter depression and self hate rants and paranoia and upset-ness last night. i love you guys loads for that, and thanks for being there for me when i needed someone to be there for me the most. and Daniel i hope you did ok in your exam after ikept you awake till like half 2 this morning.  i just want him to tell me everything's alright and that i didnt hurt him, what i really need is to see him but i dont know if he wants to see me let alone hold a conversation with me now after last night. FUCK!!! i really am starting to think i have screwd everything up now for me and him, i don't know what to do, i feel so incomplete, i need him in my life.  so many decissions and so many choices, which do i make?
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      english lit exam went ok.  got many texts of crazy mark from whit camp which was nice.  man i feel shit, i've upset him and i didnt mean to damn my bouts of depression. i hate what i've done to upset him, i didnt mean it, i was just being the stroppy moody old cow that i am.of course i trust him, he should know that, shouldn't he? it's times like this when i feel like i'm losing him, that i know he's all i want and nothing else will do, i don't want to lose him, i need to work harder at our relationship, because i need him in my life more than anything.  fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck.  what have i done? shit i dont want to lose him. i love him too much now to be hurt again because of my own stupidity, and incapeability to know what to do and say when in a relationship. i text him the most heartfelt text i have ever written in my life, and i dont know if he has any credit left to text me back or tell me to fuck off coz he doesnt want me, and that all my fears are right, he could do so much better than me so he is going to go and find someone who deserves him. coz right now i really dont deserve him. i dont deserve anyone. DAMMIT!  TEXT ME TEXT ME TEXT ME PLEASE!!!!!!  :) Matt wanted a mention on here so there you go Matt hunny there's your mention and yeah i know all this mess i have got myself in is my own fault for being an idiot, so you dont have to tell me.  *bashes head against the brick wall* maybe if i hit the imaginary wall hard enough with my imaginary head i'll knock myself out and go back in time and make all this right.  wish it was all that simple.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dont care if smileing is spelt wrong, so sue me.  ok was scared of work due to new till,it's all pretty cool now. Ryan is a cunt, i dont care if that's really harsh, he is an absolute cunt to me. i'm always nice to him and he's always an absolute bastard to me, who ever said "never mix work and pleasure" definatly got it right, i wish the whole staff room incident had never happened,yet i still like him and keep forgiving him, why do i do it? :( i gues i just love being hurt and laughed at and made fun of and all that shit. Ross on the other hand is an absolute dude. he gets a full thumbs up. he's easy to talk to and is really nice to me. like we can talk about everything musically we just love the same stuff, except he hates linkin park, i might be able to work on that lol, i doubt it. never mind, we've been to like all the same gigs it so rocks. so i went and bought him a Teen Spirit ticket so i have someone to go with, he says he'll pay me back so just for remembering value, he owes me £7.80. ok so that was work.  i told mom i was staying at hannah's last night, i was really at nathan's we were supposed to go to mark's but didnt. his step daddy got mad at us for falling asleep fully clothed in the sitting room. like how tite you wanna get, nothing was going on.  tonight i asked hannah if she'd have random sex with me. i think i shocked her just a tad. ..... ok so i shocked her alot but we r kewl. she said yes. we r still mates, i doubt the whole random sex would ever happen though so nathan needent feel threatned by hannah.she's my best friend after all.  i dunno what to do. maybe he'd just be better off without me. you know, coz we pretty much dislike eachothers taste in music and stuff, he should be with sarah, not me. Hannah says to be strong, but right now it feels like he'd be better off with out me, he's got his skateboarding and he's got sarah and all his friends. why does he need me when he's got that at his finger tips and i'm all the way over here.  nevermind  i need a shower.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok up date as have not written n e thing in absolutly ages as i was at whit camp.  ok whit camp in short nim dan hollie luke me and mark and steph  hollie and luke awwwwwwwwww nim and jason dan wanted nim and was upset that he got led on but i think he feels better now supposedly nim "slept" with jason on the last night oh my mark and steph were my saviours from bordomn mark made me laugh so much he's a class dude.  ok back to normal typing now.  dan still has my cd's and yeah i still feel something for him but having the fact that he fancies someone else and cant be arsed to talk to you coz he wants to talk to her, kinda makes you wake up and smell the coffee. but i'll always feel something for him.  ok nathan stayed round on wednesday night, and it all went superb, apart from mom walking into my room just after we'd finished having sex. i was like mom, what do you want, she went a bit psycho but oh well, she seems cool today. poor nathan is really embarrassed by it all.i'm not though for some reason,but i do feel for him. poor baby, i'm so in love with him. his friend mark sent me a text but sent it from nathan's fone and made out nathan had recieved a hand job off amy. i woke up to that text at 3am i didnt know what to think. i was well distraught, i had to fone hannah, i just felt like slice-ing up all the skin covering my body but i couldnt coz i was too tired and i just couldnt, i had to ring hannah, coz i didnt know what to do. she talked to me and i went back to sleep and woke up feeling better after reading another text from amy saying mark was messing around. the time i spent with nathan was bliss, even though he did fall sleep on me most of the time, i didnt care i just loved having him in my arms or vice versa.i missed falling alseep in my bed with him though, i love that feeling.  yey brian is speaking to me, :) so glad he hasn't held the amba incident against me. am happy just need to ask mom about "staying round hannahs" tomorrow when i'll actually be at a party at marc's house with nathan, or should i just tell the truth?
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      first of all, a big sorry to hannah, for wakeing her up last night at half 1 in the morning to talk to her and end up in tears on the fone to her for half an hour. so sorry for that hannah, but i love you so much for being there for me and not telling me to sod off. and i take back that i wont pick up the pieces, i will, you are my best friend and i love you so i will always be there for you no matter what hunny.  so i guess you are wondering y i was calling hannah in the middle of the night/morning, if not u r gonna find out n e ways :P  it's to do with the subject of this entry, it's a message to my boyfriend, i will never make him feel as crap as i am feeling now, secondly it's a message to 2 of the people i would have trusted with my life.  i hope i'm not alone in saying that when you lose your virginity, inevitably emotions end up linked to that person too, no matter if you have moved on, right? well i think that because i can only describe last night as brain numbing pain combined with not being able to breathe and then shakeing violently from head to toe for 10 minutes, whilst on the fone to hannah.  this brain numbing pain,shakeing,tears, wakeing up with shredded lips from them being bitten to death when i finally managed to fall asleep, because i am "stressed" all come from two people, the ones i said i'd trust my life with, but now will never trust with anything again.  the reason y i will never trust one of my best friends again and my ex who i considered to be quite a good friend now, is because, it is a known rule that you don't fuck with friends or their relationships, and she has broken both those rules.  she fucked with me and she fucked with my head and my world and my life and as you can hopefully see what i'm about to say, she's fucking my ex.  and she didnt have the descency to tell me, even though she's had chances to, and she knows about how i feel about my ex and that i have emotions tied to him because of everything that i went through when i was with him. and i can't belive that some one i have been there for through all the shit that they have gone through whilst i have known them would stab me in the back like this. and to top last night off when i told my ex i was going to go to bed aka fone hannah and cry, he had the audacity to say "i have a bed ;) " so i replied top him "and you will never have me in it" so he got all moody said fine and pissed off.  then today when i'm with clem and chris, she sees me. just what i didnt need. she squealed, came bounding over to me, so i stepped back and away from her, i didnt want to be touched by her. nasty and horrid i know but i couldnt handle acting all fake and pretending like i wasnt hurt. i just told her not to touch me, but i couldnt tell her it was because of her i said it was because of people, which in theory it is, her and my ex.  i then left, with clem and chris, who completely understood, and gave me the hugs that i needed, but though they tried, i couldnt smile. i just need to forget that she and my ex exist.  so yeah, that's why i feel so shit right now, and why bad news doesnt sit too well with me.  i just hope i can last the summer out alone, without him.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      strange song for a subject title but it keeps running round in my head.  i hate kids, the kids i have to direct do not listen to me, they all need to be gagged and shut in a dark room, the fuckers.  i need to start writting songs again so that i don't sit there and imagine myself dead any more, when i get depressed, or go and do other stupid things. i need to start writting songs again, songs are better than the real thing.  ok guess you are probably wondering if there is something wrong with me in the head, and i'm sure there probably is.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      there aint no sunshine in my world no more, well there is but i'm being shipped off to paris thursday and i didnt get to say bye to ma shexay boyf on saturday and now i wont see him till august. :( sucks loads. but..................  WE LOVE ZIGGY, YES WE DO, WE LOVE ZIGGY, HOW ABOUT YOU?   hehehehe ziggy put sunshine back in my world, god i love her she's such a great mate, and rachel too i love her too, she's tops, hehe literally lol, nooooo, i love her coz she put sunshine in my world too and gave me more gay gundam wing! yus! gotta love the gay gundam wing :D specially for the gay sex, lmfao hehehehehehehehehehehhehehehehe!!!!! and Relina needs to be shot that bitch!!!!!  ok i shall stop my wild rantings.  i need alkohol and lots of it now now now!!!!! please!  vodka preferably, with coke :D
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      skewl was a blur all watching video type lessons and a form party period 7 which was kewl.  fell sleep on way home crick in neck very painful when woke up.  amba gave me one of her roses coz i've never been given flowers in my life :) it's in a vase looking beautiful and solitary but still beautiful :)  the hospital was loverly they let me in after visiting hours to see nathan, they said 20 mins on fone but i stayed for like an hour. i just wanted to crawl onto his bed next to him somehow and fall sleep next to him with my arms round him, but the stupid side things were in the way. sweet and tender kisses were all i could offer when i arrived and when i left.  i want to see him again
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      :D ok so new fone almost here, it'll either be the same as hannah's or an upgrade to a better nokia :) but the nokia costs £10 more.  :( am worried about my baby, he goes into theatre tomorrow to have his cheekbone replaced, i wish i could be with him but school is a bitch, and i have to go to school. he knows how much i love him, ijust wish i could show t better by being there for him when he realy needs me. :(   i hope my stupid father remembers to bring rachels video to my work on wednesday. if he doesnt i will not be pleased.  *sighs* love him so god damn much, i know he'll be ok, i just worry about him
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THERE WILL BE A SPONGEBOB SQUARE PANTS MOVIE COMING SOON!!!!!!!!!!  how kewl is that huh?  me and nathan have been together 3 months today, i find that scarey, not that we've been together for 3 months, but because i find myself loving him more and more, yet i dont feel shy because of that, i just feel so at ease with him. mmmm *huggles nathan*  ok enough of the mushy stuff for those of you that are reading this and have just puked up in the nearest bin or toilet or sink. lol!  ok i must say this now, even though Ryan at work still picks on me sometimes, it's all in jest, but, now that he is single and has revealed he hasnt had sex for 2 months am quite worried coz he's a randy lil fucker, lol and way too flirty with me, but i am good, even when he spanks my arse tells me i have a firm ass and then suggests we go to the toilets to have a "little feel around" (the dirty sod) i tell him no because i love my boyfriend and that i dont want anyone else but him! ha! go me! but i  know ryan will find a beautiful girl somewhere else, screw her and probably end up with her or go and screw someone else, as is his nature, i'm sure. nah i shouldnt be mean to him, i know he's nice really and that he has feelings underneath the exterior, i'm sure.  anyways, i'm gonna be sickly sweet again and rant on again about how much i'm in love with my boyfriend Nathan, he's the best, he introduced me to HIM and my love of Ville Valo :) cant wait to see HIM in october with Nathan :)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      prom was bloody fantastic, everyone looked so prettyful and smart and prettyful, ok i know i said prettyful twice but people were super prettyful last night. the limo ruled, sunroof, babysham, cd playering radio, tv with videos and play station :D  had ma first slow dance last night, yeah get me for first times! hehe first prom, first slow dance, first limo ride! yeah baby yeah! hehehe!  hehe also found out my boyfriend is a kinky lil boy ;) hehe  france is looming closer and closer, and i'm feeling more and more frightened about flying by myself :(  i forgot i got paid today so went out and spent all my money on HIM cd's :) mm Ville is so shexay like nathan, but he doesnt believe me.  grr my sis doesnt like the sound of my HIM cd's grr to her i refuse to change the cd's raaar to her  :( there's the possibility nathan could be on a 3 week holiday when i get back from france so i wouldn't see him for a month and a week :( i hope that doesnt happen but i have a really bad feeling that it will happen that way. could this change everything? i hope not, i'm not too great with change.  i cut my hair for the prom i now have a sweepy fringe and my hair is all choppy and shorter, and straight for the moment :) looks so sexayful but i'll wash it and end up with curly hair blegh.  mmm shleepy as hell and i love ziggy so much right now, she's the best :)  i told hannah i'm tired of picking up the pieces, i've always been there to pick up the pieces for all of my friends when they have chosen to do something that i disagree with coz i know in the long run they will end up hurt, they never listen and i always have to clear up the mess afterwards, but i wont this time. sounds harsh i know, but i dont see why someone would put themself through something to most likely come out with a messed up head at the end of it all again. *sighs* but i also know, that even though i have said that, i will still be there to be the one they cry on at the end of it all.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Grant = Great Randy And Notoriously Talented  hehe came up with that just now         I tashte like  Alcohol .   Heh. Heh. I taste like beer. I like beer. Buy me a beer. I'm not drunk, I can drink plenty without... What was I saying? Beer.  What Flavour Are You?       if i'm not alcohol i'm tea hehe i'm both god dammit!!!!         Cor blimey, I taste like  Tea .   I am a subtle flavour, quiet and polite, gentle, almost ambient. My presence in crowds will often go unnoticed. Best not to spill me on your clothes though, I can leave a nasty stain.  What Flavour Are You?       hehe steeeev gave me those i taste like alcohol or tea, how kewl is that :D  i had a fab day today besides the rain which soaked me jeans right through and no one was about so i went to Daniel's, i would have text him in advance but i haven't got enough credit by 1p how lame is that, ahh well it was superb to see him again i hadn't seen him for like a month owwwww man i love his hugs makes everything ok :)  la la la la la la *prances around*  i bought a cd single today coz i love this song it's called "Move ya Body" by a twin sister duo called NINA sky it's kewl it's a bit dance hall but i like that :) coz i'm weird with my musical taste like that :)  may write some more laters but not now, coz i cant think of any thing more to say.  toodles xxx 8:25pm  ok i have just found out  I AM FAMOUS!!!!!!!! i was in the evening news last night aka i was in the evening news on monday night :D  ahahaha and i'm in it talking about how i deal with being dumped lmao!!!!!! like how ironic is that!!!!! hahahahahaha!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Git = Gay Ignorant Twat Gimp = Gay Ignorant Man Pimp Mofo = Mentally Orally Fucked Object Snob = Sterile Nob Of Bastards Muffin = Mentally Unhinged Finger Fuckin Indecent Nob Ziggy = Zyborg Imprisones Girl Going Ya ya Keturah = Kinky Excentric Timeless Unforgetable Randy And Happy Hannah = Horny And Nuttily Naughty As Hell  hehehe dammit ziggy went offline so i had to finish the hannah one so it's a bit crap. today i rented Honey on DVD and it was great to watch jessica alba dance around in skimpy outfits :D  ahh gotta love ma momma she's cutting all my nails for me coz i'm retarded and cant do them coz i normally bite them, so now i have nice nails :) well sorta they just need to grow back a bit now  hmm i hope grant is drunk out of his mind, it's just makeing me turn towards women more and more, they way men are all acting right now. he defaced a pic of darin yevonde who is an absolute sex god, not good. *sigh* ok so maybe slight over reaction. hmmm.  god i loved the storm this morning at 6am i didnt open my eyes to see it but it woke me up like KABOOM!!!!!!!!!!!!  god it sounded like it was right over the house it was so kewl :D then tonight the storm was tip top too, thunder lightning and oodles of rain :D i wanted to go out in the rain but i missed it :( o well next time no matter what i'll b out there dancing in the storm yeah baby!  woop! louis has said he'll take me for a spin in his fucking lush mini!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! woop! got to love all my old skewl mates, i miss em loads right now. *sniffles* must arange a meet up with all of em. :)   i hope sexy tom comes to city tomorrow coz i need to buy that HIM tickit off him for ziggy, coz she's an absolute babe and deserves to go so much.   you hear me tom that tickit is for me to buy for ziggy kapish!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so i watched that dvd on friday, my empire records dvd, and am now listening to the sound track wich aint as groovy as the movie coz they ran outta money and couldnt put all the cool tunes on the sound track from the movie.  Nathan and me seem to be all cool now and i think the friends thing is settling in, which, even though i want him back, is probably for the best, because i know i am not what he wants. we just both need to let go, which i know he has done so i just need to catch up and let go too. then we can both be happy :)  today was so god damned boring, and i feel super fat coz i did fuck all, except sit and watch tv, god i'm sad, but it was mainly good tv it was the world rally chamionships, so like rally car races and shit it's so bloody kewl :D  i got a surprise text of jordan today which was nice but took bloody ages to send a reply back coz in my step dad's house i have fuck all signal, but he just wanted to know if i had a girls mobile number but i didnt know who he was talking about so i felt a bit crap not being able to help him.  Edwyn Collins song "A Girl Like You" fookin rocks and so do fizzy coke bottles, those lil penny chew things, i've started eating the things and i cant stop and i know i'll end up being super hyper again :D hehehehehehehehehehehehe!  16 days to go!!!!!!!!!!!! till i'm 17 woop!!! what shall i do to celebrate? even though every time i've celebrated it fucks up and goes wrong, fuck the evil curse of birthdays i'm 17 must be celebrated! i wanna go all kiddy and go to pleasure wood hills hehe that'd b a laugh and a half but i dunno how every1 would get there and tis prolly major loads of money, which none of us have. i can't b arsed with a drinkin party like last year, too much effort. would go to cinema but hannah not like cinemas. *sighs* what to do?  wooo! Daniel comes home today!!!!!! which means i can go see him soon and get a fantastic hug off him coz i feel like i haven't seen him for a month. will b nice to see him again and to catch up.  hmm fizzy coke bottles starting to taste of lemonade hmmm not good, better eat a couple more just to test them :D hehehehehe  yes these too taste of lemon, not good, damn french fizzy cola bottle chews!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah i'm tired of being alone now. i know it's the whole re-bound effect taking hold of me but i just want him back, i miss him so god damned much, everything reminds me about him, and us and how it all used to be. :( life now officially sucks, i'm alone and i ript my kewl long goth skirt today and i love that skirt, and all around me there seem to be happy couples.   and on top of that today it was the first time i had seen ryan today since the last time which would have been a month today, and he was ok with me last time i saw him but today he was being a complete and utter cunt and so mean come on like cant me and him ever be friends? from the looks of things i'd take it as a no. damn him! why do i care? ok so i know why i care but i wish i didnt care. pretty much ever one of the old crew at work dont like me i think, coz they are all so similar and all one of the popular crew people from the old skewl days i reckon and i just dont fit in with them, it's like i'm out of my league. lol, ironic really, that i say i'm out of my league with work, ryan is all i look forward to at work coz we usually get on and have a laugh but looks like him and hannah O. are all buddies at work now, i hate being excluded, dammit, no one told me they were all going out on the town when i got back.   ok so i am having a major bitch session at work but i'm allowed to ok, coz i hate life and it just keeps getting worse because on top of all that ross is like majorly like hugging and touching my ars all the time, yeah ok i get it he fancies me but i dont want him like that, i just want him as a friend, i dont want any kind of a relationship right now. like the title of today's entry says in the lyrics of white snake "here i go again on my own, like a twister i was born to walk alone" i guess i'm just ment to live my life alone, because how could anyone deal with some one like me, i'm just too much hassle.  ok i really should stop comming back to this after i have written it, this is the second update of tonight.  i spoke to nathan again tonight, he didnt mean that i love him too much, he ment i was too possessive or how ever you spell that word. but then he tells me he was a retard for splitting with me but b4 telling me i'm possesive he tells me he thought i looked really pretty when i saw him on thursday. Kat just went, "oh my god what a total mind fuck" yeah it has fucked up my head again, but i just told him if he didnt like me hugging him so much he should have just said get off, and i would have. but i know he doesnt want me back no matter how many times he says he should have never split with me, i wish he never had split with me, we should have just talked this through. god i miss him so much. he said he'd forgotten it was saturday coz the only way he knew it was saturday was by walking me to his bus stop in the morning but now he doesnt do that.  i feel so alone in the world now, all my friends are trying so hard to lift me back up onto my feet but i just can't feel happy.they are saying everything that i say to them when they are in my position, but now i know it just doesnt make a difference, i still feel shitty and alone, and i'm not over him. because i still want him back, and i still want him, so much. i tell myself i need to let go, because that's what he has done, and i try to do that, during the day when i dont think about him, when i push all this to the back of my mind, i'm fine, but then it's now when it all comes out and i just feel like if i wasn't here it'd be so much better for him and for me. i'd be over all of this, and he wouldnt keep getting confused when i talk to him. coz i know he'd get over it if i died, not get over the break up but get over my death.  listening to the sound track from the film The Piano makes me think abouth what it'd b like to drown, is it like suffocating but with water? i have a weird imagination, i see my death. do you want to know what i see?  no i didnt think you'd want so.  look what i just did again its supposed to be the HIM song that i am, seems to be true after what i found out tonight,this is what it said:  urlLink     Which HIM song are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so i didnt exactly explain about the auction of my boobs properly yesterday, you do not get touching rights or viewing privaledges u dirty pervs you!!! only a certificate saying that my boobs are belong to you. understand?  ok today was soo fucking weird and awkward for me. i saw nathan today for the first time since he split with me, so i ran over and spoke to him, he was with deli, it was really awkward :( he still looks beautiful as ever and i just wated to hug him and kiss him hello, but i knew i couldn't even touch him :( this so completely sucks balls coz now after seeing him i miss him so much and just want him back. i miss his little kisses and the feel of his arms around my waist and i miss the feel of his skin against mine :( he was the only person i have ever let kiss my nose and i havent freaked out afterwards, coz i hate people kissing my nose it feels rank but he did it in such a way that it didnt feel rank. DAMMIT! how can you love some one too much???? *sigh* i dunno but it's one of the reasons he split with me that and the fact "he can't handle me" and "he wishes he'd never split up with sophie" dammit y do i have to still like him.  jimmy today did the sweetest thing for his girlfriend he baught her this amazing necklace and it looks like it cost him like a few hundred and it's as a thank you for helping him out through loads of things, it's like major awwwwwwwwwww factor.  oh and Fitz has made me part of his hareem, so i'm now his bitch hehehe! and i had a great conversation with him about underwear and how stockings and suspenders rule. which they so do. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yeah how fucking sexual did i feel today on a scale of 1 to 10.........hmm. about 9 and a half coz of that fucker that ruined the start of my day buy implying i was a hooker, the TWAT! ahh well i told him to fuck off, coz i have class baby oh yeah :D lol! but saul was like ooo look at youwith yur legs out and gave me one of his lush hugs and ross at work was like oh my god how sexy do you look today and he said i had a shexy face too and i was like urm yah what ever u must be blind and jimmy was like "and you said you had no goth wear" lol and the dude that owns the fuck off huge metal trike said i had sexy legs and nice new rock boots :D so all round i was like yeah baby do i look good? HELLA YEAH! amba said i looked gorgeous and so did katie to so we love them too!!!and i walked past some road workers and 2 ( a diff 1 each time i walked past) was like oi oi! and then to top my day off this kewl lady asked me where i got ma loverly dress from so i told her and was like dude score! hehehe the only other thing that ruined my short day was the dentist, i now hate the dentist. he drilled into my tooth and then blasted it with cold air and i was like "OWWWWWWWWWWWWW" but it's all in the aid of healthier teeth, right?   oh yeah b4 i forget i have a large announcement:  I AM SELLING MY BOOBS TO THE HIGHEST BIDDER!!!!!  lol! Roo and i made a deal that she should have my boobs but then i remembered loads of other people want my boobs too so i said i'd auction them off to the highest bidder, hehe! Roo says she'll always be the highest bidder but i think she might have some stiff competition! :D the highest bidder will get a signed certificate saying my boobs belong to them, but, there r rules, if i ever get a boyf or girlf again the owner of my boobs has to let my boyf or girlf have the privalidges that they rightfully get aas being my girlf or boyf, and my girlf or boyf must not get jealous that some one else actually ownes my boobs. so you know it's all fair and square :) bidding shall commence today i have decided hehe!!!!  so yeah BOOBS FOR SALE!  ooo look what i just did i hope it works ok       Your love is... by  urlLink  ChibiMarronchan        Your name is...           Your kiss is...    erotic      Your hugs are...    warm      Your eyes...    burn into my heart      Your touch is...    irresistable      Your smell is...    beautiful      Your smile is...    encouraging      Your love is...    everlasting              urlLink  Quiz created with MemeGen  !      
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah majour update, since i last wrote on here.  last time i wrote on here i was majourly pissed off at amba and daniel but i spoke to daniel about it all and it's all kewl now with me coz i shouldnt stress over it coz my friends should be able to do what they want, so yeah they can go screw each other as much as they want it's kewl with me :) so i'm like yeah amba i love ya buddy u sexy thing, and i'm like yeah daniel my bestest boy buddy luv ya too :D  i went on hols, that's why i haven't updated for ages and ages and ages, but yeah paris was kewl saw pretty much all the tourist sites and famous things and i went to disney and nathan dumped me, but he didnt want to via text. it's all one big mess now really but i'm kewl with being friends, coz in the end i think it's the best thing for both of us coz i'm not the kind of girl he wants really.  but now that i'm single i turn around and all the fit people have dissappeared o gone and got a girlfriend, and there r not fit women anywhere that r single lesbian or bi. i love k8t but she's a mate so it's a no no. coz i have found out sleeping with mates is wierd the morning after when they have decided thay are actually staright lol oh well tis kewl.  all is kewl right now, i'm just glad to be home, i just want to see every1 and daniel doesnt get back off hols till sunday so i have to wait untill halfway through august to get any more "ahem" foto's of me which is kewl coz means my skin might not be such a bitch and by then it might b looking peachy :D  nath was being so weird with me last night, i dont like it,  i can try the whole friends thing if he will, but i dunno it takes to wo work at friendship as it does at everything else. but kel is still an absolute babe for being spectacular as usual and grant he's a babe too for being so fantastic. coz i remembered something he said to me prom night about me lookin ok and not like a hooker, and that was really nice of him, but he probably lied coz i reckon i did look like a hooker. ahh well paranoid mofo here!!!  need to speak to Ryan, i havent seen him for 3 weeks i went to work to check rosta today am only on for saturday which is great, plus Ned is back at work. which reminds me, god i miss Ned from NDHS he's my lil army man who i havent seen in like almost a year *sniffles* i miss him like hell, he's like one of those best friends that you miss like hell, and when you are with them everything is kewl and you just have a laugh, hehe i bet he's got majourly taller again, he made me feel so mini last time i saw him :) oh happy memories :)
     
    
</post>


</Blog>