<Blog>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      There is a wlays a first Sitting in front of a blank page wanting to write but feeling kind of embarresed to start.  I have decided that this is going to be my blog on the finerside of me. My love for Tolkiens books, History and other related items. For that reason I have chosen the nick Gilraen Surion. That is the name that was given on one of those sites that changes your name into elvish. Alway thought that was great fun and somehow the name stuck with me I actullay like it a lot. It is kind of ambigeous yet eerily female and beautiful  Who am I? Well I live in NZ but was born in the Netherlands. I emigrated about 8 years ago and haven't looked back. My arty farty side as I tend to cal it is inspired by a love of history and all that it entails. My main interests lie in the european middle ages because that was a very confusing time in many ways. But to be fair I like anything from ealy middle eastern civilisation all the way to before 1800. After that it rapidly tapers off and after the 1930's I loose completei interest. Strangely enough as that is where my partner is really interested in. Maybe that is why we are compatible.  Art wise I tend to like the gothic and pre-raphalite periods. But again I like a lot up to Art Deco, art deco is sort of the separation point Modern art well a lot of it I just find dull and uninspiring Sure there is good art but that tends to be noted by art critics as old fashioned, nature bound folklore etc. Which to me is a snobbish attitude. I will make an exeption for surrealism which I find often incredibly clever and all encompassing in that is kinds sucks you into the painting. As a result I completely understand that top dollar is paid for Faberge eggs and van Gogh.  The combination of the two  Well I have a passion fo jewellery as long as it is simple and very wearable. Jewellery that you lock away is useless, may as well not own it. As a result I tend to go for nice fake as I cannot afford a lot of the real stuff. Besides a lot of the real stuff is so overdone and tacky that I would not even want to be found close to it. Celtic inspired always has me raving It gives me a high feel good factor  Tolkien well what can I say: I have loved the books for a long time and the movies are incredible, the attention that PJ paid in them in beyond obsessive compulsive. My most favourite are the costumes. Ngila Dickson is my hero. I have always fancied sewing and partly due to the movies I am now sewing and a lot will go into costuming.   My first two costumes were for the world premiere in Wellington, the return of the king. I made for myself an adaptation of the requim dress as worn by Arwen and for my partner a Ranger outfit. He looked stunning. We went to the One Ring Party and were at the red carpet; sunburnt and all. We were joined by a friend who was also wearing her self made costume and some other fans that we met in Wellington. We had so much fun both making the costumes and wearing them.   Other than Tolkien I tend to read a lot of historic novels (a suprise this is) and science fiction. In SF I like Isaac Asimov, David Brin, John Barnes (please no more sequels to a million open doors), Terry Pratchett, JK Rowling and some Greg Bear, Neal Stephenson and Ben Bova. There are many that I have yet to read. We have about 3,000 books at home and hence there is a lot of reding to do. Most of the books belong to my partner and he reads fast and lots.   Anyway I think this suffices for now I will post whenever I feel like it 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Not much happening at present. We bought ROTK on video and of course watched it immediately. Can't help but completely gush over the costumes. They are so beautiful.  My own sewing projects are quite different but still enjoyable. I have made the jacket from Butterick 3936. It is officially colonial but has some nice Victorian overtures. As it was the first time I made it I used very cheap fabric.  I made it at sewing class and guess what My teacher told me to take 10 com off the sleeves as the sleeves were too long. Needless to say they ended up being too short as she had not properly checked the pattern and had failed to notice the ballooning top of the sleeves. Anyway with a fake cuff that was sorted quite nicely The rest of the pattern came out well and really fits nicely. My partner loves the pattern and has asked me to make it in a thin type of PVC. To be honest I find the fabric a bit intimidating but  also think it will really look very nice once finished.  I used the same cheap fabric to make myself some pants for work and these cane out really well. The front crotch is still a bit too long. I used Butterick 3527. This was the second time I used the pattern. The first time I had to redo most of the work as due to again my sewing teacher not paying enough attention to the pattern I ended up having to ay the waist out. I re-did most of the pants by re-inserting the zipper and making the waistband fit my waist. I know my sewing teacher twice. I am going to change teachers.   Somehow I don't click with this lady. Her style is too boring for me I like to be a little bit more flamboyant with my patterns do strange things with them make them more personal I mean why else would you sew?   Anyway the second one was better. Looks completely different from the first one. Adaptations were that I overlocked the seams where I could. I also made the waistband wider than on the pattern. Furthermore as I wanted the stripes vertical in the waistband it had to be cut at a 90 deg angle from the grain. As a result I interfaced the whole waistband and that gives a great finish  The pattern was altered in the hip and the crotch to accommodate by wide hips and relatively high narrow waist. I signed up for patternrevie.com and that means I can now cross reference  Now I sew all of a sudden is seems everybody does. Very weird but big fun at the same time. Not sure what I'll do next feel like making a simple little summertop. That of course while it is winter here! Oh well having fun with it 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>