<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So last night Marlee came over and we walked to Lanark. We dropped by James' (marlee's James...thats now official because I'm insitant) house and him and Mar slept over. We smoked some pot and then watched movies all night...it was awesome...but we ended up sleeping (hahah spooning) on the floor cause there wasn't enough room in my loft. So yeah..floors are not all that comfortable.  This morning we watched like all of the movies we watched last night AGAIN cause we didn't pay any attention to them first time...except for me...but I know them all off by heart anyways cause I hate TV so I watch movies!! So yeah...I had an all right time...better than being alone! hahaha...when Marlee's dad picked her up James waited in my room until they left to walk home...it was funny...he is such a pussy...and Marlee is going out with him!! They are overly cutesy...its adorable!!  hmmm...camping with (my) James (there are to many Jameses)...my mom is all 'I want to talk to Ursula to make sure she is okay with this first." and "I think I have a responsibilty" blah, blah, blah...I'll be able to go though...its funny cause I'm not even sure if Bob is coming so calling Ursula is a little ridiculous...I told mom that and she was like, "Well get James' number so I can talk to HIS parents" and I was like...uhhh...I don't even know his parents...meh...I'll figure things out...I still have like 23 days to work things out.  I must go eat...I promised Ma I'd eat with her and Mike (stepdad.)  Chiao
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things that make me glad (today):  1. In the letter James is sending me (I mean Rames is sending Bo) he included a dead flower with a caption that reads "Unlike this flower, my love for you will last forever" that is the sweetest thing ever!!!  2. I finally have plans!!! Marlee is coming over!!! YIPEE!!!  3. I ranted at Jenny and made some fun whore comments about Geena in Keri's entry about the party Geena and Jenny aren't invited to!!!  4. I took pictures...and I'm hot...haha...I'm so falsly conceited!! And by falsly I mean I am NOT conceited...although really I shoul be...ust look at me!!! I'm just kidding...  5. I am about to go eat chicken!!!  6. Now I'm just grasping at straws!!!  So I am done...  XOXO
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      More and slightly better pictures of me!!! Yipee!!                           The last one makes me smile...and sorry about the ones that are basically doubles...meh...you like it!! haha  James loves me more than Pearl Jam...and he really loves Pearl Jam!!! He was telling me a story which was indirectly about us and then my computer froze...that made me really sad...I haven't talked to him since :(  "Dirty, dirty fingernails. Out of the shower, onto the bathroom floor. Out of the kitchen, underneath the casserol. Dirty, dirty fingernails." -Dirty Fingernails by Modest Mouse  I love that song!!  XOXO
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really wanted to go see a movie tonight but Adam fell through, Phill has a mass amount of homework and Khala's mom had sex, had a kid (who is apparently a girl) and Khala has to babysit the 11 year old nuisance, so she can't go either. And I am NOT going to see a movie with my mom.  haha, I tried to convince James to hop on a bus and come to Perth for the weekend but his parents are nazis and would slaughter him...but he really wants to and I really want him to.  Maybe he will come down next weekend...Jeffrey too!  haha, Camping: my mom wants to talk to Ursula (Bob's mom) to make sure she is aware of the camping trip and that there will be boys and girls alone in the woods.  She is worried we will have 'too much fun', meaning sex of course. I asked James if I should bring my tent and he said that i should just to make it look like we WON'T be sleeping together...of course we will be...but hey!  Anyways...Khala wants we to go to www.illwillpress.com so I'm off to check that out...bye!  XOXO
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today we were in the Fry Hut and we saw Geena, the walking std coming towards the Hut.  So we were like, Oh! Here comes the walking, talking std with bad hair.  Eric over heard us and was all I'm in! So when Geena came inside he was like which one of them (she was hanging out with three orie kids [grade eights on an orientation trip to the highschool]) is the walking std?? And we just laughed and laughed. God I hate Geena. I can't find a single redeeming feature about her. She is a short, ugly poser sporting a bad attempt at emo hair.  I hate everything about her. The way she walks, talks, thinks, looks, acts. Everything.  Anyways, 'nough about her.  So next weekend Jeffrey is coming over...which means Khala will probably come too because she wants him...and he is a bloody riot!!  I'm hoping I can get Bob and James to bus down here aswell and we can have a big party!!! Haha, I let Khala add James on msn but I made her promise not to love him or let him love her.  She guaranteed me that he wouldn't love her...then I gave her a virtual hug!!  My Bus: My mom has taken to giving my busdriver info on The Green Party, meaning a) I have to deliver it, b) he calls the house and c) Jim is scary... Today we passed a horse shitting...that was pleasant...  lalala...no one is on msn...James said he'd come on earlier today cause I'm always logging off when he is logging on :( I heart him...he is my emo-boy, sex-bomb!!!  My Homework: Two sheets of 'fun' science homework about the periodic table, drawing a totem pole and a pictorial story for art, and for gym (yes, gym) -drum role please- a touchdown dance...Mrs.Rumball is bloody awesome. Wow, thats the first time I've evr called her  MRS .Rumball.  Dreams: I had this dream about Stephanie cutting herself...which is weird, cause I don't   THINK   she does, but she very well might...once I had a dream about Justin S cutting himself but I don't think he does either...wow...weird, Steph just logged on...speak of the devil and she will appear...wild...  I guess I'm done here...  Chera!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Girls bug me. In all their girly excitableness.Kyle Tengelics just asked out Geena, which I really don't give au fuck about. He is dirty and boring, the only reason I ever say anything to him is cause he is hot.  Anyways, Ashley was doing that whole girly scream thing cause she was happy for Geena.  A bunch of 'Oh My God's were exchanged.  And Geena explained what happened, with many 'like's through out her tale.  I saw it happen...I watched from my desk...it was rather anti-climatic.  Teenage relationships are ridiculous.  Speaking of relationshipds, I love James.  I'm going camping with him soon!!! (I had a dream last night...it was me and my mom and stepdad trapped in some wooded area trying to build a shelter) And Jeffrey might be coming up this weekend or next. I miss Jeffrey, and I can't wait to go camping with Bob and James!!!  Okay...should be doing math...  C ya
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot to mention my dreams last night (yeah, I've come to the conclusion that I always have multiple dreams at night) one had adam in it and i can't really remember much of it...and the other was a silent film starring Keri in a big white wig (like the ones the judges wore) and she was at my house (which had transformed into a victorian mansion) and there were all of these bizarre people there...the one i remember best was the very last one...this really creep female contortionist. I blame Adam for that...he started talking about contortionists the other day.  Anyways...so when Keri saw the contortionist this big comic book-esque speech bubble popped up and it said 'Oh my!' and then my alarm went off...it was funny...the silent film...even though it was scary I just thought it was odd that I dreamt a silent film.  XOXO  P.S. James is back...he was just getting drunk...thats why he hadn't been online.  Anyways...bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rugby is killer.  Gillian drove me into the ground shoulder first and then spun me like a screw into the ground...it was AWESOME!!!  Dave is back...but I didn't get a chance to talk to him cuz I had detention...and the guy supervising was a total reject and didn't know how to tell time.  Awesome Guy (Jon) seems really pissed at Dave...poor Dave...but it was his choice to go to the library and not hang out with us...GO BOOKS!!!  Today on the way home on the bus I saw Eileen (stepmom) driving.  I immediatly had this overwhelming sensation of utter disgust.  Got home, had a shower (I was bloody dirty from rugby...it was rainy) and now I'm here...I should do my science before I forget and get caught up in talking to people on msn...speaking of which I haven't talked to James for like five days :( Keri was really happy when I told her that, said that I belong with Dave, not James :( oh well...I miss James...but Dave IS hot...but still...jaaaaammmmmeeeessss....  Chera
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't think this weekend will ever end.  And the power keeps going out cause its raining and what not, which means it might go off tonight and fuck up my alarm clock and then I will be late waking up.  I had this dream last night and there was this talent show at the school but it was held outside (in a field that is identical to the one at my dad's place...why do my dreams always end up there???) Jamie did this dance thinger with some other people to the song The Sad Robot by Lardpony...but it wasn't The Sad Robot...it had messed up pop, girly lyrics...which pissed me off tremendously.  And I told Khala that and she was like "No, they didn't rip off Lardpony, its the otehr way around" and then I got even more mad cause I love the song The Sad Robot...anyways, the whole thing was a little trivial, but I really like that song... urlLink  The Sad Robot   I wonder if that link thinger will work...meh...if it doesn't then go here:  urlLink http://www.lardpony.co.uk/music.html   Okay...anyways...lately I have felt like doing something creative but I'm not into working on  urlLink my book  so I considered making a comic but I' not all that good at drawing...but I started one anyways (What Happened Last Night, Starring: Sketchy Guy) but it isn't all that great...meh...  So I need something to do...Maybe I will start an e-zine...again...for liek the 80th time...speaking of zines I still haven't published  Superheroes Chased Butterflies Too...  which I really should do cuz its awesome!!!  Okay...so I guess I'll go make an e-zine...or something...argh! I hate weekends!!!  Chera
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What does your keyboard smell like???  Mine smells like Jeffrey....Jeffrey and a dry leaf.  Thank you. That is all.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The best thing I have seen in weeks:    urlLink        And this one represents my love of pirates (ie. me [God {The PIrate}]):      I love comics...
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I had two dreams...is that weird...I usually only have one...  So the first one had to do with my dad and stepmom...who I don't live with anymore because they are collectively satan.  Anyways I was at their house (which wasn't really their house but it was a dream so I will excuse that) and I don't really remember much...but it was weird...cuz I hate them...  The second one was really long and strange...I was at this farm like place and there were a bunch of people my age and it was like we were being tested or trained for something.  It was kinda scary...they had us doing all these things...like there was this horizontal pole really high up and we had to put something in the middle of it...and then there were shovels...and I got yelled at a lot...I just remember bits and peices but it was weird...  Okay...I was thinking about this while I was waiting for the computer to boot-up and I really want to fall asleep in someone's arms while watching The Labyrinth and drinking vodka and vanilla coke...the thought came out of no where...  I hate my computer...my msn isn't working again, meaning I have to re-boot, which psses me off...maybe I'll go make a disgustingly sugar-y treat...ice cream, marshmallows, chocolate, cinnamon...mmmmmm...okay anyways, I think thats all I have to say right now...  I love old music...thank god for growing up with hippies (granola...haha Dave...)  Still haven't found Eleanor Rigby...maybe cuz I got fed up and stopped looking...if anyone finds it could they please link me to it...thanks!!  XOXO  P.S. I just realized that the time on my updates is way off...but now that you know its wrong all is well...so I won't bother changing it every time i post...  Chera
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                               Yeah, thats right...I'm awesome!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've always hated short stories...they bug me...I don't feel as though I have enough time to develop what needs to be developed.  But I suddenly had the urge to write one like 5 minutes ago...so I started this one about this evil guy...it sucks...but he is evil...so thats awesome!! There aren't enough evil protagonists in the world (and yes i realize thats a little oxy-moronal, but I don't care cause to me oxy-morons make the most sense...paradoxes are awesome and you know it!!!)  So yeah, Kalam (my character. name derives from the word calamity) he is evil...he kills people and loves it...its potentially great...but I want ice cream and sleep so I'm going to go now...  Chera
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...or, atleast I would if I wasn't God (The Pirate)  I have been very sick...for no apparent reason. Arggghhhh...blah....  No one is on msn and that makes me gloomy. I want people to talk to so my mind won't be on how ill I am right now. *waits for people to come online* Maybe I will draw some pictures on paint...make some icons for all of my various online journals...too many journals...its a wee bit hectic.  I spent a rather long time trying to find a free mp3 of Eleanor Rigby by The Beatles last night...I ended up downloading an mp3 of some guy telling me its not nice to take music without asking, and a thrash cover of Eleanor Rigby...which was alright, but not any where near as good as the original.  Yeah...so I guess I'll go do something produvtive with my time now...productive-ish...  Chera
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dave looking like Adam Brody:     Dave wants you!:     Dave with a hat:      Dave is pretty...
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate weekends. And side walks, but that is beside the point. I never do anything on weekends...I used to...*sigh*  I want James to come online so I can love him. He makes me ridiculously happy. Which, inturn, makes me ridiculously sad when he leaves. I can't wait till after exams when I go camping with him...he is so god damn sexxy. James is THE SEX! hehe...he promised me nakedness when I come and visit...which is awesome!!  I don't love Dave anymore...maybe its cause he has been away so long (suspended for streaking) but I am losing interest in him...I heart James so much!  Rugby is awesome...although today I over-exurted myself and was sick :( I slept through math class...my teacher gave me permission "If you are sleeping you won't be talking" So I am going to sleep in math class for the rest of the year :)  At lunch I was sleeping on a picnic table at the Fry Hut and Eric slapped my ass really hard and it hurt.   Okay...I think I am done...for now...  Chera
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate you. I hate you with an undieing passion that cannot be refuted. You can do nothing to bring me back...if that is even your goal. Perhaps you just want to ruin my life no matter what it takes. I wish you were dead. You drove me to trying to kill myself, you and Eileen (She shall never be forgiven either) did, but really YOU are those who should parish, not I. I have friends, people who care. Do you? Do you go out and have fun? Or do you just spend your nights in front of the TV or the computer just watching me? Recording everything I do. Well stop. You are  NOT  my father any more. Stay away from me, in both the real world and this cyber world we call the internet. I want nothing to do with you.  Ever . I hope you both die terrible, excrutiating deaths. And now, my little elaboration on the 'structured' lifestyle that presides in your hell hole you call home: We all know you smoke pot, and GROW pot. One time me and my friends smoked pot from your stash. And Spartan smoked it all the time. You look at pornography on a regular basis...and you accuse ME of looking at it?? What is that about. I don't even...like if I did I might understand why you would say that. But I don't. Now, may I ask how you met Eileen? Was it not over the internet? How could you be sure she wasn't some raving lunatic? Well...you shouldn't have taken that risk. She   IS   a raving lunatic. Okay, and onto your 'structuring' my life (when I was there): Yelling at me for the tiniest things I did wrong, every week, every day. You ruined my christmas, my new years eve, my life, with your 'little chats' trying to make me a 'better person'. And NEVER did you congradulate me on anything.  urlLink PRoN  is a perfect example of that. Sure, I wrote ONE paragraph on you guys...ONE. But the rest was well written. You HAVE to admit that. And guess what Jacques, I'm getting my book published soon. But I had to re-write the first 8 chapters. You know why? Cause I wrote those when I lived at your house. And since I moved out my writing capabilities have improved ten fold. And don't expect a free copy. You won't get one...the only thing I would ever even consider sending you is an envelope of Anthrax. Is that still on the news lately? I ask you cause I know how the only highlights of your life are the things you see on TV. Like kids being abused. Speaking of which, lets re-visit some of my child-hood memories. Like that time in Quebec at that motel when I was crying cause I couldn't sleep and I was home sick. Do you remember what you did? You hit me. Hard. Which definitly didn't stop my crying...sure I tried to be a little more quiet as not to get hit again, but I cried. The whole night. And do you remember that time you wouldn't let me say good night to mom who was down stairs. Every time I tried to exit my room you would jump out and grab me by the wrist or whatever else you could grab onto and threw me back in my room. It scared me, so much that I tried to run to mom. I screamed for her. I armed myself to try and get to her, but you took the big cardbored roll from my hand and hit me with it. Do you remember that Jacques? Do you? Cause I sure do. I've never been able to forget it. Did you know that when you and mom split I went to councelling? I think you found out about that after the fact when I gave you that letter and you ask if mom got one too and I asked why she would. I have NO issues with mom. None. Just you. Cause YOU ARE AN ASSHOLE. Oh, so back to councelling. I drew pictures of my family. In everyone of them you were coloured red. Red for Rage. And hate. The hate you had for everything. And I had red too. But only in the pictures where I was near you. I have always hated you Jacques. Always. And that will never change. And I will never come back. I think a word about how much I love it here is appropriate: Here I can talk freely. Here people listen to me, enjoy hearing my opinion. Don't critisize EVERYTHING I do. Here people love me. Cherish me. You never did any of that. Here I do things by my own free will. I bake for everyone, I make lunch, dinner. I peeled some potatoes for Mike and my brunch one day. He was out working and I decided to make some hashbrowns and hotdogs. He was thankful. Didn't make some comment like 'its about time' or 'do i know you?' Mike is more of a father than you have EVER been to me. So Jacques, stay away from me, and stop reading the things I write.  I hate you, Elisha  P.S. Stephanie did not get drunk. She had some pizza the night before that had made her very sick. Stephanie hadn't drank anything. DO NOT drag my friends into the issues you have with the family that hates you. I'm NOT your family anymore. And my friends are even less of your business than I am.  Have an awful life.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wwwo.bunnyherolabs.com   urlLink     hmmm...I hope that'll work...  XOXO
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so my weekend was awesome (I'M AWESOME!! haha...goos times me and Justin Timberlake...haha yay for Saturday Night Live) I went to a dance and a wee party, like all the time with Jeffrey and Steph who I think have fallen madly in love with each other (mild exaggeration.)  So really there is way to much drunken details to explain and I  REALLY  want to get back to my book ( The Da Vinci Code ) so I'll skip those details.    I stayed home yesterday cause I was in serious need of sleep, and I went home right after first period today cause I'm sick...blaaahhh...but the up side is that I am like three quarters of the way done the book (that I started yesterday afternoon) and will DEFINITLY be finished by tomorrow sometime...I AM LOVING THIS BOOK!!! It is fantastic. Nothing can discribe how eather-real this is...and I'm not even sure how to properly use the word eather-real or how to spell it...but I like this book so much it just HAD to be said!!!  David is a cool kid. He thinks I'm hot and awesome...which is good...more people should think that. He said I rock teenage hormones...isn't that sweet?? hehe...he is a gnarly kid.  Anyways...do I have anything else to say?? Well the book I'm reading has jump started my work on the sequel to my book...so I intend to mosey on along in writing it as soon as I'm finished reading  The Da Vinci Code .   Umm... My new philosophy (as read in a pull out of a Teen Titans comic book) is   If you intend to die, you can do anything   I love that...it is so utterly true...and I live by it...in my own twisted way...woot! woot!  XOXO  P.S. my blog is now on Blogwise:   urlLink     
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jeffrey has titties all over his body.  I thought that would be good to start off with!!  I have to take Jeffrey to the train station now...but i will add more to this when I get back...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So yesterday I wasn't sure if Jon (awesome guy) was coming onto me or if I was just imagining it...but today he made it VERY clear...everything we talked about ended in him making some relatively sly comment about me and him having sex. For example: yesterday was 'I'm single now' and staring at me, today when i was talking about the walking std he told me he was std free, today when i mentioned that Jeffrey was coming to the party he started asking all these questions about him then said that 'this Jeffrey kid' is at the bottom of the list (or something like that) meaning that he gets me (IN BED!) first...which is saucy as hell...yeah, but James is saying all this stuff about how he is a huge flirt and that i'm (only) 14 so it won't happen...but all I wanna do is mess around with him...thats all...and I'm pretty damn sure thats what hes thinking too.  Okay...so Yipee for the weekend (TOMORROW IS TOO FAR AWAY!!!)  XOXO
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I had written this big long post yesterday and then the power went out. So its all gone. So here is the jiffy pop version with some updates included:  I wish I could turn off my emotions Jeffrey better be able to come up on friday I'm taking Jeffrey to a dance and to a party at (Marlee's) James' house I got Jeffrey's letter and it was awesome I spent like four hours making stuff for people and writing letters to people yesterday I hate my (ex)dad... I hate my (ex)stepmom... This kid David (from GJ) is pretty saucy 'I like to play'-Garth from Wayne's World...I'm sorry...I had to add that I'm trying not to love James...and I'm doing a pretty damn good job of not thinking about him...mainly because I haven't been talking to him a lot because I think he is avoiding me... Dave is a neat kid Jon (awesome guy) broke up with his girlfriend...and I think he was hinting for me to jump him at the party on saturday...which is weird because he is usually all 'nooooooo...no underage girls' of course he says it in a much more suave way I think I'm done here...  XOXO
     

    
</post>


</Blog>