<Blog>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       So I was going to wait a while for someone else to post up here but seeing as Andrew can't really figure out the internet at my house...its only been me who's been able to post this entire time. But let me tell you a bit about my Saturday evening.   I had been at my best friend's graduation party (yeah..she was josh's date at homecoming) and after we went back home I stiffed some money from my dad to go rent some musicals to watch. You see, I'm on a search. I want to find out what the musical is without anyone telling me. You see this is the smart way because not only am I finding out what next year's musical is by a wish and a hope, but I also get to teach myself about other musicals in the process. Its a win-win situation. So let's hope I'm doing this right.   Anyway I went to the Blockbuster where I've been renting family fun videos ever since the damn thing opened in the early '90s. So you'd think they have a good selection of videos...no. Sure they have some musicals but no Joesph and the Amazing Technicolor Dream Coat, no The Wiz, nothing much really. The only thing they have worth mentioning was West Side Story and Grease and those movies have been played to death on VH1 I was sure if I went home I had a good chance one of them would be on that night.   So I left that store because quite frankly that Blockbuster sucks ass. So then it was to Hollywood Video where I spent at least twenty minutes trying to find some damn movies. They were out of the Music Man remake (2003) that has Matthew Broderick and Kristin Chenoweth as the object of MB's affections. That sucked but then I continued to run around and I found *gasp* Little Shop of Horrors! Of course i knew the movie sucked and I shouldn't be spending $3.99 of my father's hard earned money to rent it, but I couldn't resist, I had to do it. So I pulled the DVD off the shelves and continued on my search. And wonder of wonders, what should I find at the very end of the row, at the very bottom of the shelf but The Wiz! I screamed in delight and got a kind of weirded out look from the resident Hispanic Family in the store. I didn't care, I happily skipped to the line where I was ready to spend $8.00 in happy musical movie bliss.   That was until I saw that there was only 1 cash regsiter open and the guy was stopping every other minute to yell at one of his coworkers or to look and see what the other was doing. Wonderful.   Finally I got to the front and the guy asked me for my card. "I don't have it." "What's your phone number?" "No. I mean I don't have a card. I don't rent from here usually."  So the moron had to pull me aside from the line and make me fill out these waivers and what not for a card. So a 17 year old girl can't walk into a random video store and rent some movies without having a damn membership? She has to get a stupid ass card and take her movie viewing pleasure away for 20 minutes as she fills out her address and whatnot.   Of course I had to wait while everyone else got served (that was a popular movie rental of the night. I was there long enough to take note of that) before the kid would help me out again. My patience was running thin. The guy had taken another 10 minutes to enter my information and get me my card. Can't I just take the damn movies and he could do that later?  But finally, another five minutes later he was meeting me at the exit with my two movies of choice and a bag of overly buttered popcorn for my already clogged up arteries. "Enjoy your movies," he said to me.  "Yeah sure."   So I get home and immediately pop in Little Shop and couldn't help but laugh at how corny it was. Rick Morannis of course, was Seymour Krelborn and he was laughable. Granted this movie was made 18 years ago so Rick didn't look 18 years older than he is, he was a cute nerd. Ellen Greene (who was Audrey in the original cast) was in it too and she was pretty annoying. It would have been great to have a taped version of the revival and the original and compare Ellen's performance to Kerry Butler's (she's Audrey right now in New York, but is leaving soon). And the whole damn ending was different! I was ready to hear 'Somewhere That's Green (Reprise)' and see some carnage but IT DIDN'T HAPPEN! I was so ticked but then I guess Frank Oz (Yoda!) the director had a screening audience and they were so upset at the original ending tht he had to change it. I would have said 'Screw the audience, just kill 'em all!' but no...he changed it and I was pissed.   So against my mother's wishes I put in the Wiz and I still have to complete it seeing as its 2 hours and 13 minutes in length. Costumes are awesome and many changes involved...awesome music...awesome cast....awesome, awesome, awesome. Of course that was only the first hour of the show so I have yet to finish it. I'll let you all know how it turns out.   See you all tomorrow  Amanda 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Okay so I figured I'd update tonight just to tell you of a musical adventure I just had tonight with our very own Andrew Bautista. You see...we didn't want to be losers tonight and not go out, so we opted for a night at home watching a video I took from Mrs. B (the choir director) and we ran around town picking up my brother and chowing down at Sonic. Then it was back at my place to watch a concert featuring Andrew Lloyd Webber songs and it was live...from Bejing! We had Chinese people and it was awesome! It opened up with some extremely hot and extremely awesome! He opened with Jesus Christ Superstar and Andrew and I were blown away.   But the party didn't start until Andrew, my mother and I sat down to watch Jesus Chirst Superstar which was crazy awesome. I think Andrew and I melted in our seats because nothing can top the rock and roll screeching of Jesus and Judas...we even felt sorry for the poor bastard and couldn't believe what he did to himself near the end...it was a freaking 'G' rated movie! But really, no matter what your religion, this movie should be witnessed by all. It has amazing music (Andrew Lloyd Webber and Tim Rice? One of the best Broadway duos since Rodgers and Hammerstein!) and a wonderful message. Its the Passion of the Chirst set to music and they're all hippies! We saw some pipes and reefers in there that made do a 'jigga wha'?'   I'm also talking to my parents about letting me have a Tonys party or something on June 6. I'm still working on it though, I think it'd be great to hang out before the summer really kicks in ya know...start off the summer on a sweet, sweet note. So let me know about coming to this wonderful fiesta...of course that is, until I clear it with the parental units!   Have a good weekend everybody!  Amanda   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        So Andrew and I were bored tonight and decided to mess around on blogger.com. Of course this was after we watched a kick ass guy sing Jesus Chirst Superstar at the top of his lungs but that's beside the point. We decided to make a blog cataloging our short lived experiences of Musical Theatre Troupe. But of course, MTT will live on in our hearts and of the handful of people who watched us kick ass on Friday May 14, 2004 on our debut performance "Love Changes Everything."   So this blog will be used by all the members of the Musical Theatre Troupe of 2003-2004 and all other MTT performers to come. But first, Andrew and I would like to list the members of the 2003-2004 Musical Theatre Troupe.   Justin Wagner Chris Carnesi Andrew Bautista DJ Grahmn Jake Dennison Justin Walgren Lauren Hord Amanda Carungi Mikaela Shaeffer Robyn Keith Melissa Davis      Andrew here.    Now, I know you're all wondering, "What the hell am I gonna do with a blog?"  Well, because we're so gosh darn nostalgic, we thought this would be an excellent way for us to keep in touch, because calling is each is quite a hassle, and I'm willing to bet that there'll never be a time when we'll all be online at the same time...so this seemed like the best way.  It may seem daunting at first, but give it a try.  It's easy once you get started.  And did I mention that it's a ton o' fun?    I know that DJ is planning this huge pool party thing sometime during the summer, so if he's willing to post the details, this would be a much more convenient alternative to invitations, because we all know that we're invited, right?    So yeah, if you're reading this, you should have received an email invitation, allowing you to post on this with your own name and whatever password you choose.  And make sure you post in a different color! Let's be individuals! :)     Yeah.  And if you don't, I'll fucking kill you.  [End] 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>