<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well here i am again....bored to hell but ya know...i get by....it is the day before Gregg's party......cant wait...tomorrow is the competition between me and Quinton....YOU ARE GOIN DOWN QUINTON!!!...anyways...the competition goes like this....Quinton has an extreme liking towards peaches....at sight of them she turn into the friggin hulk...and im known for going insane on 2 cokes......but im gonna be on 3 SOBE No FEAR's.....which contain mass amounts of caffeine....lol....my heart is sure to explode....which worries me in a sense.....but im a bettin man....ill prolly jus puke it all up anyways.....ya know how it goes....well ima get goin...screw you guys...cyaz!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey people....its Britt! First post ya know. So yeah! Today is a pretty boring day. Nobody is really home or online prolly cuz its like 9 a.m......that may be the reason. My girlfriend Katie went out on the boat with 2 of her friends, her parents, her moms sister,and her brother......so she left me all alone....i could have went but i have to work today so thats a bummer....but its ok....she owes me anyway dont ya baby....?....¿....yeah ya do....its also good cuz i have the coolest job in the world....i work at the local theatre....basically i work my tail off for 20 to 30 minutes....and then the movie starts...and so i either watch the movie....or chill and eat free popcorn and candy....lol.....and its a good thing to.....hours are pretty decent and so is pay i guess.....man im hungry....im gonna go freak on some pop tarts so ill cyaz laterz.......*stuffs face with brown sugar pop tart*
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to tell you.....my best friend Aaron performed at a local garage which we like to call the Quail Creek Lounge.....he performed Little Wing by Jimi Hendrix......he surprised us all with a lil wah wah solo in the last verse......it actually made my heart skip a beat and I almost wanted to cry because it was so beautiful. It was the most amazing thing I have ever heard. I almost cried but I didnt wanna look like a pansy so I held in the tears. Yes......I guess by admitting this I do sound like a pansy....but hey who cares right? Well anyways.....I am outta here cuz Im bored....so cyaz!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Only 2 more days till my vacation to Myrtle Beach! WHOO HOO! Cant wait. Its gonna be soo much fun. I get to take Aaron with me which is a cool thing. Although I am going to miss all of my other friends (Mariam, Jon, Jesse, Lauren, Gregg, etc.) Aaron will be with me so it will all be good.Its a good 12 hour drive to Myrtle Beach so it will be slightly boring. So we hooked up the N64 in the van and there is tv and happiness for all. Lovely aint it? Yeah it is. Goin to the House of Blues! That will be sooo much fun! YAY! Im gonna miss you people though! :( But hey itll be alright...right? It better be..Ok...bored. Im gonna go now. Bye!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's see. Monday morning at around 3 AM my family and my best friend, Aaron (lead guitarist in my band Los Barqueros) are leaving to go to Myrtle Beach. Its a sure 12 hour drive from where I live to Myrtle Beach. But its ok. We have a tv in the van we are riding in. Me and Aaron, my grandfather and his wife are riding in the van. There is a tv, we can hook up an N64, and there is enough room to jam with both of our acoustics. We are gettin some songs ready to play on the streets of Myrtle Beach. Hopefully we will make some money playin. Enough money for me to spend on stuff down there. Im currently poor. So this might be a good thing. Anyways...we have a bunch of romantic songs lined up to play. That will be fun. We never have ev er really played any slow songs. So this could be a new experience for us. Hopefully it will. Well Ima get goin. You people have a good day! Cyaz!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes....JELLO DANCE!!! DANCE OF THE JELLO!!!! J-E-L-L-O.....It's alive! Ok enough of that for now. Good things are-a comin my way. We get to play at another club again. All is well in the land of the Kiebler Elves. We have 6 songs lined up to play. This is a show without drums which is so not our style but its still really fun as it is. The songs go as follows: 1)Red House -Jimi Hendrix 2)Layla (Unplugged) -Eric Clapton 3)Castles Made of Sand/Little Wing Medley 4)Pride and Joy -Stevie Ray Vaughan 5)Empty Arms -Stevie Ray Vaughan  6)Villanova Junction -Jimi Hendrix  Those are the songs. Which is gonna make it sooo cool. Those are some of the best songs to play at an all acoustic show. I cant wait for it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Recently, my computer decided to die. That isnt a good thing so I had to show it just who was the boss. Apparently, I am the boss. I spent all of yesterday workin on this thing. I formatted the computer and instead of reinstalling Windows ME... I wanted Window 98 Plus. But that didnt work. We were baffled how we couldnt fix it. We thought we were going to have to go get it fixed and it would have cost us extra money that we dont have. So....desperate times call for desperate measures. So I woke up this morning and used the system recovery disc. It worked and I reinstalled AOL and Yahoo. I must be some kind of genius. Well Im done. BTW...HI MARIO! Heh heh. Well Im outta here. Cyaz!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! Yesterday it seems I have fixed everything. Lauren and Gregg were having there little problems and as usual I have to step in and save the day. lol. Also last night, I talked to Mario on the phone for almost 2 hours which is quite a while in my book. She relayed some info to me that she could talk to me forever. Im guessin that is a good thing right? Sure it is. We talked about serious stuff, funny stuff, not so funny stuff. She is someone who is awesome to talk to. She keeps things interesting. She said something about not liking clowns. But I found one word that she does like.....poop! Simple pleasures for simple minds I guess. Heh heh. Its ok Mario! I have a simple mind too you arent alone. These things happen. Talked to Gregg last night. He seemed to have had a good time in N. Carolina. He went to a five day gymnastics camp. He said he could barely walk. That leaves me the perfect opportunity to kill him if he messes up. Which isnt likely to happen. I should go kill him now while he least expects it. MWAHAHAHAHAHA! ok Im done. Well folks.....Im outta here so have an incredible day! Buh bye!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today I return to work because I was off for 2 weeks. I return today to the sounds of screaming kids, popcorn popping, and my boss's yelling....lol! Yesterday I met Mario at the HFFC. She seems really cool.....smart yet odd, likes aardvarks, and is extremely pretty. Her, Lauren, and I spent the day together. Later that night, I went to a show to hear my friend, Aaron (lead guitarist in my band, Los Barqueros), play. He played an excellent show. He gave all of us a surprise wah wah solo in Little Wing by Jimi Hendrix. It really touched my soul. I almost cried but I didn't want to look like a sissy. LOL! Well Im bored so I am gonna get goin. You people have a nice day! Cyaz!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey again. Just got back from my father's house today. I Love my father. Anyways....new developments in my realm! I have become acquainted with this person. Her name is Mariam. She seems pretty cool. I have heard some stuff about her and I was recently introduced to her. We talked on the phone a couple of times. She called not too long go and we talke for a solid hour and maybe some more. We share the same interests predominantly. Her favorite band is the All American Rejects where my favorite band is The Jimi Hendrix Experience/Band of Gypsies. But hey these things happen ya know? She's weird though. So a I so I guess we fit right in. I think she is pretty cool. I am supposed to go meet her sometime. Either at H'ville Family Fun Center or Nashville Shores. But I am hopin she will come with me to the show I might be playing atwith some members of my band(Los Barqueros=The Boatmen). Although I haven't asked her yet. I will next time we talk. Hoefully she will say yes and com along and have a good time. Ya see my date for that night decided not to talk to me for...well going on 9 days now. So screw her. Even if I dont go with anyone I will still have a good time. Good times....good music...good stuff. Heh heh. Gregg is gone again to gym camp. 5 days. Gregg recently went to Vegas for a week. He is a very busy person it seems. I'm not. I dont have t work until Sunday which is just fine by me. Gas money! WHOO HOO!!! Thats a rarity. It happens. Well dinner is just about ready. And I choose food over all of you guys. So cyaz! (God Bless Jimi Hendrix!)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! Today is Monday or something.....my parents are makin me go to church every friggin day this week....and I dont like my church at all.....i cant stand the people, what they stand for, and not that I am religous or anything but I can tell that God doesnt want me there....of course my mom is too pissy about things.....so if I tell her that...then she will have a fit.....a big one...ill get grounded to hell and i'll still have to go anyways....therefore i lose....not even if i tell her that God doesnt want me there.....she'll say something like..."You dont know that...you are too young to know what God is telling you"....something to that order.....so ya know how it goes....damn this world.....well i just had to vent or whatever they call it....so ill cyaz guyz later! Adios!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well funny things have happened. It seems that Mario and Lauren seek to take guitar lessons from me. I have accepted. Although I am not too experienced at this, I will give it a shot. Hopefully, I can help these girls. What will make this so interesting is the fact that I have not yet learned all the ways of the guitar. This will be interesting and fun because not only will they be learning but I will be learning with them as well. Which will be a good thing for me. I look forward to attempting this wonderful endeavor. It shall be fun. Indeed, it will........
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sadness indeed...I have not talked to Mario in days. I miss her a lot. We should talk tonight though. I cant wait at all. Havent been writing. Been workin a lot which is why I havent talked to Mario. Sorry Mario! And I am about to go to work again for another 6 hours...i put in 6 hours yesterday and 11 before that. I know not much. But hey it gets me gas and spending money. Well Ima get goin. Bye people!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Night falls. And I'm alone.  Skin, yeah, chilled to the bone.  You turned and you ran.   Slipped from my hand.  "Blue on Black.  Tears on a river.  Push on a shove.  It don't mean much.  Joker on Jack.  Match on a fire.  Cold on ice. A dead man's touch.  Whisper on a scream. Yeah doesn't change a thing.  Don't bring you back.  Blue on Black.  "Blind. Now I see.  Truth, lies, and in between.  Wrong can't be undone.  Slipped from the tip pf my toungue.  "Blue on Black.  Tears on a river.  Push on a shove.  It don't mean much.  Joker on Jack.  Match on a fire.  Cold on ice. A dead man's touch.  Whisper on a scream. Yeah doesn't change a thing.  Don't bring you back.  Blue on Black."       "Blue on Black" by Kenny Wayne Shepherd is one of my favorite songs right now. I love the lyrics and the solo. But you can't hear the solo. Too bad. Go by the CD. Or listen to it online. The CD is call "Trouble Is"....go buy it. Every song is good. Well....I am outta here. Have fun. Cyaz!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well like always....there has to be conflict in my life. But its ok I guess. Im a tough man. No Im not. Im a big fat loser. Thats what I am. But hey...I get by in life I guess. And if I dont. Well...Im a gamblin man. Im willing to take a risk. Although it seems I have been taking risks this entire time and I have got shot down every time. Probably because I am so gosh darn unlucky. But hey it happens right? Sure it does. It always does. In case in you havent figured out by now...by life has taken a dramatic turn for the worst. But Im not one to sit down and take all of this. I am standing up against this so I can make my life better. It is going to take a lot of work and concentration. But...I am willing to work for what I want. Nothing comes free and easy to me anymore. I guess that is because I am not a kid any more. Ya know when you are a kid, you got it soo easy. When you're scared you can run and hide behind mommy or daddy. Mommy and daddy are always there for you. Or at least they were always there for me. Some people arent as fortunate. But I was lucky. I had parents that cared for me and watched over me. Anyways...when you're a kid....life is easy. You get what you want. No car insurance payments, jobs, telephone bills, utilities. You dont worry about that. I am growing up and I finally realize that life is getting tougher. And ya just gotta roll with the punches. Well lately I havent been rolling with the punches. I have been letting the punches hit right in my face. And let me tell you....it hurts. But the thing is ya gotta keep living. And the people who say otherwise are the ones who throw their lives away and go suicidal. But I choose to keep living. Ya take the good with the bad. Everybody gets the blues ya know. And without the bad times....it wouldnt make the good times so good ya know. For me at least, when bad things come around, good things come around eventually. Sometimes in small amounts and sometimes in great blessings. I have received blessings this past month. I cant deny that. But I have also gotten screwed over. I didnt screw myself over. My stupidity didnt do this to me. It was simply fate. Fate has a way of kicking me where it hurts. And when fate teams up with bad luck....thats pretty much an unbeatable combo. No denying that. But I do know one thing out of all of these bad things that have happened to me in the past days. I do know that 2 things help me deal with all of this and keep my on the ground. 2 things so special that they make me happy no matter what I am feeling inside. The first thing is music. Music is a lot of my life. My passion. It never fails to help me and is always there for me. The 2nd is a person. A real good friend of mine. The smallest thing this person does sets my heart at ease. And I am not going to tell you who it is. Because I am sure this person doesnt want publicity. And I just like to leave ya guessin. LOL! Well I guess I have been rambling for quite a while now. Sorry....I just had to get some of this stuff off of my chest cuz it was cloggin my brain and I couldnt think straight. Thats what this thing is good for I guess. And I am going to leave with one of my favorite quotes. Here it goes: "Love is always patient and kind.   It is never jealous.  Love is never boastful nor conceited.  It is never rude or selfish.  It doesn't take offense.  It is not resentful.  Love takes no pleasure in other people's sins  But, delights in the truth.  It is always ready to excuse,  to trust, to hope,  and to endure whatever comes."    Well thanks for listening to me. I had fun rambling. Have a good day. Cyaz!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Guess what....today is Mario's Birthday! This is the day she was born on 16 years ago! The day of her birth! When her mother gave birth to her...it was on this day! HAPPY BIRTHDAY MARIO!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently got back from Myrtle Beach. It was so amazingly beautiful. The first day there we went straight for the beach. As usual I got burnt pretty bad. No...I put sunscreen on but the sun ABSOLUTELY LOVES to find ways to annoy hell out of me. Anyways, the seconf day there we went to the malls and whatnot. That was kinna fun. Took me forever to find something to buy for Mario. But it seems I have found the perfect thing.Heh heh heh! The 3rd day we went shopping some more and then went to the Aquariam they had. The next day was our last day and so we awoke and hit breakfast buffets. YUMMY! I got home and was extremely relieved. I was away from the people I loved more than anybody on the face of this planet.....my friends. Oh yeah by the way....HAPPY INDEPENDENCE DAY! Well cyaz people!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well.....while away on my vacation to Myrtle Beach this past week I discovered some things after talking to someone before I left. I thought about it long and hard. I called this person from Myrtle Beach and asked her if it were possible that we could be more than just friends. Part of me wanted her to say that she wanted to be bf and gf. But the other part of me (the majority) was actually proud of what she said. She replied,"Yes I do but I dont want to be bf and gf yet. We have only met once ya know." Im really glad she said that. I like this girl. Her name is Mario by the way hence the title of this post. This girl can make me feel a lot of different feelings all at once. That is kinna creppy in my book cuz that usually doesnt happen. But the best part is her free spirit. I love free spirits. I love how they are so out of this world. That makes things interesting. And it keeps me interested. Which is a good thing. Well I just thought I would throw that out there being as I havent written in my blog in a long while. Well cyaz!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>