<Blog>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Had to work today. That was exciting.  I'm getting so bored with my job...this always happens to me.  Took me longer with this one.  Will be 2 years in Sept. and I'm just tired of going there every day and getting run over with the bus.  My forehead does not say COTA Stop.  UGH  Had alot of fun actually today..>I got to see a bunch of people that I rarely get to see.  I don't usually work weekends.    Went to lunch with a friend that used to work with me that I don't get to see much now.  It was a good time.  I miss her dry wit that is so much like mine.  We are such different people, that I almost wonder why we get along so well, but we do.  Last we talked on the phone, she said she had something to tell me that she couldn't tell me on the phone, but she didn't mention it so I didn't either.  She'll get around to it I guess.    Thats about it.  Nothing much else happened.  Ho Hum 

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm not going to do one of those this is who I am, stuff I like, blah blah blah kind of first posts.  Those annoy me.  You'll figure it out if you stick around. I will say that I am female and just turned 25.  Spent today at my Grannies house.  She has a small pool in her backyard and we were helping her get it ready to swim in.  Good times, but I'm wicked sunburnt now.  I should know better.  The boys had a ball in the sandbox.  Its been raining tons here, so the sand was soaked.  Their underwear were brown through their pants which were just unspeakably dirty.  Boys will be boys, though, huh.  Bryan got a letter today saying that they are doing away with the inactive portion of the reserves.  So he will either get called back in and deployed or put in a unit.  The latter is preferable as he ETS's in September.  Glad I went back in when I did, so I don't have to be forced to.  Something just different about being able to make that choice.  I will be lost if he has to go though.  The year and half he was in Korea was bad enough with a toddler and pregnant then with an infant.  I totally empathise with all single mothers everywhere.  You are the strongest people.    I tried to call Linds today...She and I never seem to be on the same page as far as contact.  The trials of having a best friend that lives 500 miles away.  Wherever you are, Pookie, I miss ya and love ya.    Trying to decide what sounds good for dinner but our fridge died yesterday, so not much left. Thank god for the deep freeze or we would have lost alot of meat. I hate going to the market, but looks like I'll have to. ARGH  Off to bathe my babies.  I'm sure snorkels and masks will be involved.   Its a new thing. @@   

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   She didn't call.  She told me the other day she would call and she didn't.  I even emailed her to say hi and she didn't reply to that either...I'm so angry  Good news tho...I got my college assistance paperwork approved so I'm starting school soon.  Should be great...cept my classes are principle of management and foundations of marketing...eww  I keep thinking that my problems will get easier with time.  Time only seems to help them get worse.  Time means time to think.  And a very wise woman just told me a few minutes ago that time to think is bad.  Its true enough.  I ponder often just exactly where I "belong".  But then i decide that I'm not going to label myself after 3 encounters with one person.  But then I wonder if I'm cheating myself of my true identity and so it goes.  I think its just curiosity really.  But does that mean that your curiosity should be satisfied when the desired end is reached?  Cus if so, then it goes beyond that.  I'm still curious.  I see women that I find beautiful and I admire them.  Do I know that, if faced with someone other than P, I would be able to let my guard down enough to be with them, no.  Do I want to, so I can know that this is real or not, yes.  Do I have the brass ones to actually do it? NO.  I just don't know what to do.   

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ive been sitting here trying to figure out what to write and a very wise woman said to write what I feel...That is so hard for me...I'm my strongest critic and can't stand to see my words glaring out at me.  But I'll try.    I feel inadequate.  As a wife, for the feelings that I have for her. I love my husband with all my heart.  I want her just as much as I did 2 years ago when this all began, but that doesn't diminish in any way how I feel for Bryan.  That probably makes no sense at all to anyone but me.  As a friend because I think that if I had been strong enough to say that it wasn't for the best, I wouldn't be dealing with not being able to connect with her. As a mother, for my lack of patience.  As an employee cus everyone makes me feel that way.  As a daughter cus I get so disgusted with my mother on a daily basis for who she is.  And because they tell me that alcoholism is a disease and they can't help it and sometimes I don't believe that.  As a stand strong and tall woman because people feel the need to start rumors that they can't validate and I am too much of a puss to confront them and face what they are saying.    well I kinda feel better Okay not...because I know jen is gonna read this and think I'm nuts...but she thinks that anyway I think...shhh-we won't tell her its true, let her find out on her own.  LOL   

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Got an email from "Pumpkin" finally...Very short, about "Mojomomo".  Like I care about what hes doing. @@  Things seem so different now.  We used to talk every day almost.  Hours upon hours late into the night and on into the morning.  Everything was game for conversation.  Until we conversed about the things we had both been considering in our own heads late at night after ending the call.  Round and round we went until last fall when we visited her.  Finally we were alone...drink flowing like a rushing river.  One thing to the next and we were there.  Alone. Together.  Ahhh.  then again a couple days later.  Things were fine after.  No worries.   She came here.  A week, I fought my interest.  Once again in the bottle, and dancing.  I don't dance but she made me.  I suppose I wanted to, huh.  Again, we were there.  Since, we don't talk much.  She claims life happened.  All of the sudden she is too busy for me.  We voicemail.  never seem to catch the other.  I'm afraid I guess that someday it will be over and she will be gone.  I don't even care if I never get to touch her again, I just don't want to never be able to talk to her again.  I would be lost.    I'm so confused... 

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Strangers in the same space Ive known you forever But do not understand you Crazy whims, fantasies you have That make no sense When spoken out loud We have the same hands Long fingers, pink nails The same education, profession, Mirror images of me, you, us But never so different  As we are now The secure one  ~~~~The unsure one  The happy one  ~~~~The one always wanting more  How can we reside within Each other seemingly well Yet disagree with  The others every move Sometimes I hate you For the choices you make  ~~~~I think its funny  ~~~~The chances you don't take  I love him  ~~~~I like her  Will there ever be a meeting Of our like mind Will your freedom Shatter my joy in security  ~~~~Will your reality ~~~~Clip my wings  

						
</post>


</Blog>