<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't wait for this to come on VH1. I really dolove the 90s & the fashions & the shows like "My So Called Life". Also Nirvana & a lot of good bands were big in the 90s. Woo-hoo!
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love my mom. We went grocery shoppig & she bought chips, pizza, english muffins, gatorade, pepsi, & chocolate syrup. Yummy! (I' been craving english muffins for days. I don't know why. But they are really good with melted butter.)
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK my friend Loren is going to come over on Saturday if nothing goes wrong. She's a way preppier than me but I'm cool with that. She's also a drama student at my school whereas I'm a creative writer. We had Lang. Arts (adv.), World Hist. (adv.) & the gym class we had for a semester & the health for one quarter & the study skills for one quarter. I also have other friends. I have Ryann who i think I men - speak of the devil she just came online.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I get new chores as we moved in to a new house. yay (see title). My old chores were: clean bathroom, clean my room. Now they are clean bathroom, wash dishes, and keep my part of the room clean. yay. I get ten dollars a week. I don't think my brother should get any. He should get a job. He graduated high school for gosh sake. geez.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm writing this via e-mail just to test it out cause I'm sooooo bored. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so bored. Dammit. I wish I had AIM so I could chat with my friends but we don't have it. i wish we had AOL but we have High-speed comcast. Bullshit. It's slower than dial-up. sigh. I'm going crazy! In my old neighborhood I had at least one friend but I don't know ne1 here! Aaaaaaaaggggghhhhhh. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey yeah we had everything vinyl on mono And we looked the other way man we were so dumb...lol I love this song Mono by Courtney Love. I want the CD. But I have 2 save up then convince mom and then still get the clean version. Oi.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How did this happen? Yesterday I was healthy as could be. Now my muscles are all achey & I don't feel good. Neither does mom. Ugh... I'm 2 tired 2 type ne more.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm actually kind of curious to see what's lurking in it. Ok...got it...opening it... 1st item: CD player & headphones. It is red & has Letters to Cleo's "Go!" in it. 2nd item: mirror. fake gold. given to me by great-grandmother. 3rd item: bright red New York Colors lipstick. 4th item:another NYC lipstick in deep purple. 5th item: wallet with calculator. contents of that: three dollars, a library card, & a 600 minutes phone card. 6th item: small daybook 7th item: numerous notes from friends and one from my crush 8th item: ew. A wad of chewed gum in a wrapper. throwing that out... 9th item: small bottle of lotion stolen from Hampton inn 10th item: covergirl "shimmering onyx" eye shadow & jordache black eyeliner               to be continued...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sooooooooooooooooo bored! I wish I had something to write about but the sad truth is my life is one of the most boring ones I know.(weird phrasing but oh well)  Plus we don't have home phone so I can't call my friends. We rely on my brother Ardis's & my mom's cell (still working on getting my own. Mom is putting on a strong front though. Could take some work. Ugh) so I can't call my friends if mom is out & ardis is too. High point of the day: stuffed crust pizza for dinner. I also went to the gym (my gym is Curves the one for women in case you were so bored you were actually wondering) My mom works there & she's a member too. Anyway going to go now
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love Charmed the TV show. I'm watching & typing at the same time. I wish I had the name Piper. My real name is Katherine. Ugh. I also wish I had Piper's power that would be soooo freakin' cool. I could freeze stuff. Like if I was in an incredibly boring class I could freeze everything but the clock would keep on going so I could shave off some minutes off the class and get out sooner. Excellent
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok I'm soooooooo freakin bored.I wish my friend Ryann was over. She's a girl. Her name is Elizabeth Ryann but she doesn't like Liz, Beth, etc. so she is called Ryann. She's an aetheist & sorta punk. But she doesn't do what you expect. Like the second to last day of school she showed up in the preppiest of outfits. She had on a crisp white, pink -pin-striped shirt & a pink cardigan over that with the bottom of the shirt showing. The she had on very light colored jeans and pink flip-flops. It shocked everyone except me because she hinted that she was going to do something like that. Well she gave a hint to everyone but I seemed like the only one who remembered. Anyway I hope she can come over when my brother goes camping next weekend. (We live in a two-bedroom house but we have three people. My moms & me share a bedroom but when Ardis is gone me & Ryann can use his room & not annoy the living hell out of mom. Wow that was a lot of "&"s) I'm gonna go call her now.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm a writer but I also like to pretend that I'm a fashion designer. I have ummmmm... quirky taste. I really love my outfit today so i'm writing about it. I have on A long black vest & dark jeans. I also have on a black band tee. (the band is Neat-O, a local ska band.) Then I have on three necklaces. One is a black string with a silver peace charm, another is a silver chain with an antique key on it. The last is a silver cross that I got from one of those 50 cent machines. And last but not least I have a black sorta fedora hat. So cool. If I can get a pic it's going to be in my portfolio.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is my blog. If you are reading this you are probably bored. Well you have come to the right place! Not. The title was sarcastic. Well I live in Florida which means school was out on the 21st. We go back on August 7th. That's about all. If I think of anything else I'll add it later. Gazzie signing out
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Langston Hughes You give me the blues Cause my teacher made me Write a poem Like you Stupid Says Roman I agree This assignment blows Woe is me
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My friend Kai is comin' home from Mississippi where she was visitin her dad. I can't wait 4 her 2 come over. Fun fun fun.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      that place rox. I love hottopic.com   It's so cool. I don't think my Dad is going 2 get me nething from my wishlist on there though. It's 2 freaky or something. ooooooooooooo. freaky
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK so the nite b4 last it was thundering so me & ardis (bro) were playing trivial pursuit. Then the next day when we told mom she said she wanted 2 play so we went into a non-planned family game nite. Weird but cool.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      piper's spell just went bad. uh-oh.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't get excited. Not the city. Neway me mom & ardis moved down 2 FL when I was 6 & he still lives in NY. I'm goin up there on the 15th of July & comin back on the 5th of aug, 4 days after my b-day & 4 days b4 school starts. My bro ardis is comin 2. it's not like he has nething planned. Also my Nanny wants to throw me a b-day party while I'm up there. I just hope she doesn't go all crazy & get all pink stuff & a Barbie cake. I would like a chocolate carvel ice cream cake. Those r good with the little chocolate crunchies & we don't have ne carvels near me though they do sell the cakes in the grocery store. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of the guys who was supposed to put in the new linoleum 2day cracked 2 of his ribs. ow. So obviousley they're not doing it 2day.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i didn't sleep last night. The matinence guys r coming to do the linoleum 2day. oi. I had 2 get up very early cause mom thought they would b here at like 9. Well it's 9:19. sigh. I'm doing this just to kill time. I'm also watching Charmed on TNT. yay
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my mom is mad at the cat she says. It woke her up early & wouldn't stop. then she went to take a shower & when she came back the cat was asleep. Oi. evil. she shook him awake & fed him. Oh course i was asleep through all this.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We just moved as u might know but we can't find the printer cable. Mom thought it was in a box but Ardis says he saw it & it wasn't in a box. So now he's going through everything looking 4 it & it's really annoying.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      She actually went home yesterday but oh well
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm still surviving on sandwiches & pasta but now we have soda. Pepsi. It's the ultimate. Coke sucks. also popcorn. Mom bought us that. No idea y. probably cos loren's comin over.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok when my friends Ryann, Janaye, Natasha, & Katie come over next weekend I'll give you an excerpt of the book we are writing called "The Elements". We're nowhere near done w/ it so we're going 2 try 2 have meetings where we can write & type it up on my computer. as for now I can't wait for loren 2 come over. Im probably going 2 have 2 go grocery shopping first. We have basically nothing in the house. No soda or anything. i'm surviving on water, sandwiches, & pasta. ugh 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm bored as hell just sitting by the computer listening to Less than Jake's "Anthem" online. My mom had her first college class 2day. English. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went asleep at around 8:00 last night. That's unusual for me. I'm an insomniac. And I finally got up around 3:00(pm). I felt continually tired for some reason. Mom thought I was sick. She said I had a fever. Well now I feel great so whatever.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok I'm a little PO'd. Dad got tickets 4 me to come up but not bro. He says he wants 2 give me a week up there alone while Ardis finishes school applications or whatever or job applications. Well guess what dad. Ardis says he doesn't want 2 go 2 college & though he's filled out some job applications he won't get one until he returns. PLUS mom won't let me go up there until he gets tix 4 Ardie. sigh. *&%$#@^*$%#$#$%!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm basically writing this so I can look on my blog & c what day it is. I'm too lazy 2 go & look at the calender. I'm hungry.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>