<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry it's taken so long to get another post up, it's been so busy at work that I haven't had time to post....  We've reached the end of the first week, and Wow, What a Week!  Polls that show the conservatives at 35% in the Polls vs Libs at 40%, Nationally 30 for the Conservatives vs 38 for the Libs. That seems like an upset to me.   In LNC, things are flying along smoothly. We're getting great reactions from people at the door, and we are getting lots of "I was a life-long Liberal, but I don't like that Martin/Fontana guy". To me, that smells like a riding that will be shifting to Blue!  Personally, it's incredible to see the change as people are now relying on me as a bigger partner in the campaign team. I guess offering 50 hours a week to the campaign can do that :) I only wish I could bump it up to 100, but I guess it's a good idea to be paid, so I'll keep the job here for now :)  Today was a great canvassing blitz that was extremely positive & helped us to via for a dominant position in the riding. Joe Fontana's boys/girls are running scared & we are on a clear path with a strong strategy. Here's to it's continued success!  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not sure whether you got a chance to watch Paul Martin walking from 24 Sussex to the Govenor General's residence. If you missed it, good for you. If, like me, you had nothing better to do at 1pm than watch it, I feel great pity for you (and for me?).  The throngs of reporters around him as he walked up with his wife was ridiculous. Why not have one or two cameras, feed it into a pool, and give the man his last dignity. After all, he won't be making a walk like it ever again (a la Winds of Conservative Change).   The idea that this is such a huge media event is just silly. It doesn't even deserve to be labeled with the much hipper word 'ridiculous'. Let's call it what it is, silliness. Do any of the reporters there really expect Paul Martin to drop some type of bombshell announcement as he walks up to have the writ dropped? And if he did drop some tid-bit anyways, wouldn't a single feed for all the networks offer access to the same information?  Ok, so that got more attention, even in this post, then it deserved.  This morning I was out at 7 am putting signs on bridges in the city. There's something about putting up a sign in the pouring rain with lightening starting overhead to make getting involved in a campaign seem fun. If you doubt whether it can really be fun, give it a try (seriously good times)  Tomorrow should bring with it some light door-knocking (after all, it's a holiday & time to relax!)....
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As pretty much everyone knows, the writ gets dropped tomorrow.  In those immoral words from 9/11 "Let's Roll!"  (disclaimer: this is not to indicate that the Liberal hold on Canada is in any way related to the grip of terror that the 9/11 terrorists held over the U.S, but instead to applaud the call to action of those brave heroes ~ if you thought this, then really, what is wrong with you ?!?)  More large signs go up tomorrow morning at 7 am for a copy of hours. After a 17 hour day today, that's pretty brutal, but that's life on the campaign trail. Good thing tomorrow is a Sunday, and therefore should mean a bit of a respite.  As the last little bit for today, I just have to say that there are some real sharp people working on the Gatten campaign. It should be quite a ride...
     
    
</post>


</Blog>