<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since I am just beginning this blog I decided to give a little information about me, not that anyone has asked but it is my blog so I can do whatever the hell I want.  My name is Rachel, I am 22 years old. I have lived in Long Beach all 22 years on this planet. I attend C.S.U.L.B currently working on my B.A. in Creative Writing emphasis in poetry. My mom attended C.S.U.L.B, as well as my dad. My parents met while my mom was hitchhiking near school and my dad decided to give her a ride and this lead to 23 years of marriage, my dad passed away August of 2001, more thoughts will come on this.  So, I am an only child and was pretty sheltered most of my life, as my dad tried real hard to keep me inside his protective bubble but it was bound to pop eventually. Most people's first impression of me is stereotypical girl next door type but that is why first impressions are so misleading because that I can assure you, I am not. If I had to choose three words to describe my personality in a nutshell I would choose, Sensitive, imaginative, and Courteous.  Although, I believe I have changed a bit and allowed the flame which I contained inside of me out.  So here are some things that piss me off and spark this rage...  When someone refers to me as "woman" an ex. Of this in-case some are confused would be a guy saying, "Hey, woman get in here." Now I know I am of the female gender so I find it completely unnecessary to refer to me or address me in this way.  Yes, my breasts are real. No, you sure as hell can't touch them. No, I will not show them to you. Stop starring at them because that is not where my voice comes out, you simple minded ass!  No one in any state of the U.S. can drive!  Why can't I have my own road that takes me anywhere I want to go, where I can drive 100 mph, smoke a fucking cigarette and listen to pink floyd!!!????  Why, why, why, do people constantly tell me to relax? Just in-case you people haven't noticed, it didn't work the first time, in fact all it does is aggravate me more. So Stop! Let me be!  I also can not stand when people point out that I look sad, ex. "you look sad." "why are you so sad?"  Ok, have you fuckers looked outside into this fucked up world we live in?  That's why I am sad.  If you are a guy and you need a ladder to get into your truck, you should be shot.  If you are a girl driving a truck that you need to use a ladder to get in and out of, you should be shot as well.  EVOLVE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  These are just some of the many things that piss me off, I chose this topic instead of things I like because I think you can know a person better by the things that anger or hurt them, because these are usually the things that are most meaningful to human beings. Anyways, more to come at a later time. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    dreaming&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Seductive Red&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Whirlwind of Blue&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This guy makes me smile everyday! http://www.eonbeats.net/deadblog/index.html
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      At first this summer consisted of me enjoying myself... In a matter of one day, I am now taking two classes during summer session both four hours twice a week for $644.00 fucking dollars. I tell you something if my mom wasn't a damn teacher for 25 years I would say fuck it but she would kill herself and me with the constant bitching. I would rather listen to crows, HA.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My mouth has been stuffed and my stomach is full with emptiness. I am sick of never feeling good enough, it always leaves a sinking feeling in my heart. I try so hard, so much effort is given to just be acknowledged, to be heard. It returns each time, overcoming, negative creeping in, and I am reminded once again that I am nothing amongst giants, a little being standing alone, silently screaming, wanting nothing more but for you to love me.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I came to the realization that I don't feel older but each of these years seem to speed up and pass me by as my eyelashes raise from the blink of my eye. I am turning 23 in a few weeks and the anxiety of school is weighing on my mind. What the fuck did I do for the last 5 years??? I changed my major four times is what I did, talk about being indecisive as if my major even matters at all once I am done. Really I am in no real rush here, as I have come to accept the fact that I have diddley dick to do when I graduate. I am a writer, I will write, but my mom thinks I am going to trot off to graduate school, and that is not sounding like good times at this moment in time. I also have been drifting off thinking about my dad more lately... I seem to remember my 20th birthday vividly but 21,and 22 don't seem to stand out as much and these are the two he was not present for. I think I am just missing his open-mind and understanding of things because I seem to be feeling that loss the most.... *sighs* Ho hum that is all from me for now...
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I lay here crying for you, I feel your heart has hardened. I can no longer breathe you in and I am screaming for your pain to end. I wish you wouldn't cast me away, for you to find peace I would die. This life for me is worthless if your happiness does not exist.  I no longer see your light shining and I am searching for it to return to me. I fight for you, silent within me I battle demons unseen that only you and I can see. I will fight until it is all gone away unable to darken the fire which lies inside of you. My destiny is you and until we are together I will not breathe. I dream of our embrace it brings strength within me and I continue on. I want to take you in and wash away your pain  with warm rain which falls for you to finally breathe in as we finally fly far away from here, knowing only our love for one another goes on infinitely. May these words bring you strength when it seems nothing else is able.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I am not sure if the entire universe has gone ignorant but this pissed me off something fierce...This is on one of the poetry sites I frequent, First I will post the poem in which I posted, second the assholes reply to the poem, and third my response to the asshole's reply...   Farewell Beneath Stars -----------------------  Seeing you there upon your knees Is humorous to me We are beneath the nights sky  As the cold blows by Your eyes are red from tears In which you shed Fear of losing me seeps in Pain I also felt once deeply within I feel nothing now but the chill  Here in the darkness of night  My heart has been covered by  Your coldness, turned ice You plead and beg for me  To love you once again You ask this of me but I respond I am not one to forget  All the aching pain caused With this constant memory I am not able to forgive The hurt which lies inside of me You may remain there on your knees Hoping for me to return to you I have already disappeared from view Free to sail straight to the moon My final exit away from you      His comments...  So true, he held the match, he burned the bridge. Who are you to fly across the gap he left? And why would you? Once burned twice shy yada yada yada. So many men, so little time. No need for second chances, no. Dave   My response...  I found your comments to be quite rude, and you said nothing about the piece in which you were replying, "so many men so little time" please you have no idea, don't pretend to know me or what my intent of this poem was about. Stick to the writing.     This was truly just shocking to me, that someone would have enough nerve to say such a dick comment based on merely a poem.  I am finding that many people at this site in which this took place seem to care more about what the poem is saying as if it is actually my life right now. Buzzer off!  Even if this was taking place right now I don't need your opinion on what I should do ever! Although, no matter if I say this or not it seems people always dish it out.  All I know is I shut this asshole up real fast and if he comes near any of my writing again I will shut him up once more. HA
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I received the oddest e-mail this evening...    "My  Dear Rachel,  Surely you don't mean that the soaring magnificence of Shakesperean poetry was a result of a mere putting of pen to paper! What I am interested in, is that combination of skill and experience we call technique. Blank verse,meter, alliteration,... That, Madamoiselle, is what, at the moment, I am interested in. I thank you for your help viz. free verse! Now! To work! The Art of Prosody! How!Just write!   Out of the Depths of my soul, to you."     This was my response to his e-mail...    "Dearest Joseph,   Surely you have mistaken what I have said, I certainly do not believe that an artist such as Shakespeare merely picked up a pen and began to write.  My advice was to drown yourself into the world of literature, make it your life. I also advised you on two books to look into, I chose these books because I believe they contain detail on how one can write with skill ( I.e. meter, alliteration, verse, etc. ) I also meant by reading and writing constantly this will help develop skill to become a note worthy, great writer.  So, I am glad that this is what you are interested in for it is my interest as well.     Allow emotion to bleed,  Rachel     This e-mail was in response to a reply of mine to a post from this person at a poetry website. Now, I have only read and replied once to this person and when I first received this e-mail it took me a little bit to figure out who this was from because he never states any information. What bothered me besides the fact I felt he was trying to be coy not stating his name and where I know him from but also how he took my reply to his original question/posting. I felt that he completely misunderstood what I had advised and I find that I am misunderstood quite a bit and it is so frustrating. I truly feel at times I am standing amongst a crowd of people silently screaming. Or when someone is listening they twist and turn my words into a knot, which they create by not really listening, just thinking their thoughts before grasping my own. Oh well *sighs* at least I know what I meant. :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "Okay folks, I have officially been renewed in my musical inspirations. I have some major ideas unfolding, and they are shaping up to be some seriously kickass new tunes for your listening enjoyment."    He brings a smile to my face every minute of everyday, he brings meaning to my life with his light of energy, which I feel burning inside of me. He is excitement. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       lttlamb says : So how are you?   lttlamb says : happy, sad, tired?   Anonymous says : actually pretty at peace - not tired, not sad - I guess I am happy,  things are actually going well in my life   Anonymous says : what about you   lttlamb says : Hehehehe   lttlamb says : you said, "things are actually going well in my life"  I found this little conversation to be amusing, for a few reasons really, first I find that people seem to phrase this, "things are going good in my life" the same. Secondly it comes to a relief to know that this person who is one of the most important people in my life, who is my only friend, whom I know will always be there and support me as I for her. To know that she is happy means a great deal to me because she deserves this and has for quite sometime.  We have been through a lot together and we have come a long way since we first met in, fucking kindergarten (geez) but we really got to know one another in fifth grade.  We will always understand one another and this is comforting in a world of chaos. I admire her for her grace, intelligence, wit, and overall being.  Cheers! Karebear :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My terrible pic for preview of my work&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got to see a little bit of Texas today, it is strange how different it seems then what I had expected it to look like. I guess in all honesty I never imagined it would be that pretty. Although, it might be the individual who took the pictures ;) I think that was just a bonus. I will upload a few of my favs...  The following image posts are all thanks to this creative individual, visit his sight at, www.eonbeats.net
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Amusing and I enjoyed the perspective :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Interesting building, will have to ask what its purpose is...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A perfect moment&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My heart skips as if it can not  keep up with the  excitement, which runs through me. This is all your doing.  I feel my stomach twist and tighten with joy and anticipation. This is your doing as well.  You are a brilliant light that has entered into my life.   Without you I believe  I would be consumed by darkness.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate the feeling of regret, and at this moment in time I have that feeling.  I have this terrible habit of over analyzing every minute detail that I experience or come in contact with.  When you constantly are over thinking things this always leads to more questions and doubts. In all honesty as much as I am confident and secure with who I am, because of past experiences in my life I have a difficult time trusting and I also doubt myself. I doubt myself because I was put down, I was told I was shit, and even though that part of my life is gone it is so god damn difficult for me to believe that I am something, that I am worth anything.  It is a struggle inside of me because as much as I know I am not a failure there is still a part of me saying that I am. I think there will always be this negative part of me because I put everything on me, I take on everything and blame everything on me, even when it is not mine to take. I am seriously fucked up, think it is time to give that therapist a call... 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who ever thinks it is funny to post anonymous comments about somehting I have written, it is not. So instead of posting a comment just shove it up your ass next time. Thanks
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i let you in entirely under my skin diving deep  down into the depths of me  consuming every inch of the darkest parts of  this shattered little soul  now i must release you penetrating this flesh slicing these tiny wrists with a blade so piercing as it reflects luminescence off your beautiful soul  you watch as the blood  streams out of me i smile as i go  06/17/04 R.L. This is what bothers me
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ode to stupid people who do stupid shit on forums...Why the hell do people not use the large brain that has been attached to the rest of their bodies? It angers me so when people don't think... I am referring to those individuals who do the following inconsiderate acts... 1) People who post an excessive amount of their poems and don't have the time to reply to anyone else's work. 2) Usually these same people will also only log on to reply to only their poems and then log off. 3) These same people will also bring back a post of their own work from three months ago just because they are so self absorbed.  4) These same people also bring their business to the forum, for example their friend, or girlfriend/boyfriend posts a poem and as far as the rest of the world knows it really could be about anything or anybody but then instead of replying with a comment about the poem they will comment and reply "I am sorry" bringing their business out into the internet world for all to see.  What the fuck? They could just private message, instant message, e-mail, or fucking call them on the phone or something. I would seriously like to kill people, it is really too fucking bad that we fucked up the survival of the fittest because I tell you people this fucking stupid and inconsiderate deserve to be dead. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you knew I was the one to unlock your heart, would you let me in? If you were in pain and cried out my name, do you think I would come? If you fell in love with me, would you let me see? If I told you I needed you,  would you come to me?  Are you able to admit this all, when the time comes? Will you acknowledge it for what it is?
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This rant is to all of those fucks out there who have colored, fluorescent whatever the hell they are called headlights. Why the fuck do you need to have colored light shining out of the front of the car? What is the purpose of this? There is no good from this pointless creation, only bad. Nothing pisses me off more then when I am going way over the fucking speed-limit and all of a sudden I piss in my pants because I see out of the corner of my eye a flash of blue, or yellow, or purple, and then I look in  the rear view mirror and see that there was no fucking reason to piss in my pants because it is merely one of the ass-holes with lame fucking colored headlights. Die fuckers die!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "A lot has been going on in the real world, keeping me from the digital one. All that is now passed and I can safely sit down to write this. Nothing much to say right now, other than I am back in full swing...more soon..."   You deserve this... Within the last few weeks I have envisioned you sitting in a wooden chair in a shadowed room with a bright white spotlight beaming down on your broken being. You sit in this chair holding in your hand your heart pumping slowly as you watch it leek your blood until it is emptied, fallen to the floor, into a puddle of painful emotion, which you were forced to feel. You amaze me because even though I imagined you in this state I also knew you would regain, I admire who you are, as I cherish each time you are reborn. You deserve more.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I find it terribly depressing that even though my family and few select friends are here with me in this California fallacy, at the same time I have never felt so lonely here as I do now. I want to get in my car and escape somewhere far from here. I am stuck and can not move, I am done writing for now because this is shit... FUCK!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today my heart beat faster then it ever has before, my spirit sang out for the world to hear. A smile radiated light, reflecting the happiness, which you instilled in me. I stripped bare, standing naked, revealing insecurities, and you embraced me. I saw your smile, heard your tender voice. Feeling you were next to me, and for that moment the world fell into place, and everything was right.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to tell him so much.. How I dream of his touch to my skin.  My desire to memorize each detail of his body with my tongue.  I want to know his random thoughts and what he feels in the depths of his beating heart.  I want to be his escape from the shadows of this world.  I want him to know how my  spirit sings for all that he is.  For him to know without doubt how he caresses every part within.  06/10/04 R.L. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am in a dark place at the moment, I have been stuck here unable to shake the shadows that have taken me for quite some time. It is mostly anger I battle, filled with so much rage. I am sick of hurting and I can't seem to find how to cease this pain. Someday though...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I allowed myself to be taken To a far off land of fantasy I believed in beauty I saw I trusted the joy felt within me Let it all in to consume me  Now I sit silent here aching as my heart bleeds Red blood 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is very strange to look at my mom and I and see how our roles have changed.  A sadness over comes and sometimes I wish I could go back to when I was young where I could ignore my worries and escape into my imaginary world. Where I could breathe in and feel peace.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I see failure in everything I do, all that I am and this is my hell.  Nothing in this world do I hate with the amount of passion as I hate failure, but it always seems to fucking happen and I can not stand this sick disgusting thing.  I am done trying, done with pretending because I can not handle the fallacy bullshit act anymore. So here we go, I am failure, it is my life, my soul, and my best fucking friend.  Big fucking surprise isn't it? I am not perfect and I am not so optimistic. I am darkness soaked in failure, my destiny, and so let it be.  The ultimate failure is giving up and I am ready to succumb.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Puma, I envy her.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I had someone ask me, "how I was not sick of poetry?" My first response was to laugh because I find it humurous to have someone ask me this knowing that I am a writer.  Then I said, "What the hell are you talking about? I will never get sick of poetry.  It is my life, it is what I do." That was the end of the conversation, as the day went by the remark began to get under my skin and my feather's began to ruffle because this person is supposed to understand me when in fact they don't. This thought left me uneasy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The following is a snip it from my fathers journal written seven months before he passed away.  He had contracted Hepititis C, which is a disease that attacks the liver usually leading to the development of tumors on the liver. Due to years of heavy drinking his liver was failing as well, he was put on the transplant list at U.S.C.  The journal is an interesting look at one human beings struggle with pain, loss of control, acceptance, and the fusion of the spectrum of emotions.    Feb.2,2001    "The sun has warmed the day enough to allow the doors to stand open but there is still a hint of chill in the air.  Outside the world is going about its buisness.  a trash truck is making its noises way down the street while in the rear yard the crows are fighting over a few scraps of bread, tossed out for their welfare.    A few minutes ago I was dwelling on sadness and fear.  In other words I was in the future thinking about cancer and death and missing out on the lives of my loved ones.  This is what fear does for me.  It creates a world of negative possibility and as long as we live in fearwe are paralized, unable to enjoy what we have now."
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel blue :( This makes me smile...only when I am reading it though. *sighs* "Chin-up, Pretty, chin-up."-Sandburg   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Do not go gentle into that good night" By Dylan Thomas    &nbsp;  Do not go gentle into that good night,   Old age should burn and rave at close of day;   Rage, rage against the dying of the light.    &nbsp;  Though wise men at their end know dark is right,   Because their words had forked no lightning they   Do not go gentle into that good night.    &nbsp;  Good men, the last wave by, crying how bright   Their frail deeds might have danced in a green bay,   Rage, rage against the dying of the light.    &nbsp;  Wild men who caught and sang the sun in flight,   And learn, too late, they grieved it on its way,   Do not go gentle into that good night.    &nbsp;  Grave men, near death, who see with blinding sight   Blind eyes could blaze like meteors and be gay,    Rage, rage against the dying of the light.    &nbsp;  And you, my father, there on the sad height,   Curse, bless, me now with your fierce tears, I pray.   Do not go gentle into that good night.   Rage, rage against the dying of the light.     "When I have fears" By John Keats    When I have fears that I may cease to be  Before my pen has gleaned my teeming brain,   Before high-piled books, in charact'ry,  Hold like rich garners the full-ripened grain;   When I behold, upon the night's starred face,  Huge cloudy symbols of a high romance,   And think that I may never live to trace  Their shadows, with the magic hand of chance;   And when I feel, fair creature of an hour,  That I shall never look upon thee more,   Never have relish in the faery power Of unreflecting love! -- then on the shore   Of the wide world I stand alone, and think   Till Love and Fame to nothingness do sink.   &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Human beings are sometimes so absent minded...A captive Orca turned on his trainer of 10 years and chased him around the performance pool for quite sometime.&nbsp;Now, I mention this because I find it hard to understand that we being animals ourselves although we&nbsp;have evolved (I don't know how) to have the highest level of thinking with our large intricate brains, still have this ballsy misconception that we have the power and right to control this earth and the animals which help us along in this circle of life. If you keep an Orca captive and train it to follow your commands eventually one day you are going to get fucked, it is against the nature of a mammal like the Orca to be held captive away from it's pack/offspring/and home in the great open sea.&nbsp;I am also highly suspicious of any animal (i.e. dolphin, whale, dog, etc.) which violently attacks it's trainer or owner or any human being for that matter, because I believe that there is a reason for an animals violent actions either it has been provoked, sick, or merely acting out of instinct. You can train an animal all your life but the bottom line is you can not change the animal which I believe lies in all of us.   (This is my extremely short version of this all, I could go on and on about what is covered in this tiny paragraph, I am simply putting my two cents out there)   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will disappoint. If people have expectations about me, I will fail to meet these expectations.&nbsp; Through out the days of my life I continuously fail to meet my own goals and strivings and it is hard enough dealing with my own recognized failures...So it is destructive for my general well being and others if people push their expectations on to me. Although, I do wish I was perfect and I was a person who did and said everything right in life, I have repeatedly come to the realization that I am not perfect nor is anything else in this far from perfect world.&nbsp; I will continue to be a perfectionist and I will continue to fail but my feelings and guilt are&nbsp;at least my own.&nbsp; I find it harder to deal with other's disappointments in me more than my own realizations of shortcomings. *sighs*    
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I’ve become impossible    Holding on to when 
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have managed to completely push everyone away in my life...Keep all at a&nbsp;distance until they are sick of trying to find the entrance in. Being an only child I have spent my life as an independent individual, but I must say even I can not make it through this world, left with only my thoughts which dance in my mind...   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Die Götzen-Dämmerung - Twilight of the Idols   &nbsp; Friedrich Nietzsche [ 1895 ]    This is one of my favorites...Found a link to it online, if you have not read it before I highly suggest reading these profound words.    urlLink http://www.handprint.com/SC/NIE/GotDamer.html   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What the hell! Is it just me or do people just say things to hear how it sounds in their fucking heads? I am so sick of bullshit, please refrain from talking to me unless you are truly telling me something that does not contain any bullshit. Within the last few days I have been handed and stuffed with some meaningless nothingness and I am just really full.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everything manages to fall apart it seems, and somehow I feel it is due to my shortcomings that this happens.&nbsp; I sometimes can not stand the way life pulls and pushes you in directions that beat you down.&nbsp; I am tired, and out of sorts I guess. The night from hell still looms over me and I am trying to shake it but when I open my eyes and my mom is bitching at me (always endless banter) and things are different, missing, and gone, I just want to crawl back into bed and remain there until everything else simply fades away.   One strange and interesting thing is that last night I found a lady bug in my purse, I am not sure if that is good luck or bad luck but I guess just some luck...I set it free outside so that it may eat the aphids on the flowers in the yard because I don't have any aphids in my purse...Last time I checked at least. :)     
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some of my favorite words heard and read...    &nbsp;  "The meeting of two personalities is like the contact of two chemical substances: if there is any reaction, both are transformed."&nbsp;  -Carl &nbsp;Jung      &nbsp;   &nbsp;  "Works of art, in my opinion, are the only objects in the material universe to possess internal order, and that is why, though I don't believe that only art matters, I do believe in Art for Art's sake."&nbsp;  -E. M.&nbsp;Forester      &nbsp;  &nbsp;   "I write entirely to find out what I'm thinking, what I'm looking at, what I see and what it means. What I want and what I fear."&nbsp;  -Joan Didion      &nbsp;    &nbsp;   &nbsp;  "Theology is never any help; it is searching in a dark cellar at midnight for a black cat that isn't there. Theologians can persuade themselves of anything."&nbsp; -Robert A. Heinlein     Finally, from two of my favorite movies from the great director Paul Thomas Anderson...    &nbsp;   Barry Eagan:  I have a love in my life. It makes me stronger than anything you can imagine. ---Punch Drunk Love     &nbsp;   &nbsp;   Jim Kurring:  ...whatever you wanna tell me, whatever you think might scare me, won't...and I will listen...I will be a good listener to you if that's what you want...and you know, you know...I won't judge you.... I can do that sometimes, I know, but I won't...I can...listen to you and you shouldn't be scared of scaring me off or anything that you might think I'll think or on and on and just say it and I'll listen to you....  ---Magnolia       
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My heart is heavy with pain, it aches here today for my mother.&nbsp; Watching your mother in pain is torture and I feared these days since my dads passing.&nbsp; I can do nothing but be here for her but I am of no use, I am not the one she wants and just me alone will never do.&nbsp; I hate this feeling, where I am the parent, no longer the child but I guess this is the progression of things.&nbsp; I just never imagined it would feel the way it does, it is a lonely thing when you switch roles.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     http://www.eonbeats.net/index.htm &nbsp; urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Traveling Somewhere&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I sit back and watch another year pass on by and I ponder what I have learned in these 23 years in which I have been breathing this current&nbsp;life...     I know with complete certainty that I have the ability to handle anything that is dealt before me.&nbsp; This might seem to some as obvious but for me it was a realization because three years ago I couldn't say this and actually believe it.&nbsp; Now three years later after experiencing both emotional and physical battles that at the time nearly rendered me unconscious, I now know that I am much stronger than I originally thought.    I know that I do not believe in god or gods, I have questioned it, I have searched for answers and studied many possibilities. Nothing has ever clearly answered   my questions or ceased my doubts.&nbsp; It is not something I can believe,   there are far too many cracks in the board for me to trust.    I know that with art no matter the form as long as it is creative I am happy.&nbsp; Creativity is a beautiful thing, it feeds my entire being.    I know that my dad is proud of me.&nbsp; This means everything to me.    I know that we as human beings will be the cause of our own extinction.&nbsp; It has already begun it is only a matter of time.    I know that passion is one of my greatest pleasures in life and without it I would never be content breathing.    I know that I am not perfect but I also know that I will never stop trying to achieve perfection.    I know that I know nothing and I am always seeking knowledge.  haha seems as if that last one would cancel out the ones above but for me it doesn't, it is merely a statement which is a reminder to me&nbsp;to be conscious and continually seek the unknown. Cheers.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;         
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       When my thoughts return to him a smile is brushed across my face. No matter what my trouble or mood may be he manages to create a pleasant peace in me.&nbsp; There is a beauty in him that I will carry with me always...    
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is to those who hold themselves on a high pedestal where they are far&nbsp;to grand to be considerate to people who comment on their work.&nbsp; It takes one rotten egg to pass up the entire dozen, and frankly this is how I view a certain forum. People who are inconsiderate get under my skin like nothing else, and I want nothing to do with people of this nature, it angers me so.  *obscenities flare*   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      -Bush/Cheney '04: Apocalypse Now!   -Bush/Cheney '04: Because the truth just isn't good enough!   -Bush/Cheney '04: Compassionate Colonialism   -Bush/Cheney '04: Leave no billionaire behind!   -Bush/Cheney '04: Four More Wars!   -Bush/Cheney '04: Over a billion Whoppers served!   -Bush/Cheney '04: Putting the "con" in conservatism   -Bush/Cheney '04: Thanks for not paying attention   -Bush/Cheney '04: The last vote you'll ever have to cast   -Bush/Cheney '04: This time, elect us!   -Bush/Cheney '04: Assimilate. Resistance is Futile.   -Don't think. Vote Bush!   -George W. Bush: A brainwave away from the presidency   -George W. Bush: It takes a village idiot   -Let them eat yellowcake! Vote Bush!   -Vote Bush in '04: "I Has Incumbentory Advantitude"   -Vote Bush in '04: Because dictatorship is easier   -Vote Bush in '04: It's a no-brainer!   -Bush/Cheney '04: "Leave no child a dime!"   -The last time people listened to a bush   -They wandered in the desert for forty years.   -Support the environment; plant a bush back in Texas.   -Outsource Bush & Cheney   -NO ONE DIED WHEN CLINTON LIED 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not comfortable in my blog, and I can't seem to find one that fits. I am getting sick of this one, oh well this is really a nothing problem, a problem that fits under the nothingness category. I have class today and my goodness it is from 1:30-5:15! I am going to be sitting in art history for four freakin hours! :0 I can't sit still for that long, I am going to go crazy, I mean I love art history but people come on four hours???!!!!!!  This blog of nothingness is not going to change my situation, it could be worse though I could be sitting for four hours in a math class of sorts. That would be the end for me! haha. :) FIN
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing has ever felt so good, each and every one of my senses comes alive in the presence of this breathtaking individual. There is a light within in him that shines into the depths of my shadowed soul. Electric our love. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Show me one thing that is real inside my mind Where my imagination stirs generating A pool of all thoughts illogical, untrue I want us both to release and brake free  From this barrier that we have only created here I try so hard to smash it down and diminish the forces Which tie us down and prevent our passions from  Grasping one another until the end of time  I know this is what we both yearn for  So I can not understand why we are fighting  Against what we have always hoped for deep down inside I am screaming for you to come near and let me in  To the parts of you in which you locked but knew  I had the key from the very first spark between our hearts You still hesitate to let go and I am weary of this all We keep trying to remain fighting for each other  Till our pain is put to death by the faith, our love  I am aching for you and I can not breathe without you near   Your breath, the beauty in your eyes, I need you, Hear me crying for you now, screaming to you  Telling you how I want you to let go and love me  Dive in to me, let go of everything, enjoy us 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am exhausted from all the lies in which those have spoken. It leaves me feeling drained with an outlook of this entire world is bullshit. I don't really care if people think I am feeling sorry for myself, I could give a flying fuck if people are sadened by this post, and you bet your sweet ass I don't care if you all are pissed. I really just don't care anymore, fed up, so tell yourselves whatever you need to get by, whatever helps you sleep peacefully but don't tell me shit, I just don't want to hear myself being fed false hopes and meaningless banter...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have never gone to bed this early in a long while, but I yearn for my escape into my bed where comfort sets in and my troubles disapear from my mind and my heart is finally free to fly. I embrace this, let it consume me entirely, sleep is where I yearn to remain for all the rest of my days dreaming of all the things that dance inside my mind with the grace of a beautiful breeze.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why do I feel so anxious? What is my deal? Why do I ask myself questions in which address myself and my problems when I know I am the only person who has the ability to answer questions of this nature? For the first time in my short lived life I am actually dreading my birthday, this is something that is new to me, for I have always enjoyed this day in the past and look forward to its arrival but now I do not and this troubles me. I can not even grasp it in its entirety, I will return to this when I do.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      fhfaklfjakljfqaojfihfkwklq;kq;fkjouvjvsmfl;qpiroqrqkdl,. amkanicnkkfql;k'aifuttqpiqlknjcbcbuhqjqckml;k;wkvshdiwofhsihfsk lfklsjflkjslkfjidjfidjfll'l'DKSPIDSOJDAIODJ;;knvsdhudshoid;akdl;akd; skdosajfia;ip.  Ok translate! hahahahah I can not translate babble,  you people speak a language of nonsense,  I do not know fluent nonsense. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have suddenly developed an overwhelming feeling of anxiety, I don't know why, I don't understand myself. I am turning 23 in a matter of 12 days and I have accomplished nothing, really nothing, still in college, no book, no apartment, no self-respect obviously as you can obviously tell.  I miss my dad so much I can't even breathe lately, just typing that brought tears to my eyes. I thought by now it would get easier, I thought by now the pain would start to ease but if it does it only returns ten fold. I want him here to tell me what he thinks of this world, his life, our lessons, my life, I want him here to just be. I cry and scream for him to return but there is no response only silence as my tears fall down the side of my face. He is not able to return, I can not wish enough, scream loud enough, cry hard enough, run far enough or search every inch of this earth to find him he is gone and I have no control over any of it at all.  I suppose it will get easier as time goes on, right? Fuck off!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       (My feathers are still in a bit of a ruffle from the server going down at PA and deleting my comments about my thoughts on this website, so I come here...)    I must promote this website because I am very impressed by the effort and creation of the owner/author's finished product. The website now updated is one of the best layouts I have seen on the web, it has new music added, plus his entire music catalogue is now available, everything from Red Skull-Infernico music (I didn't even know existed). I applaud this created feast for the eyes, ears, mind, and spirit. Well done and cheers! Go take a looksie...Click on the link above, for it will show you the way. ;)  I know you all think I am some sort of crushed crazed groupie... Please, shove your judgments up your ass and then vomit them up in the toilet. :) Bottom line, anything created with passion and respect always seems to produce an amazing finished project, which is exactly what Eonbeats.net is. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am surrounded by many but at the same time I have never felt more alone. People look right past me, never hear me completely, and can not grasp or understand everything that makes up who I am as a human being. My frustration has been building and now I feel deep within me at the bottom of my beating heart the fire go out. I see my anger and snaps of temper and hate this newly formed self. I can not stop it, I don't know how to solve it, all I know is my heart is suffocating and dying from frostbite.   Take me in your arms   I want to fly away from here   Hold me close to your flesh  I feel at home here  As we glide through the air  To our destiny
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hurt because I know he aches,and yearns. He is pained by this worlds endless stupidity and is angered by the worlds destruction of human and animal kind. I know this all and feel it as well.  I smile because I know I unlock the happiness that he has been seeking. Together we feel complete as we travel through this world and continue on, in love.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since I am no longer on some sites, I have chosen to keep all my work here...  urlLink http://www.eliteskills.com/u/Belle%20De%20Jour  Feel free to browse...:) 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not one to be very open with people I don't know and frankly to be quite blunt I usually don't trust people until they prove to me they are worthy of my trust. This internet world has its perks and has many downfalls. So far I have weaned out the freaks who scare me and kept the people who don't, although there is still one guy who for some reason has the need to say hello to me on one of these messenger things everyday but that is all that is said and I find that to be the most annoying thing ever so I will rid myself of this annoyance. So I have no idea what that has to do with this but I figured I jot down some things about myself because I feel like sharing I guess...Go figure, I am feeling festive. :)     I am an only child but I do have two half sisters and one half brother who are way older than I and I really never see them. Just the mention of them makes me want to call them but this leads me to...  I am stubborn and I find most people are.  The arts have always been in my life...Danced for 11 yrs. Figure skated for 7 yrs. Theatre for 5 yrs. Fine art since I could hold a paint brush and writing all my life.  Although I can put on ice-skates and glide with ease and grace I still manage to walk into door ways and fall down stairs.  I laugh at my own jokes.  I love animals with all my heart, I have a connection with animals and I have always had it you can seriously call me Dr. Doolittle, this leads to...  My gift from Never Never Land...Puma she is my kitty (her picture is my profile picture for this blog) She is the sweetest and cutest cat, she is seriously my companion and you all can think I am crazy but I don't care.   I have never moved, I have lived in the same house for 23 years and I know Long Beach California like the back of my hand.  I am quite a conservative when it comes to sex, I am what some would call a tease and I do not give it up for just anyone.  I drive like a fucking maniac, a race car driver.  I will never jump out of a plane, or bunjee jump, I am scared of heights and falling from high places.  I am also surprisingly gullible and people who I am close to constantly abuse this.   I love the sound of piano, George Winston and Yann Tiersen are excellent choices.  I can not stand to watch living things suffer and living thing even if it is a deadly insect I still can not stand to watch it suffer.   There are many more but I think this is enough for now... :)    
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok my life is a crazy mess right at the moment...I just got back from taking care of my friends cousins because their father had a seizure and needed to go to the hospital. My day started off with my mom calling me telling me that she is on her way home and she is bringing with her this woman that she sponsors (my mom is in Al-anon if you don't know what that is then I am sorry you all need to open your eyes to the real world) anyways this woman is darling and she is pregnant meaning going into labor any minute pregnant and she is staying with us for a week because she was staying with her brother who is an alcoholic and was abusing her and that is just not a safe fucking situation so she is staying in our guest room which is fine and I am glad she is safe. I have finals in like a week oh joy and it is hotter then hell here and that is all I have to say at the moment. Ta Ta :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can not stand people! That is all...I am leaving it at that for now. hahaha 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am feeling better today...I feel myself starting to get back where I have yearned to be for quite sometime. What doesn't kill me only makes me stronger, this I know. I have not been writing but I am not going to push it and feel it will come when it comes, I have no fear. I can't expect to write continuously everyday, so I have been thinking and turning lines over in my head and I feel something developing inside this mind of mine. Here are two of my favorite quotes on writing...    "I write entirely to find out what I'm thinking, what I'm looking at, what I see and what it means. What I want and what I fear." -Joan Didion    "The only thing I was fit for was to be a writer, and this notion rested solely on my suspicion that I would never be fit for real work, and that writing didn't require any."  -Russell Baker 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well...I am not happy and I am not sure what I am at the moment. I am a mix of emotions and sometimes this is worse than feeling numb. I have found out some news about my best friend, I already was suspicious of some funky activity going on that she wasn't telling me about, and I was right. I am angry and I only see bad things coming her way based on the decisions she has made. I will not go in to detail but I thought she would have seen what happened to me and steered clear from that deal entirely but she didn't and this is going to affect our friendship, I know because it already has and because it is something that bothers me a great deal. I suppose in the next coming weeks I will have to sit down and pour all this bullshit onto her lap and we will see how she deals with it, and I know she won't take it well...She never does take anything well when it involves someone pointing out her faults, we are two of a kind when it comes to this. This probably doesn't make any sense to anyone but I will clear it up as I go along as well. :) My head is spinning...I feel like a dradel. :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am going through some shit at the moment...I will not be on as much as normal. This angers me a great deal but it is my own fault. Everything is lacking and I have to eat my peas before my desert as my dad used to say and how I do wish he was here for some support at the moment. I take a deep breath as I dive into the deep end. I will be responding to e-mails obviously, and I will be around I am sure, can't seem to stay away to long from this internet world.  May the force be with you...well at least I still make myself laugh :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Dimension, done in Jasc PSP8&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So, so you think you can tell   Heaven from Hell,   Blue skys from pain.   Can you tell a green field   From a cold steel rail?   A smile from a veil?   Do you think you can tell?      And did they get you to trade   Your heros for ghosts?   Hot ashes for trees?   Hot air for a cool breeze?   Cold comfort for change?   And did you exchange   A walk on part in the war   For a lead role in a cage?      How I wish, how I wish you were here.   We're just two lost souls   Swimming in a fish bowl,   Year after year,   Running over the same old ground.   What have we found?   The same old fears.   Wish you were here     This song always reminds me of you, mainly because you listened to Pink Floyd so much. :) I miss you so much it burns within but I know you are proud and that is all that matters. You are with me every breath I take. I continue on... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>