<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      EEEGGGGAAAADS!!!!!! Help help!!! I find this ironic; here my post is saying celebrate and be happy, while I am currently very stressed, panicked, and I dunno....depressed? *goes crazy and starts foaming at the moath*  Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! *trips over a chair*  Ok ...murrrr.....what am I going to do!? What if I fail this semester. What if I flunk my finals?! And for gawd's sake, I still haven't finished that blurdy porfolio. Neh! *clenches her head* GAH!!!!!   I feel myself falling deeper and deeper into oblivion. Deeper....deeperrrrrrr. I need to eat something.   Why, am I doing so bad this year?! I feel like my grades are going to spontaneously combust, causing my whole future to be consumed in a huge destructive conflagration of failure. AHHHH!!!  I've ruined myself:  -I'm going to screw up my GPA -I'm going to end up miserable -I don't know how I'm going to survive next year. -I've been procrastinating way too much. -I'm drifting away from my friends -I feel like people don't even want to be around me any more  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to the beach yesterday, for swim banquet. It was boring. Too rocky, only good for surfing. -_- bwifff.  Oh ya, my other computer broke down. All the files, everything, was lost. Gone! FOREVER :(!  Oh well, I keep most of my files on my laptop anyways. The things I lost were, my scanned drawings, some old assignments. Oh poo. Today, I shall mourn the loss.  I fixed it though. Now the computer seems so empty. It's got nothing, just an internet explorer icon. Blank! Wow...so cute. It's like a newborn baby...time to install all the old programs again. *sigh*   Hooray for laptops. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      darn I guess it doesn't work for animations. Oh poo...
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heh...it's Girrrrr! I'm just trying out the new Hello-BloggerBot-posting-pictures-thing. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hooray for Deviant Art!   This is probably, by far, my favorite picture at DA! Not only is the painting awe-inspiring, the whole concept is great. She's still smiling. Be happy for her, she's free! Here's the link!  urlLink MUST SEE 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hooray for blogging. Wow, I don't know how often I will post here but...oh well. I think chose to actually make a blog so that I can comment on other people's pages. The old commenting ...thingy, doesn't work anymore. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoosh, gone! This year just went by so fast. It was a good year...mostly. Met lots of people.  Why do I not feel that excited? In fact, I'm kind of resenting it. Kind of...  I don't know, it's probably because I'm so paranoid about...stuff.  Toot-a-toot. Well, maybe I'll feel better tomorrow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hooray for Pathogens. I got sick...I think last night...or was it early morning? I kind of forgot...or I'm too tired to remember.   Ya...it was stomach flu-ish. So I don't have to go into the details of my horrific experience.  Wheee...I took some tylenol. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>