<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was pretty good, i had an easy science quiz, all the usual boring school stuff...but when i went to courtneys house with sammy, we went downtown and had some "interesting" experiences.  When we go into Guess, we see this 65 year old lady with gray hair wearing...whats that? a black MINI SKIRT and a white OFF THE SHOULDER V-NECK SHIRT EXPOSING HER SAGGY CLEAVAGE? yes...and then she comes up to me and asks me where i got my shirt because thats "EXACTLY!" what shes looking for...then the lady working at Guess wont show her some of the shirts available because some of the logos are too "weird" for the lady to wear...maybe she just is trying to help you avoid some embarassment? Then we shop for a little more and go to Starbucks, where this probably college guy working there makes a sad attempt to flirt with us.  He kept cracking stupid jokes like telling us the totaly was $5.44 and then when we would hand over the money, he would be like "its 10.44"...um funny? i dont think so, and the best part was him offering me anything of my choice "on him" bc i didnt buy that much? and of course the fat ladys purple underwear sticking out of her pants...at least i got some tank tops and the purse mel gave me money to buy for her...never knew we had such freaks in Westport!! g2g do some of my english essay and finish up packing, cya tomorrow on my last day of school before going to the bahamassss (in case u DIDNT know)  :P
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, i did not have a wonderful day...social studies test (actually that was really easy so thats good), then i get a shitttload of hw and we have to sit for an hour and a half listening to Holocaust stories.  i feel bad about their experiences, but really, i think maybe a 30 min presentation wouldve been a little better! at least i missed pres. skills so some freakkkk (no names) won't molest me and i wont have to present my dialogue.  when i get home i start doing all my hw and im surprised to see that its easy and taking less time than i thought! right now im about to start typing up my ss hw and studying for finalssss bc i wont have time to next week that much (im not gonna say why bc if u r reading this u know where i am veryy excited to go on sat. lol)...so soon my dad is gonna come home and im gonna have to eat my grandmas shit meat loaf which looks suspiciously like dog food.  At least ill have dance class later!! we can dance like sluts in our gross costumes (white, red, and black...the pants are see through basically and the shirt shows my whole stomach).  My teacher also either left suddenly or got fired according to our new teacher, which is a good thing bc she cant teach for her life.  So today we're supposed to be redoing our dance to something less "nasty and inappropriate".  I'm gonna go do my hw like a good girl...kisses
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, i love monday mornings...so i normally am supposed to wake up at 6:15 or 6:20...my dad is screaming at the top of his lungs for me to wake up at...6:10? alright..so i wake up, get ready, all the normal stuff, and go to school, where i go to war in badminton (me and courtney) vs. kat and caitlin hahah.  Then i get to math, and i learn useless stuff and i find out i have a quiz tomorrow.  Then later on i have lunch, pretty normal, computer, boring, and science...samela deletes our whole lab assignment (hes a smooth one).  When i get on the bus (lys is coming home with me), she bare asses me with her jean skirt (very lovely experience lol), and when we get home we eat...very normal amounts of ritz crackers with cream cheese.  then we go online for a while, talk to sean our best friend, and have some...fun secret experiences during our get-together. Then after she leaves i do a shitload of hw, and when sue (dads gf) comes back from boston to pick up her dog, we have dinner with her and two of her daughters.  We mostly talked about how i might not go to school on friday so we can get manicures and pedicures before leaving for the BAHAMAS!! its gonna be amazzzing (btw on sat. night at 11:30 i started packing bc i got really bored..) alright i gotta go to bed, so ill talk to you guys laterrrr...
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tanning was a little boring, so later on i went to CVS and Barnes and Noble.  In CVS, i got the usual: hair products, with a few different sunscreens (hahah im cool like that). When i was there, i saw a girl from my dance class.  After i left, i went to Barnes and Nobles to get a few books with my sister.  Some of them were The Clique, GOSSIP GIRLS (so excited), The Insiders, The Devil Wears Prada...yes i read very deep, philosophical books.  Surprisingly, my dad didnt question me about the appropriateness of these books like normal.  Finally, we got to the register line, and this rude lady goes, "Don't you want to be standing where you're SUPPOSED to be?" Oops, i guess i was standing in the exit place instead of the enter.  I'm sorry i ruined your day, little old rude grandma.  Speaking of grandmas, next i had to go to my grandparents condo in Southport to pick up food (they love supplying my family with food...).  That was pretty uneventful except for my grandma telling me for ther second time in a week that shes glad i am skinny because you can die from being obese (completely normal, i guess?) Then i came home to start working on my english essay outline, math final stuff (yes beispel our plan is the best), and other boring stuff. Much love...until later
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i tanned outside with Mel...very nice, very nice, i got a little bit of a tan :) except my neighbors were having some kind of party in their backyard so i got the feeling they were looking at us (not cool).  I'm gonna go to CVS in a little while to get stuff for the BAHAMASSSSS (i'm going in a week i'm sooo excited)...cya later :P  ___Britt___
     

    
</post>


</Blog>