<Blog>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well to catch everyone up on my life.  I am 24 years old almost 25.  With three children.  I was married and have a 8 yr old son (Jacob) and a 5 yr old daughter (Gabrielle) from my marriage.  After I left my marriage I met my ex boyfriend Mike.  And him and i planned our 2 yr old son Joseph.  Things ended really bad between him and i which has caused me to wanna stay single and not get into a relationship for the past 2 and a half years.  I have a lot of mistrust and anger.  My two oldest live with my parents in Rockford.  Belding schools suck and eventually when i am done with my college I will move to Rockford.  Before i decided to have my kids move to rockford with my step mother and father Mike and i decided to have joint custody of joseph but he lives with Mike.  I recently decided to give in and see someone seriously.  We've been seeing eachother for for about 2 months now. Things have been going really fast to the point where we are deciding we want to live together.  I live in Belding which is near Grand Rapids he lives in Dundee which is near Ann Arbor.  It's about a 2 and half hour drive.  He has 2 children that he loves and lives in monroe.  He brought both of his kids up yesterday and my kids were here.  It was nice but he had to leave today.  I've actually debated if i want to continue the realtionship because of the distance.  He moved in with his father to start saving up money.  So that in a year we can move in together.  He said he's tired of struggling and tired of seeing me struggle.  That he wants to have something underneath us when we do move.  And by then i'll be almost done with college.  It was kind of weird.  He had a dream lastnight that i ended us because of the distance.  I didn't tell him i had actually had thoughts about it.  He is so strong which is good...i mean emotionally.  I have no patience.  I love him so much.  I mean he is everything i want in someone.  Yeah there are some things i don't care for but those are things that i can live with.  Nothing is perfect.  I just know that i wanna be with him and make life choices with him.  I get the feeling he is the one.  So why am i having my doubts?  I think i am just scared.  I don't commit well...I run.  There was only one other person that i commited to after mike and that failed too.  The rest i ended.  I couldn't do the commitment.  I was raised in a broken home.  I have had no one to show me what a relationship is supposed to be like.  I'm just worried that i'll find someway to screw this all up.  I just gotta quit being so negative on everything and when he leaves quit being so sad.  So that he doesn't have to deal with that when he leaves.....  But this is it for now....my thoughts of the momen.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>