<Blog>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have another blog, www.xanga.com/bogdana, and its easier to navigate than this one, so check it too.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The opening was awesome. I loved the artwork. The movie was cheesy and inconsistent with the comic books, but, I've come to accept that from Marvel and their movie remakes. If they were too close to the real thing, the movies would be long and boring and wouldn't wrap very neatly. At first, all I could think about was Horatio Sanz saying that he is Spiderman "but I was stung by a thousand bees!". Some other items of note were- he washed and dried the spider suit at a LAUNDROMAT. I would have thought that Lycra would be "dry clean only". Hal Sparks did a great cameo in an elevator scene. He needs more airtime. I think the entire aunt - packing- up her- things scene could have been cut, it was worthless and a big chunk of a timewaster. Good time to go pee. Oh, and for half the movie Tobey aka Peter Parker and his red bloodshot eyes looked higher than Redman and Methodman. I guess he DOES love Mary Jane. i have to work on my set, because im doing side splitters thursday night, in case anyone wants to see me be silly. i hope stage fright does not grip me again. It's horrible. I'll drink an amaretto suor or two,that usually works. I won't be driving.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First, I just have to say, I felt special today. Someone recognized me from my stand-up. And said nice things. wa hoo! next stop, superstardom (or, TWO people might remember me in an Applebee's). Anyway...- Black Hawk Down - no one even realizes Ewan was in this one.I know you think I am biased... but seriously, he was a rare bright spot. The desk worker who made coffee through Desert Storm, he gets thrown into the operation and thankfully comes out alive. His biting sarcastic lines well matched him. This movie was long long long. Lots of gunfire of course. Strangely though I didn't feel emotional for any of the movie. I've seen plenty of war movies... but all I felt during this one was, "is it over yet?". God bless the men that this movie was based on- but this movie was an arduous, painfully long journey with either half cocked actors, or half baked writers. I cannot tell which one. Do I really, truly have to know about 35 different characters? It was menial information overload. I had a hard time figuring out which shallow character development matched which actor. Orlando Bloom, Eric Bana, and Josh Hartnett (ugh)were also in this film.                                                Rating (between 1 AND 5): 2
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As Ewan McGregor week winds down to an end (recap-Trainspotting, Down with Love, Big Fish, Moulin Rouge, and now Nightwatch- two more to finish the week off !), I am going to review "Nightwatch", a little known Ewan suspense-thriller. It also stars Patricia Arquette, Josh Brolin, and Nick Nolte. This movie definitely had its slow parts. I guessed who the murderer was within 30 minutes. It was still intense and freakish and had me on my toes at the really scary parts! I was pretty much feeling suspenseful the whole time. This is an 1998 American remake of the 1994 Denmark psycho thriller "Nattevagten" by the same director Ole Bornedal. I suggest it as a good dont-have-anything-else-to-do rental! One of the best thrillers I have seen in a while. Plus it was nice to see Ewan in a uniform, even if it was a security guard one, hahaha. I have noticed one thing about Ewan though... he really likes to get a nude scene into whatever movie he's in! "Black Hawk Down" to be done tomorrow!  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW. This is an awesome documentary. The only thing is, it made me mad- mad that I feel like I can't do anything about the malformation of our country, and the corruption of its so called leaders. Mostly because all my suspicions that I've had from the beginning- Jeb Bush helping out in rigging the Florida vote; oil money; halliburton; george sr; the Iraqi war; relatives of Osama... he gave significant evidence for everything I've thought about and hoped I was wrong. I knew Osama had a brother in Orlando. I never could make sense of the Iraq war. Don't get me wrong- I dont consider Moore's work, however insightful and accurate, the Gospel Truth. One thing I know is that I'm young and don't know a lot. I do, however, know not to blindly trust anyone, including Bush. In the past, I had interest in politics, and what was happening. Not soon after Bush was elected. Hearing him talk made me think "who the hell is this man who can't speak in public, and why is he at the helm of this nation". The minute the election crisis was over, I was disgruntled about what happened and thought it was shady, and I thought Jeb had something to do with it. Then W opens his mouth and talks. Even if you dont like michael moore- you cannot take away the fact that what George W says on TV cameras is inane. He's asinine, truly. "lets fight terrorism. now watch this drive". leave the jokes to the comedians.Funny how the inaugural parade involved tens of thousands of protesters. I never saw that on Fox, fair and balanced (and related to Bush). W,  you are a friggin "world leader". I thought before and I still think now- George is the biggest puppet with the longest Saudi hand up his ass moving his mouth. Greed has always ran the US, but its getting a tad out of control. Yes, its true Moore cuts film to make people look more stupid than they really are. However, what is being said is to them real. The young kids who don't know what they're doing, talking about listening to the "right music" to get "pumped up [to bomb and shoot at Iraqis]", were made to look like idiots more than in normal context, for sure. But they still said those words. Its not like it was spliced. It was smooth continuous tapings. These kids are brainwashed, and they're dying,  next to Iraqis, so that A few fat white guys can add a few more million dollars to their already grossly lined pockets. Now due to the Patriot Act, I'm sure I'll be getting a letter from some Federal Agency questioning me. McCarthyism at its best. I can't believe its happening again.  You know what else bugged me? Saudis have 830 million dollars invested in american companies, including aol and citibank. So, when I use my citibank credit card at the gas station, their raping my wallet TWICE. Thanks W. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to "The Real Gilligan's Island" open casting call today, and it was really fun! I auditioned for the Mary Ann character. I'm not drop dead gorgeous so I had to rely on my mad comic skills to work. I think I actually did rather well. I had 3 interviews, and all three the camera guy, boom guy and interviewer were cracking up. Some of the questions I answered - "Finish this sentence- I would make the Ultimate Mary Ann because..." I said "I am cheap and easy to work with". "If you had to be stranded on an island with three other people, they would be..."  I said, "Ewan McGregor by himself would be fine, thank you". and "One thing I will look forward to about living on the island is..." and i said "muscle tone". see. those are way more interesting answers than the other skanks. I mean girls.  Ewan McGregor week- today's movie is Moulin Rouge  . I saw the real one in France from the outside. The movie was different. I liked the 80s and 90s music juxtaposed with the early 1900s scenery. It was like a pop up book come alive. I enjoyed it. Nicole Kidman's baby voice was a little irritating. John Leguizamo's lisp was hysterical. The whole show was put together well. I especially liked the ending-not happily ever after. Its refreshing to ditch the white horse and the sunset.  Rating- 3 1/2 stars
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Dodgeball". If anyone is depressed out there please go see this movie. It is magically stupid. I thought "Zoolander" was the top of stupid funny, oh no, dodgeball is better. I have a soft spot for stiller. no, not that spot. He does good physical comedy. The cameos were worth it by itself to see this movie. the ESPN 8 "The Ocho" commentators were friggin hilarious. You could tell Bateman couldn't do any of his lines with a straight face, I wonder if he was high. Anyways theres no explaining its obvious what the plot is from the trailers just go see it.Matinee preferrably so you save a dollar.  rating- 3 stars
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Super Size Me- Well, I just saw this one. It was very interesting. The director/star, Morgan Spurlock, has good humour. It was a bit more like watching a Discovery Channel special, though, than a movie. Let me just say... I have sworn off beef (or what is labeled as such) for the last 4 months, and it has helped me become healthier. I am now going to swear off anything McDonald's. I probably eat there once a week, because there is one in my hospital (an irony that the documentary touched on- my hospital is not the only one). I love those damn egg & cheese biscuits. I eat one once a week. No more! I owe it to my liver. This movie was kind of preaching to the choir though- the entire audience that I saw it with...were in decent shape. No fat people at all. Oh well. It was informative, slightly liberal (I love liberals don't get me wrong!), but I think he did his best to give a rounded documentary. Boy capitalism sure has its downfalls (meaning big companies fuck us up by telling half truths). No I am not communist. All I can say about communism, though... even a broken clock is right twice a day! hahaha  noooooo, McCarthy, don't put me on the Un-American list!  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Down with Love- Well, this movie was really cute. I liked that there were parts I couldn't predict would happen, so it was enjoyable. Thankfully, I felt no chemistry between Renee Zellweger and Ewan McGregor. It looked like it pained them to kiss each other. I know this was the Rock/Doris homage piece, (i.e. nothing overly sensual)and I liked it, but since I haven't watched a Doris Day movie in God knows how long, I can't really compare the two. I really loved the cheesy sexual innuendos, and Ewan got to practice three dialects for the part- American high roller, American hick, and Scottish you can understand! David Hyde Pierce gets typecasted as a neurotic man that doesn't see much action, but he does it so well!   rating: 2 1/2 stars
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To continue with Ewan McGregor week, I watched "Big Fish", and I am pissed that I paid 12.99 for it. Not  because it was depressing, but because I bought it "pre viewed" from Blockbuster and it had scratches that prevented me from seeing certain parts. Don't buy pre viewed DVDs. VCR tapes never did that when I bought them used. What do people do, when they're done watching it do they go rub it on the sidewalk?    So "Big Fish" was not as good as I thought it would be. It was just too long and sooo sad. I know thats a Tim Burton thing, and I usually like it, but it was just depressing for me. Maybe its because I don't have parents (*tear in the eye, sniff*). More likely its because he really looked like he was dying and it happens all the time where I work. The directing was spectacular, and the Art director I hope won something for this, but the actual plot was just too dragged out. I just wish they hadn't ruined Ewan's character by making him have a southern accent. It made my ears bleed. Dont get me wrong, he did a GREAT southern accent. It just didn't seem right! *footnote- I realise a lot of people disagree with me on this movie. I think I was being a little harsh with my rating so I added a smiley. Maybe lot of people misconstrued my distaste for the elongated plot as a disgust for the movie in general. I just thought it could have flowed better. But what do I know? All the actors did well and the cinematography was fantastic for sure! Plus it was a bummer to have the son treat his dad like crap the whole time, even if it was irritating how he kept telling the same stories. I wish I had had a dad that TALKED to me I dont even care what he said. So maybe I was just bitter at the son the whole time! hahah. I still think the artistic merit far supercedes the plot. Lets look forward to Burton's remake of Willie Wonka, shall we?   rating- 3 stars!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trainspotting! Its Ewan McGregor week just so you know. I've officially announced it. I like this movie (and the soundtrack), VERY realistic ("BJ, what do you know about heroin addiction!?"). I like how they DONT glamorize skag. It's like this, I see people on smack every day in the hospital, and they hate it and we hate it. Its nasty shite. My favorite line, as he was trying to get clean on his own- "...and a bottle of valium, which I had already procured from my mother, who is, in her domestic and socially acceptable way, ALSO a drug addict."  I went running today. I need to lose at least 12 more pounds and turn the rest into MUSCLE grr yeah. Creepy old guys on their porch stared at my boobies. I hate that. But, as a typical woman, if they didn't bother to glance, I'd be insulted then, too. Men can never win with women. so i give trainspotting, ten years late, a 3 1/2 star rating. wa hoo!  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back and have to say it was a great movie. No insanely slow parts like I had expected. This movie is a prime example of why Spielberg makes gagillions of dollars when he directs a film. He gets the script to a perfect balance of symbolism so that you might have to think, for us geeks, and blatant, easy to understand dialogue for those of us who like mary jane a little more than we should. a stoner and a professor can both appreciate the simplicity of the story line. Not to give anything away, which I make a point of not doing, but I thought the ending was well done and realistic (well, realistic enough for the movies). Catherine Zeta Jones's flight attendant role was perfect for her, it was almost like typecasting, she played a co dependant, lonely, old-man-humping, pathetic woman. The brightest spot? Gupta the Indian custodian. I love him! He was EXACTLY like an older Indian man. Embellishing stories and whatnot. I have a couple Indian friends and they say that Bollywood movies correctly depict Indians- melodramatic to the nine. Good example for those who dont know Bollywood (the indian hollywood) is Bend it like Beckham, and how over the top the indian girl's family was.                            Rating (from 1-5)    1/2   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW! Last night I did open mic night at The Improv and I am rediculously proud of myself. I did not screw up my set at all, I got everything out (I chickened on a few gags b/c the audience wasn't right for them), and I got a great response from the audience. My nerves did settle after a drink though. I wish I had the calm to do it without an amaretto sour or two. At least they taste good. Anyway, It was a very eclectic night. Most people were horrible as usual (please, people out there, stop using PROPS, Carrot Top barely pulls it off so what makes you think YOU can!?), but we had a couple of great ones. I don't suck! Much! YEEEAH!!! I can't wait for Super Size Me to finally get into a dang tampa theater! WHAT is taking so LONG!?
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didnt perform, but I went to see my friends Chris and Geoff at  urlLink Sidesplitters  last night.Geoff did great on the open mic, and the other guys too. My new buddy Chris did really well. Hes been to a few open mics in NYC. I dont think he's as new as he would like us to think, hes too comfortable onstage. or maybe he was a drama kid, who knows, i wish i had been allowed to be one, id be much better at stage presence by now. everyone says im "cute" still. i dont want to be CUTE! how is it that im&nbsp; making fun of bad stuff but im still CUTE! eek! congratulations, folks, you have all now met the Drew Barrymore of stand up comedy. Cute, talented but not rough arund the edges. Well I guess that still makes me original.&nbsp;A&nbsp;large percentage of&nbsp;female comics are lesbian, so that is a polar opposite of such. Im going to see a movie. i think bourne supremacy. I will tell you all about it later!   .   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did so much better tonight than last night! coconuts was a blast. before we went onstage, me, Geoff and Jym decided to give each other obscure phrases from the day that we had to fit in our set. I got '67 alabama, Geoff got "Whats fun about a building" and Jym got "120 lb test". Because of this stupid idea, I did the best show ever. I wasnt nervous at all. i even fubared a part and just went out and pointed it out, and it was hilarious, i couldnt believe it. i got '67 alabama in there three times too!  *EDIT* How did I get '67 Alabama in there? well, ive got a "my moms a racist" joke, and at the end of it most people just go "oooh" instead of laugh, so i said "its colder than '67 alabama in here!". Lame, but effective. everyone laughed. From there I just threw in " 67 alabama" wherever I felt appropriate. If Bernie Mac can go "you just dont understand" in between everything, well then, I can say 67 Alabama for no reason.  Thank you for the props. IM going to go see a few movies today to catch up with my reviewing- Ive been so busy being a comedy geek! more later im at work!  Look, its me and my homies-&nbsp;        
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW! Today has been an awesome picture day. I got to use some black and white film. You can see all my photos I take at  urlLink http://photos.yahoo.com/bogdanawdw  . These are a few of my&nbsp;better ones&nbsp;that I took this afternoon. I think you can click on them tomake them bigger and w. better quality.          
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mm mm! Taco Bell. Nothing better to go to bed with in your stomach than a bean burrito, cheesy potatoes (i barely ate them), and a fudge round. i did nothing but eat junk food all day, so what the hell! I think it was my 8th time on stage today. Im getting much better. I forgot my newest and one of my better jokes, but I wont forget it on tuesday. this is such a stressful business. Its worth it, but its killing me, im becoming neurotic. plus ive had more secondhand smoke in the last few months to last me an eternity. interesting fact: white people dont like it when white people joke about Puerto Ricans, yet Puerto Ricans have no problem and are good natured about white people doing those same jokes. Why are white people so uptight!? Its comedy! 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      take my quiz- i want to break 1000 quiz takers!  urlLink http://quizilla.com/users/BogdanaWDW/quizzes/Are%20you%20a%20Tough%20Crowd%20Comedian?/ &nbsp;a pharmacist at work thinks I'm racist and thats why I look at him funny. That is the most rediculous thing I have ever heard. I look at him funny, because I think he's a tard. He's always talking to me in French-lish, and&nbsp;God knows my French is about as good as my Czechoslovakian.&nbsp;It has nothing to do with him being black! I am down with my Urban Individuals! He does speak too much French to me. I have pretty much no clue what he's saying.  I got my camera! It was a whole $29 at wal mart. But it has a ZOOM lens! we will see how the b & w photos turn out that I am trying to do now. FUNNY CRAP RIGHT HERE I know everyone on the globe has seen this but if you haven't go NOW its hilarious -  urlLink http://www.jibjab.com/  !  Im doing a guest spot tonight. I practiced a lot&nbsp; in the mirror so maybe I wont suck this time.    
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      take my Tough Crowd Quiz- I want to break 1000 quiz takers! Its good. refresh it if it gives an error, the site doesn't have very good servers.  urlLink http://quizilla.com/users/BogdanaWDW/quizzes/Are%20you%20a%20Tough%20Crowd%20Comedian%3F/  I just found out how to put pictures on this blog. deeerrrr. Ok Ive just taken up photography out of sheer boredom and frustration. Im using a Discovery 35mm with no zoom and, in some instances, no focus. However the photos are not turning out halfway bad. So do you think the color one is better, or the sepia tone:  &nbsp;      1982 - I began table dancing at a young age to feed my family of twelve:     Since my camera is so crappy, I am going to go get a new one. Nothing&nbsp;too fancy, just a nice $30&nbsp;camera with a zoom lens, So the next time I happen upon a fire, I will be ready! Plus, I am going to try to&nbsp;do my own headshots, hahahahaha.       
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (For lots of pictures, go to  urlLink http://photos.yahoo.com/bogdanawdw &nbsp;.&nbsp;)&nbsp;I hate cats. I have now irritated most of the people who read this but I don't care. Cats, in my view, are like oversized hairier rats that procreate faster yet live ten times longer. Cats are horrid, stinky little creatures. Forget spayed or neutered, please just drown them. Ive got cement and burlap bags in my garage if anyone needs them.  I hate cats particularly today, not only because we have a one hundred and twelve year old calico that goes pee pee on my towels constantly in my bathroom, but also because some jackass who didnt have the cajones to drown his own kittens threw them out of his truck and now theres four to six kittens making a helluva lot of noise. My mother in law, God bless her, did waaaay too much weed, and she is supposed to be going to work, but no, no I hear "ooohisntitacutewiddleting" blah blah. Shes coming towards the door so I lock it and say "Go to work!" "NO I need to get the ladder and get the kitten out of the tree!" "WHAT THE&nbsp;*expletive that rhymes with puck*&nbsp;IS WRONG WITH YOU OLD WOMAN! You are not getting the ladder on my watch. I'll be damned if you get quadriplegia because you SUCK at ladders so you could get a kitten that could easily jump out of our damn ten foot tree!!!!" "nooo let me get the ladder" (*i proceed to bolt the door*) "oh-never mind-it got out by itself".   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its raining AGAIN. POURING. Do I LIVE in friggin Hawai'i? No, no i do not. Actually it used to rain like this all the time 10-12 years ago. Just I am not 13, now I am 23, and I have to not only drive 30 miles to get to HCC, but also have to get gas on the way. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My tentative schedule - tuesday, somewhere in zephyrhills theres an open mic.... weds, either coconuts or i might get a guest set at sidesplitters, thurs, i dont know yet maybe city lights. we shall see. i need more stage time. got a new possible cure for stagefright- Dr do right prescribes: propranolol. we will see if it works. its a heart med (beta blocker for you drug nerds), and off-label its used for anxiety and sometimes stage fright. I need something&nbsp;because drinking doesnt work!!  words or phrases people say that make me want to ram a blunt object into their temple:  1.)'salmon' with the l.&nbsp;&nbsp; if you say salmon and not samon, you deserve to rot in purgatory.  2.)'warsh', 'warshington'- theres no friggin R. where the hell did you go to school, Florida?  3.)acrosst -across never happens. its not a verb. its an adverb. therefore you can't place it in past tense. so STOP.  4.) 'irregardless' the 'ir' cancels the 'less' and makes it regard.  5.) et - this is a form of&nbsp; "eat" that only hardcore rednecks partake in. It drives me nuts.  6.) zink - its SINK dammit SINK! zink! UUUUUGHGHGHGH!  7.) steer - no. steer is a type of bull. 'stir' is what you use if you are 'stirring' something. we will work on this one.  8.) incorrect apostrophes- now you know im a friggin anal grammar nazi. you can imagine the seizures i have when i go to a site that says, "HeYs Yahlls wazzz up ins da hows".&nbsp; if its more than one bagel, its 'bagels' not bagel's. if you put "I have three bagel's" its not even a complete sentence. " 's " is for possession. like "the teacher's cocaine shipment". " s' " is when it belongs to more than one person or thing, like "the girls' marijuana farm".&nbsp; basically my message is simple- either use apostrophes correctly, or just leave them out all together. dont go through the trouble of placing them anywhere they dont belong.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I, Robot - Well! Im a sucker for Will Smith movies, they are usually fast paced, with good action and silly dialogue. The plot was good, the action was great, and I cried when that beautiful Audi got beaten up. sigh. Im sure there were deeper meanings of predjudice and acceptance in it but I thought that was a bunch of crap. They are machines dammit.  Rating (from 1-5)   3 1/2 stars 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went all the way out to Ft Myers to do an open mic last night and I have a feeling I wont be doing that again for awhile. ITs a 2 hr drive speeding,which I was pulled over for by air patrol (planes talk to troopers in cars, silly). The trooper was insanely nice I  thought it was the twilight zone or something. He really let me off the hook, I just have to send in proof of insurance and the $5 , he wanted to know why i was 'in a hurry'. I told him the truth- ive got to get to Ft Myers to a set and Ive never been there. "what kind of set?" oh no, hes going to ask me to tell him a joke isnt he. "a stand up comic set". "you make a lot of money?" "actually im doing this for free". "you a student?" "Yes sir". "ok this is what I will do for you..." wow. im so thankful b/c i seriously did not have the $200 for going 80 something in a 70. so there you have it- for once i dont have to pay an outrageous fine. believe me I have in the past so dont get all "shes a girl and got out of a ticket" because I was sure troopers dont let people off.   the crowd  was small which is fine, but too PC, so some of my slightly off color stuff didnt go over well. i liked orlando a lot better.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoo hoo tonight I sucked! The crowd wasn't too excited to begin with, but I forgot half thats right HALF of my set. I ended it well though. My nervousness is of world record caliber. i saved it, but it was a mediocre night for me.and to make things worse. they laughed at the guy after me who was a psychopath. he hit his head with the microphone, on purpose, and it started to BLEED. and he pretended to be an indian after donning a headdress. i wanted to slit my own throat to save myself from it all. SO except for the dramatic pauses I sprinkled in my set everywhere because I am a dumbass and forgot everything....it was great! Ugh.  i give myself a rating of (from 1-5) : 2, for what the fuck happened? im not even on drugs! 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      BONKERZ orlando- This was my first time at this club, in a lovely Holiday Inn, yeah I am living the high life. In order to beat traffic I went early and boy I see why so many on-the-road comics are into porn on the internet. There is nothing to do in a city you don't know (it was more "Altamonte Spring" than "Orlando". I lived in Orlando for 2 whole months once).  My four minute set yielded 22 good laugh pauses. I think I am getting a lot better. I audiotaped it but it sucks. Since Im going to do the same set tomorrow, I will take the audio from the videotape from there and record it on to the computer. Then the WHOLE WORLD can hear me WOOOOW. OK Im a little whooped. I gots a lot to do tomorrow. Oh, and Ian the open mic MC was surprised I didnt stink up the place,  and said most women comics blow but Ive got something that could make me this generation's female comic. aaaaawe that was so NICE! I hope all this praise doesn't go to my head!  I do like to hear that I dont suck as much as I think I do. I am definitely my worst critic. I keep remembering it might just be the big fish/little pond issue here. I mean, what comics of greatness have come from Florida? just me hahahah yeah right! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      King Arthur - For all the mediocre press its been getting, I thought this movie was pretty good. It was slow at times, and the 'comic relief' banter near the beginning was both too soon and out of place, but the scenes were spectacular, and the music was perfect for the time of the film and the overall movement of the action. I will take a sword and archery  movie over guns any day. It takes some skill to swing those 50 pound beasts around. I appreciated the sheer planning of war scenes. One thing I thought was funny - when Guinevere and Arthur were doing there tiny love scene, I did realize that Clive Owen now knew what it was like to make out with a 15 year old boy. hehehe. The story was solid and the action was great, but the dragging keeps it from a good rating.  rating (from 1-5) : 3 stars 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was taking some IVs to the Burn intensive care unit today when I walked by the waiting room, and noticed someone wrote "your a fag" in either noxema or peppermint pattie filling, that was the consistency of whatever it was, on the glass window. First I thought, dumbass, its 'you're' not 'your', because I am a spelling Nazi. Then I was really irritated at how asinine it was for someone to do this. The BICU is a horrible place in a hospital. A lot of people don't make it out, because they are burned too badly. I am really sure their families appreciate seeing 'your a fag' written on the waiting room glass while their loved one is clinging to life. I washed it off, of course, after I dropped the IVs off. People are such assholes.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Anchorman - Wow, what a disappointment. I know my reviews have been on the negative side lately, but it certainly isn't because of my personal life because that's been great. I really think these summer movies are blowing! Will Ferrell is one of my favorite comedians, but this movie was not full of the laughs I had expected. There were several great classic Ferrell moments, but the movie as a whole was a bust. My favorite part is the 'fight scene' a la West Side Story with Ferrell's channel 4 team and Vince Vaughn's news crew. Other news crews show up and the cameos, familiar from "old school", were pretty fucking hilarious. But that was the best part. All the other great parts you saw on the ads and on the trailer. One incredibly sore spot for me- the camera shots sucked. They were blurry, and not well lit. Unless they were outside, they were crappy shots. Oh well. I guess they used all their money for the writing team. Let me leave you with this- White Chicks was funnier. rating- 2 stars.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from Side Splitters. This is my 6th open mic and my 2nd at side splitters. I am so thankful for the help I've gotten in organizing my ideas. I used to be all over the place and now, I can make smoother transitions. YAY! So I did reeeeally well tonight and the club owner invited me to do a guest spot on Wednesday. Paul, the comic who has been around for awhile and is HILARIOUS, said that this is a HUGE deal, because usually it takes 6 months of open mics before you get asked to guest. So I am really excited. Oh my God I might be able to do this for a living one day! that would be heaven. a really smoky heaven with bad food and watery coke (that is ANY club), but heaven nonetheless.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This movie was mostly a bore. You know you are in trouble when the best part of the movie is all the Cameos. Schwartzenegger, Owen and Luke Wilson, Kathy Bates, Sammo from all the old Jackie Chan Movies, to name a few. Those were the best parts. I give the movie 2 stars.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      White Chicks - This movie was surprisingly good, but ONLY because of Mr. Terry Crews, who played an NBA star named Latrell. I almost died laughing at almost every scene he was in. He keeps trying to woo one of the Wayans (dressed as the white chick), and doesn't stop at anything, including singing some horrible girl song which was HILARIOUS to watch. He was also great in the club scene but I'm not going to give too much away. Keenen Ivory Wayans needs to realize that a plot is not necessary in a Wayans film, yet he half-ass attempts it every time. Just let it be what it IS, Wayans family! Slapstick, rediculous, no thought, sketch comedy! We will appreciate and respect you for it! Don't try to make it REAL! learn from Ben Stiller!  Rating (from 1-5):   1/2 - and all because they cast Terry Crews perfectly. right on.   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      White Chicks - This movie was surprisingly good, but ONLY because of Mr. Terry Crews, who played an NBA star named Latrell. I almost died laughing at almost every scene he was in. He keeps trying to woo one of the Wayans (dressed as the white chick), and doesn't stop at anything, including singing some horrible girl song which was HILARIOUS to watch. He was also great in the club scene but I'm not going to give too much away. Keenen Ivory Wayans needs to realize that a plot is not necessary in a Wayans film, yet he half-ass attempts it every time. Just let it be what it IS, Wayans family! Slapstick, rediculous, no thought, sketch comedy! We will appreciate and respect you for it! Don't try to make it REAL! learn from Ben Stiller!  Rating (from 1-5):   1/2 - and all because they cast Terry Crews perfectly. right on.   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have this one joke and ive got writer's block. can i get some input from you crazy people out there?? here it is: I just got a tattoo. It’s the size of a half dollar. I threw up three times and passed out while I was getting it. It’s the Japanese character for “Endurance”. I think my next tattoo’s going to be the Japanese character for “(blank)". i thought 'comedian' or 'funny' would be great, because this is a self deprecating line (whatever I say in the blank has to be opposite of what I am, like obviously I did not endure that tattoo very well). someone said 'bootylicious', hah. can you think of something?  i was going to see aruond the world in 80 days today- but there were only 3 showings and i was at work the whole time! and the 2 indie movies we have in town look retarded. i wish i, robot would come out already that one looks fun to watch. and has a cool Audi in it. I have an affinity for German cars.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      GOOD NEWS! I rocked the house baby. My set was killer. I've never gotten that many laughs. I need to work on eating the mic more, I'm way too far away from it. I will be finding a way to put the audio on the internet for anyone who wants to hear it. I just need to work on not getting nervous, speaking INTO a microphone instead of around it, and pausing dramatically for better laughs.  I think I shocked the club people. They seemed as if they were sure I was going to blow. hehehe.   as far as deb lafave goes, the teacher who committed lewd and lascivious (sp?) acts on a 14 year old boy... i wonder which one of her Uncles raped her. she looks like someone who would work at Mons Venus, don't you think? Pretty, but inherently Slutballish. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im having technical difficulties! At home all I can do is check AOL. So I wrote my Manchurian candidate review in an email and sent it to myself. but now im at work, and the internet explorer is like version 0.5, so i cant open AOL mail from here! grr! I'll go to USF later and put it all together. Anyone know whats wrong with AOL? I try to go to any website and the window just stays blank, not even an error!   EDIT- ok i found a computer that worked so I could get my review from my email. Here it is!  George... George Bush... George Walker Bush.... Listen....  WOW! Manchurian Candidate has Oscar landslide written all over it. This movie was awesome. It keeps your attention from beginning to end, has just the right amount of suspense without being overantagonizing, and Meryl Streep deserves an Oscar for her� Hilary-Clinton-meets-Lizzie-Borden Senator part. The movies ending was slightly predictable, yet still suspenseful, and the timing of it all was excellent. I could have done without the occasional reverse-Oedipus complex incestual nuances, but other than that it was awesome, the flashbacks were piercing, and it becomes too realistic to describe.  On a funny note, I recognized a strong resemblance of today's incumbent president and cabinet to this movie's plot line. Cheney is Streep's character and it all falls in from there. I wont give away too much.  Rating (from 1-5) : 4
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those who love the comedic gold of Rich Vos, Jim Norton, Patrice O Neal, Robert Kelly and the like, go to the  urlLink Cringe Humor   website. Its informative and has some hilarious interviews, my favorite being the "great hack debate" between Dan Naturman and Patrick Milligan (he runs the site) while being moderated by Robert Kelly and having Keith Robinson make retard remarks in the background and laughing like the wicked witch.   I took more pictures today, but this roll of film just doesn't seem to want to finish up! Matt, I haven't forgotten your liquor store. I will try to get to that one soon. I sent some of my better pictures to BBC.co.uk hoping they would use one in "this week in pictures". We shall see. MSN wont accept any for their site. Cocky American conglomerate. And yes I spelled that right without spell check, believe it or not.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           If I could afford another bill, I would SOOOO get XM! Its only $2 a month though I probably can handle that. These guys are hilarious.  So I am driving down the road in lovely  Pasco County [read: 4x4 trucks bigger than their homes], and I happen upon a billboard that looks, loosely, like this one:   .    I made that, thats why it looks ghetto. I do not understand my photoshop. Anyway, first off, this kook's name sounds like a national holiday for masturbaters worldwide. Second, Vote for my day in COURT??? who the hell wants to be IN COURT?? who came up with this slogan!Someone who got PAID to, thats who! i cant believe it! oh wait yes i can this is FLORIDA. bass ackwards, USA. Typical non partisan!   One more thing. I found this person grading childrens pictures on a site and saying horrible things about them that were HILARIOUS. Here is my favorite:     Ding Ding! Here comes the shit-mobile. I've never seen a fire truck that needed to be shaved. I would rather be burned to death than be saved by this hairy piece of shit. F   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did Coconuts St Pete last night and killed an audience of 9 paying customers and at least 15 comedians. Its hard to make comics laugh b/c they're so busy thinking about their own shit. I had an awesome time and im doing sidesplitters tonight. im not SUCKING for once YESSSS! Oh and Im super thrilled Opie and Anthony are going to be on XM because as far as I know, that means I will get to hear them.  EDIT: IT is 10pm ,and i did AWESOME at sidesplitters! I am rocking this week. Not NYC quality yet of course but I definitely am getting there, slowly! They made me go first, which is hardest, because the MC barely warms them up. I got it on DVD and my friend Robert might help me attempt to put it online, if not i will put the audio online. I fumbled in a few places from nerves and I spoke too fast, which is a big mistake with this expander in my mouth. No one appreciated the insanity of my dead puppy in a chilled glass joke, so its 1 for 1 at the moment. Other than that I killed AGAIN! YEEEAH! People were laughing and there were at least 100 people there. I wish I could have stayed but I was falling asleep at the wheel trying to get to the club from all the late nights. SO I am off to bed! zzzzzzz
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from Bonkerz. Man, If I-4 wasnt so FUBARed, It wouldnt take7 hours of my time. It took 2 1/2 hours to get to a place an 1 1/2 away, then 2 1/2 hours to get BACK home, plus the 2 we spent at the club, and we didnt even get to stay and see everyone do their thing. I love going there, because the guys are great and actually funny, and very supportive, but the crowd is really a captive audience. Its in a Holiday Inn near nothing so they dont have much of a choice :( . I tried some new jokes out but i forgot the beer one. Here it is for your enjoyment:  Have you ever gone to Busch Gardens [home of Budweiser besides St Louis, for those who may not be familiar] and ordered a Miller Lite just for fun? They glare at you like you just asked for a dead puppy in a chilled glass!  ok its sick but sometimes you just gotta go with it!  Im going to Coconuts tonight after i practice my set a billion times. Im going to have more pics soon too! Can you tell Im getting a little overworked here in the practice room @ USF ??    One more thing. I am not very happy with a few of my friends. For their protection, I will call them ERIC AND LORI from work.      Not only did Eric keep throwing trash out my window which I HATE with a passion (im a recycling earth friendly person! dont throw shit out the damn window!), they are messy drunks. I love my car more then some men do. Its my baby. These dingdongs got so drunk they spilled half their captain and cokes (yeah they were drinking in my car grrrrrr) all over, and crushed up those damned multicolored pepperidge farm goldfish during their shenanigans. Now my car smells like Captain Morgan and is decorated with a rainbow of salty snacks. I feel like a homosexual puerto rican driving around now.     IM MAD THAT MY CAR STINKS LIKE RUM!!!!! YOU GUYS SUCK!!!!!  WEDNESDAY 9:48 AM  The great part about falling asleep again only to wake up 2 hours later, if there is a great part, is you usually get a hilarious dream. I dreamed that my brother in law got a metal detector and made me follow him up to UT to use it. Then this guy who Ive said maybe 3 words to in my life, Antony, gets out of this strech limo surrounded by black cop cars, with a giant, cartoon like blunt in his hand, And hes dressed in like Roman Empire Kingwear LTD or something, robes and shit. Then his parents get out, each with a 5th, and hugs him goodbye (I guess he was going off to be king of UT). There was more to the story but i forgot it all by the time I wrote all that. I need a mind recorder. It was so weird and retarded!   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          So This is at USF ARTS department where I used to go to school (LONG story for later). Its a wood sculpture done by the students. Im going to Bonkerz tonight to practice more for my Thursday open mic. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Todays Topic ! Anorexia. Special thanks to  urlLink AriAna82  for reminding me how many millions of unhappy women there are in this world. Im going to do the best I can to keep from being preachy. But today, I accidentally ran into all the secretive Ana and Mia people by finding  urlLink AriAna82's  site. Granted, starving yourself can make you lose weight pretty fast. But when you get to the point where you can watch your food digest, there is a serious, horrible mental disorder taking over your life. I had a friend ultimately die from it, and i see them in our psych ward all the time. This is an issue that needs to be addressed, but it never is because you cannot control a person. I wish these women, and a few of these men, that were starving themselves to look like models and movie stars would instead become more confident in themselves and what they have to offer others in this world with their mind and personality. That whats on the outside is not that fucking important, no matter what MTV says. Youre thinking, "yeah, fat ugly girl telling us its the inside that counts". I would say "go screw yourself" but its already happening. Im extremely concerned for all of you with an eating disorder and I hope you get help. If you want help I will get it for you no matter what. Here is a self help website for those of you who think that we are all out to destroy you, maybe you can get the cajones to help yourself:  urlLink ANRED  And, if you aren't Ana or Mia, and if you happen upon these Ana and Mia girls' weblogs and think, wow its working for them, i should do it too... please, dont. You will end up in the deep end of the pool of psycho. You know what scares me the most? How they trounce around online and try to make it glamourous. When they take photos all together, I cant tell if its a concentration camp or a daycare in Ethiopia. You dont see schizophrenics trying to come up with cutesy little names and forming blogrings and the like "supporting" each other to be mental and not get help. Its such an attention tactic. looks like i got preachy. my bad. I am, by nature, controversial. OK! on to my MOVIE OF THE DAY!   Today I saw Napoleon Dynamite, and this movie kind of goes along with my anorexia being a problem part of my entry. I think the main moral here is "Be yourself". Theres not much of a plot to the movie besides being in high school and being a geek that doesnt even hack computers. Napoleon is your typical Dungeons and Dragons nerd, and its great to watch. I support renting it for sure. The characters are all well thought out, and I wish I could describe every single one. THeres a lot to look at and think about. My bright spot was "Deborah" played by Tina Majorino, a geek as well, but cute and not beating herself up that she isnt popular. Shes focused, intelligent, and adorable. SHes me when I was in high school, haha. My favorite part with her is when Napoleon's Uncle Rico, a tupperware hawker, is also trying to sell "natural" herb enhancements for larger breasts to her and said "Napoleon said youd be interested". She calmly called Napoleon (who did not even say she was interested, Uncle Rico was just being an ass) and said "I just wanted you to know you are a shallow friend. I dont need Herbal Enhancers to feel good about myself." It was great. YOU GO DEB! Napoleons big pick up line to her was "I see you are drinking 1% milk. Is it because you think you are fat?? Because youre not. You could drink whole milk quite easily."  Her side ponytail and stirrup pants and all the jewelry brought back memories *sniff* i will have to scan some '80s pics of me if i can find them. i was like 8 years old, but still looked like them. Pedro Sanchez was awesome (Efran Ramirez). He delivered his lines with classic Mexican style. I especially loved all the Jesus and mary statues, pictures, and candles in his house. So stereotypical, yet painfully realistic. The hydraulic Vote 4 Pedro car his homies drove was excellent. THe Pinata that looked like Summer Wheatley (playing the pretty annoying chick didnt seem like to much of a stretch for Haylie Duff, whose talent fits directly into my Prince collection-someones trying to ride coattails...wow im old to use that phrase) was genius. I noticed that the "happy hands club" used Backstreet Boys "larger than life" in the skit and so i got a little confused, is this movie in the 80s or 2000s? i think they just felt that particular song was appropriate. This movie is too much to try to explain. I just want a "Vote for Pedro" T shirt and some moon boots now. some great lines in this movie could have been catch phrases if more people had seen it. Here are my favorite phrases and lines: "BOW TO YOUR SENSAI!" "Theres a lot of gangs here. They all wanted me because Im pretty good with a bo staff." "Jes." and " somsing". "its a sledgehammer." "you caught like three feet of air that time." "I already get my hair cut at the Cotton Corral." Rating (from 1-5) :  3-  theres alot more to this movie than meets the eye. But I dont get paid to break it down so Im not going to try. footnote: Hey if movies that involve regular looking people keep popping up, I may just get a career! 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright. I just took 2 rolls of film to the Walgreens 1-hour photo, so, in 2 hours I will have more photos to post. I am sure this has been visited numerous times, but they should change their "1 hour photo" name in the spirit of defraudulization ( i think i made that word up). Its either 45 minutes, or 2 hours. Ive never gotten photos in an hour. I reorganized my set to get ready for the big 'graduation' show we are doing next tuesday. I get 7 minutes which is cool. Jaime is taping it on DVD too which will be nifty. I might even find a way to put the video feed online. maybe. EDIT: PICTURE TIME! Here is me in my car. I used the timer. This is not exactly a poetic photo but I laughed at it. My friends at the sidesplitters Comedy club. We are all comedy geeks. Chris, Geoff with a G, Jym, Phil, someone new I dont know, lets call him "luke, only taller", and Dan.   This is Jym Gray. Rather fine photography if i do say so myself. Go, Fuji Discovery 35mm no zoom no focus! Those japanese are so innovative, like asian McGyvers!  In the Gan Shalom cemetery. Who takes photos in a cemetery? The same people who use it as a dog park, thats who!   . 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I just saw The Bourne Supremacy and it was GREAT! Im not a huge Matt Damon fan, but he does a great action dude. The first one was good, but Id say this one was better. I was never once bored or lost interest. The director had the perfect bounce- some movies overdo the blair witch effect, but Bourne was just enough to make it exciting without nauseating the audience. I like how there was no love story too, hehe. And, Im a car dork, I loved the BMW 700s they had in Moscow. Now, Ive been to eveyrwhere they went for this movie, which was cool because I recognized some things. Correct me if I am wrong though. BUt the Moscow train station looked like the real Berlin Hauptbahnhopf to me. I may look it up sometime and find out which sets were on location and which ones were fake. I do recognize the map though, that he tried to follow while driving in that MASSIVE car chase that was FREAKING AWESOME near the end. ITs in the trailers. Anyways I hate how all the roads are YELLOW on german maps. Oh, and the Berlin they had was awfully German. It seemed so much more Russian to me when I was there, because of the war. I caught a possible mistake, but Im probably wrong. In the very beginning, where the 2 guys were in Berlin, the special ops guy said something in English. I thought he was supposed to be pretending to be Russian. Oh who cares it was AWESOME go see it. Rating (from 1-5)    
</post>


</Blog>