<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I wish I didn't have to work.  More to the point I wish I didn't have to work with irritating, lazy children who are more interested in talking to their matesa nd recovering from hangovers than in actually doing what they are supposed to be doing.  I was fuming this morning, and seriously considering taking up smoking again just so I could have a fag break every half hour like one colleague I was supposedly working with.  I'm not getting at Brian and Joan who work their arses off every day, but because it was bank holiday we had all the young student lads and girls in, and to be frank, they just can't be bothered, and it really pisses me off.  Even when I was a student and thought, 'it's only a part time job til I finish college', I worked hard, I did my best, I tried to be as helpful and concientious as possible.  These guys don't seem to give a shit when they let people down and turn up late and then do no work when they do turn up.  And two of these lads are supervisiors.  It makes me really angry and frustrated.  Grrrr.  Things to be grateful for: 1.  Getting out of work an hour early 2.  Being able to put my point across that some of the staff are not doing their jobs properly (not telling tales, just suggesting that the boss has a word with people about rotating old and new stock, I ain't a snitch.) 3.  Going to the pub.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Well, I came back.  I had a truly dreadful day at work today.  For starters I couldn't get in when I arrived because the guy that had the keys was twenty minutes late, Me and Joan ended up having to walk down to his house in the end where he was just coming out of the front door.  Consequently I was behind all day, and because the Kwik Save up the road is closed cos they're converting it to a Somerfield, it's been horrendously busy.  At least I didn't burn the bread.  I did have hundreds of reductions to do tho, because it's the end of the month, and the majority of products have best before end codes on them.  By the time I'd finished the reductions, it was nearly 2.30 and I hadn't had my lunch yet.  Hopefully next sunday won't be as hectic, but I'm not counting on it. I looked through the paper for jobs when I got in, and there is nothing.  Nothing that I'd consider doing or have the qualifications for anyway.  I wish I'd left school at sixteen and gone into a crappy office junior, filing and making tea kinda job, cos I'd be earning about four times as much as I am by now, and I wouldn't have all my student debts.  Anyone who may be reading this who is considering going to university...Don't, unless it's for something that needs a degree for you to do it, they are a waste of time and money.  I have a degree, but I have no relevent life skills, so no one decent wants to employ me, so I'm stuck doing a low paid retail job.  People keep saying 'oh you're intelligent, you could do anything', but it's just not true, I may be fairly intelligent, but having a brain isn't anything when it comes to getting a job.  So much for my dreams of having a house of my own and a dog and being happy.  I guess I'll end up living with my mum and dad for the rest of my life... Things to be grateful for: 1.  Not burning the bread 2.  4pm when the shop shut 3.  Having parents to spend the rest of my life with.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I didn't write anythong to be grateful for last night, because quite frankly, I didn't feel like I HAD anything to be grateful for.  I'm feeling better today, my head is a bit clearer and I'm thinking better.  But I didn't get much sleep last night so I'm grumpy.  Hopefully things will keep on getting better now that I've started taking my nerbal happy pills again.  Hopefully I will also be able to get my head out of my arse and stop upsetting people albeit unintentionally.  I may be back later to add to this, then again I may not...
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Sitting on the bus today, I passed some fly posters with the words 'Shout GOURANGA, Be Happy' on them.  It made me laugh in a really bitter and cynical way.  The people that posted those bits of paper really and truly believe that shouting some wierd word can make you happy.  It doesn't work.  At the moment things seem to be going from bad to worse.  Everything I say or do is misunderstood, when I say something it seems to have hidden barbs in it, even though I don't mean it to.  I don't want to hurt anyone, but I do.     I wish I could make things right with the people I love.  I wish I could make them understand what's going on in my head and how I really feel.  I find it hard to put into words, and I'm afraid of hurting them, so I stay silent, and my silence only pushes them further away.  When I do talk, I can't seem to express what I mean very well, and so things often come out wrong, meanings get confused and people are hurt by what I say, even though it wasn't meant to hurt.  There is so much I want to say, so much I want to explain, and I'm afraid that it's too late, that things have been said that can't be unsaid, and the things I want to say, the time has passed to say them.   I feel like I've burned my bridges and there's no going back, no matter how hard I want to or wish to, I feel like the decision is out of my hands now, and my happiness depends on someone elses choices.  All I can do now is hope that I'm wrong, that I'll have one more chance to sort things out.   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I didn't do an entry last night, for a couple of reasons... I went to the pub, and when I got back I was so tired and miserable I went straight to bed and nearly went to sleep.  In the end I wrote a story, thats always a bad sign, when I'm being creative, that means I'm miserable, haven't started writing poems yet tho, so it can't be all that bad.  No one is ever going to read this story ever tho.  It was very depressing and ended up with everyone dying, so I read it through, and then destroyed it.  The bin is probably the best place for it.  I would have burned it, but knowing me I'd have burned the house down too.  I didn't have a lot to be grateful for last night.  I haven't got a lot to be grateful for tonight either.  Life sucks when you're miserable, and only seem to be capable of hurting everyone around you, especially the people you love the most.  It doesn't matter how much I apologise or try to explain, I don't think I'm ever going to be able to undoe the damage I did last night.  I stopped taking my happy pills, which on reflection was a very silly thing to do.  I don't want to be happy just because of some herbal happy pills, I want to be happy because I am happy, not because my brain is being chemically altered.  I suppose it will take time, for now I've started taking the pills again, because even herbal happiness is better than depression.  I hope I will be able to rebuild the bridges I started to burn last night.  I need to be able to fix things, because I can't live my life knowing I threw away happiness because I couldn't be happy.  If that makes sense. I'll try for 3 things to be grateful for today: 1.  Weetabix, cos it's easy and filling. 2.  Writing, because I can get all of my frustrations out on paper and analyse my thoughts and feelings and try to work through them. 3.  Still being alive this morning (although I don't know whether to be grateful for that or not...it remains to be seen)  Incidentally, if you read this Pete...Please don't disappear.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Well, I say lighter, it's mainly just my three things to be grateful for, tho my fish tank is looking less cloudy, and I had a good day at work. Three things to be grateful for today: 1.  The boss being off. 2.  Being on time despite the bus being late. 3.  finding all my fish still alive this morning.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I was reading the local paper in my lunch half-hour today, just flicking through really to while away the minutes until I could go back to doing my job (because it's such an exciting and invigorating job!).  There was a letter from a girl who was replying to one published the previous week which I remember reading from a lady who was basically complaining about the 'Youth of Today'.  This girl was sixteen, and was quite rightly pointing out to everyone that it is not the majority of youths that cause problems and vandalise property, but a very small minority.  She also put forward a very valid point indeed:  That everyone is born into the world helpless, and that we are shaped into the people we become by looking up to our supposed elders and betters, basically, that no matter how hard the older generations complain about the behaviour of younger generations, it is ultimately their responsibility for the examples they have set and the way they have brought up their children.  I know other factors are heavily involved in how people develop and howthey 'turn out', but this letter struck a chord with me and I found myself agreeing with a lot of what the girl said.  The younger generations get blamed for a lot of ills in the world, and a lot of what they take the rap for isn't necessarily their (our) fault.  I do think that maybe the blame lies somewhere in between.  I see a lot of children (working in retail as I do) who have little or no manners, and no respect for property or person.  Invariably the parents of these children have no disciplinary skills, they let their children run riot, if the child wants sweets and the mother or father says 'no', the child will pester the parent until he or she gives in.  Equally tho I see parents who rule over their children with an 'iron rod' of swearing and threats.  I cringe when I hear parents screaming at their children, I know my mum never had to scream at me, a quiet word and a look was enough to know that I'd done wrong.  I think that there is a middle road when it comes to parenting, don't get me wrong, most parents do a fantastic job, and it is only the minority that I am talking about here, I know that I couldn't do it, certainly not yet, probably not ever.  I also think that as each generation grows up and produces their own kids, they think 'I'm not going to treat my kids the way my mum and dad treated me.'  I know I did when I was about 16 or so.  I have grown up a lot since then and I realise the need for disipline.  If I do ever have children I will try my hardest to bring them up with manners, and a respect for people and property.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Another day in work has passed, and I'm already forgetting that I had a holiday last week.  The days are going quite quickly tho, so it's not too bad.  I wish I had a different job though.  I also wish I could sort out my fish tank, I don't know whats wrong with it, I'm doing everything the man in the shop told me to, but now the water's gone all cloudy and it's starting to smell.  I don't think the fish are too impressed, I did another water change today, but the water is still cloudy, and another fish died.  Maybe I'm just not meant to have fish.  I will persevere, and if it's no better by saturday I'll go back to the shop and ask their advice. Hopefully the fish will last until then :-(   I lost my purse today, fortunately I hadn't lost it anywhere bad, I'd just left it on the dining room table, but I got a fright when I opened my bag at lunchtime and found it wasn't there, I worried about it all day as well, it's a horrible feeling.  I had a nasty feeling I'd left it in the pub last night, but then I remembered that I'd had to take it out of my bag to get to my phone last night, and I reckoned I'd just forgotten to put it back.  And there it was, laughing at me when I got home...    It's payday on thursday, and sometime this week I'm planning to go and see The Day After Tomorrow, although I have heard it's had some bad reviews despite all the really great adverts.  Ah well, we can go and see for ourselves and make our own minds up.  Thats it for today I'm afraid, didn't do anything exciting so I'm just wittering to myself...and you.  Things to be grateful for today: 1.  The boss not shouting at me when I was half an hour late because of the buses and roadworks. 2.  Getting home earlier than usual because I was lucky with the buses (obviously not in the morning) 3.  Finding that my Siamese Fighting Fish was looking better despite the nasty tank water, I'd expected it to be dead several times over the last few days.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wow.  I've been doing html, and I'm quite impressed with myself, because I've never done it before.  You see all those links down the side of the page??  I did those!  Ok so I did have a lot of help from Mart, and it wasn't all that difficult once I got into it, but still, I'm proud of myself for even attempting it, instead of running away and either leaving it as it was, or getting someone to do it for me.  That's one to me I think.  Well it was my first day back at work today, and surprisingly it wasn't too bad.  Everyone seemed in a good mood for once, even the boss, and the day went quite quickly.  We have some new staff too, one of whom was in today, he seems quite nice, tho I didn't really have a chance to speak to him all that much.  I just hope that all the new staff doesn't mean that my hours will be cut, because if they are, I will have to find a new job pretty sharpish, I can just about afford to survive on what I'm earning now, provided I don't try and leave home again!    Well all this exciting html stuff has left me a bit tired so I think I will leave it for tonight.  Things to be grateful for: 1.  Martin's help with the html 2.  Happy work colleagues 3.  My own determination to master even the simple bits of the html  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, here I am again, trying a different site for my online journal.  I found that LiveJournal wasn't all that good really, and AOL is still not working.  Mart suggested blogger.com, so here I am, and I have to say that it seems a lot easier and better to use than livejournal. Today I have had a wonderful relaxing and peaceful day, the last day of my hols.  I spent it wandering aimlessly around bits of the Wirral with Pete, my fella.  It is going to be one of those times that sticks in my head forever.  Sitting on the sandstone formations at Thurstaston with Pete, with the sun warming my face, and the wind blowing my hair, just watching the trees waving in the breeze and the clouds scudding across the incredibly blue sky, I felt so happy and peaceful I didn't want to move on.  But we did, I had to go home eventually.  Now I am home, and I realise that I should have taken some sun cream with me, because I'm decidedly sunburned, and the cardigan I'm wearing because of the chill, is irritating it slightly.  I looked in the mirror about ten minutes ago and my nose is all pink, and my top has left me with stripes on my shoulders and a big pink V on my chest.  There's even a little white spot where my pendant was lying.  :::sigh:::  Looks like I'll have to get out the aftersun.  I realised while I was out that I forgot to take my happy pill again this morning.  When I mentioned it to Pete he said: 'How do you feel?'  I guess I didn't need it today, The first day that I've been properly happy without the pills for a long time.  I hope this is a turn of the corner and things will continue to get better.  Even if it isn't, I have today to look back on and think 'this is how I can be if I give myself time and encouragement.'  Its something to strive for at least. Three things to be grateful for today: 1.  The feel of the wind in my hair. 2.  Cute friendly dogs. 3.  Fantastic all day breakfasts  and one more for good measure... 4.  Knowing I'm loved and that I love in return
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I realised that though I write a lot of stuff on here, many of you won't know a hell of a lot of details about me as a person.  I know my profile doesn't say a lot, and thats the way I like it really, I like to be quiet and enigmatic, but now I feel it's time to come clean about a few things.   The two main things about me that people don't get to know straight off is a) I'm a diabetic, and b) I'm bisexual.  The bisexual thing most people get first, cos I'm prone to dropping some heavy hints  (usually along the lines of 'cor she's cute', or 'I'd do her!' maybe not quite so vulgar, but you get the idea).  The Diabetes thing is something I've lived with for more years than I like to remember, I was diagnosed at 17 months old, and I'm now nearly twenty six, so you can do the maths if you want, I really can't be bothered ;-)  My GP at the time, told my mother she was being neurotic and there was nothing wrong with me, I was 'only teething' apparently.  Fortunatley my Mum ignored him and got a second opinion or my life could have been much different, shorter for one.  Anyway, being diabetic sucks for the most part.  I kinda have it under control most of the time, but as with everything there's good days and bad days.  My addiction to cream cakes doesn't do it much good, but I've tried to cut it down to one a week ;-)   I hate being labelled, I am not 'a diabetic', I am a PERSON with diabetes.  I know I'm usually quite scathing about political correctness, but this is one instance where the PC lobby are right, just because you have a disability or an illness, doesn't make you that disability or illness, you're still a person, I'm still a person, just because I have a problem with my health...  :::gets off soap box:::  It's kinda the same with the bisexual thing being bisexual isn't the be-all and end-all, there are other aspects to my personality.   I first suspected I 'wasn't quite right' in school, probably about fifteen.  It scared the hell out of me, I wanted to be 'normal' like the other kids, but never really fitted in anyway with most of the other kids at my school.  It was at college that I finally accepted in myself that I was attracted to women and men, but even then I was afraid of people's reactions to it, and I didn't come out for ages.  I vividly remember the first person I told.  I'm not sure why I did then, other than the fact that I was a little bit drunk and needed to talk to someone.  I was pleasantly surprised by peoples reactions (tho as yet I haven't found a way of telling my mum and dad, there's not really any need for them to know while I'm seeing Pete), Everyone was really supportive and just took it in their stride.  A couple of people were surprised, but others just smiled like they'd known all along.  I'm happy in myself now that I can be open about it.  I don't know if that was my problem when I was in school and college...repressing how I felt, and not being able to talk to anyone because of fear, I felt so much better when I got it into the open...      Ahh I feel like I'm waffling now, ad I've probably said too much and bored you all.  Depending how I feel tomorrow about what I've said tonight there may be more, then again I may be too embarrassed for bearing my soul like that and never come back ;-)  Things to be grateful for... 1.  Beechams Powders 2.  Bacon crispies. 3.  Honesty and openess
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I'm not feeling so good today.  Felt a bit grotty all day, and then came home and fell asleep.  Only just got up now :-(   Hopefully I'll feel better in the morning.  I don't like being not well, it makes me miserable as well, but I'm fighting it :::go kate!:::  Anyway, baby fishes are still looking good :-)  Things to be grateful for... 1.  Work not being to busy today 2.  Bacon flavour pot noodles cos I couldn't be arsed making real food when I woke up 3.  Weetabix, for the same reason.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I feel a bit of a bitch.  I landed Aaron in trouble today.  Yes, the guy is a lazy so and so, and I was really pissed off at him yesterday when he was chatting to his mates instead of working like he was supposed to..he is after all a supervisor, and not a pleb like me and Jo.  I told the manager what he'd been up to today, this wasn't something I did lightly, I'm not the kind of person that goes round snitching on people, but the boss was having a grump at me for various things that weren't my fault because I spent most of the dat doing stuff that would have taken five minutes if Aaron hadn't been pissing about and had got off his arse and helped.  Joan, agreed with what I'd said.  She said it wasn't fair that Aaron was getting away with stuff, and talking to his mates, arranging his social life, sitting in the office on his phone, while me and Jo were working and trying to hold the shop together.  I still feel a bit guilty tho, even though it's me that gets the grump attacks from Bob on a monday morning when things haven't been done.  I usually get on alright with Aaron, but the sunday situation can't go on.  It's as simple as that.  I get really stressed out on a sunday when it's busy, and I'm trying to do the jobs that I need to do, and I'm not getting any help, and then I get stressed out on monday when the boss starts grumbling.  He say's it's not aimed at me, but I'm one of those people that take things personally, even if theyre not aimed at me.  :::sigh:::  I hope this will sort things out, either Aaron will pull his finger out, or Bob will find someone else to do the supervising on a sunday.  Things to be grateful for... 1.  Baby fish still doing well after 3 days...  :::crosses fingers more tightly::: 2.  Orange Reef 3.  Cuddling up to my Pete
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        ::::Grins:::::  Well I don't know what that was for, but I like it. Went to see Shrek 2 yesterday...for those who haven't seen it, GO SEE IT!  It's great.  I think it might even be funnier than the first one if that's possible. I didn't come back yesterday, as you may have noticed ;-) reason being we decided to go and meet a friend, and we ended up staying out til 1am...tsk, another late night.  I can guarantee there won't be many ore of them this month...I'm trying to conserve my money a bit more so I don't get over-overdrawn again.  We had fun tho, apart from the walking through the scary bits of birken head at nearly midnight.  Was certainly interesting, like something out of a horror movie.   I'm currently listening to my The Calling album.  It's a good album, I especially like 'Wherever you may go', which was the first song they released and what made me buy the album in the first place, and 'Unstoppable', oh and 'Adrienne', but only because I wrote a story by the same name once.  Things to be grateful for... 1.  'Unstoppable', because it reminds me of how I feel when I'm with Pete. 2.  Great nights out. 3.  Sprouts.  :::looks at everyone's expression of confusion:::  What??!!  I like sprouts...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I have come to the conclusion that fish are not very bright at all.  I have just had babies.  Not me personally, one of my fish I mean...I noticed that one of them was looking quite fat and pregnantish (and thats a real word too  ;-)  ), so I took her out and put her in this little floating tank thing.  It's got a bit that goes in the bottom that has little slats in so that when the mother has babies, they drop through so she can't get to them and scoff them.  Unfortunately, it doesn't stop the babies from trying to swim up through the slats.  When I noticed them last night I had 3 babies, about half an hour later there was one left and mother was looking very unhungry  :-(  There wasn't a lot I could do about it, if they had been born in the main tank they'd have been et by the rest of the fish, so they stood a better chance in the breeding tank thing.  I turned the light off and left them to it, I can't watch the poor little buggers getting eaten by their cannabalistic mother.  This morning when I took her out and put her back in the main tank, there were two baby fish hiding in the bottom of the floating thing.  They look marginally happier now there is no chance of being eaten.  I don't know how long they will last, the last time I had babies, I rescued about 20 of them out of the main tank and managed to rear one of them.  He died when I had my tank problems a few months ago, and I got really upset when the other fish ate him.  It's a cruel, cruel world.    Anyway, I'm going out to watch Shrek 2 with my fella.  I may be back later, with baby fish developments, then again I may not...
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        My regular readers may be wondering where I was yesterday.  My best mate came back from Southampton for a couple of days so we decided to go out, watch the footie and then get pissed.     The football?  Heh, do I need to say anything?  Disallowed goals and that penalty from Beckham....have had a few amusing emails about that.  Has anyone else noticed the distinct lack of england car flags around in the last 24 hours???  To be honest, I find it all a little amusing, although I do think that maybe we were a little unfairly treated in the matter of the disallowed goal...thats football though.     As to the dancing, well, I did get a little bit drunk last night.  We went to the Krazy House in Liverpool, it's a fantastic club, and it feels like home everytime I walk in there.  After one redbull and aftershock, and several bottles of reef, I was dancing like a loon and having a thoroughly good time.  At the end of the night I was being an aeroplane (running round the dance floor with my arms out making vroom noises) to the tune of Purple Haze, I was quite drunk.  Fortunately happy drunk not sad drunk.  A good night was had by all, all my mates said I provided some great entertainment value.  I'm not sure how to take that :-)   I think I may have overdone it a little on the 'dancing' front tho, I wasn't too bad when I got up to go to work this morning (at 8am!!!  I didn't get in til 3.30am), but now my spine feels like it's been removed, stamped on a bit, twisted, attacked with a sledgehammer and then put back the wrong way up.  In other words I've given myself minor whiplash from moshing too much, oh and I feel like I've been eating glass, from the way my throat feels.  But hey, I don't care.  The only down side to the evening was the fact my fella couldn't make it.  I realised when I was there that it was the first time in nearly two years that I'd been to the Krazy house without him.  It felt wierd.  Things to be grateful for... 1.  The oain that tells me I'm too old for crazy dancing ;-) 2.  Seeing my best mate again for the first time in 6 months 3.  Realising that no matter how long we don't see eachother for, when we do, it's like she's never been away.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Lovely weather we're having for october.  Shame it's actually June.  The air outside is a maelstrom of howling wind and driving rain, and forgive me if that sounds a little melodramatic, but after standing at a bus stop for nearly forty five minutes in said maelstrom, I think I'm entitled to call it that.  Bloody Wimbledon.  Because that is what it is that's causing this weather...tennis, there's something about men and women smacking defenseless rubber balls around with raquets that angers the weather gods I think.   Ah well, I'm home now, and dry and warm, so I can't really complain anymore.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I'm feeling a little better now.  Blogs are great for venting some of that nasty, evil mood.  I'm not as miserable either, although I'm not happy as such.  Ah well, life goes on.  Things to be grateful for... 1.  I didn't get rained on coming home from work 2.  I checked my balance BEFORE going to the pub, and therefor didn't get ven more over-overdrawn 3.  Pete still loves me.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I am in need of a hug.  Don't you just just hate rude old people?  I had one customer today who is the nastiest, rudest woman I have ever met, she throws her shopping at you, throws her money at you and never says please or thank you.  She wanted a bottle of gin today and instead of saying 'could I have a bottle of gin please?' like most normal people, she flicked her finger at me and said 'Gin' like I was some kind of stupid, freak not worth speaking to.  Snotty bitch.  The two women in the queue behind her were laughing, probably at my very carefully immobile expression.  They could tell I was fuming.  It really makes me mad when these old baggages come in with no manners and expect to be treated with the same respect as the nice, polite people.  Respect is earned, and I'm sorry but if they are going to treat me like shit, they don't get any respect from me, I don't care how old they are, it doesn't make them right and it doesn't gve them the right to speak to me like that.  In contrast we have a little old lady that comes in, she turned one hundred last week, she can't see very well, and she is the lovliest person you could ever meet, you would do anything for her, and she is polite and grateful for any help.     Despite the evil old woman, I was in quite a good mood today, until I checked my bank balance.  I'm over my overdraft limit.  Don't know how I managed it because I thought I had a bit left in my account, but there you go.  You work 40 hours a week and you can't fucking afford to live.  What is the point???  I'm really pisssed off and miserable and I don't really give a shit about anything any more.  Sorry about the language, but as you can see I'm not in the best of moods  Things to be grateful for?  Not fucking likely.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Some one said something last night in sci fi chat.  I think he was joking but it made me think a bit about how I react to life and stuff.  I'd been in the room the night before and been a bit down about life and work and stuff, and had a bit of a moan and a grumble.  Last night tho I was happy and cheerful and bouncy and well, yes I suppose a little bit manic.  Not for any particular reason, in fact I can't place why I was so happy, just glad I was.  Anyway this guy just commented on how different I seemed from the night before.  'Where's the depression from last night?', I just smiled and said it had gone.  And then he asked if I was a manic depressive, just in a jokey way, not seriously, but it did make me think.  I don't think I do suffer from manic depression, when I'm happy I'm not usually manically happy, and I don't usually get really depressed, tho I have very occasionally in the past.  I can see how people might see me that way tho, I can be happy one day or hour or minute and down the next, but I think that is all part of being alive, part of being human?  Does anyone else know what I mean?   Later on I was tlaking to Mart about death and grieving for lost loved ones, and he said that sometimes you have to go a little mad just to stay sane.  That is so true.  When my Nan died I don't think I went mad, I needed to because I wasn't there with my family on the night she died.  I was staying over at my boyfriend's house.  I'd been to see her in hospital that evening, and she was looking better, so I went to his flat instead of going home with my mum and dad.  My Nan died in the early hours of the following morning, Valentines Day, and I will never forget the phone call from my Dad that woke me up.  I feel guilty that I wasn't there with my mum  when she went to the hospital, I feel like I should have gone home that night, not to Pete's.  There is nothing I can do about it now, I can't change the past, and I am grateful that Pete was there for me to hold me and comfort me when I was distraught.  Things to be grateful for... 1. Family 2. Pete, I love him more than words can express :-) 3. Madness that keeps you sane.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Why?  Just because I like them.  I got some going cheap in work today, AND there's still some left!!   Hmm what to write??  Aaron was only ten minutes late for work today, so thats better than the hour and a half he was late last week.  It seems the co-op is safe for a while yet, nobody has been notified of any development plans, so we've still got a chance.  I'm still going to look for a new job tho, if only becaue this one is mind numbingly, brain meltingly boring, that and the heavy lifting and constant standing around isn't doing my back, knees and shoulder any good...:::sigh::: I'm falling to pieces.  Things to be grateful for... 1.  Ferrero Rocher 2.  Cheesy pasta and tuna 3.  Fruit pastilles - they always seem to cheer me up!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        As you might have guessed I've just been to see HP and the Prisoner of Azkaban.  It's not bad, I didn get the feeling that they missed huge chunks out of it tho, I can't remember which bits because I haven't read the book for a while, it just didn't seem to flow right when I was watching it.   On the way home I was standing in the bus station, and this group of girls came in, probably just been to see the same film, and they looked about 12.  Unfortunately they were dressed about 18.  It scares me when I see things like that, they were all wearing short skirts and boots and far too much make up, and don't forget this is at 10.30 at night.  My mum wouldn't have let me out on my own at that time, when I was their age, I was running around in jeans and t-shirts and trainers, not tottering around in heels and mini skirts!  People wonder why there are more paedophiles around than ever before, I'm sure that dressing kids up as little mini adults can't be helping, and it frightens me.  On a slightly lighter note, there was a bloke on the bus wearing a t-shirt...it made me grin like a loon, it said...  'I'm going to close my eyes when we kiss and pretend you're a pint of boddingtons'  Heh heh heheheh
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I went in Burger King for my lunch today, seeing as I was down town buying stuff.  I decided to try one of their new chicken caesar bagels.  I have to say it was much nicer than I thought it was going to be.  I'd even go as far as to say that it was the nicest burger I've had all week.  Come to think of it, it was the only burger I've had all week, but that doesn't make the statement any less valid.  The chicken was moist and chargrilled to perfection and the salad was fresh, there was just enough caesar dressing on it, yup it was a good burger.     After Burger King I went on to do a bit more shopping, and as I was walking past WHSmith's, the heavens opened, literally.  One minute it was quite sunny, the next the sky was completely black and the rain was bouncing off the pavement.  Luckily I was under the glass shelters they have all along the sides of the precinct, and I stopped for a few minutes to watch the rain, and the people all scurrying for cover, looking like very angry drowned rats.  I couldn't help but smile.  I do like Summer rain, it's refreshing, it takes the excessive heat out of the air, makes you appreciate the sun a bit more.  There is a wonderful smell about summer rain, a smell that winter rain doesn't have, I don't know how to describe it, it's sort of sharp and fresh, but it smells of earth and growing things too...if you know what I mean?  Even down town among the concrete and glass and tarmac it smells...well, alive I suppose, and it makes even the unhealthy, scabby looking trees in the town centre look like they're growing.  The rain didn't last long.  I managed to keep dry, so I was happy, because it's also quite windy today and I hate being wet when it's windy.  The bus ride home was a nightmare, screaming kids and moaning old ladies.  Things to be grateful for... 1. Summer rain 2. The smell of growing things 3. Helpful Dads that know what they want for Father's day
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      :::sigh::: I'm not happy and I don't know why.  I'm trying my bestest to look on the bright side of things and think positively, but at the moment it's just not working.  I haven't stopped taking my herbal happy pills or anything, so it's not that...makes me wonder what I'd be like if I wasn't taking them...doesn't bear thinking about.  I think most of it is the stress with work...it's been so busy what with the Kwik Save down the road closing, and the customers are extra moany because the co op is extortionatley expensive, and now, well, I could be out of a job fairly soon, and if I don't find a new one fairly quickly I'll be unemployed and then I won't be able to survive.  Shut Up Kate, you're depressing yourself.  I've been having mad dreams lately.  One of last night's was one I've had before, about a really old fashioned school, and me being late for a class with a really nasty teacher, and for some reason I always get lost and end up being later than ever, the other I don't want to talk about, it wasn't very nice.   Ah well, it's my day off tomorrow, I really need a week off, but I suppose I'll have to make do with one day  :-(  Things to be grateful for... 1.  Having an idea for a story that actually makes me enthusiastic! 2.  he fact that the dog isn't barking out of the window at the cats in the garden 3.  Cheese, not cheesy rock this time, just cheese.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        There is nothing greater than a nice bowl of weetabix to finish the day.  I have to have at least one bowl a day to feed my addiction  :-)  It's something of a running joke in UK Science Fiction chat, Kate and her weetabix addiction, has to be proper milk tho, none of this half fat semi skimmed crap, and as for skimmed milk...just don't go there, it's what the milkmen have left when they've washed out the empty bottles.   I really must start looking after myself a littlebetter, all this full fat milk and pub food can't be doing me any good.  That and the fruit cocktail trifles I keep buying at work beacuse they're going cheap.  I mean they are only little, but still...I'll be furring up my arteries to have a heart attack by the time I'm 35.  Ooh this is turning into a cheery post, I guess it's just the mood I'm in at the moment, been grumpy all day, and a little bit down.  It turns out that the leaseholder for our store is selling the lease, so if a developer buys it, then we might not be there for much longer, and I'll be unemployed.  Not that working for co-op is tht great anyway, but it's a job, and it keeps the bank from ripping me to shreds.  :::sigh:::  I'm going to shut up now before I depress myself even more.  Things to be grateful for: 1. Having a roof over my head 2. Having a steady income (for as long as it lasts) 3. The moon 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Damn, damn, damn, and quadruple damn.  One of my fish is looking ill again.  I'm hoping it's not a recurrence of the last problem, I've done a couple of water changes over the last couple of weeks, and I'm not feeding them nearly as much as I was, the others are looking ok, so maybe it's just something wrong with this one fish...fingers crossed.    I'm currently having a retro hour or so and listening to my Power Ballads CD...lots of 80's and 90's cheesy rock!  Ah the joys of cheesy rock, I love it, real sing along and annoy the neighbours stuff...I blame my dad for this, having been brought up on Status Qo and Dire Straits...(we won't mention the David Essex and Chris De Burgh my mum force fed me - although I do like a bit of Chris De Burgh on occasion).  I think thats why I like working at the Co-op so much (not) the music is the best bit.  I was going to say something else here, but I can't remember what it was. Damn, memory like a sieve.  Anyway, things to be grateful for... 1.  Cheesy rock 2.  My fella who bought me the cheesy rock for christmas 3.  My ability to sing along to said cheesy rock  ::::Dances::::
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have to say after reading the fantastic jokes on Pendragon's thoughts, that Pete IS the God of Comedy!  And there is no sarcasm in that at all, honest :-)  On a more serious note, I had the song from the AA advert stuck in my head, and Mart kindly found out what it was for me... It's 'I was Kaiser Bill's Batman' by Whistling Jack Smith.  Thank you mart.  Unfortunately I can't write it down here because it has no words, and thank god the tune has left my brain at last!  Last night I was watching Four Weddings and a Funeral.  I'd forgotten quite how funny it is, but it also seems very dated now too.  It made me think about marriage and relationships.  Marriage is a pointless waste of time and money (In my opinion of course, I don't want to upset any prospective married couples)  It just seems to me that for the expense, and hassle and stress of marriage, you could just spend the money on a nice relaxing holiday somewhere and keep your relationship as it is.  There are plenty of other ways to show you are committed to someone without having to get a bit of paper to say you're attached.  Thats what I think anyway.  Things to be grateful for: 1.  Mart's inexhaustible supply of useless information 2.  Having a happy, fairly stable relationship 3.  being far too sensible to ever even consider getting married or having kids
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Food poisoning.  Apparently that is what my supervisor had yesterday when he couldn't get to work.  Hah!  I think that is highly unlikely, if it was food poisoning he wouldn't have been in today, and he certainly wouldn't have gone to college like he did. Ah well, he's digging his own grave if he carries on the way he's going.   I have had a song going round my head today, can't stop singing it, it's Weak by Skunk Anansie (God that woman is incredibly sexy!) so here it is...  Lost in time I can't count the words I said when I thought they went unheard, All of those harsh thoughts so unkind Cause I wanted you.  And now I sit here I'm all alone And here sits a bloody mess tears fly home A circle of angels deep in war Cause I wanted you  Weak as I am No tears for you Weak as I am No tears for you Deep as I am I'm no-ones fool Weak as I ammmm  So what am I now I'm loves last home I'm all of those harsh thoughts I once owned If I opened my heart there'd be no space for air Cos I wanted you  Weak as I am...  In this tainted soul, in this weak young heart  Am I too much for you? In this tainted soul, In this weak young heart Am I too much for you? In this tainted soul, In this weak young heart Am I too much for you  Weak as I am Weak as I am Weak as I am, am  Weak as I am, am I too much for you? Weak as I am, am I too much for you? Weak as I am, am I too much for you ? Weak as I am   Things to be grateful for:  1. Skin's amazing singing voice 2. Asda Curries 3. Raspberry shortcake Icecream
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I have had a dreadful day.  It started when my supervisor didn't turn up for work.  It's his job to open the store, and as the only contactable keyholder for today, we were kinda stuck.  He eventually turned up at 10.30am, after a lot of running around by me and Joan, and ringing of various people to try and contact him and/or get some keys.  The manager got involved, and was on his way.  Aaron, the supervisor didn't stay long.  He drove up, handed Joan the keys, mummbled something about hospital and drove off again, giving no real explaination as to why he was one and a half hours late, and not staying.  we eventually got the shop open and running, but because we were so late, the cashin up from the night before hadn't been done, so we were short of change for most of the morning.  The Boss turned up to see what was happening at about 11am, not a happy bunny, because he was supposed to be having a day out with his family in North Wales.  He had to stay all day because Aaron had gone off.  As well as that, it has been horrendously busy all day what with people getting beer and food for the football, people getting barbecue stuff because of the weather, and lots of just general shoppers because the Kwik Save down the road is shut for refurbishment.  I was late out too.  I hope to God I never have a day like that again, but I don't suppose it will be as bad as the day Aaron is going to have when the Boss gets hold of him!  I wouldn't be surprised if he was jobless by tomorrow unless he can come up with a really good excuse...  Things to be grateful for:  1.  The fact it wasn't raining when we were sat outside the co op for one and a half hours. 2.  My dad picking me up from work 3.  fruit cocktail trifles.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I didn't write yesterday, not because I was camping as the title suggests, but because I was elsewhere, not at home by my beloved (hah, yeah right) computer.  Today I have been trawling the internet looking for a campsite that is easily accessible by public transport so I can go camping for a few days in september with my wonderful fella.  I'm not having much luck.  Mainly because a lot of sites that are listed have no pictures and no information, they are just addresses.  Most of them don't even have a web site or email...I mean what century do they think they are living in???  No web site?  This isn't the stoneage.  I have found a couple of nice looking sites, now I just have to work out how to get to them using only the trains and buses (oh for a car).  Alternatively it's a case of turning up where I want to go, and hoping there is a free space to put my tent!   Well I'll keep you updated on what happens campsite wise... For now here are some things to be grateful for:  1.  Ribena 2.  Dominoes Pizza 3.  Friendly cats 4.  Silk 5.  The internet.  What would we do without it??
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I am extremely tired, so this is only going to be a short one today.  I've had a very busy day in work lugging big cases of fizzy drinks around, I'm sure my arms are at least six inches longer than they were!   Anyway, things to be grateful for:  1.  People with a sense of humour 2.  Hugs 3.  Hot Juice
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I just read a post on a certain person's journal, concerning a certain song.  Now I have the damned song going around MY head!  I do quite like the song in question tho, even if I can't remember who it's by.  It's 'Tracks of my Tears' by the way, and now I'm really annoyed that I can't remember who it's by.  Can anyone help?   I have also decided that I'm going to try and write a book of politically correct proverbs and sayings.  Of course, to do that I need to find a lot of proverbs and sayings, so I might have to go out and buy a normal book so I can translate them into politically correct speak.  How much money do you think I could make out of this???  Things to be grateful for:  1.  Silly Ideas 2.  Old Ideas developed into new ones 3.  Potato croquets
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I read a blog today called Pika's troubled philosophy.  There was an entry in it called The Ant Philosophy, and after reading it I felt, I don't know, more hopeful I suppose.  It made a lot of sense to me, and gave me the kick that I needed to look at life a little differently, or at least give it a go.  It's worth looking at...   The Ant Philosophy:  1.  Ants never give up - keep trying, if one way doesn't work try another way to reach your goal  2.  Ants think winter in summer - plan ahead for what you want, set attainable targets  3.  Ant's think summer in winter - Always think positively, find the bright side in every situation  4.  Ants always try - Do your best in everything you do, don't be lazy and do yourself down.   Thats the essence of it anyway...     Incidentally the midge bites are feeling a bit better tonight!  Things to be grateful for:  1.  Sorting out misunderstandings 2.  Pub food. 3.  Having free texts to text animals sounds to my fella (don't ask!)
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I itch all over.  Serves me right for walking around the woods in the evening when all the nasty little bitey things are out and about I suppose.  Even so, there is no need for this many nasty biting midges to have bitten me.  I look like I've got something nasty, and I'm driving myself mad trying not to scratch them.  I've resorted to putting plasters over them to prevent me from scratching.  It does look quite silly, but at least I can't get to them.  Consequently I've been in a dreadful mood all day, well mainly because of that, also because of the weather being nice and being stuck in work.  Personally I think shops should be closed in the summer.  Well the shops I work in anyway.  Things to be grateful for: 1.  Plasters. 2.  That I'm not too stubborn to apologise for things (most of the time) 3.  Roast beef and crispy roast potatoes.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I was in Boots the other day, looking at make up, as you do.  Behind me looking as some other make up was a woman, with her two children who looked about four and six.  This woman was talking to her boyfriend/husband on the phone, asking him to find out what shade of powder she had in her make up bag.  Evidently he wouldn't go and look, because she slamed her phone shut, and said, quite loudly 'F*cking B*stard' (except without the *'s)  I was disgusted to hear her swear like that in front of her two small children, but it got worse.  She then turned to the smaller of the two and said 'your Dad's a f*cking W*nker!'.  I went cold.  Nobody should ever speak to a child like that.  What made the outburst even more chilling was the childrens reactions.  They were not phased at all by the language coming from their mother, in fact they seemed oblivious to the fact that her language was extremely offensive.  I guess she uses the 'f' word around them all the time.  I just wonder, if their mother speaks to them like that now, what are they going to be talking like by the time they are fifteen?    Something that happened today also made me question the future of humanity.  In work we had a couple of drunks in the store.  One of them was spilling orange juice all over the floor, while another dropped his medicine bottle which smashed.  Apparently this man had just come out of hospital where he's been in with pneumonia, he also said he needs to have his medicine every day or he'll be back in to hospital.  fter dropping his medicine on the floor, several things happened...Firstly he asked me for a straw, then when I said I couldn't give him one, he got on his knees and started LICKING the medicine off the tiles.  I kid you not.  The supervisor told him he couldn't do that because of the danger of glass shards being licked up, and told him to go to the local hospitals drop in centre to see if they could help.  As he was leaving, we noticed that he had a leg of lamb stuck down his pants that he'd nicked on his way round the store.  We stopped him, took the lamb off him and then barred him from coming back.  It just shows how disgustingly shameless some people are.  Things to be grateful for: 1.  Sequoia Dendron (or Giant Redwood trees to the uninitiated   ) 2.  Midge repellent (even though I haven't got any and am now bitten alive. 3.  Chocolate eclairs.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        People can be very stubborn.  I know, because I am usually stubborn.  I wish things could be different sometimes, but I guess some things you just can't change, like people's ideals, and peoples opinions of you.  It makes me sad when I lose friends because of misunderstandings and things that happened in the past, but I've tried to apologise, I've tried to make things right.  I guess sometimes bridges can't be rebuilt.   On a brighter note I've had a good day.  It didn't rain, well maybe a little, but not much at all, I went down town and didn't spend loads of money, and I went to see 'The Day After Tomorrow' with Pete.  It was a fairly good film, apart from the silly bits and the directional inconsistencies, oh and I'm not convinced a tornado would do THAT to a building  .  But apart from that I liked it.  Went to the pub afterwards which is why I'm so late writing this.  Politically correct thought for today:   Who's the more intellectually challenged, the intellectually challenged person, or the intellectually challenged person that follows the intellectually challenged person?  Things to be grateful for: 1.  Alcohol 2.  Golf courses. 3.  Mild nights so that you don't mind walking home after you've missed the last bus. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I think the happy pills are working, amongst other things.  Life is being kinder to me at the moment, I'm feeling better about myself, and things are working out.  I hope they continue to work out, and I'm going to do my best to make sure they do.     I didn't write last night because I got a bit drunk in the pub, andwhen I got in my dad was on the puter.  I also realised that I didn't do 3 things to be grateful for the night before, or last night, so I have three sets of things to do for tonight.  Here goes...  1.  Imagination.  The world would be a very dull place without it. 2.  Trees.  I like trees, one tree in particular, in the park :-) 3.  Ice cream on hot days, although it hasn't been too hot here recently, so just ice cream I guess.  4.  Healthy fish. 5.  Baby Guineapigs. 6.  Freezing cold water to drink.  7.  My friends 8.  My brother because he's always sticking up for me. 9.  Pete.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I am not a happy bunny.  I'm not sleeping well at the moment for various reasons, and the sleepless nights are making me grumpy.  Today in work I have been patronised, prodded, been made to feel like an idiot, thought of as an idiot, oh and I had my arse pinched by some pervy man.  I'd have slapped him, but I wasn't quick enough, and slapping customers isn't good for business.  Anyway, today I hate my job.  Sometimes I like it, but today, today if I had had the opportunity I'd have burnt the place to the ground just to get a few months off while they rebuilt it, I'd have handed in my notice if I had the money or prospects to do so, but I haven't so I didn't.  Tomorrow doesn't look like being much bettee either.  It's delivery day.   I was going to go to the pub after work, but no-one could make it.  I was even thinking of going on my own, but when it came to getting off the bus, I just didn't have the energy, so I came home and fell asleep for a couple of hours instead.  It did me good, I feel more refreshed and awake now, and a million times less grumpy, so I think it was probably a better idea than going to the pub.  Lets face it, drinking on your own is never a good idea, and I'd have only ended up getting drunk on my own, and wouldn't have got any sleep tonight either.  I'm still yawning tho, hopefully that means I'll sleep properly tonight and I'll be bright eyed and bushy tailed tomorrow morning, like those bunnies I mentioned... 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I was on the bus today, coming home from work, and this woman got on the bus.  She must have been in her late fifties, maybe early sixties, and she started asking the driver questions where he was going, whih is fair enough, so he told her.  He was obviously going where she wanted him to, so she made to go and sit down.  He gently reminded her that she hadn't paid yet, and she looked at him like he was stupid and said 'I've got a pass.' in a very snotty tone of voice.  The driver was very polite and just said that he would have to see it before she could go and sit down, so she made this big show of having a hurt arm and putting her bag down before she could get her pass out.  (A few seconds later she was holding onto the bar with both arms as the bus drove off quite happily, so her arm can't have been that bad).  Anyway, she only went a few stops, and as she was getting off the bus she turned to the driver and was really snotty and nasty to him saying things like 'I'm from the honest generation', and 'you're obviously not an honest man to see dishonesty in me' blah de blah de blah.  The rest of the passengers on the bus were like 'Oh shut up you silly mare, he's only doing his job.'  What annoyed me most was the fact that she said 'I'm from THE honest generation', like all the rest of us were untrustworthy thieving liars.  Personally I don't think there is such a thing as an honest generation.  There are always going to be good people and bad people in any generation, people who will help others, and those who are out for all they can get and will try to get away with anything.  There are just as many eldrly shop lifters as there are young ones, it's just the elderly ones tend to get away with it more... Things to be grateful for: 1.  Regaining my muse and being able to write again. 2.  Not being so self obsessed and snobbish to think I don't have to show my pass when I'm getting on a bus because the 'driver should know I'm an honest citizen' 3.  having my blog to write in to keep me sane (ish) 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; I have just been to see Spiderman 2.&nbsp; It's good, I'd recommend it!&nbsp; We went over to Liverpool to see it, because there's a new cinema opened...not sure how long it's been there. but it can't be that long ago it opened.&nbsp; Anyway, it's a cool cinema, they let you take beer into the cinema and everything ;-)&nbsp; The film finished about 11, and we, well I decided it would be best to get the bus home.&nbsp; Stupid idea of mine.&nbsp; The last bus didn't turn up, and by that time we'd missed the train too, so we ended up getting a taxi with 3 random old blokes who'd also given up on the buses.&nbsp; I swear it's easier getting home at 3am from liverpool, than it is getting home at 11.30.&nbsp; Grrr, damned buses! 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; I just re-read yesterday's post.&nbsp; I didn't set out to write it, I just did.&nbsp; I was feeling a little bit down, and a little bit bored, and I had nothing interesting to write about, so I just opened a new entry page and started to type.&nbsp; I'm quite impressed with how it turned out.&nbsp; It's not great, and it's very simple, but it's got potential I think... 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; When I first started blogging, way back when I was using aol Journals (how I laugh at my folly!) I intended to use it for writing down my thoughts, and things that happen to me during the week.&nbsp; More a news item than anything else.&nbsp; Now I've been doing it for a while I've found that I use it to write down anything and everything.&nbsp; There's a lot of stuff on here that I don't speak to people about much.&nbsp; I feel I can tell my blog anything, even though I know people will read it, it somehow doesn't feel bad to bare my soul like this, unlike trying to talk to people about stuff (which I am notoriously bad at, ask Pete about that some time!).&nbsp; I find it easier to write what I'm feeling, I can take time to think about it and get it right, otherwise what I'm trying to say comes out wrong, and it either makes me sound completely crazy, or I end up hurting someone with misplaced words.&nbsp; I'm glad I started blogging.&nbsp; It's the best therapy anyone can have. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; She sits in silence, staring at the mist as it swirls through the garden outside.&nbsp; The room is sparsely furnished with a table and chair and a narrow bed across one wall.&nbsp; It is her prison.&nbsp; She stands and she paces from wall to wall and back again, to and fro until you can almost see the groove being worn in the bare floor boards where her&nbsp;naked feet pass.&nbsp; A hundred, a thousand times she paces back and forth, then she stops, flopping listlessly onto the hard mattress of the bed and turns her head to stare from the window at the mist once more.&nbsp; She is waiting.&nbsp; Not even she knows what she waits for, but wait she does.&nbsp; She has been there for centuries it seems, seconds rolling slowly by into hour long minutes and year long hours.&nbsp; Her impatience is palpable, but still she waits.&nbsp; The door is open, but the corridor beyond is dark and cold, unlit and unfriendly, and she is afraid to step beyond the boundaries of her room.&nbsp; So she sits and waits, and watches as the mist curls around the garden.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Night falls, and with it; total darkness.&nbsp; She lies upon the bed and closes her eyes, but sleep will not come.&nbsp; She has lost count of the nights she has spent like this, lying still, her eyes shut to the dark outside, only the darkness of her own head for company.&nbsp; Her thoughts are slow and heavy and make no sense, just swirls of pattern in her mind.&nbsp; When she opens her eyes it will be light again, and the mist will curl around the garden outside.&nbsp; And days go past, fragmented by the dreamless nights, always the same, like recycled time.&nbsp; She sits and waits, and watches, she paces and lies upon the bed, and closes her eyes when darkness comes, and the mist curls around the garden outside her window.&nbsp; Nothing changes.&nbsp; And so she waits. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; I felt a little better today until I remembered it's tuesday, and that meant I had to go on checkouts most of the day.&nbsp; I hate checkouts, it means I have to deal with people on a face to face basis.&nbsp; I mean I have to do that on the chop floor too, but not as much, and you can escape by saying you have to go and do some work or something.&nbsp; I really do hate this job, it's doing my head in. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Boyfriends are great :-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; Paranoia is one of the most dangerous emotions.&nbsp; It is damaging, and it makes you do things that you wouldn't normally do and say things that hurt.&nbsp; I am an extremely paranoid person, paranoid and insecure.&nbsp; Most of the time I can control it instead of letting it control me, but sometimes it's takes over.&nbsp; I try not to listen to the voices inside of me, telling me that I'm ugly, or I'm unlovable, or I'm worthless.&nbsp; I try not to think that people are talking about me, or are out to get me or hurt me in some way.&nbsp; I know deep down that I'm being silly, but I can't help it.&nbsp; It's worse when you love someone.&nbsp; You're constantly afraid that they are going to leave you, just walk away and leave you on your own, and the stupid thing is, the more you act strangely because you're paranoid, the more likely they are to get fed up with the moodiness and the misery and decide that it's too much hard work.&nbsp; I hate the way I feel sometimes, the way I act and the way I am.&nbsp; If I could change overnight I would, but I can't.&nbsp; It's a long slow process, but I think I'm getting better, I'm not as bad as I used to be... 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; I dyed my hair.&nbsp; Its now a kind of gingery blonde.&nbsp; I quite like it, but it hasn't made me feel any better.&nbsp; Pete hasn't spoken to me for 2 days now.&nbsp; I wish I wasn't so damned&nbsp;useless at relationships.&nbsp; Same as everything else I suppose. &nbsp; I went out with the girls I used to work with last night.&nbsp; I had planned to stay in with a bottle of gin and some tonic, but instead I went out and got drunk, smoked my way through a whole packet of cigarettes and danced a bit.&nbsp; Bang goes the giving up. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; What exactly is happiness?&nbsp; I always used to believe that happiness was being happy all the time, but now I don't believe that's possible.&nbsp; There is always something to bring you down.&nbsp; I suppose happiness is relative.&nbsp; If you spend every day of your life wanting to die because you're so depressed you feel you can't go on, then the day you wake up and don't wish you had died in your sleep must be a like a kind of happiness.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Bob is back in work on monday.&nbsp; I'm dreading it.&nbsp; I've spent the last fortnight actually feling useful for a change.&nbsp; Bob makes me nervous, and he makes me feel useless and worthless and pathetic.&nbsp; He has this way of making me feel about 6 years old, like I used to feel when I was in primary school and could never do anything right.&nbsp; He makes me feel like an idiot, like my opinions are not worth anything, like I'm getting in the way.&nbsp; I feel like that anyway at the moment, I can't seem to do anything right, I'm upsetting people all the time, I feel like I'm useless, a waste of space, a little bit pointless.&nbsp;It will be worse when the boss gets back, and then Joan is going on holiday too in a week or so.&nbsp; Joan sticks up for me, she's like my back up.&nbsp; She has confidence in my abilities, I think she's the only one that does&nbsp;at the moment.&nbsp; I don't know what's wrong with me, I was happy not so long ago, this evil mood has dropped on me like a stone, suddenly with no warning.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; I'm not happy tonight.&nbsp; I'm not sure why, I just feel miserable and irritable and fed up with everything.&nbsp; It's like I can't see where I'm going anymore, and I don't know where I'm supposed to be or what I'm supposed to be doing or anything.&nbsp; I want to hide for a while and forget about the world, but tha's not an option, I've done that before, and it just makes me worse.&nbsp; A few years ago I made myself almost agoraphobic with depression, I didn't want to leave the house, and when I did I had panic attacks and could barely walk to the shops down the road without flinching when someone walked past me.&nbsp; It got to the point where I had to put my foot down and force myself to go out of the front door, to walk to the bus stop, to get on the bus.&nbsp; I only managed it by listening to my discman on full blast.&nbsp; It was like walking around in a&nbsp;little coccoon of, well, Linkin Park and Nickelback of all things, surrounded by the music I felt safe, and gradually I started to pull myself out of it.&nbsp; I was still miserable, but at least I could go out&nbsp;of the front door without having a panic attack. &nbsp; That's all in the&nbsp;past now though, and I'm no where near as bad at the moment as I was then.&nbsp; I do have a tendency to shut&nbsp;myself away and try to block out the world though.&nbsp;&nbsp;Now I know how bad I can get, I won't let myself&nbsp;get that bad again.&nbsp; There are worse things than agoraphobia, and I've&nbsp;done some of them, sometimes, when I've hated myself in the past.&nbsp; I promised myself that I wouldn't do it again, but the thing about promises like that are that when you promise, you're not in the same frame of mind as you are when you're doing it.&nbsp; I just realised that I haven't said what 'it' is.&nbsp;&nbsp;'It' is self harm.&nbsp; Not to a huge extent, but it's still not healthy.&nbsp;&nbsp;When I get to that stage,&nbsp;it's like there's two of me, Sane Kate and Crazy Kate (and even sane Kate isn't that sane, but crazy Kate is terrifying- She scares me anyway).&nbsp;&nbsp;I haven't been that bad for a while now.&nbsp; Even when I was down the last time, I wasn't that bad, and the herbal happy pills seem to be working ok.&nbsp; I didn't intend to write about this tonight, but&nbsp;my fingers seem to have developed a mind of their own.&nbsp; I'm in two minds whether to even&nbsp;post this or not.&nbsp; It seems a little self indulgent, and attention seeking.&nbsp; It's not intended to be.  I appear to have found my muse aswell.  I am closed, Mourning for the birth&nbsp;of doubt, And the death of&nbsp;a dream. Thoughts move like Icebergs, Creeping in the fridgid waters of my mind, And molten tears slip from tired eyes. I am lost, Not knowing where to turn, Or who to trust. Friends seem like strangers, Strangers like deadly enemies, And&nbsp;fear holds me as they circle. I am dead, Waiting for the night to claim me And the stars to fade. But from the east comes dawn, A bright glow bringing peace And hope, to give another day.&nbsp;&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; I've been in a dreadful mood all day, nothing has gone well, nasty customers, busy shop, too much stuff to put out...&nbsp; I hate my job with a vengeance.&nbsp; And I was late out, and I was supposed to be going to a friend's house tonight, but I really don't feel like it, I'm grumpy and I have the worst headache imaginable, and I think I'm going to go to bed...Hopefully I'll feel better in the morning. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Life   I am the bright light in the darkness, I am the shadow on the moon.  I am the rainbow in the downpour, I am the cloud that hides the sun.  I am the love that heals a nation, I am the hate that starts a war.  I am the fire of burning passion, I am the ice of abject fear.  I am the words that start a friendship, I am the silent solitude.  I am&nbsp;creative inspiration, I am the&nbsp;destructive muse.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I am the sun, the moon, the planets, I am the earth, the trees, the sky.  I am the tiny new born baby, I am the ancient mountains high.  I am everything and nothing, Universe to tiny cell.  I am thought and I am motion, I am heaven, I am hell.  I am the youth, I am the aged I am the free, I am the chained  I am life in all its power; As at the start, so at the end.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Kate 7/04 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       &nbsp; I found out today that Myrtle died yesterday.&nbsp; Myrtle was one of my customers, one of my nicest customers...she was lovely!&nbsp; She always had a smile and a word of kindness, always wanted to talk and would make time for chatting.&nbsp; Se would ask how we were, and how the job was going, she was one of the nicest people I've met.&nbsp; I will miss Myrtle.&nbsp; She had a stroke about 3 weeks ago, a bad one that left her without speech, we sent a card and some flowers to wish her well, but I suppose it was only a matter of time before the inevitable happened.&nbsp;    &nbsp; Hoylake seems to be cursed at the moment, the nice people suffer and/or die and it's just not fair.&nbsp; They say only the good die young, Myrtle wasn't exactly young, but she should have had a good few years in her yet, the two young men that were killed in the crash on saturday night, had their whole lives ahead of them but for one silly mistake while driving, Joyce's Husband, John, a lovely, friendly man who didn't have a bad word for anyone, died a few months ago after an illness.&nbsp; It's depressing, and slightly worrying that Hoylake seems to be a black spot for unhappiness at the moment.   &nbsp; I was upset to hear about Myrtle, and I was sad for the rest of the day.&nbsp; I went to Pete's after work tho, and he cheered me up.&nbsp; He's good at that (amongst other things ;-)), and I do feel better now despite what this post might sound like...&nbsp; I was bad tho and ate a couple of sweets and some skittles.&nbsp; Evil temptor that he is :-)  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp;  I was going to write a poem today.&nbsp; I've been thinking about it all day, but I've tried this evening to get something down, and the ideas just won't write themselves.&nbsp; I guess I'm not as creative as I used to be, now that I'm happy, my poetry brain has given up.&nbsp; I don't know if thats a good thing, when I read back on some of the stuff I used to write, I go cold.&nbsp; My state of mind is written down on the pages for everyone to see, and some of it is scary stuff.&nbsp; I don't think I want to be back there again, and if losing a bit of talent is the price I have to pay for not being scary anymore, then so be it.&nbsp; I miss some of it tho, some of the stuff I wrote wasn't scary, but it was quite good...only from my point of view, if I like it then I don't care what anyone else thinks...   &nbsp; Except I suppose, deep down, if I let anyone else read any of my poems, I would care what they thought about them, which is probably why no one reads them, they are locked away in a box out of sight of the world.&nbsp; It's likely that that is where they will stay too, safe from criticism.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp;  On the way to work today we had the radio on in the car.&nbsp; There was a news report about an accident that had happened just off the M53 near Morton.&nbsp; Just a short piece about a car that had come off the road and wrapped itself around a lamp post.&nbsp; I didn't think anything of it, accidents happen, the thought that went through my head when I heard it was along the lines of 'silly buggers were probably speeding or something'.&nbsp; When I got to work, Joan said that the lad, Chris, that was suposed to be supervising, hadn't turned up yet, and fleetingly my brain wondered idly about the crash, not really thinking that he had anything to do with it.&nbsp; He had been.&nbsp; He had been in the car behind fortunately, so he was unhurt, but he lost two of his friends when their car hit the lamp post.&nbsp; The whole of Hoylake is in shock, it's the kind of village where everyone knows everyone, if not by name, then by face, and by the time the shop opened at 10am, everyone seemed to know, and everyone was talking about it.&nbsp; There are a lot of rumours going around as to the exact details of what happened, a lot of speculation.&nbsp; None of it really matters to me, the important detail is that two young men died last night.&nbsp; I didn't know them personally, I was aquainted with one of them because he used to come into the shop either to see Chris or Aaron, or to shop.&nbsp; He seemed like a really nice bloke.&nbsp; He was nineteen, the other lad was seventeen.&nbsp; It is such a waste, such a shame.&nbsp; I can't think how their families and friends must be feeling now.   &nbsp; I have been in a dreadful mood all day with a lot of the customers, complaining about petty quibbly little things, it puts life into perspective when something happens like this, and I'm sorry, but I cannot be happy and cheerful when dealing with somebody's buy one get one free offer that hasn't gone through, or a query as to why their deodorant has gone through at 99p instead of 98p, when I know that people I know are suffering and distraught somewhere and I can't do anything about it.&nbsp; I actually feel quite guilty for being a little upset.&nbsp; I didn't know the lads that died other than as faces who sometimes came into the store, friends of colleagues.&nbsp; I guess what I'm feeling is a kind of general sadness at the loss of life, brought home because it's closer than just a news article now...  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       &nbsp;Grrrr, damned puters.&nbsp; Mine died on monday, so I've been unable to blog or chat or read web comics for a whole 5 days.&nbsp; I'm suffering withdrawal symptoms (shakes, panic attacks, sleepless nights, restless pacing...), it's quite sad really how much I rely on the computer, and surprising how much stress relief blogging and chatting online provides.&nbsp; I can rant without getting told off for shouting.&nbsp; I'm currently at my wonderful boyfriend's house using his puter to write this.&nbsp; My dad was taking ours round to a friends house yesterday to see if it could be fixed, but he was late back last night with it, and I was out early this morning to go to work so I haven't had a chance to find out if it's fixed yet.&nbsp; If it's not, you'll know, because I won't be back until I can get on here again, that could be tomorrow, but then again, could be next week.&nbsp; I'm having a night away from home tonight at Pete's because his mum has gone away to Spain for a week.&nbsp; It means I can get away from my mum, if only for 24 hours.&nbsp; That isn't the reason I'm staying over, it's just an added bonus.&nbsp; Now don't get me wrong, I love my mum, just sometimes she can get a bit well, annoying.&nbsp; And her and my dad are driving me mad at the moment, bickering and whinging at eachother.&nbsp; They're off to Turkey next month for a fortnight's holiday together, alone.&nbsp; God knows how they'll cope with being together in the same place 24/7.&nbsp; Hmm, that sounds like they're having problems.&nbsp; I don't think they are, but I never noticed how much they bicker before.&nbsp; I think they were always like that, but I was too busy bickering with my brother to notice.&nbsp; Now I'm on my own with them since my bro moved in with his fiance, and I feel kinda stuck in the middle sometimes.&nbsp; My Dad, I can deal with, he still treats me a bit like a little kid, but I suspect all dads do that, and he will continue to do it until I turn fifty, and then some, but he's quiet, and he keeps himself to himself most times.&nbsp; My mum, well I think I'm too like my mum to ever really get on completely with her.&nbsp; I can see myself turning into her in another thirty years, and that's scary.&nbsp; She moans at my dad constantly about little stuff, and my dad being stubborn, of course decides he won't do it her way etc, etc.&nbsp; If you're in the right mood, it's quite amusing to listen to, but if not, well, I have to go and lock myself in my room until they've stopped.&nbsp; I shouldn't complain really, they've been very good to me, and they've brought me up as a polite, considerate (most of the time), well mannered person.&nbsp; I wouldn't change them for the world.   &nbsp; Ooh, I just took a proper look at this create entry page, blogger has changed rather since last time I looked.&nbsp; Just been playing with the colours.&nbsp; I'm trying to decide whether a rather fetching shade of green will show up on my background colour or not.   &nbsp; I think I will try it out for a couple of lines, and then if it doesn't work I'll know not to use it again!   &nbsp; Work has been the same as usual, except that Joan is stressed because Bob, the manager, is on hols, so she's in charge of the store, and I have been doing 8.30 til 5 shifts on checkouts because Jean is off sick with a flu bug.&nbsp; I can't rmember if I mentioned it, but Aaron is also off sick, he has got Mumps, and has been in hospital with it.&nbsp; Mumps can be nasty when your older I believe, I had my MMR vaccination when I was ickle tho, so hopefully I should be ok.&nbsp; I really don't want mumps!   &nbsp; Sigh, well I feel I'm boring you all now, so I'll blog off (heh heh hehehe pun intended) and go to bed!    &nbsp;  Things to be grateful for...   1.&nbsp; Boyfriends with computers.   2.&nbsp; Cute black and white kitties   3.&nbsp; Internet banking    &nbsp;  Bad things I've eaten today (and the last couple of days)   1 chocolate bar (Wednesday)   1 berry muffin (Thursday)  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I was a naughty girl today.  I succumbed to the temptation of an egg custard with my lunch.  :::Holds out a wrist for slapping:::  Things to be grateful for... 1.  Roast chicken 2.  Calligraphy 3.  Star Trek (but only in moderation)  Bad things I've eaten today... 1.  Egg custard tart 2.  A ginsters pasty
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I was reading a blog today by someone I know that goes in the same chat room that I do.  The entry was about a guy (naming no names but I'm fairly certain I know who it was about) who is also a chatroom regular.  Apparently this guy has been annoying this person by flashing his money around and is now apparently trying to 'buy' friends by taking a friend and her mum to a concert for free.  Ok I have a few things to say about this... 1.  This guy, to me seems like a nice bloke, he's always friendly, his jokes might be a little close to the bone occasionally, but he means no harm. 2.  From what I can tell he has had to work damned hard to get where he is today, earning what he is earning, so he is entitled to 'brag' a bit, not that I've noticed him shouting out 'I've got loads of money and you're all worthelss because you haven't', nor have I ever heard him claim he's better than anyone else because of it. 3.  As for trying to buy friends?  Well, what happened to good old fashioned, doing people a favour, or being nice to someone just for the hell of it?  We live in a very paranoid and distrustful society, and everyone seems to think that everyone else has the very worst intentions, and are only out for number one.  It's simply not true.  There are nice people out there, kind people, generous people, and I, for one, happen to believe that this guy is one of them.     I would like to think that this post might make a difference to peoples opinions, and perhaps give them a different perspective on certain things and certain individuals.  I doubt it will tho, people in general are pig headed and cynical...I should know, I'm exactly the same myself.     Incidentally, I am not sticking up for this guy because of any sense of loyalty, I count him as a mate, yes, but I believe he's been unfairly represented.  I am not rich either, I'm quite poor at the moment, still living with my mum because I can't afford to move out, so this also isn't a case of the rich sticking up for the rich.  Right, I think thats straightened out...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I have just got in after being at the pub.  It was a nice evening, the pub was a bit busy to start with, but it quietened down later on.     On the way home I had to wait for ages to get the bus and some drunken scallies decided to come and share the bus stop, and eventually the bus with me.  Now I'm not against drunk people in general, and I'm not against swearing in moderation, but these people were horrible, every other word was the F word and they were screaming and shrieking at eachother like banshees.  It was quite depressing and not a little intimidating.  I should have walked home, but it was raining.  But on a happier note, yet again I have managed to avoid the perils of chocolate and cakes!  The fourth day running, I'm dead proud of myself!  Things to be grateful for... 1. Not getting my head kicked in 2. nail varnish 3. strawberries
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I got a bit tearful before, which is probably why my eyeballs are hurting now.  Damned salty tears, irritating my poor little eyes :-(  I'm feeling a little better now tho, just overreacted to the fact that I couldn't go to the pub, and I'd been looking forward to it all day, and then someone said something and I got upset about it, and then my mum started being annoying about stupid little things, and...well you know how it is, sometimes things just seem a lot worse than they are.  I was just being silly, I've calmed down now, and chilled out a bit (reading always does me a lot of good), but I think I may have an early night.   Other than that I feel great!  I've abstained from chocolate and cream cakes and trifles for 3 whole days now!  Things to be grateful for...  1.  Tropical fish 2.  Fantasy books that you can escape into 3.  The faraway realms of the imagination.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Well back to work today.  I suppose it wasn't too bad, but I desperately need a new job.  I have been very good today and haven't eaten anything I shouldn't have, although I'm having serious difficulty resisting the jam doughnut that my mum brought in.  To me that's just evil, and considering both her and my dad are supposed to be on diets....well, it's just wrong!   Not doing too well with the excercise bit tho.  I think I'll have to work up to that, maybe I'll walk part of the way home tomorrow, if it's not raining.  Things to be grateful for... 1.  Self control 2.  Feeling healthier already 3.  The filling quality of weetabix
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I have decided to start looking after myself a bit better.  Starting from today, I've had no biscuits today, or chocolate (I did have some cheesecake after my tea, but it wasn't a snack so I can allow myself that, and I was eating out.) I intend to keep this up too, I'm not going to go full out banning myself all sweet stuff and only eating salad, because I know I won't stick to that.  I'm just going to start off slowly, cutting down on the amount of cream cakes and chocolate I eat, and trying to do a bit more excerise.  That's going to be the hard bit, because I'm a lazy cow when it comes to excercise.  Went for a bit of a walk today, true it was only to the ASDA down the road, and I did get the bus back because I had shopping, and I was knackered because this bug I've had ha sapped all my energy, but it is a start I think.  I'll start off gently and work my way up to doing the London Marathon  :-)  The one thing I'm not giving up is proper milk, I can't eat weetabix with anything else on it...semi skimmed is just not the same!   I had a lovely afternoon.  I went to ASDA and bought some healthy food (well healthy for me, there was no chocolate or crisps or cream cakes anywhere in it.)  Then I came home and made some lunch - steak and salad, then pottered about a bit doing not much befoe wandering up to the park to meet my sexy boyfriend.  We sat on the grass and chilled out for a while, then got food in the pub.  It was lovely, watching the clouds and talking about silly stuff and catching some sunshine for a change.  The weather hasn't been very nice recently, and it felt good to warm my skin in the afternoon sun.  I'm back at work tomorrow :-(  Things to be grateful for...  1. Late afternoon sun that isn't too hot and isn't too chilly. 2. Lying on the grass not having to think about stuff.  3. Cheesecake  Bad things I've eaten today... Cheesecake
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I spent most of the day in bed.  Mainly because I was a very foolish girl last night and ate a whole packet of chocolate fudge crunch creams.  As you canimagine they didn't do my bloodsugar levels any good, and this morning I felt decidedly queasy.  This is a problem of mine.  Sometimes I just decide to eat myself stupid.  I always regret it in the morning, but I don't do it often.  I think maybe some people would see a problem with this.  They'd maybe see it as a kind of eating disorder.  I don't see it that way, to me, it's like maybe going out once in a while and getting totally rat arsed, it doesn't do you much good, and you get a hangover the following morning, but it doesn't make you an alcoholic if you only do it once in a blue moon.  I think sometimes you just have to let yourself go, totally pig out on chocolate, or drink yourself insensible, just to relax and forget about the world for a bit.  Geh, now I'm sounding like I want to forget about everything, and it's making me sound a bit like I need to be worried about.  I don't need worrying about, but I guess saying that will only make people worry more.  I think maybe I should shut up before I dig myself any deeper.  Things to be grateful for... 1.  The advances in medicine over that last hundred years that make me still alive today 2.  Uplifting (yet soppy) films 3.  Keira Knightley (Can't wait for king arthur to come out!)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I'm feeling a little better today, and I went to the cinema this evening.  Saw The Ladykillers.  It's not great, not as bad as some I've seen, but not brilliant.  I believe the original was better, I haven't seen the original, but people have told me it's better.  Most originals are, I don't think I've seen a remake thats been better than the original...  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        It makes me mad when people come into UK Sci Fi and ask us why we're not talking science fiction.  I've lost count of the amount of times that people have said 'just because we like science fiction doesn't mean we have to talk about it all the time.'  Science fiction isn't something we are, we are normal people with other interests as well.  It really annoys me.  There is one particular person that comes in, she has in the past said that if we're not talking sci fi, we should leave the room.  These are the regulars she's talking to.  You can imagine how well that went down.  This is also the girl that said that people wnet into space because of star trek, that everyone will eventually have their own private aircraft, and that she wants, when she dies to donate her organs then have her body shot into space so that, get this...'the aliens can find me and ressurect me'.  I kid you not.  We get the impression she's a little bit insane, which is fine, insanity doesn't bother me, it's the irritating things that bother me...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I'm bored.  I hate being off sick.  I spent all morning in bed, didn't wake up til after 12pm, had a shower which sapped all my strength, and then sat in bed for half an hour before even trying to get downstairs for some food.  I hate being ill too.  On the plus side, I haven't passed out again, so that can only be good...   Off the subject of illness, my baby fishies seem to be doing ok.  They're swimming about looking all happy and stuff, I'm still keeping my fingers crossed tho, it has only been a week!  Might be back later to add to this, might not...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        WeLl, I think thats the first time thats happened before.  I actually passed out in work today, one minute I'm stacking tins the next I'm on the floor.  Fortunately my brain waited until I was kneeling down before wandering off elsewhere, so I didn't hurt myself too much, five minutes earlier I had been standing on a stool, and if I'd done it then I'd have really done myself an injury.  I think it's due to this fluey type bug I seem to have picked up...It's my own fault tho, I should have stopped working and gone home when I started feeling unwell, but no, 'I'll be fine' I thought.  Obviously not.  Joan sent me home in a taxi once I'd stopped shaking enough to walk in a straight line.  I'm going to take the next few days off and see how I feel after that.  I've slept most of the afternoon away, and I feel a bit better, but I'm not great so I think I'll wander off and get a little bit more sleep...  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm naked.  Well almost, I decided to take my clothes off because I'm on my own in the house and I felt like it.  I just hope no one comes to the door!  I'm not in a particularly good mood.  I had a crap day at work..it's checkout tuesday again, Bob was being patronising again, and Joan is off on hols, so I have no one to stick up for me.  He thinks I'm an idiot.  It was hot coming out of work, after hammering down all morning, the weather changed dramatically to hot sun, and I had heavy shopping bags, and then, guess what..the bloody bus didn't turn up so I had to get different bus which meant I had to walk a bit to get another bus so I could get home.  The sun was so hot, and I missed the bus I wanted and my arms ached from carrying bags that I was nearly crying by the time I got to the bus stop.  And when I got home, Pete texted me to say he wasn't coming round like he'd said, because his brother was visiting.  I know it's not his fault, but I was upset anyway.  I feel a bit better now, I had some tea and fed all the animals (one of my duties while my parents are away), watched some TV.  I want to write, but my inspiration is a bit limited tonight.  Maybe tomorrow.  I'll stop now cos this is beginning to sound a little whingey and childish. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        In exactly one month I will be twenty six years old.  I've been alive for ywenty six years, and I feel like I haven't done anything.  Oh, I have adegree (the use it is), and I passed A levels and GCSE's, but since leaving uni what exactly have I done?  Nothing useful, I'm stuck working in a supermarket for peanuts.  I appear to be unemployable because I have no relevant experience and I'm crap at interviews.  The only thing that is good in my life is Pete, and I know I don't appreciate him enough.  Sometimes I take it for granted that he will always be there. I shouldn't because no-one knows what the future holds. I hope and pray that we will always be together.   I'm also putting on weight.  That is a bad thing, I don't want to get to the stage where none of my clothes fit me.  I will have to take up excercise, but I'm a really lazy person.  Oh, and I seem to be getting crows feet around my eyes.  :::sigh:::  I hate being old ;-) 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I hate nail buffing, but as I've just applied some acrylic overlays to my nails it is a necessary evil.  With any luck this should stop my nails bending whenever I catch them on things, and hopefully they will get a bit stronger because I won't be able to bite them either.  Thats the theory anyway.  They look a bit crap at the moment so it looks like I'll have to paint them and hope the boss doesn't say anything.  I so need a new job where it doesn't matter if I have nail varnish on or not.   I have missed Pete today.  He's off doing manly things with his mates in a caravan this weekend.  By manly things I mean getting drunk and very little else I guess ;-)   While he's been doing that, I've been down town and got my nail stuff, then went to the park for a bit and sunbathed with a book.  It wasn't as much fun as last weekend, cos he wasn't there, but I survived, just about.   Mum and dad go away on monday, they're going to Turkey.  Mum has been complaining that it's hot here, so I don't know how she will cope with the heat there.  It does mean I get the house to myself for a fortnight, so I will be able to have Pete round, and walk round the house with no clothes on.  I like doing that, it feels free.  Roll on monday! 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Weel, today.  What to say about today?   I got up, I got dressed, I went to work.  I got annoyed because it was busy and I was trying to do reductions on the chilled foods and Jean kept ringing her bell for assistance on the checkouts, and OF COURSE, I am the ONLY person that can POSSIBLY go on the tills.  It's infuriating.  It took me nearly two hours to finish them.  I had my lunch then, then Bob decided he was going to spring my progress review on me.  Ok so he did warn me last week when he gave me the booklet to read through and fill in, just that I hadn't got around to actually doing it yet.  It was a waste of time anyway, the usual, 'how do you think you're doing?', 'what can we do to make your life easier?' rubbish.  It makes no difference to how the shop works.  Anyway, Bob has put a couple of things down that I might get training for...well I say training...it's more like here you go, do this, you'll work it out eventually.   After work I went to the pictures with Pete, saw King Arthur.  I liked it, but Pete kept grumping about innacurate bits of history, and the lack of character in some of the characters.  I do have to say that Ray Winston's character, well it's a good character, but he's a little bit too Ray Winston, if you know what I mean?   Pete's a bit of a history geek, like the way I'm a rock geek...it's all good, history is more interesting to more people than rocks, and I like listening to him talk about it (but don't tell him I said that ;-)  ).  I still haven't told my mum and dad that I'm seeing Pete again.  To be homest I think maybe my mum has guessed, or at least suspects, but she hasn't asked.  They don't ask who I've been out with when I go out so what do they expect if I don't tell them stuff?  I will mention it soon though.   After the cinema we went to the pub, The Cherry Orchard, in Arrowe Park.  It's a nice pub, usually quiet, and it's right on the edge of the park, so it's good for night time walks.  The food isn't bad either.   I came home, had some weetabix, watched Poltergeist 3 because my dad was hogging the computer, wished I hadn't because it is a truly dreadful film, the best bit is laughing at the scary eighties haircuts and huge padded shoulders.   Well I came on here and read  urlLink my best mate's blog  for today, then, well I'm writing mine now.  It could have been a more interesting day, and easily a more boring one.  I really do need another job though.  Must make an effort.  Tomorrow I will look on the internet and see if I can find some suitable ones that I can apply for. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Urgh.  It is far too hot.  And not nice, sunny, dry hot either, it's strength sapping, mood-creating, humid and heavy hot.  On the plus side I think it might thunder storm again.   :::keeps fingers crossed:::  I'll let you know tomorrow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Adam stood silently beneath the spreading boughs of the old oak.  The earth was moist under his feet and the mist swirled lazily, dripping from the branches above onto his hair and shoulders.  He was motionless in the cool damp air, watching intently the lighted window a few yards in front of him.  The fog made him invisible, just another shadow blending into the greenery of the garden, able to observe unseen.   The girl sat on a wooden chair, gazing sadly at the mist.  Her eyes were dark pools of melancholy, her ebony hair hung  straight, past her shoulders like a waterfall of glistening black treacle.  She was slender and pale, beautiful and ageless, and Adam ached for her.   He stood and watched her all day, never moving once; observing her every movement, every expression that flitted across her face, until night fell.  Then he crept forward, peering through the glass to try and catch a glimpse of her, but the room was pitch black and no moon rose to shed light onto her ivory beauty.  As midnight approached Adam left, but the following morning he was back beneath the ancient oak, watching and waiting for an opportunity to speak to the woman.    Days passed.  Adam came every day to the garden to watch her.  He was captivated by her, by the way she moved, so graceful as she paced back and forth in the tiny room, the way she stared so sadly, yet expectantly through her window at the mist.  He watched and yearned to speak to her, but he could not bring himself to approach.  The mist was an ever present force, constantly swirling and distorting the garden around him, but one morning as he approached the oak to take up his viewing position the mist cleared for several moments.  Adam froze.  There she was, staring straight at him, her eyes wide with shock.  She pressed her palms against the glass of the window, staring hard at him as though she could not believe he stood there.  The mist swirled back and he fled under its cover, mortified that she had discovered him spying on her.  Ashamed by his furtive surveillance,  he vowed never to return, to leave the woman in the solitude she so obviously craved. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I'd just like to point out to anyone who read the story I wrote the other day, that it is not based on personal experience.  As my boyfriend pointed out to me this afternoon, a lot of people do write from experience, I as a rule don't often, I write from imagination or inspiration from other sources.  I'd like to make it absolutely clear that my boyfriend does not beat me up, and I've certainly never tried to kill him (even when I've been really mad at him!)  :-)  Happy now Pete?  :-p 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I love thunder storms, and we had a really amazing one tonight.  Heavy rolls of thunder, grumbling around the area, lightening sheeting across the steely sky.  The rain pelted the ground, battering like ball bearings and bouncing so it was like being rained on from two directions at once.  It was so awe inspiring it is impossible to describe and do it justice.   I watched most of it from the pub, I'd have been out there standing in the middle of it, but I was in my work clothes, and I need them for tomorrow.  I find storms thrilling, exhilarating.  They make me feel so small as well, it is one of the great shows that nature puts on to remind us of how insignificant we really are.  I love to watch them and stand in them and see the lightening dance and hear the thunder roar, like it's shouting its defiance to the world.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Sirens wail.  I can hear them through the glass and the curtains that cover the windows.  It is gloomy in here, an early dusk brought by the drapes that shut out the light - I like it that way, it shuts out the world.  I am sitting on the floor, my head bowed, staring at the filthy carpet between my feet.  My hand is shaking slightly, I think I am in shock.  Owen sits across from me, slumped untidily in the corner his legs akimbo, his eyes staring.  He hasn't spoken for a long time, and I dare not break the silence now.  I want to tell Owen how much I love him, that I'm sorry for hurting him, for being so typically me, but the words will not come.    Sirens wail.  They are closer now, almost at my street.  My body aches where Owen kicked me.  I think he cracked some ribs, and my eye is swollen shut where he punched me, but I don't hate him.  It's my fault anyway, I shouldn't have argued, it upset him, and now he will not speak to me.  The silence is thick between us.  I have to do something, I need to stop him hating me.  I crawl forward and put my hand on his shoulder, but his eyes are glazed and look straight through me.   'Owen?'  My voice sounds thin and frail in the darkness.  I get no response.  I touch his face with my fingers, trail them down his neck to his chest, to the warm, sticky flood that has stained his shirt.  I jerk my hand away as the last half an hour comes back to me in a rush.   Sirens wail.  The police are at the door now, shouting through the letter box, now bashing at the door with a heavy object.  I called them not long ago, shortly after my husband tried to strangle me in his rage.  Now I think he is dead. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I had a lovely day and night out with my boyfriend today.  We went down town to do a bit of shopping, then we went to the park and lazed for a while.  It was good to just do nothing, sitting on the grass and looking at the blue sky for a while.  We haven't had a chance to just chill together for a while and I had a really good time apart from getting a little bit sunburned.  Later on we went out in Hoylake with some of his friends and his brother and had a really good night.  I got a little bit drunk, am still a little bit drunk if I'm honest.   Me and Pete had a bit of a heart to heart about my mum.  It was the kind of conversation you can only have when you're a bit drunk, but it doesn't make it any less true.  The fact is Pete does not like my mum.  I can be honest about this and say that I can't really blame him.  She is overpowering, domineering, bossy and likes to get her own way all of the time.  That's not to say I don't love her.  I do, I love her to bits, but sometimes I don't like her very much, and I don't want to turn into a miniature version of her.  I feel very harsh writing this, but it's the truth.  I live in fear that one day I'm going to wake up, and be my mum.  Pete say's that's not going to happen, that I'm not like my mum, but I'm not so sure.  I can see a lot of traits in myself that my mum does, and I don't particularly like them.  Point in case...She has just told me off for being in and not have turned all the lights off yet, even though I'm STILL UP.  No, 'hi kate did you have a nice night?' no, 'are you ok?'  no, just moaning at me as usual.  She treats my dad like her own personal skivvy, he's not allowed to have opinions, neither is any one else in the family.  My brother has mamnaged to escape, he's getting married next year.  I did escape for a while, but had to move back in because of relationship and other difficulties.  It's only since I moved back in that I realised how bad it actually is.  She snipes, she moans constantly, she attacks virtually everything that my dad does behind his back to any family member that will listen.  God, this sounds terrible.  I don't mean to be so destructive about my mum, I do love her.  I don't blame her for how she is either, I think a lot of it is because of how she was brought up by my nan and constantly having her nan (my great grandmother) criticising.  I feel, I don't know, alienated in a place where I should feel at home, sometimes, not all the time.  I need my own space where I can be myself without having to agree with whatever my mum say or does or thinks.  I've worn myself out thinking about this tonight.  I feel guilty for thinking it, and eve guiltier for saying it out loud, but it had to be set into the open.    We got a taxi home me and pete.  The one we booked didn't turn up, but we got one eventually.  On the way home there was a message over the driver's radio.  It said...   'It's (the fare) at a big wedding, you can't miss it, there's a portaloo outside'.  A PORTALOO?  All I can say is...classy wedding! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>