<Blog>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      After much wasting of time deciding on what to name this, I decided on something girlier than what I probably should have put. Hmm...maybe shipping hell was a better name after all...Bah. Anyways, I need to go draw something. Ja ne =P  Icetigris
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, for Memorial Day weekend I had a  fine  time! Oh, yes indeed! It started out pretty well, I went to Ocean City, walked on the beach, playd DDR on the boardwalk (it was really L33t when people began to gather to watch me dance  ), fun, relaxing type stuff. But on the way back...  We were driving west on Route 50, on the part where you can't even see the eastbound lanes because of long stretches of forested median strip. Despite a pretty good-sized barrier, this guy was driving  THE WRONG WAY DOWN ROUTE 50 . My mom was driving, in our Honda Odyssey, and my sister was in the car too. We swerved to the left onto the grass to avoid him, but he hit us head-on. So I was just in a head-on collision.  WE'RE ALL OKAY because we were all wearing seatbelts  and the airbags deployed. Anyways, my mom told us to get out of the car and run because the other car, a '93 Dodge Colt, had caught on fire. We were afraid the cars were going to explode, so we ran like hell. Tons of people pulled over to see if we were okay and if the other people were okay; they called the police and ambulance and within probably 30 seconds, two state troopers were there and an ambulance, with two more on the way. Everybody was truly amazed that we were okay; the state troopers especially kept telling us that they were just amazed that we weren't hurt.   Anyways, it turns out that the other driver was  BLIND STINKING DRUNK because he had had 15 BEERS . This guy was so drunk, he actually openly admitted this to the state troopers and EMTs, not to mention the fact that he was so drunk he didn't even realise that he's been going the wrong way! He started making up excuses like "she was in my lane!" This guy as lucky to be alive; he had been wearing his seatbelt, but his wife had been asleep in the car and she hadn't been belted. Her head hit the windshield at 55 mph. People had to drag her out of the car and I saw her bleeding from the head. People were ripping up beach towels to make make-shift bandages to try to stop her from bleeding. I'm not sure if she's even alive now, but she's obviously seriously injured, probably irreversibly.   We eventually got into ambulances to go to the ER, just to make sure we were okay. My sister and I got our own ambulance, while my mom had to ride with the asshole who hit us. This was a  very  bad combination because my mom has high bood pressure and at this point she was freaking out because of the accident, making her blood pressure skyrocket. In the ambulance, this fucktard who was stupid enough to drink 15 beers and then get into a car, started accusing my mom of wrongdoing to the EMT, saying "she was in my lane and I'm gonna get blamed 'cause I was drunk." Yeah, no shit you're gonna get blamed, dumbass! Since when was it legal to drive around, drunk as a skunk?! Anyways, so my mom's blood pressure got so high that the EMT was worried that she was going to have a heart attack. So they hooked her up to a heart monitor and gave her an IV. Meanwhile, the other driver was spouting off some kind of stupid crap, which made the EMT get pissed off. From what my mom told me, the EMT said to the guy, "listen, buddy, if you're going to get beligerent, I'm going to have to restrain you!" And apparently he wanted someone else back there to help him out with the guy who hit us if he started something.   So anyways, after the ride (which was acutally kinda cool, in a very twisted sort of way) we got to the ER, went through triage and proceeded to wait around for 4 hours. We were supposed to pick my dad up in St. Michaels because he had gone sailing and his car was in Annapolis. We had called my dad from the accident scene, but my mom called him again so that he could come and pick us up when we were done at the hospital. At one point a state trooper came in to tell us that the other car was insured and that he had about 8 counts against this guy, including driving without a license (do we see a patter here with this guy?). He gave us some contact information and basically told us that this was going to take a while to be completely cleared up. Anyways, on a side note, my dinner that night was a couple of cherry pop tarts (with frosting) and some cinnamon mocha, both from vending machines in the ER waiting room. It was pretty lame.   So, after 4 hours of doing nothing, we finally get seen by a doctor. It turns out that had the ER people known we weren't as hurt as they thought we were, coming in from a head-on collision, we would have been seen HOURS EARLIER. I am totally failing to see that logic in this. They also kept getting me, my mom, and my sister mixed up. They never even asked me if I was in pain and thought that I wasn't hurt at all, the fucktards!!! I was actually in the most pain of the three of us, my chest really hurting from where the seatbelt was. So naturally I was even more pissed when my mom got an 800 mg dose of Motrin and I got nothing. Bastards. ANYWAYS, my mom and I got chest x-rays, but they didn't show anything. I'm convinced I have hairline fractures (which don't show up on x-rays) in some ribs, though, because it just hurts too much to be just cartilage or muscle. So, after that whole ordeal, my dad finally took us home. We got home around 2 AM, which sucked uberly.   The sort of cool thing about all this is that our next door neighbour and good friend is our lawyer in this case, and our neighbour up the street is our orthopaedist. To quote my mom, "The neighbourhood has mobilised!" And, of course, we get to get a new car now. I'll miss the Odyssey, though; 'twas a good car.  So remember (seriously, like no joking) wear your seatbelt and don't drink and drive. Me and my family came really close to dying because of a flamingly stupid drunk driver, but we were saved by the seatbelts.  Anyways, on a WAAAAAYYYYY lighter note, I tied for 2nd place in the FE club's last contest! Granted that was a while ago, but that doesn't mean I can't still revel in it for a while . I'm entering hopefully two pieces into this contest, as well as a piece into the Zelda Freak Hall contest and the SoA Fans contest (that is if finals don't completely eat all my brain cells ). Also, school will soon be over (THANK YE GODS) and I'll be a SENIOR!!!!!!!1111 I'm doing a research project over the summer, hopefully on coral conservation and genetics of zooxanthellae (don't worry, I don't expect you to know what that is ) at the National Zoo.  Anyways, I got work to do and sleep to...um...fish for? Yeah. x_x 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Most awesome cosplay EVER. I will be Samus Aran! Mwuahahahah!!!!!!!!! Ph33r m3 45 1 pwn j00!!!1&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>