<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A story from Olivia, almost verbatim: "Manera's sister and grandmother died in the Nazi war. But, the happy part is she found a new grandmother and sister. Gracie had a brother. Gracie didn't want to be the new sister, so her brother is going to be Manera's sister now. The grandmother's name is First William Born in Springtime. And, the funny part is she's not even dead yet. She's 88, but she's not dead." 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Staying up late is screwing up everything. When I don't have enough sleep, I want to drink coffee, which I don't drink, and I want to eat chocolate, which I don't want to eat. At the very least I want to eat  something . I think I should go home and take a nap. But, I rode my bike today, and I the thought of riding home right now is pretty daunting. I can barely hold my head up! 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Everytime I've written in my journal about being happy, or about loving something, or thinking someone is cool, I read it later, and am embarrassed at my past self's gullibility, my optimism, and my inability to grasp just how shitty things really are. For years, I've been reluctant to write when I'm happy, fearing the judgement of my future self.   My worst fear is that I won't be nice to myself? Don't I have  any  control over that? So, here's the happiness in my life that I'm afraid I'll be embarrassed about later. I'm involved in the ultimate fodder for good jokes. I've joined a 12-step program. I even believe in it. I joined in September '03, 8 months ago. We do group recitations, much to my horror. We talk about God, much to my horror. We routinely divulge too much personal information, much to my horror. And, much to my horror, I love it all. Cynical me is buying in, and not just a little bit.  And I haven't had a drink in 8 months. And I have hope for the future. And I feel joy... somewhat to my horror. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Martha had an appointment this morning, so I stayed home with Olivia. How awful is it that I don't want to pretend that a new baby has been born and Olivia is the mother, and I'm the grandmother, and Olivia is leaving on a plane to pick up the baby, and when she returns the grandmother is going to cry for joy to see the new baby, and ask to hold her, and ask questions about the flight, about the birth family, and about the baby? How awful is it that I don't want to play this game over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over and over? 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       When I finalize the sale of my business at the closing, I will be getting a chunk of money. It's not a big chunk, but a chunk none-the-less. Also, I will become unemployed. So, the chunk of money won't be replinishing itself. I want to start another company, so I want to live on the chunk, which means it will be diminishing every day, little by little. If I don't start making money eventually, the chunk will all disappear.   Which brings me to my car. I love my car. It's a 1999 turbo charged VW Beetle. It has leather. It has a CD player. It has heated seats. It has a power moonroof. It has everything. I keep it clean, and make sure all of its maintenance is done on time. When I bought the car, I planned to have it forever. I planned to keep it into its antique-hood.   Alas, it doesn't really make sense to have a car payment when my chunk is diminishing, especially when my office is less than a mile from where I live. We have two cars, and can surely get away with one. Martha's car is paid for, and is more practical for a growing family. (What  isn't  more practical for a growing family than a Beetle?)   After a few months of fighting the facts, I bought a bicycle, and advertised my car for sale in this weekend's paper. Here's the thing. No one called. Not one call. I double-checked to make sure the ad was there, and the number is correct. It's a little like making a joke and having no one laugh. Or, like George Costanza, saying I Love You, and having the other person not say it back. The ad runs for a month. I am trying not to take it personally. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Olivia (our 4-year-old) has imaginary dog friends. There's a core group of them including Manera, Pitty-Pat, Puppy, Wiggers, Nina, Keiffer and Gracie. I can trace some of their origins. Pitty-Pat is the name of my mother's dog; Gracie is our "real" dog; Nina and Keiffer are the names of Olivia's stuffed animals. I think Wiggers and Puppy might be the names of stuffed dogs, too. Keiffer, the stuffed animal, has been missing for over a year, but that doesn't seem to have occurred to Olivia. At any rate, it hasn't stopped him from headlining in her stories about these dogs.   Aside from the core group, many other characters, most of them dogs, appear in Olivia's stories, sometimes as her children, or as the children or parents of some of the other dogs. For example, sometimes, Manera will have 37 children. Or, Olivia will talk of her 8 or 12 or 76 children who are participating in the latest adventure.   Olivia tells stories about her dogs all day, every day. Today will be each of their birthdays. Some of them will have a baby. Some of them will get married. Some will break up. Some will "get the call" that a new baby has been born and wants them to be their mother - although ususually that honor is reserved for Olivia herself.   The cool thing is how Olivia conveys her understanding of the world through her stories about herself and these dogs.   Lately, however, no matter what Martha or I says about anything, Olivia tells a similar story, usually about Manera, but sometimes about the other characters.   Yesterday, I told a story about being in a motorcycle accident when I was in my early 20s. Olivia told us that Manera was in a motorcycle accident, too. She explained the surgery, how much it hurt when they did the xrays, how they had to put a pin in Manera's arm, how she had a total of 3 casts, how the hair grew on Manera's arm underneath the cast. Wow! I didn't know Manera rode a motorcycle.   A few minutes later, Martha told a story about having knee surgery when she was 12. Guess what? Nina had the same surgery. Most of the time I appreciate her friends and their meaning in her life. Most of the time.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink FireGirl's Hot Sauce Catalog : This is the business I sold. As I write this, it hasn't closed yet. At this point, the closing is set for Tuesday, the 3rd of June, 2004, our 6th closing date. Today was the 4th closing date, but we haven't finished all the paperwork yet.   Really, I'm just testing this "blog this web page" button on the  urlLink Google Tool Bar . Oh my. I really  don't  have anything to say. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Somehow I have this idea that I could write something that someone else might want to read. There's nothing in my life's experiences that would lead me to this thought. I am not a writer, not a good story-teller, and don't have anything in particular to say. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       FireGirl is now sold. And, I don't know who I am, or what I'm supposed to be doing with my life.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My mother called to tell me my stepfather (Carl) is urinating blood. They are making an appointment with a urologist, but in the meantime, she's a nurse, and seems to think it could be one of three things: 1) nothing; 2) prostate - and if it's prostate, it could be something benign, or it could be prostate cancer; or 3) bladder cancer.   To report that Carl is 80 years old is to deliver a not-quite-accurate description. He's healthier than I am. He is fit, trim, in good shape, and in perfectly good health... except for the pissing blood part. Oh, and except for the dizzy spells. About a year ago he started experiencing dizzy spells. The doctors discovered he has a partially blocked artery in his neck. An operation would be very risky, so they've opted not to do it. So, occassionally, he'll be driving along, and will almost pass out. I asked him whether he thinks he's still safe to drive, and he says, "Well, when I start to get dizzy, I pull over." Nice system.   That he is urinating blood is scary. I always expected him to die of... well, maybe I never expected him to die. But, I especially cannot picture him wasting away with some disease. Maybe it's nothing. Or, maybe it's something, but easily curable. Still, having him be sick, even a little bit, will force me to face his mortality. As much as we've disagreed and fought about things over the years, I am definitely not ready for him to die.    I  am not ready for him to die. Yep. It's all about me. What isn't?    
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've received two calls about my Beetle. The first call was from a guy who was looking for a diesel version of my car. Mine burns gasoline. The second call was from a salesperson, trying to sell me an ad on  urlLink The Big Lot . I can't say I'm encouranged.  I'm still scheduled to close on the business tomorrow, but the buyers won't get here today in time to count the inventory. We'll have to count tomorrow, but all delays are making me nervous.   Yesterday, I rode my bike 4 miles to a meeting, and then the 4 miles back. I know it doesn't sound like much, but since getting the bike, I haven't been very sure of myself. I am especially not sure about going up hills. So, the longest trip I had taken on the bike up until then was about a mile. Granted, it was a mile that included a VERY STEEP hill, but still, it's just a mile. After going the 4 miles, and then actually making it back, too, I felt strong and capable. I guess it's all relative.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>