<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was amazing.   A terrible storm swept through Tennessee and I loved it. There were tornado warnings out all over the place and it thundered and lightning'ed all night. Dee and I were sure that the electricity would go out at some point, so I lit some candles in preparation and we sat in the living room as the house shook with each huge thunder.   Before we knew it, it was 2 in the morning. The worst of it had passed, but there was still a distant rumble on a pretty regular basis. I'm not sure why I find thunderstorms so cool, but last night was a good one.   The power never went out. Maybe next time.   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just finished a book called "Join Me!" written by Danny Wallace. It was a quick read and an amazing story.   It's the true story about a guy who accidentally started a cult. He's an Englishman who was bored and mixed with a recent family member passing away, decides to put an ad in the paper that simply says "Join Me!" and asks people to send him a photo of themselves. And that's it. He doesn't say what they're joining (and he actually doesn't know himself) and is surprised to find that people begin to join him and his undetermined cause.   It's a humorous and entertaining ride to see people jump on board and watch Danny scramble to figure out what exactly it is he's asking people to join him in doing. I highly recommend it. Again, it's a really quick read (I'm not a fast reader and I sped through it in 2 days) and very uplifting as well.   On a side note, I finished importing all of my movie soundtracks into my iTunes. Now, with only soundtracks and comedy albums, I have 1703 tracks (4 days of music).   Now what.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've finally finished importing all of my comedy albums into my iTunes. I had a lot more than I thought. 599 cuts, 1.5 days worth of non-stop hilarity. Very cool!   Today I begin importing my soundtracks. Lights. Camera. Action.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was the first Poker Night in a long long time and it was really good to see and catch up with some of the guys (it was a rather small Poker Night...only 5 of us).   Poker didn't start until 7, so Gabe and I met Chico at Gotee at 5:30 when they closed, I had the PS2 in tow, and we played video games at the office for a bit until it was time to drive around the corner to Jeff's house and begin the festivities.   I did pretty well for most of the night...won a couple of "big" hands (or at least big hands to me) but by the end of the night, I had whittled it down to my usual small stack of chips and decided to go all in on the last hand just because I didn't feel like counting out any change. I lost, but I didn't mind. It was a good night.   Afterward Chico and Gabe and I went to the movies to see "Envy." Ugh. Poor Ben Stiller. I mean, I'm glad that he's able to work and stay busy, but he needs to learn how to say "No" once in a while. Such a big steaming hunk of crap I have not witnessed in a long long time. I actually considered walking out a few times, and if you know me, you know that I don't walk out on movies. But "Envy" was as big a pile of dog crap as ever came out of Hollywood. It actually only made me mad. Why aren't people paying ME millions of bucks to write movies? I can write bad movies, too, if that's what they're looking for. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night Gabe came over to play. It was an excellent excellent evening. He came over yesterday in the mid-afternoon and we played a bunch of PS2 games and talked and messed around on the computer and went to Fat Mo's and hung out with Dee after she got back from work....it was a lot of fun. And I just realized he was over for like 12 hours! That's crazy! But I guess that's when you know you have good friends with cool hang time, because it felt like he was over for like 3 hours. Very cool. A good man, that Gabriel is.  This morning I went to the bartending school to check it out. Pretty cool. Not too shabby. Definitely thinking about it. Deanna might have to go to NY for a bit next month. Maybe I'll do it while she's gone. She'll come home to a professional mixologist.   I think Homer our cat might have caught my cold. He's being an idiot.   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The audition today was one of the quickest I'd ever been to. They were looking for someone to stand-in for the Jesus that had already been cast, so basically either I look like the guy already cast or I don't.   They had me go in, take off my shirt, hold my arms out to the side like I was on a cross and then turn to the left and then turn to the right and that was it.   So who knows.  They had me stand there for a long time and I am proud to say that my arms didn't twitch or move. I was rock steady baby.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Indie comics annoy the heck out of me.   You know those "cool" indie magazines that every city has...a lot of times it's the city's paper that lists all of the happenings for the weekend or what have you (here in Nashville, it's "The Nashville Scene"). And toward the back of the paper right before the ads for bi and lesbian couples they have a page of comics that are too cool for me. The main character is usually a triangle with a beret and a little bug sidekick that go around doing nothing and making remarks about it, pretending to be deeper and more insightful than it really is. Usually it's barely even a cartoon because each panel is crammed with so many words, there isn't any room for the artist left to draw in.   Like they'll be at the grocery store and Triangle Head says "Hey do you know that the gorvernment is watching everything we do?" and the bug will say, "It's true." And then a guy who looks like a cartoon from the '50s will pop his head in and say, "That's right folks! The government hates you but now I have Brill Creme!" and in the last panel Triangle Head says "But the beaurocratic sense of development sure can't compare to the investigative crack journalism I see everyday on my local news affiliate!"  These things don't annoy me because they're comics yet aren't funny or interesting or because they are so presumptuous. It's not the fact that it's not even really a comic but a rant (and I don't mind rants...that's what THIS is...but the fact that they are trying to disguise their rant as a comic is insulting).   I think the fact that annoys me the most is that I know they are getting paid to draw and write bad comics.   No fair.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A pretty cool way to end the day....  Dee and I decided to go to the theater and check out Shrek 2. Dee was so cute. She was so excited to go to the movies (as was I...I don't know how long it's been!).   Shrek 2 was amazing (did we expect anything less?). And it's always easy to tell when Dee likes a movie because, as we were leaving the theater (be sure to stay after it's over...there's a bonus scene about halfway trhough the credits!) she said, "We need to buy that."   And that reminds me. We like to sit through the credits most of the time. Sometimes we're pleased to find a little bonus scene midway through the credits or after they've rolled and there's a little surprise at the end. It always makes me feel a little superior to the people who needed to race out of the theater to be first ones out the door. Ha ha suckers! We get more movie!!  Upon leaving the theater, Deanna asked if I wanted to go see   Van Helsing   as well. Wow, cool! I'm usually the one that loves seeing two movies at a time, but I have to go by myself because Deanna doesn't usually like to sit in a theater for that long (so I go see the scary movies that she wouldn't want to see anyhow) so of course I jumped at the chance to see a double feature!   It was also a lot of fun. It won't win any Oscars (maybe visual effects) but it was a good summer popcorn movie and Deanna was scared and held onto my arm and of course, that made it all worth it.   We came home, ordered pizza, and I'm in love with my wife. Not bad for a Monday.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got a call from my agent. They are sending me to an audition tomorrow to audition (I believe) for the role of Jesus. HA HA HA. I'm not sure what it's for, but I do know it's a photo shoot. The same company is also wanting me to do a voice-over audition where I have to read some Bible passages. One of their stipulations, though, is that the person has to have a hairy chest.   So that's what I learned today. Apparently Jesus had a hairy chest. Groovy.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm thinking about going to bartender school. Could be fun. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was to be my first day at a fancy shmancy hotel here in Nashville. I was kind of excited to be working full-time but also kind of not excited because I would have to be there at 6am every morning.   They didn't tell me specifically what I was supposed to wear, so I looked it up in the "appearance" section of the worker's manual they gave me last week. It said that if you don't have a uniform, guys are supposed to wear a collared shirt with black dress pants and shoes. You don't have to wear a tie, but if you choose not to, you have to wear a jacket.   I opted for the jacket.   As I was getting ready this morning, I was sad that I had a job where I had to dress up every day. Oh well. It was work, and they offered benefits.   Donna, the lady in Human Resources who originally contacted me for the job, lost her job last week. When I was there to fill out papers, she informed me that the hotel was being bought out and her position had been eliminated. Lot of that going around. Yikes. Not even hired yet and already my first boss has been fired. My new boss is Jennifer and she told me to meet her in front of the gift shop at 6AM on Monday morning.   "6AM. In front of the gift shop."  "6AM in front of the gift shop," she repeated.   So it's Monday, 6AM, and I'm in front of the gift shop. The gift shop doesn't open until 6:30 AM and no one is inside. There's a table and chairs conveniently located in front of the shop. I have a seat.   And I sit.   I wonder if I get my new employee locker today.   And I sit.   I wonder where the lockers are. I've only heard of them; never seen them.   And I sit.   I wonder where the breakroom is. I get a half hour for lunch. All I brought was a Power Bar, some granola bars, and bottled water because I don't know if they have an employee fridge and/or microwave. I mean, I  assume  that they do, but I knew that if I brought anything that needed heated or cooled, that the particular device needed would be unavailable or out of order.   And I sit some more.   The people here seem nice but no one else is wearing a jacket and shirt. Everyone else has on uniforms. I wonder if gift shop workers get uniforms, too. I hope it's  not the black vest-over-white shirt combo. I don't want to wear that unless I'm dealing blackjack.   It's been 45 minutes and nothing.   I decide to call the hotel and it dawns on me that I have truly been ill-informed to begin my day. I should have clocked in by now, right? Where do I get my time card? I haven't been given the tour of the labryinthian employee maze that is downstairs.  The hotel operator answers and I ask for Jennifer.   And then I find out that Jennifer has been fired, too.   So what about me? Jennifer hired me and I'm supposed to start today.   Apparently when they got rid of Jennifer and Donna, they also got rid of everything they were taking care of. Including me.   So I've already been fired?   Basically.   Awesome.   I'm going back to bed.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A new Chinese Restaurant, CHINA DRAGON, has opened up around the corner. I like to frequent their fine establishment and it's gotten to the point where they recognize me when I phone in my order and carry on great conversation while I go in to pick up my food. Yesterday when I went in they threw in a FREE DESSERT! How cool is that. I feel like such a part of the neighborhood now. It was a cool adventure and a nice warm fuzzy feeling.   And speaking of the people in my neighborhood, I have become hooked on a Broadway musical that I have never seen. Those of you who know me know that I am into acting, but most of my knowledge is in movies. I haven't seen many musicals and even fewer plays. There is a new musical, though, that is at the same time a biting satire on "Sesame Street" and current events. I'm a huge fan of parody (but only when it's done right...lame parody is just...well, lame (are you listening, Apologetix??)) but the fine folks who put together "Avenue Q" are geniuses. I saw a small bit of their performance during the Tony awards and I was like "Hm." I did a search online and downloaded a couple of songs to test it out and was hooked. The next day I went out and bought the CD (not all people who download songs are evil, eh?) and I can't stop listening to it.   If you're able to get up to NYC, check this show out. "The Lion King" used to be the Broadway show that I "had to see" but I believe the animals of Africa have been bumped by some foul-mouthed puppets from New York. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The weekend is over and the results are in. "Dodgeball" was the highest grossing movie of the week, smashing it's opening-weekend competition, "The Terminal" starring Tom Hanks and directed by Steven Spielberg.   I didn't get to go see "Dodgeball" (but believe me, I want to) but I did catch "The Terminal." I've read some reviews and seen some reviews on TV and some of them have been less-than-flattering. Please let me take this time out to encourage you to ignore those reviews and check it out for yourself.   I hate to tell people to go see movies because when people tell ME that a movie is amazing and what have you, my expectations are always really high and inevitably I am disappointed. I don't want to do that to you. But I   do   want to encourage you to check it out. Tom Hanks does an amazing job and by the first 5 minutes, I forgot that I was watching "Tom Hanks."   Two fun things to talk about after the film is over:  1. It was inspired by actual events. If you pass it off as "oh that could never happen," then know this. There is a guy (I believe from a middle Eastern country) who has been living in a French airport for the last   fifteen   years.   2. You'd think they had to shut down parts of an airport in order to film everything, but they actually REBUILT AN AIRPORT TERMINAL inside of two huge airplane hangars, and you'd never know. Amazing.   But now I'm ready to grab life by the ball....
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A couple of days ago I went to Office Depot to buy some mailing envelopes. Upon checking out, the cashier told me that if I called the number on my receipt and took part in their customer service survey, at the end of the phone call I would be given a secret code that would give me $5 off my next purchase at their fine establishment.   I thought that was awesome. Each pack of envelopes that I got was about five bucks, and since I knew that I would probably be going back soon for more, that meant that one of the packs would be free. FREE I SAY!!  The time had come to purchase more and I went back today. On the way there I had it all figured out. I'll buy two more packs, one of them will be free, and then I'll take THAT receipt, do the survey thing again, and get another $5 off and go back for two more in a few days where one of them would be free and so on down the line. I had found a loophole (kind of like the pudding tops and free air miles in "Punch Drunk Love") and I would soon be swimming in free mailing envelopes! The genius of my plan!!!!!  But this time when I checked out I just got a regular dumb old receipt with no option of a survey. Just an itemized list of my two packs of envelopes.   It seems the marketing geniuses at Office Depot are one step ahead of me. Well played, Office Depot. Well played.  
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight while watching "The Next Action Hero" (I'm hooked already) I was playing with my dog Soda during the commercial breaks. She would chase me around and I would tackle her and we would play fight and all that but of course I emerged triumphant and won.   Every time.   So the show started back up and I sat back on the couch and she got some water and then walked up to me and put her nose in my face like she wanted to give me a kiss so I bent down to scratch her head and SHE BELCHED IN MY FACE and then ran away.   She's a clever one.   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was a really long day. Not sure why. It wasn't a bad day, it just seemed to last forever. Probably because Deanna's away on a gig for a while. She got a call from a theater up in Albany about doing another production of "Ain't Misbehavin" and flew out yesterday. The director of the production here in Nashville recommended her to a colleague who was looking to fill a role, so that was cool.   She'll be gone for about a month and a half which means I can listen to Weird Al really loudly in the house for a couple of weeks. And Robbie Williams. I've just started getting into his music. Good stuff.   You know, for a Brit.   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some good friends of ours, Pete and Kelli, are leaving town (and in turn cutting the population of Mexicans in Franklin in half by doing so). They and their two children have packed up their house and are moving to the San Fernando Valley in California. So many mixed emotions when friends leave....and when they are moving to California, one of those emotions is jealousy. They'll be back in the land of In & Out Burgers and IKEA!  Although they were able to pack most of their things in the truck, there were some things they had to end up giving away. One of the things that was passed on to me is something I am proud to have.   Once I went over to their house and saw that in front of one of Pete's paintings he had on the wall, he had a really fancy schmacny addition to the display. Two of those gold posts with a velvet rope between them like you see in an art gallery to keep people back or in a movie theater to keep people in the ticket queue. I had to ask where they got such a cool set-up. Pete went on to explain that he had gone to the movies once in Franklin and apparently had a very bad experience with the staff. On his way out, he grabbed the posts and velvet rope and continued out the door. No running or scrambling, just walking out like he was on a mission. And I guess he was. That was his little piece of retribution from Tha Man and I thought it was both crazy and amazing that he got away with it. And those posts are HEAVY. I was impressed even more last night when I picked them up to load them in the car.   So now I have a cool little piece of furniture with an even cooler story behind it.  Pete leaves tomorrow to make the drive out to Cali, and I'll be back over today to see him off and wish him the best. Have a safe trip, Ortas. You'll be misssed.   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a few days since I've posted anything. I've been painting the outside of the house, and the heat and humidity have drained any and all creative juices from my poor lifeless body.   Working out in the heat, I get really super thirsty. In our fridge there are like 4 beers left over from a dinner party Deanna and I had. I don't recall who brought the beers, but they left them with us, and neither of us are beer drinkers. The last time I even tasted a beer was back in the '70s. I was just a kid, and my dad let me taste his while we were visiting some relatives. It was disgusting. Yech.   And so I never had a beer after that. Just the smell of it would bring that taste back in my mouth, and kind of quenched any desire I had to taste it again.   But I was working out in the sun, and when you work out in the sun, you're supposed to have a beer when you're done, right? That's what manly men do. And I've grown a bit since I was 6 and my tastes have been refined and matured, so who knows. Maybe NOW I like beer. Maybe beer is like asparagus. You hate it when you're a kid, but then when you get older you realize it's actually really good.   So I popped open a Blatt Blue or whatever it's called and had it.   It took me like an hour and a half to drink it. It was disgusting, but I didn't want to be wasteful. So I sipped. And squinted. And sipped. And squinted.   90 minutes I put myself through that. Phew.   Beer is still gross.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've spent most of this week painting the front of our house. It's gone from a bland light-gray color to vibrant and fun orange and blue (sounds weird, I know, but looks really cool). My right arm is sore from holding the gallon of paint the whole time, but all is well. Yesterday while I was painting the front door, I decided my music selection of choice would be CARMAN'S GREATEST HITS. I'm not sure why. But part of the door stuck to itself and peeled the paint off. It was wet and rainy and I think that's why the paint didn't dry as quickly, causing it to stick to itself when we left and closed the door. Other people would blame the peeling paint on the music that was being played.  Dee and I met Gabe and Bethany for dinner at a new Italian restaurant in town, Mafiaoza's. None of us had been there before and it was a lot different than most of us expected. I think we had pictured a middle to higher class place with a lot of brick inside and tall booths and what have you. It was a pizza parlor. So that was weird.   Then we went out to Opry Mills to have dessert and show Gabe and Bethany the new restaurant Aquarium. It, again, was very cool and the desserts were quite good.   After that we went to see "The Day After Tomorrow," mostly because it was the only movie that had any showtimes that started after 10. It was actually pretty good and much better than all of us expected it would be. The effects were amazing and even though I've read the events are pretty implausible, the moviemakers still did a good job of convincing you that it COULD happen. It was a fun summer blockbuster kinda-movie.   The paint cans are calling, so I must be off. To see what our house looks like with it's new exterior, swing on by. I'll make coffee.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 8:30AM and I am exhausted. Most people are probably already out and about, but when you're out of steady work and in charge of your own hours, going back to sleep because you're still tired is one of the luxuries that suckers who work don't have. :)   I got a message from a friend this weekend about the possibility of doing some comedy at the Creation Festival (think Woodstock for Christians). That would be a lot of fun, but right now it's just a possibility (and probably a remote one at that) so who knows. :)  I'm not quite sure what's up with me ending each paragraph with a smiley face icon-thing. I'm usually quite annoyed at that but this morning I suppose I have decided to annoy myself. I'm just like that. :)   Hung out with Gabe almost all day yesterday. Went to his place and watched some of the stuff he'd created in years past. It was fun and that kind of thing is always inspiring. We talked about making a kung fu movie just for the heck of it. Again, one of those luxuries that you people with real jobs would know nothing about. How many of you can sit around all day and make homemade kung fu movies? Or even consider it?   That's what I'm saying. Being out of steady work is very underrated.   :)
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today ended up to be a really great day, and when I woke up this morning I had no idea where I would be 12 hours later.  Gabe called to invite me to see Earth Wind & Fire and Chicago live in concert! It seems his dad goes wayyyyy back with the EW&amp;F guys, and he was able to snag 4 passes for Gabe. So there we were, only about 10 rows back and smack dab in the center. We also got special "Guest passes" that we hoped would get us backstage, but no one working at the Starwood Amphitheater seemed to know what we could and couldn't do with them. Fools!  Earth Wind & Fire put on an amazing show. I've never been much of a fan of music from the '70s (I still hold fast to my theory that nothing good came out of the '70s), but I'm not so anti-70s that I can't appreciate a good show when I see one, and EW&amp;F definitely put on a good show. The sound was amazing, Philip Bailey has a range that would make Mariah Carey cuss, and the horn section was unbelievable. They had the entire crowd on their feet...and then Chicago came on stage and bored everyone to tears and they played their little power ballads and all the white girls in their late-30s stood up and raised their hands and sang along and wished they were back at Senior Prom again.  Luckily EW&F came back onstage at the end and both bands played together. The sound was, again, amazing.  Even more entertaining, though, was watching Phillip Bailey spot Gabe during the show, recognize him, and tell him to go backstage. It was great!! After the show Gabe and I found out what the magical Guest Passes were for. There was a holding room of sorts where a "meet & greet" was going on, so Gabe and I waited in that area to figure out how to get backstage from there when suddenly a voice called out and there was Phillip Bailey. Making his way through the crowd, he had come out in search of Gabe (and me, since I was with Gabe). That was really really cool. He took us backstage and introduced us to the other 2 founding members and we got to hang in his dressing room for a bit and try to carry on good conversation.  All in all, a great night. Lots of fun and it won't soon be forgotten!  I still think that 70s music is horrible, but at least I am learning that the people who make it can sure put on a great show.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yikes. What a week it's been. Methinks this blog entry will be a lengthy one, so tuck in the kids and make sure you're comfortable. I am about to embark on a tale of pain and agony, and I think what struck me most during this encounter are the random thoughts that popped into my head and I actually considered. Observe:   I woke up Monday morning at 6:30 with an excruciating pain in my left side. It felt like I had just done a million oblique crunches and now my obliques were going into spasm. It was more than just an upset stomach kind of feel where everything is a bit woozy, but it felt like something inside of me exploded. I briefly wondered if it might be my appendix but then I remembered that the appendix is on the right side of the body. I then went on to wondering if perhaps I was a medical anomaly and MY appendix is on my left side and what do you know, it done blew up.   My next thought went to “hernia.” I’d never had one of those before, but I know it’s a really sharp and sudden pain in the side. But I was also pretty sure that when you got a hernia, something stuck out of the side of your body like a lump (I learned that from “Friends” and the old Bill Cosby routine) and since my side appeared normal in appearance, I discounted that as well.   All the while, I was in unbelievable pain. I wondered if this is what a gunshot victim felt.   I really didn’t want to have to call an ambulance or anything, just because they cost money, something of which we don’t have a lot of lately. I lay there a bit longer hoping that it would at least subside a bit, but no such luck. The pain was constant and the pain was extreme. &nbsp;I briefly considered driving myself somewhere, but had no idea if I was going to pass out and run over a fleeing Eddie George or not.   I lay in bed, one hand on my side, my eyes scrunched and my teeth clenched and I was MAD. I was mad that I had no idea what was wrong with me and I was going to have to spend money on medical attention. I was mad that I had a job interview the next day and might have to miss it. And I was mad that I was in so much FREAKING PAIN.   There is a fire station just a few blocks from our house and an ambulance is also housed there. I heard the sirens wind up and begin to wail. Seconds later I heard the ambulance zoom past the house. I shouted, “No, that one’s mine!” but I don’t think they heard me. I chuckled to myself but it hurt.   Suddenly I tasted metal in the back of my mouth. You know how blood has that distinct metallic taste? Well, I tasted it and my mouth suddenly filled up with liquid. Great. Was I about to commence vomiting blood? I briefly wondered where my video camera was and if the battery was charged. It might make for some awesome footage.   I didn’t bother with the camera and instead made it to the bathroom. I knelt over the bathtub and spat. Whew. It was just spit. No sign of blood. But it sure tasted like blood. And my mouth kept filling with saliva. I spat and spat and spat and couldn’t stay ahead of it. Finally my saliva glands slowed down.   I wanted to call an ambulance, but I just woke up and my hair was crazy from the sleep. Should I jump in the shower first? Or maybe just stick my head under the faucet and wet it? Or maybe I should just bring a hat. A hat would be fine. But what if they need me to take the hat off and then my hair would really be insane. And I might leave my hat there. Screw that. I’m not leaving my hat at the freaking hospital.   I grabbed the phone and dialed 911. It rang once and I hung up. I can’t afford an ambulance. Maybe I’ll wait a few more minutes and see if I’m good to drive.   The phone rang in my hand. Wretched caller ID. “Did someone call 911?” they asked. And I gave in.   “I think I need an ambulance.” The pain was making my voice really raspy and it was hard to get enough breath to finish an entire sentence.   We exchanged info and I remember congratulating myself on how even keel and levelheaded I had been. I had remembered all my vital info and even told them I’d turn on the porch lights for them. If I were in a movie and I got shot I wouldn’t be the wimp that falls down and tells everyone else to “Go on!!” Doggonit I would be the guy who lags behind and slows the group down but keeps on going and then gets shot again LATER.   I put the dog outside. Who knows how long I’ll be gone. A few minutes later a fire truck pulled up and some fireman dudes came to the door. They were going to stay with me while they waited for another ambulance, since the one down the street was on another call. I knew it. I sat on the couch holding my side while two of the firemen sat beside me and asked me questions and a third perused my bookshelf. I seriously thought he was going to ask to borrow a book he was looking that hard.   In the meantime, the incredible pain continued. I tried to be a polite host but it was hard doubled-over and wishing one of them would just clock me in the head with a tire iron and put me out of it already. One of the firemen told me there wasn’t much else they could do unless I needed oxygen. I was about to tell them I’d give that a shot when the EMS pulled up. I was excited. My first ambulance ride and here we go!!   We all got up, I locked up the house, and they walked me out to the ambulance. The driver was a huge overweight guy with a moustache that made him look like Mario from the video game. I’m thinking his shirt had a stain on the front of it, but my memory might be adding that slight detail because if there wasn’t a stain on his shirt, one definitely needed to be there to complete the picture. Ambulance Jane came around the other side. She was short with a buzz cut hairdo that made me wonder and helped load me in. I tried to make eye contact to smile and kind of nod hello but she paid me no attention. Instead she started talking to one of the firemen about a friend of theirs who had a baby and yadda yadda yadda. After I was all strapped in and I thought we should be on our way, we continued to sit there while they continued to talk about the new baby. I don’t know if the pain actually got worse or it only seemed to get worse since I was beginning to get angry and impatient. Let’s go, Emergency Jane!   Finally Emergency Jane seemed to have told Fireman Bob all of the info she had on the new baby and Fireman Bob left. He closed the doors and we were off!!   Sort of. First of all, I noticed that we were cruising without the siren. Rip-off! The second thing I noticed is we were going about 30 miles an hour. Stopping at all of the stop signs and stop lights. I could see cars passing us. And I was like what the heck is THIS?? Let’s go!! You obviously can do nothing to alleviate my pain, can we at least get to the people who can a little quicker?   During the ride I tried to be light-hearted and make jokes with Ambulance Jane but she either didn’t get any of them or wasn’t interested because I wasn’t a hot girl. I remember saying “Boy being in an ambulance is so much more anti-climactic without the exciting chase music in the background.” Yuk yuk yuk. I thought I would at least get a friendly smile. Instead she answered, “We hardly ever drive with the siren on. We probably only turn it on 5% of the time and that’s only if someone is dead.”   All right, Ambulance Jane, you crazy party girl you.   I finally get to the hospital. Ambulance Jane tells me to feel better and I secretly tell her to fall in a hole. They wheel me into what looks like an examination room in a doctor’s office instead of the standard “hospital room” and that’s fine with me (maybe cheaper!). Nurse #1 comes in and asks me all of the questions and I give her the rundown. She asks me how much pain I am in on a scale of 1 to 10. At first I say 10 but then tell her on the grand scheme of things compared to other people who’ve had metal pipes lodged in their heads, it’s probably only an 8. Nurse #1 laughed and I thought “All right.” At least it’s not my material. The ambulance was probably just a bad crowd.   I’m still not sure why I feel the need to make people laugh, even when I am in pain. Shouldn’t it be the other way around? Shouldn’t people be trying to entertain me? I think it’s just another classic Ed example of putting others in front of myself. I don’t want my pain and inconvenience to make them feel uncomfortable, so away I go. I don’t know. Just a theory. Not like I know what I’m talking about or anything.   Nurse #1 said, “But this is the most pain you’ve ever been in, right?”   Definitely right.   She wondered if I had kidney stones and I thought that was odd. I’d heard guys’ horror stories about kidney stones and thought there was only pain when they were actually trying to pass the stone. But what do I know. I only realized that the U.K. was an island last year and I’m 33 freaking years old.   Nurse #1 left and Admissions Nurse came in and took all of my information. After a few minutes, Admissions Nurse left.   And there I was all alone. Just laying there and then the saliva started up again. I felt like I was going to puke and I sat up. There were two trashcans in front of me. One was your standard trashcan and the other was for hazardous waste material. What’s the proper etiquette in this case? I mean, vomit isn’t exactly hazardous, but it’s also not paper or plastic cups. I assume the hazardous waste can would have a liner inside that might hold up better against vomit, but at the same time I didn’t want to puke in the hazardous can and make herpes splash up into my eye.   So I opted for the regular trashcan. I was so mad at the possibility of throwing up because I was about to break my 17-year record. I was a middle school kid living in Indiana the last time I threw up and I loved impressing people with my tremendous record.   I heaved.   Nothing came up. Whew. Technically my record still stands.   And then something weird happened. The pain started to go away. Seriously. As quick as it came, the pain started to subside.   I sat back on the gurney and lay down. Hm. That was weird.   I didn’t hurt anymore.   You mean if I had stayed at home and just waited it out for 45 minutes everything would have been cool? Well that sucks.   And now what? When the doctor comes back, should I pretend that I’m still hurting or should I just be like “UM, I’m OK now?” That would be a waste of everyone’s time. But these people are professionals and they’ll know if I was faking it. But I wasn’t faking it earlier. For real!   Nurse #2 came in and announced we’re off to get a CAT scan. I was excited. Another new adventure!!&nbsp; So many new things we’re learning today, kids!   Nurse #2 explained on the way to the scan room that she too thought it might be kidney stones. I told her I heard they were awesome. She asked me if I needed anything for the pain and I told her it’d actually gone down a lot. I told her it was a 4 on a scale of 1 to 10. In reality it was probably only a 1 &nbsp;or a 1/3 but I didn’t want them to throw me out quite yet. I wanted a CAT scan!   The CAT scan was also anticlimactic. I was picturing the big white tunnel-thing like you see on TV and I wanted to show them that I was a man and wouldn’t freak out like those wimps you see on TV (“It’s too small! I can’t stand it! Get me out of here!”).&nbsp; Instead they had some new-fangled device that was basically a small wall in part of the room with a hole in it. Kind of like they stood a big piece of drywood up on end and put a hole in it. Not at all intimidating.   They scanned me and&nbsp; took me back to the room and told me it would be half an hour. Awesome. I felt fine. I can do a half hour. And I fell asleep.&nbsp;   &nbsp;  I was awakened by Nurse #2 returning to announce that Yep, It’s Kidney Stones. Awesome.   The good news is the stones I have (3 in total. Or as some people say for reasons I’ve yet to understand, in toto) are only 1mm in diameter. Interestingly, the Nurse informed me that I probably wouldn’t even feel them when I passed them, but the passage from the kidney to the bladder is when I would actually feel the pain, since it is a much smaller tube than that from the bladder to the toilet. She said I was actually fortunate, as in most patients the pain lasts much longer, even a few days. Well, Nurse #2, most patients aren’t Ed, are they? They gave me a prescription for the pain and sent me on my merry way.   Awesome. I’m free to go and my hair isn’t even close to being presentable.   I called Drew and Andrea and they were awesome enough to swing by the hospital and pick me up (as my friend Nik says, hospitals don’t exactly deliver. Except babies. Heh heh. I’ll have to tell Nik my addendum to her little joke). I got home and felt great. I didn’t even bother to go to the CVS down the corner to get the prescription. If I start to feel the pain, I’ll run down (it’s literally ½ block away) and pick some up.   About 3 hours later I felt the onset coming, so I went to the drugstore, added a book of puzzles to my purchase, and returned home. I took a pill (the prescription indicated to take 1-2 pills at a time, but since I don’t get a refill, I decided to conserve).   The pill hit me faster than I anticipated and I was out for the rest of the day. Goodnight Irene. Kidney stones are cake.  I awoke the next morning at 5:30 am in pain just as horrible as the day before. I did not fret, though, because this time around I knew what I was in for and I also had medication. The pain will last for 2 hours tops but hey, I have medicine so we can cut that out of the equation. I took two pills and went back to sleep. Or at least tried to.   Apparently 1 pill is all Ed needs. Two pills means vomiting.   My record was broken and there were no technicalities to dance around this time. I was vomiting. I threw up perhaps 6-10 times before 9 am so I knew I was in for a great day. And I must have vomited up the pills’ super powers, as the pain did not subside. I couldn’t even hold down water. It was an amazing display of biology.  I won’t bore you with all of the details. This thing has already run on a bit too long and worn out its welcome, so let me begin to wrap up. Basically the pain on Tuesday lasted until that evening. Maybe 9:00. It was definitely a very bad day, one of the worst ever. Also that night, the A/C in the bedroom conked out. And if you’ve spent any time in the south, July isn’t exactly the best time for you’re a/C to conk out.   I spent the rest of the week recuperating. I’m still a little sore, but I think the worst is over. Actually the most pain I have now is in my back, probably from spending so much time laying down (and not exactly laying straight…a lot of it was curled up, so my spinal cord is probably more twisted than the “21 Grams” storyboards.  I was able to get my job interview postponed and I went in on Friday morning. It went really well and am going in next week for the follow-up interview to meet some of the management.  Davy and Jenn got in touch and offered to pick me up and take me to their house to rest up and recuperate. You (and they) have no idea how much that meant to me. Friends like that are indeed a rarity. I didn’t get their message until Friday afternoon (I think they called Thursday) and by then I had some gas from Venus and didn’t want to bring it to their fine house. Drew also called to check in and make sure everything was OK. I didn’t get his message until I got the message from Davy and Jenn (when I got back from the hospital on Monday, my cell phone somehow ended up under some pillows behind my bed).  OK, that’s enough. I’ve kept you too long. Go out and get some Chinese and a breath of fresh air. That’s what I’m going to do.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A great day of painting over at Drew and Andrea's.  &nbsp;  I returned to the house with splotches of paint all over and thought it a good idea if I took a shower before I retired for the evening. I showered and lathered and rinsed and repeated. I finished up, turned off the water, and threw back the shower curtain.  &nbsp;  There in the middle of the bathroom floor sat our two cats, staring at me. In all of my dripping wet nekkidness our cats just sat there and watched me. I couldn't&nbsp;tell if their expressions were one of curiosity or amazement or just boredom, so I raised my hands out to my sides and shouted "BEHOLD THE NAKED HUMAN!! LOOK AT ME!!"  &nbsp;  They scurried away and I laughed my silly head off.   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The truth? It sucked. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In a previous post I mentioned how my last 3 Netflix rentals all had something in common (they were all based on true stories). I thought it was pretty cool, since it had happened unintentionally.   Well, I am very happy to announce that it has happened again. I'm on a roll!!  My movies this week were "Shadows and Fog," "The Majestic," and "Mighty Aphrodite." 10 points to the person who can guess what the connection is this time around....they all feature David Ogden Stiers*!!  OK, OK, I know he's not as recognizable as Harrison or Julia, and I probably wouldn't even have noticed it if it weren't for my knowledge of Disney films. (I'm going somewhere with this, I promise).   I remember listening to the director's commentary on a Disney animated film (I think it was Atlantis) and David Ogden Stiers had a short cameo in the beginning as one of the professors. The director mentioned that DOS is like their good luck charm and they use him in as many of their animated films as possible. As I reference the Internet Movie database, I see that his stint with Disney began with "Beauty and the Beast" (he was Cogsworth the clock) and has since appeared in most of the films (he was the villain in both "Lilo & Stitch" and "Pocahontas").   So, as I saw his name on the opening credits of "Shadows and Fog" (I love Woody Allen!) I was excited to look for him and see what he looked like. Unfortunately, most of the film took place in shadow and fog and the cameos were so quick, I couldn't recognize him by his voice. I was able to point out a young William H Macy, who was at-the-time listed as WH Macy. Kinda cool. And by the way, it's too bad that "Shadows and Fog" is such a hard film to find anymore. A hidden treasure!  I didn't recognize him in "The Majestic" until the very end and I was like ohhhhhhhh ok. By the way, this film got a bad rap. Kinda like "The Cable Guy." I think most people were expecting another Ace Ventura wildman out of Jim Carrey and instead they got a Capra-esque drama. But give it a chance. Much like Adam Sandler's "Punch Drunk Love"...only easier to make sense out of. But to be fair, the poster for "The Majestic" was, in my opinion, the worst poster EVER. A watercolor painting of Jim Carrey? And a bad one at that? Booo!  I haven't even watched "Mighty Aphrodite" yet. As soon as I saw DOS's name in the credits, I flipped out and had to let you know about it. Turns out that he also appears in a lot of Woody's films, so this might be cheating a bit, but since I didn't know, I shall excuse myself and still bask in the wonderment of coincidence.   My next 3 Netflix movies coming are "The Truth About Charlie," "My Family (AKA Mi Familia)," and "Air Jaws 1 and 2:Sharks of South Africa." I think I may have just put the kibbosh on my "3 films that are oddly linked together somehow." But who knows. I'm hoping Edward James Olmos will surprise me.     *[For all of you M*A*S*H* fans, David Ogden Stiers played Maj Charles Emerson Winchester III on the TV series. I have no idea who that is since I've never seen an entire episode of the show. I try not to watch horribly overrated TV shows that are in truth just plain boring]
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I mean, REALLY, I loathe shaving. But I don't want a beard so it's somethig I have to live with. I've never liked shaving. Never ever. I can remember my first time shaving back in Indiana and thinking to myself "Well this is gonna suck." And it does. Shaving sucks.   Beards serve no real purpose to me so thank you, Ed's chemical makeup, but no thanks. Yea sure, maybe back in the caveman days we needed them to protect ourselves from the sun, but I'm not a caveman and I need no such protection. Unless I'm Amish and I want to let people know that I'm married, I don't really need a beard.   And hear me when I say I'm not coming down on people with beards or goatees, it's just not for me. But I  AM  coming down on the guys with pencil-thin sideburns shaved into intricate designs. I mean come on. Seriously.  I'm also not saying people (guys mostly) shouldn't have the choice whether or not they want facial hair. I'm just saying that if they do, they should have to work for it. Like abs. You should have to do facial crunches and then the more you do, the more beard you grow. That way those of us who hate shaving can live peacefully and care-free for the rest of our lives and those who want the stubble just have to put in a little effort. But, no, a beard you can have for free. Abs you have to work for. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been a subscriber to Netflix for some time now, and I think it's awesome. Well worth the money. Considering how much I'm into movies and how much I WOULD spend a month on rentals, I'm saving a lot of money. And now I think Netflix should give me 8 free months for that piece of advertising since MILLIONS of people read this blog each day.   Anyhow, I received my 3 latest movies from them and without even realizing it, I had chosen 3 movies that were based on actual events. "A Beautiful Mind," "Radio," and "Blow."  I'd never seen "A Beautiful Mind" simply because I can't stand Russell Crowe. If ever a face was asking to be slapped with a dead fish, that face is Russell's. But, because I am impartial and a true and just man, I was able to look past my dislike for him and actually thought it was a pretty good movie. His acting was very good, he did a nice job of capturing John Nash. I gave it 4 stars out of 5. But I still think Russell Crowe is a dork.   "Radio" was stupid. I wasn't expecting much, and it STILL managed to let me down. This was actually worse than "Forrest Gump," if you can believe it.   I gave "Blow" 4 stars as well. Great movie. I was going to give it 5 stars, but I can never justify giving ANYTHING with Bobcat Goldthwait in it 5 stars. Johnny Depp more than made up for it, though. He always steps up to the plate and this time around was no different. After watching the bonus footage and the interview with the man Johnny was portraying, it only showed how good of a job Johnny did.   So three movies in three days. Not too bad. Two out of those three were actually worth the rent and worth recommending, so again, not too bad.   As I check my Netflix queue I see that the next movies on my list that are coming to me are "Shadows and Fog," "The Majestic," and "Mighty Aphrodite." It's been a while since I've seen a good Woody Allen film, so don't let me down "Shadows" and "Aphrodite." Or face the wrath of my NEGATIVE REVIEW IN MY BLOG!!!  Bwa ha ha ha ha ah aha ha ha ha ha ah aha ha ha ha
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's this commercial that is played too many times here in Nashville and it's gotten to the point where every time it comes on I want to put sharp objects in my eyes.   It's a BellSouth commercial advertising their High-Speed DSL service and features a bunch of cool hip people running around doing hip and cool things as they constantly proclaim throughout the entire thing "I WANT THIS MUCH SPEED!!!" and they stretch their hands out. Quick cut to a shot of them with their thumb and index finger an inch or two apart. "BUT I ONLY WANNA PAY THIS MUCH!!!"   And they scream this particular desire over and over and over and over. And over.   It's just funny to me how, after seeing the same commercial 5 times in one half-hour block, a bunch of young hip people doing young hip things who want this much but only wanna pay this much magically transform into little whining annoying cheapskate babies who want everything they can get but are too cheap to actually pay for it.   Idiots. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I tried e-mailing Frank yesterday to let him know what was up and explain I wasn't being evil, but of course, the e-mail bounced back to me. I tried calling him at the office but couldn't get past the screen (please say who's calling at the beep). I left him a message to let him know that his email wasn't working, which is why I sent the email to the other guys in the office and yadda yadda yadda.   Soon I got an email from him saying thanks for the explanation and I'm such a talented guy and a nice guy and it was weird that not half an hour earlier he was telling me how awful I was and how I can't be trusted and I have so many issues to get over.   People entertain me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone who knows me knows that I lost my job at a Record Label at the beginning of the year. In March they brought in a guy from another label to fill the position (let's call him Frank), and I was glad they did. I knew Frank, and he does a really good job working radio and I knew that the artists would be in good hands.   I'd tried to email him a few times after he got the position to congratulate him, let him know to feel free to call me if he had any questions, and also to let him know of contacts who had gotten in touch with me saying they needed radio servicing. I know sometimes that can be a little uncomfortable but I thought it was important to let him know there wasn't any bad blood. Unfortunately, all of my e-mails either got bounced back to me or went unanswered.   Today I was in touch with a radio station that said they hadn't gotten any radio servicing in a long time. I dropped Frank a line to let him know, but it again bounced back to me so I sent the head's up to 2 other guys in the department to let them know that this station needed some music and hope that the email went through.   And that was it.   No biggie, right?   I mean, the same thing happened when I was there. Someone in another department would hear from someone saying they needed music, and so we'd get it sent out.   Not Frank.   The email went through to the other guys and Frank sent me a long ranting diatribe about how I need to get over being fired, deal with my bitterness, and I cannot be trusted because I didn't send it to him.   So apparently I'm really evil and stuff. Why do I even try? 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, this weekend went quickly!   My dad and his woman Char came down to visit for the weekend. It was a pretty good time. Char is allergic to animals so they weren't able to stay here at the house. The cats were glad, because otherwise they were confined to the upstairs portion of our stately...estate.   Saturday Davy and Jenn and Amanda came over for a Game Day. It was a pretty good time indeed. Charades, Taboo, and also a chance to teach the gang The Great Dalmuti!! A fun card game indeed. After all of that and hopped up on too much coffee, it was time to pull out the big PlayStation Karaoke Revolution and sing our little hearts out.   Sunday Dad and Char and I went to see Spider-Man 2 (Dad only fell asleep once. Aunt Mae will do that to you). We also walked around downtown and watched all of the sad hillbillies who hang out there and then went to Franklin for some Buca Di Beppa.   A good time was had by all and they have returned to the land of corn and basketball.   In the meantime, I am continuing the big Job Hunt 2000. And yes, I realize it's 2004, but doggonit things STILL sound so much cooler if you tack on a "2000" at the end.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The other night I was craving one of those Hershey pies from Burger King. Like a pregnant woman craves Haagen Daaz, that was me with the Hershey pie. I hopped into the car and zipped through the drive-thru and ordered two (count 'em, two!) tasty treats.  My total came out to like $2.23 or something like that, and I decided to pay using the change that I keep in my car's ash tray. It was mostly quarters and nickels if memory serves, but it was exact change and I was about to enjoy my pies.  I handed the change to the guy who looks at it like I just handed him Martian currency, turns to the manager behind him, and asks, "Do we take change?" The grumpy manager growled, "No!" and the kid turns back to me, gives me back my money, and says, "We don't take change."  Was he serious?  I asked him why not and he said he didn't know. I told him, "But its money" but I wasn't being too persuasive and he just shook his head. So I just said, "Forget it." The Drive-Thru Kid was literally astonished. He got a look on his face like he couldn't believe it (probably more concerned about not knowing how to cancel an order on the register) and I zoomed off...without my pies!!!  I was angry and I wanted Hershey Pies! I arrived back home and immediately went online to the Burger King website. If there's one thing I learned from my wife, it's that if you are a victim of shoddy customer service and you let the right people know about it, sometimes you get free stuff.  BK Customer Service was closed for the night but you bet your butt I was on the phone the next morning. The woman who took my call was very polite and sounded more than a little shocked that they refused to take my money. And my free coupons are in the mail!!!!!  So I eagerly await the arrival of my two favorite four-letter "F" words: FREE FOOD
     
    
</post>


</Blog>