<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For some reason, when I hear the word memorial I think of a casket.  So there's my advise.  Go with the pine.  It's cheap and I think it looks better than those cheap ass metal ones anyway.  I don't suppose you get that super seal warranty thing with the pine though.    I saw a show the other night with some guys who'd had body parts blow off while serving in Iraq.  So very sad.  And for what?  None of them seemed bitter in the least.  (although I don't suppose they would select guys with an axe to grind to be on their cute little program, now would they?)  At least their recoveries seemed very quick.  Fit and healthy going in...no arm and a fucked up foot coming out.  geez  We spend the last couple of nights in Shiner.  It was hot.  And there's not a lot else to say.  We celebrated Connie's 60th with fajitas and chocolate cake, which were both fantastic as usual.  Some cat that I didn't know existed had 6 super cute little kitties which were in a box in the corner at Kenneth's.  I guessed we pissed her off with all of our fondling of her babies and she ran off with them this am.    Super evil cat Baby has now taken over the tv room.  That is the most horrid creature that ever lived.  I think next time we're there I'll accidentally leave out some rat poison.  where do i buy rat poison?    Trevor washed the dishes.  (Yes, the above statement was significant enough to warrant a paragraph all of it's own.)  About paragraphs, I think i might need to freshen up on those.  One main idea or something...  We tried a new barbeque place on the way home--Old Smokehouse Express or something like that.  The bbq was pretty good, but the floor was very greasy.  It was really crowded though.  I'm not sure why that would make the floor greasy, but...      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      School's out for the summer.   Emilie burst through the front door Wednesday, which was the official last day in Cy Fair, and proclaimed "this is the best day of my life!"  Ah, be still my heart.  This exclamation comes close only to her first "i love you" when she was 2.  Yeah, my little girl is so happy.   4th grade was an emotional roller coaster akin to the Texas Cyclone.  Every day it was a dispute with another friend.  One day Rachel is her very best friend.  The next day Rachel hates her.  One day Jackie is a snob.  The next day they're on some new level.  (they have this elaborate way to rank their friendships-"well,now we're one step above acquaintances, MOMmy!  We're not enemies any more")  I swear some days I dreaded coming home.  How am I supposed to stay neutral in all this?  I mean, I will admit that my own child can be a little on the mean side.  I doubt that she's little miss innocent cast to the sidelines of 4th grade without provocation.  Still, they made fun of her acne.  Ooooh...don't go there with me little missy.  And called her a geek?    Anyway, apparently things were sorted out on the last day and everyone is right as rain again.   AND, Emiie got 100 percent on her math TAKS and only missed one question in writing and one in reading, earning her the honor of commended performance.  She's extremely proud of herself (rightly so).  She sorta slipped in the report card with an overall average of 89.  She had to kiss the $50 bucks good bye.  I gotta think of a better incentive for next year.  Ideas anyone?  Maybe we should just ground her when she comes home without all A's at the 6 weeks like Jessica's parents do.  hmmm     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      2  Dear Blog 8  Monday and Tuesday were not nearly as interesting  1  as  8  the weekend.  So this really does not sound  5  like a poem, but i  9  gotta keep goin, cause once you start somethin you    7  gotta finish it.  Or so THEY say. 8  Put the cookies on the tray.  Drank lemonade. 4  Fifth grade graduates chomped. 4  Fourth grade girls romped.  Emilie got the Language Arts award for her writing skills.  Her poetry folder inspired my Telephone poem.  Her classmates voted her Most Trustworthy which she wasn't too thrilled about.  Not sure what she wanted, I think most athletic, which went to Jackie.  This girl who was helping us serve cookies and punch says "Well, my class gave me Best Sense of Humor.  But only because there was nothin left!  I'm not even funny!"  I quelled my instinct to hug her and tell her that you don't have to be funny yourself to have a good sense of humor.  She seemed ok with it though, just peeved. Here's part of one of Em's poems:  15 maybe 16 Things I worry about   1.  My parents go to jail  I won't write the rest of it without her permission, cause it is pretty personal, but WHAT???  Why is her first worry that her parents will go to jail?  Are we too vocal in our disdain for the President of the United States of America?  (My country tis of thee) Was it because of that time the neighbor called the cops on Trevor?  (Sweet land of liberty) What the hell?  She's more worried about us going to jail than she is of us dying.  She says they weren't in order though.  Anyway, I better go work on my portfolio so i can get a JOb so i can keep out of trouble and stay outta jail... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, so this seems like a cool idea, but how can it be "free"???  hmmmm... Here is the low down on our big adventure yesterday:  Trevor, Pat, Uncle John and I were hanging out while Forrest and Papa worked on Papa's will.  Suddenly, the front door bursts open and two sweaty girls (they would be Emilie and Paige) are screaming that there is a boy stuck in a hole.  Trevor, Uncle John, Forrest and I rush out (well, I had to flip my high heeled sandals off first--how can one save a child from a hole in those things??  How do I even walk in them...oops, another matter entirely) the back door and through the back gate that leads to the cement encased bayou that runs behind my grandfather's house.  Paige and Emilie lead us to the drainage hole that they say they heard a boy yell "help!" from.  We can't see or hear anything.  The girls are pretty sure someone's in there though.  I go ahead and call 911.  In the meantime Trevor has gone over to the other side of the bayou and appears to be entering the hole.  He still can't hear or see anything.  I can't get very close because the people who live two houses down from my grandfather and uncle don't mow the section of grass behind their fence and I keep stepping on sticker burs.  Emilie and Paige keep inching closer to the very shallow, but very green and icky water at the bottom of the steep cement wall.  Within a few minutes two patrol cars drive up and first one and then another Pasadena Police Officer approach from the side where Trevor and Forrest are standing.  (The child is stuck in a drainage hole that is on the side opposite from my grandfather's house.)  They ask a few questions then go down to have a look themselves.  The dark haired officer goes to his car and gets his jacket, then returns to the drain.  The blonde officer is still shining his flashlight in the hole.  (They were both pretty good lookin I just have to add, because well, i wouldn't be me if I didn't add that.  Very young. Very polite.)  I figure we'll just go about our merry way now that no hysterical boy has been pulled from the muck.  I call out to the officers that I'll be at 1106 and they say they'll call me if/when they need me.  Uncle John, the girls and I retreat to the santuary of the house.  (It was 90F and no shade on the bank of the bayou).  No sooner do we enter the den when we hear sirens blaring.  We peek out the window and now see at least 5 or 6 additional vehicles.  The fire fighters are wearing their gear and appear to be looking into several man holes which I can only assume connect to the soon to be infamous hole. My cell phone rings.  The officers want to speak to me.  We rush out to Forrest's green Explorer and he deposits me and the girls.  He and Pat drive off into the sun.  The girls give their account of the events leading up to and immediately following their discovery of the boy in the ditch.   It went something like this:  "First we heard a loud banging.  We screamed and ran.  Then we came back because we thought we heard voices."  'You didn't see anyone else around?', Blonde Cop.  "No.  No one else was out there but us.  He yelled 'help!'"  'How did the voice sound?', Dark-haired dancer, I mean officer (I kept getting a little confused cause he sorta reminded me of that boy at LaBare ;-) inquired.  "It was a little boy, maybe 5 or 6 or maybe 9-10."  'Was the voice loud?' from either the blonde or the brunette, I can't really recall.  When was the last time I went to LaBare anyway?  I think Desi and Shauna said they were gonna take me to some club.  hmmmmm They make the decision to enter the drainpipe since there is the possibility that a kid is down there.  They just want to be thorough.   By this point men from the water department and addtional fire fighters have arrived.  The I think fire marshal informs us of the risks involved to his men (methane gas, etc.) and that they will look as far as they can, but that they have a camera on the way that they can slink through the pipe where the officers can't reach.  He mentions something about growing up around here and riding his dirt bike along the banks.  I don't recognize him, but I'm sure he wouldn't recognize me either, even if we knew each other.  I must mention again that all of these men were so very polite.  Amazingly polite.  Strange.  I'm surrounded by such polite and friendly people these days.  It's so very bizarre.  Quite refreshing, just BIZARRE.  God, I do NOT miss my job.   Anyway, the camera finally arrives and we watch them insert it into the pipe.  They don't see anything.  All those men leave.  No sauntering about.  They were there, then they were gone.  All those trucks, all those men.  Gone.  It's truly amazing how efficiently and quickly it all happens.  On to the next drama... Mr. May (he wears his hair short and spiky, like the boys in Emilie's class.  God, Trevor's gonna kill me when he reads this.) jots down my name, driver's license number, name of my eyewitness daughter.  I thank him profusely, shake his hand and we're off.   I forgot to mention that while we waited we discovered this tree with these little red berries all over it.  They look sorta like tiny strawberries.  I dropped the leaf that I was gonna use to attempt to identify it with.   So, we didn't have time to swim so Em and Paige (she is Emilie's cousin, by the way--Let it BURNNN.  Usher is only good when Ludacris helps him, just in case you didn't know that) played in the sprinkler and covered themselves in mud.  All the sugar kicked in and Em had a meltdown.  A major meltdown.  She would absolutely kill me if she knew I wrote this so she can't read it.  She can't know about LaBare yet anyway. She slid in the back door and it was funny.  I laughed.  A lot.  Apparently people who care about their children do not laugh at them in their time of need.  She did admit at dinner that it was funny.  disclaimer:  Particular details may have been slightly exaggerated or improved upon for the amusement of the reader and kimpossible. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Forrest and Pat got Trev a scanner for his birthday.  Way cool.  Now we just have to scan in the hundreds of pictures hanging about the house and closets.  (and uncle Ernie's rock slide collection, apparently)   We had LaHacienda for dinner.  Has anyone who has ever been to our house not had LaHacienda?  We need to broaden our horizons.  When we walked in the mariachi sang "watch your step, watch your step". Umm, he need to venture out a bit himself.  Poor baby.  It is a pretty tricky little drop off though.  I can only imagine how many margarita laden folks have tripped on that one.  It's probably pretty funny to just sit there and watch.   Then as I walked by on the way out I smiled and he played three chords (I guess chords...du, da du).  Good thing I'm not going to be a music teacher.  Altough I always get all those questions correct.  Pretty funny fellow in any case.  Okay, kim, STUDY.  That's what I've got to do.  I think I better head off to la libreria to do it, cuz it just ain't happenin here at home.  The rain is getting to me!  How do people live like this??? An Emilie story: This summer she is staying with my neighbor down the street again.  Only this year instead of only Emilie and Grace's two girls (all 10) two brothers, Jacob (10) and Joshua (8) have been added to the mix.  You can imagine that Josh is not the happiest little boy.  The others are mean to him. (He can be kinda bratty, but he is honestly the most adorable little thing ever.)   So one can just imagine the scenario with three 10 year old girls and one ten year old boy.  During the school year one of the girls liked (was crushin on, whatever it is that they're calling it this week) Jacob.  That ran it's course and she can't be bothered by him.  The other two, however, have both decided that he's all that.  So 'they' (Emilie of course) MADE him choose which one he was gonna crush with.  --I've acquired this information in bits and pieces from Josh (he'll tell us ANYthing we wanna know) and amazing GRace.   One day he chose Em then the next day he chose Zoe.  How Em can be mad about this when she "got" a boyfriend the last day of school, then "got" another one a few days later, but has yet to tell the first one that he ain't 'gotten' anymore.   In any case, Grace pulls them all together and tells them all that no one is gettin anyone and that they're all friends and if she hears one more word about it then she'll sit with them in the playroom all day.   She calls to tell me that she had a discussion with Zoe and when Zoe told her that she thinks Em is just the coolest kid, Grace asks her why she thinks that.  Why does she think that???  What is she saying??  HELLO.  Who is the coolest kid's mother??  I'm not kidding either.  I was offended that she had to ask.  The funny part is Zoe said that she thinks Em is cool because Em told her she is.   LOL.  That's why my kid is GT.  She just goes around telling people she's cool and wahla.  She is.  That's brilliant.  I'm gonna try it tomorrow...    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I fell in love with the Doctor on the ship.  I think I've seen this Paul Bettany character around before (and it appears he's 'linked', 'crushin on' or some more other less polite term to Jennifer Connelly.  Good thing I'm married.  She would have to be sought out and destroyed).  In this film however, he is absoulutely adorable.  To die for.  When that jerk-off sea captain Russell Crowe who thinks he's all that sails away from the Galapogos Island I just about cry.  How dare he??  So that he can chase after some ghost ship?  He broke the promise he made to his very best friend.  I was so incredibly pissed I couldn't believe it.  Do I perhaps have issues I need to deal with??? hmmmmm Anyway, there is just way the hell to much killing.   And I can't believe those little boys really had to work on those ships.   It's an okay movie.  I probably won't watch it again.  But we own it, so feel free.   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We watched Children of the Corn with Emilie which was a very bad idea cuz that's a truly gory film  (the 1984 version).  I think we had confused it with something else maybe.  So we are very bad, horrible parents.  But the problem was, we had really hyped it up.  Looked everywhere we went to buy it.  (Really it was Trevor, not me.  I had only a very very tiny insignificant miniscule part in it all.)  So when we finally broke down and rented it, and noticed it was rated R, what were we to do?  Tell her never mind?  So she saw it.  And will probably have nightmares forever.  And will never view corn in quite the same way.   That Malachai is one BAD boy.  And that Isaac is a FREAK show!!  Those eyes, that face, that VOICE.  My absolute favorite part is when Isaac blasts up into the sky, sparks flying, from the makeshift corn stalk crucifix.  Followed closely only by the scene where Burt and Vicky discover corn stuffed into every nook and cranny of the chevy convertible (i don't know the model...Trev will get with you on that one).  Those kids musta been GT!!!   Suffice it to say that Em spent the night in the middle of our bed.  (That was a first since we got the KING size and i must say that i barely noticed her presence.)  You gotta see this movie again though.  It's pretty funny and still a little scary.   "MALACHIA, he wants you TOOOOOO"    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On the way home from class I heard this song on World Cafe "Morning Glory" by the Subdudes.  It's really cool  "hey morning glory, please tell your story"  Very catchy, nice kinda bluesy, funk sound.  I get this great idea that I could play that song while we plant morning glory seeds as an experiment.  Or perhaps make predictions about which seed would be larger a morning glory seed or a weeping willow seed (the song later goes on to say save your tears for the weeping willow or something like that).  I could have pictures of morning glories, weeping willows.  Maybe even branching from a willow and flowers from the m.g.   So I just did a search to see where I could get some morning glory seeds (it is one of my very favorite flowers--the blue ones) and up pops this sight: http://www.erowid.org/plants/morning_glory/morning_glory_basics.shtml Who knew you could ingest the seeds and it's like LSD.  I coulda been fired before I even got hired!!!  No more science bullshit for me.  I'm doing Language Arts.  And for this mandatory science experiment we're doing water displacement and I'm reading Archimedes Takes a Bath whether the other two groups members like it or not.   Exciting news:  When I got home from class today there was a message from a woman with the Young Learners School requesting that I call to schedule an interview!!!  Yeah, my first response.  And it's a Preschool program.  It would be completely perfect for me except.... Damnit, isn't there just ALWAYS a f'ing exception.  All the locations are either downtown, on the eastside or south side.  DAMNN.  Poor people live on the north and west sides of town too.  I'm gonna go interview anyway of course.  I've heard about the program and it sounds awesome.  They place certified teachers in Head Start and regular child care centers.  Anyway... Trevor and I went on a study guide hunt Friday night while Em spent the night with Zoe and Marissa.  We decided to try Book Stop on Alabama since I hadn't been able to find it at any of the used book stores or even the B&N over here.  Can you believe BookStop is B&N too????  I'd no idea.  The guy said they had been for like the last 15 years.  Can that be for real???  Time keeps on slippin, slippin... So first we look ourselves in both study guides in the balcony and education on aisle 2.  Not there.  Then the guy looks in the computer.  Then we follow him to the education section and then the balcony.  Guess what???  Good answer.  Not there.  But the computer shows that they have three.  He's sure he's seen it.  He goes somewhere to find it.  No luck.  He escorts us to the exit where we can put our name on a list or something and I spy the book.  It's in a pile of books with yellow stickies attached.  Darest I steal from another????  Then when I finally hear the cute girl with the way cool glasses asking me if she can help me find something.  I ask if I can have that book and she says the girl who ordered it doesn't want it anymore.  YEah!  It was 'meant to BE' as Robert would say.  If you don't know who Robert is, then good, you don't watch as much television as I and your brain has not yet rotted to a shriveled pulp.   So I study while Trevor solves computer issues at home and work Saturday.  We spend a horribley long and awful time at Fry's Electronics where I thought I might have to chew off my leg if we didn't leave there one minute sooner.  Everyone knows how much I love babies and toddlers, but by the time we had to wait in that psycho line with two girls crying alternately in unison then in round, I honest to god thought I might have a hissy fit to rival one of Em's best.  We made it through with one nifty little portable seat/combo carry all thing for Forrest.   I'm gonna start putting my movie 'reviews' --hahahahaha-I'll think of a term for them as separate entries cuz this is gettin way too damn long.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I discovered a dollar theatre with Carol Friday.  While I should have been studying, cleaning, entering online applications to school districts which they will ignore, I went to see 50 First Dates with Carol.  It was cute.  Better than 10 ways to lose a guy or whatever that was called.  I was getting them confused.  I prefer Drew to Kate and of course I prefer that boy with the southern accent that i can't recall his name at the moment to the funny brunette who I can't recall the name of either.  So they're about equally silly.  But happy, happy.  Friday night I went to South Beach with Danish Muffin (so dubbed in the women's restroom by German Jeff).  Her friend Teresa was there as well.  It's free to get in between 10:30-11.  Of course I get fucking lost and end up getting there at 11:30.  somehow I manage to end up at Elgin and 45.  Some guy told DM that Elgin turns into Westheimer and if i just keep going straight I'll get there.  Maybe he said something about north  or south.  I didn't fucking have a compass, okay.  I just thought taking I10 would be quicker than the loop.  And it would have been if I had exited WAugh instead of going all the way into downtown.  Anyway.  Teresa was very freaked out about the fact that men were in the women's restroom.  I was very freaked out about the fact that even gay guys don't wash their hands.  And I couldn't shut up about it.  And she couldn't shut up about how nasty the restroom was.  And Danish Muffin couldn't shut up about how rude people are and why doesn't the bartender speak.  He only smiles.  Sweety, with a smile like that, he don' need ta speak.  So at one of our many treks to the ladies' room, this guy steps on Danish's foot.  She makes a huge deal out of it.  Foot stepper's friend gives her $20 after I point out that I love his bracelet and DAnish Muffin says it's TIffany.  "We like anything in that blue box."  So how do you like that??  Someone steps on her foot and she makes $20!!!  No one gave me $20.  (well, one freaky guy gave us each $5 to put in the underwear of the three dancers.)  Why didn't he just give the dancers the money himself?  That's what I asked.  "the dancers are straight.  they would rather be tipped by women."  I just did that crooked raised eyebrow thing at him.  "I really just like to see people enjoy themselves."  Bullshit. But whatever, I decided to play.    Miss Muffin said only to give the money to the guy on the end, and most especially NOT to the one in the middle.  But I felt each guy should get an equal share.  But she was vehemently opposed to the one in white undies.  "white underwear. YUCK"  Well, so I give the favored one on the end his $5 and tell him that i've been instructed to give this to him by a secret admirer.  He says "instructed?"  I say "someone TOLD me to do it."  I tell my husband this and he asks if i think the dude was offended.  I honestly don't think the guy knew what instructed meant.  Anyway, the middle guy went on break and I gave the other $5 to the one with white panties.  He apologized for being sweaty.  whatever.  I dont' have a problem with sweat.  We pocketed the other five.  Danish Muffin made us.  She was in rare form.  I LOVE my Danish muffin, though :-).  So we dance the night away, freaky guy buys us some drinks, we have a conversation with a guy in a t-shirt cut out for the breasts to stick out about which hurts more, having your penis pierced or having your nipples pierced (he says penis, someone else told us nipples b4.  i'll just accept that they both probably hurt a whole hella uv a LOT.), then Teresa's "friend" Sign Guy (he installs signs at her office?  I don't really understand it, but he's oh so much cuter and sweeter than her boyfriend) buys us some drinks when he arrives after attending a show at Last Concert.  And he didn't even drink himself.  He had water only.  That was VERY very nice of him.  Unfortunately i was just way too drunk to drive home so Teresa drove us back to Miss Muffin's where I immediately fell out.    Next morning, we go to get my car and I can not find it.  I'm just about to call Trevor with the news and have about decided that I want one of those little bitty square cars to replace mine and wondering if they're cheap enough and if the insurance company will cover a rental and how long it takes before they accept that the car is stolen and fork out the cash when we find it in some lot not any where NEAR where the valet guy said he parked it.  I love south beach though.  Everyone is so friendly.   Saturday was spent trying to deal with the damn bees AGAIN!!!  Last year they cost us 400 bucks to get rid of.  It was kinda fun and a learning experience and we got to have all that honey.  This year, I'm just PISSED at the fuckers.  They should not have come back.  The bee guy took the hive out.  He stuffed the area with insulation.  DAMnit!  So we have basically sealed the tiny hole near the kitchen window and all along that entire side of the house so that they can't get out.  A few have managed to find their way into the light fixture above the sink.  We just keep spraying.  I have this really bad feeling about all this.    Em's friend spent the night and today we played Apples to Apples.  I LOVE that game!  Aunt Emi and Uncle Mike are the greatest!!!    
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So today I was my second day of class.  I absolutely love it!  The first mishap occurred promptly with the first few seconds of class time.  I arrived early (halelujah sang the chorus)and was getting my stuff all together, markers, highlighters, notebooks, all my shit pulled out of the bag.  The sign in log finally makes it's way to me and I'm not in there.  That's when it occurred to me.  Fuck.  I'm Kim T-C, not Kim C.  The M-Zs are in the other rooms.  Shit.  Now I waltz into my real classroom (did i happen to mention that we had already made our nametags and the teacher had already started telling us about herself in the first room) of course the last one there.  Fortunately they had not started doing anything yet.  Teacher informs of that someone is coming late.  (thank god, i'm not really the last one).   It was a fun day.  The teacher is extremely good.  Lots of experience.  She's done Reading recovery in title 1 schools and such.  (now i know what a title 1 school is :p) I feel kinda oldish.  The average age of these women is probably like 24 or so.  Most of them just graduated within the last semester to couple of years.  No men.  Only 2 black women and 3 hispanic women.  Total of like 22 in my class.  I'm learning to teach pre-k through 4th. I volunteered for everything (very teacher's pettish of me).  I was Papa bear in the retelling of Goldilocks and the Three Bears.  No one else wanted him.   The lights went out during the massive rain storm.  We all got soaked.  But the band played on. Today, 6/9/04.  I can add it to one of my most embarrassing moments.  One of the very top of my very many, many moments.  I'm wearing this button up short-sleeved striped shirt with navy blue capris.  (no this is not a Danielle Steele novel.  I was not wearing a Donna Karan suit with black leather pumps carrying a gucci bag.)  The desks we sit in are those typical plastic chair with wooden top attached that you slide into.  Well, I guess I need to work on my sliding skills cuz when I went to get up to throw my Java House coffe cup away, I hear this ripping, sorta shredding noise.  I turn around and the women behind and beside me have their mouths open with their jaws on the ground.  "Oh no!" one exclaims.  The woman beside me, whom I now know to be Elizabeth, starts laughing so hard tears are rolling down her cheeks.  She says, "that's it for you, papa bear, no volunteering for stuff in that shirt."  You can tell the teacher is a bit miffed at our disruption of her lesson.  The next thing I know, she's calling me to come up and underline phonemes.  As I walk up, she bemoans (huge intake of air) "Oh my gosh!  What happened to your shirt?."  It is at this point that I can no longer even pretend not to be completely humiliated.  I can't stop laughing though.  Even now, as I recall that sound and their faces I just can not stop laughing.   I said something about going to Target to get a new shirt and pragmatic Elizabeth says why bother.  "We've already seen you now."   So i just go to lunch in the torn shirt.     Then later we play phoneme bingo and i win.  I have to say the sounds of the letters, i say /k/, /l/, /h/ and /z/.  Then for some reason correct myself and say /ks/ (x), i think because Elizabeth and I think that is so weird and we've been saying it all day, ks, ks, ks.  Now more laughter and the teacher makes me do the whole line again.  I didn't even eat my lollipop.  I feel like the class clown or something.  And I meant to have a much different image.  oh well, i yam what i yam. The other crazy thing i just remembered is that someone asked about the letter people and what happened to them.  Of course, most of us don't know who the fuck the letter people are.  The imagery going on was crazy.  It turns out they are these big blow up letters similar in material to beach balls.  I guess each letter has a person on it.  Some teachers had the whole alphabet.  Our instructor says "oh, they've gone out of favor."  The world of education has shunned the Letter people.  First they ditch Dick and Jane, now the Letter People, who's next?  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's what I wrote in my journal at the teacher job fair today.  I felt so totally like a Plain-Belly Sneetch.  Everyone was wearing these tags and the certified teachers name tags said real BIG 'CERTIFIED' applicant.  Everybody else was just well, an applicant. It makes sense and all and I totally understand it.  Would I rather have my kid taught by some fresh outta the water mackeral?  Of course not.   However, I spent all this time and energy working on the damn packets to pass out.  And I felt like they looked really good and totally reflected my abilities and personality.  And at most of the tables they didn't even glance at it.  WHAT??  Aren't you gonna jot down that I'm lookin really spiffy in my nice new suit??  How bout that lesson plan?  And of course I threw in my transcripts for the fuck of it.  Even if i did graduate a million years ago, I did it with honors, damnit!   At the Cy-Fair booth, which is where i would prefer to teach, since it is where i live and pay may taxes, blah, blah, the lady tells us 'oh, i hate to tell you this but go ahead and remove your resumes from the binders, cuz honestly, we just throw them away.' DAGNabbit.  (I started feeling like I should not blaspheme, even in my mind, whilst looking for a job teaching young children).  I paid almost $2 each for those damn things.  I hope to goddess that the others did not just chunk them.  geez  It was very polite of her to tell us though.  She then basically said until we get our test scores back not to bother her.  But she said it in such a very positive way.   So that's over.   One woman actually did glance at my resume' and exclaimed "oh, my son went to HeartsHome last year!"  So please tell me she wrote something positive about me on the damn thing.  Unless of course she hated the center and will never take her son back there because another 4-year-old sucked his penis in the bathroom.  That happened alot in my caseload.  Especially when I had Dickinson.  Try explaining to a homophobic dad that it is NOT considered abuse when two children of the same age experiment in sex play!  Let me mention again how much I do not miss my job.  Of course the same shit is gonna happen while i teach, but you better believe that I'll be in the boys rr.  'keep your penis to yourself'  If i've said it once, I've said it a thousand times :-).  How's this from 3-year-old WC "hey kim, look! It's big"  Until I taught preschool I'd no clue that 3-year-olds have erections.  Now I do.   Same boy comes in one morning and tells me he likes my haircut.  Wow!  Did my husband notice my haircut?  of course not.  Three years old!  Then he says 'Hey Kim (he always started every sentence that way...all day long...hey kim, hey kim, hey kim) you wanna come to my house and have a beer?'  HAHAHAHAHA  no kidding.  I told his dad, thinking he would be embarrassed or something.  His response:  "oh, that's a great idea.  You can come to the Hockey game with us"  That apple fell right under that tree.  I wonder what little sis is like.  I loved that kid though.  When he moved into the classroom beside me he would sit and cry "i want my kim" at the door.  The doors were all glass.  I thought it was gonna kill me.  I think he would be in third grade now.  I should try to find them. I need sleep.  I didn't go to bed until 4am and got up at 7.  I don't feel much more tired than I usually do however.  But then, superheroes need no sleep.  dootdootdoodoo
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's Em's favorite song right now.  (ok, I'll admit it, I'm pretty into it myself.)  How funny is that song???  I had to look up the lyrics cuz well, what the hell is boo boo?  Rhymes with poo poo, so I assume... Emilie and I said this over and over together: Crazy bitch (repeated in background) Bitch, stupid ass bitch Old punk ass bitch, old dumbass bitch A bitch's bitch, just a bitch She just loves to say the word witch with a b and not get in trouble!  hahahaha Trev and I saw Van Helsing last night, which was hmmmm, a bit on the odd side.  Count Dracula has these weird ass hos that shriek like wild banshees.  Perhaps they are banshees.  What the fuck are banshees?  I think maybe some Irish thing.  Anyway, Van Helsing is hot and so is Anna, but she's a tad on the chilly side.  But those outfits she wears...weeeheee.  Frankenstein is just a sweetheart.  You simply must adore him. Trev helped me work on my resume today, which is thankfully near completion.  I get to wear my new suit at the job fair Monday.  Should I wear black hose or nude??  Ah, the dilemnas of life.  By the way, I have decided that I am a damn good employee.  Hell, who wouldn't wanna hire me.   We saw Harry Potter 3 today.  I loved it!  I wasn't really into the first 2 and I haven't read the books since one, but this one was totally awesome.  Extremely entertaining.  Those damn dementos are some super scary psychos. I talked to Party Patty (we worked together some years ago as temps at this insurance company) today and she officially dubbed me Happy Hour Kim.  I can not let her down.  I could hear little Gabrielito in the background.  She only pays attention to him when there's blood.  God, I miss her.  A true soul mate.  She's moving to San Antonio and will teach 2nd grade.  She always makes me laugh.  At least I can remmber her wedding aniversary since it's on April fool's day.  I seriously thought she was kidding.   Emilie's babysitter Grace et al are in Disney World.  She called Friday to say that the college kid who is house sitting called to tell her that Fidget the dog had been missing for "quite some time" and he had looked for him, but didn't know what else to do.  Did I mention that he is an Aggie.  And his dad is quite honestly a rocket scientist at Nasa?  Of course he can't find the dog.  So Em and I drive around a bit along with everyone else in the neighborhood (not really, just like 3 of us) and low and behold, Aggie calls to say call off the search party, Fidget just walked in the doggy door. I'm reading like 4 books right now.   I must sleep.  The doc gave me a script for some stuff that is supposed to help with my restless leg syndrome.  It's habit forming and it is used to treat people with seizures.  ummmm, this seems a tad bit bizarre to me, but what the hell do i know?  You don see no MD in fronta my name.  Everyone can use another habit no?   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here's more bullshit:&nbsp;   In the summer of 1997 I was the primary caregiver of a group of 8 two-year-olds.&nbsp; We were all very excited to learn that we would soon be getting a new friend.&nbsp; His name was Bradley.&nbsp; There were already 5 boys in the group so I was a bit apprehensive.&nbsp; You can imagine the activity level in our group.&nbsp; It sometimes felt like there were 20 of them! So the day finally arrives and Bradley’s mother (who was to be the Kindergarten Teacher) comes through the door with Bradley clinging to her hip.&nbsp; The kids all excitedly rush up to greet him.&nbsp; He buries his face in his mother’s neck.&nbsp; I ask the other children to give him some space and to remember how they felt their first day at Hearts Home.&nbsp; I started talking to Bradley’s mother—showing her where Bradley’s cubby was, where to put his lunch, etc.&nbsp; The other children slowly went back to their usual activities at their centers. Bradley finally allowed his mother to put him down and he went over to explore the lego table.&nbsp; One very boisterous boy, William, decided to join him.&nbsp; This sent Bradley into a mild panic.&nbsp; He ran to the door seeking his mother, who was now in her classroom, which conveniently had a shared window into our room (she knew this, but Bradley did not).  Bradley would look at me, and let me comfort him, but he would not talk.&nbsp;  I had heard him speaking with his mother.&nbsp; He was an extremely verbal 2-year-old.&nbsp; However, he did not speak a word that whole day. Or the next.&nbsp; After several days the children began to ask him if he could talk.&nbsp; He just looked at them.&nbsp; He would join in all the activities.&nbsp; However, he did not speak to me or the children.&nbsp; After about a week, I finally heard him talk to William, who was to become his best buddy over the next two years.&nbsp; He then started speaking to me.&nbsp; But in the mornings when all the others would come running in the room seeking hugs from me, Bradley would just quietly put his things away.&nbsp; He still didn’t talk much to the other children either. And then one day on the playground when everyone in the group came running towards me wanting hugs, Bradley joined them.&nbsp; He was the first to arrive.&nbsp; And what a huge hug he received from me!&nbsp; From that point on, he was part of the group.&nbsp;  I taught this core group of children from the time they were two until they were turning four.&nbsp; We had so many, many successes.&nbsp; They were toilet trained, they learned to ride trikes, they started recognizing letters and writing their names.&nbsp; But Bradley’s slow but eventual connection to the group stands out in my mind as one of my most successful events.&nbsp; I had just learned about different learning styles and personality types when he arrived (I had only been at the&nbsp;center&nbsp;about two months myself).&nbsp; He was definitely slow to warm, but our patient understanding paid off in the end.&nbsp;   ( i didn't put this on the application, but not everyone was so patient.&nbsp; my coteacher (and 'mentor') in the room at the time would say things to him like "you can't have a piece until you ask for it."&nbsp; it was so cool to seem him just stare at her.&nbsp; haha.&nbsp; so much for her brilliant plan. ) 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This weekend was jammed packed action.&nbsp; Well, as much action as we're likely to see these days.&nbsp;&nbsp; Jenna and Hayden had their birthday party Saturday at Papa's.&nbsp; (1 and 4 respectively).&nbsp; Jenna is almost walking.&nbsp; She cries every time Robbie leaves the room.&nbsp; And she refuses to let anyone but her mother and father hold her.&nbsp; I decided that while she was drinking her bottle would be a good time to steal her away.&nbsp; (after all she was otherwise engaged).&nbsp; She kindly spit milk in my face.&nbsp; I held her anyway.&nbsp; Gotta admire her spunk.  Hayden got spiderman gear and when he donned the helmet and gloves his 4 year old cousin from dad's side says "but if Hayden's Spiderman, we have to be the bad guys :-("&nbsp; I think they worked it all out.  We went to Astroworld Saturday and it was truly nasty.&nbsp; I think I may have mentioned in an earlier post that I didn't mind sweat.&nbsp; Let me revise that statement.&nbsp; I don't mind sweat when it's on a 6' good lookin muscular guy dancing in front of a waterfall and i'm drunk.&nbsp; When I'm getting on board some roller coaster or standing in line next to stinky, wet people it thoroughly grosses me out.&nbsp; Does this mean i'm getting old?&nbsp; I don't think that bothered me all those years I worked at that place.&nbsp; Ride after ride, other people's sweat after other people's sweat.&nbsp; I'm not quite as bad as Monk yet.&nbsp; And the smells.&nbsp; Eeee gads.&nbsp; No more summer time amusement park trips.&nbsp; And the woman with us had the nerve to say that she didn't smell when I complained that i needed a shower.&nbsp; I couldn't quite find a way to tell her that yes in fact she DID smell.&nbsp; I was the one standing next to her, ok.  So we decide to go home and take showers and then go see Bourne Supremacy 2 or whatever.&nbsp; The beginning thoroughly pisses me off.&nbsp; How dare they kill her off??&nbsp; What's the point of the movie without her?&nbsp; I didn't really get the movie.&nbsp; The car chase is all you ever really wanted in a car chase, however.&nbsp; (personally, i can do without another car chase scene and live quite happily ever after, but some of us are into those).&nbsp; Bottom line-kimpossible says two thumbs down.  Oh yeah, the woman who didn't stink (NOT) did not take a shower.&nbsp; She put on a wrinkly shirt and came out of the house lookin worse than when she went in.&nbsp; I did not sit by her.  I started the following by saying that education is a process of evoltion not unlike the unfurling of a fern frond.&nbsp; But then it just got way too cheesy and i suppose i need to actually get a job in education before i can aspire to such lofty metaphorical ambitions.  so i left it at this:  My Philosophy of Education  I believe that each individual is born into this world with an innate desire to seek knowledge, ask questions and be accepted.&nbsp;   It is my duty as an educator to provide an active learning environment where each student can feel safe, accepted, challenged, and motivated.&nbsp;   I will provide differentiated learning experiences that will be conducive to a variety of learning styles in an effort to foster the development of self discipline and a love for learning in each student.  My classroom will be a warm, fun place filled with busy, happy sounds, children’s creations and many, many books.&nbsp;   We will embrace each other’s differences, share each other’s triumphs and learn from our mistakes.  Each day will begin another journey of discovery of ourselves, each other and the world around us.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So there is so much to write and so little time.&nbsp; I'll have to be catching up soon.&nbsp;  Today I had to present a lesson plan in front of my Universtiy of St. Thomas class (like for a grade and everything ;-), unlike the lass class).&nbsp; This was a plan based on a Madeline Hunter model with all these elements and it ended up being three pages in length.&nbsp;  So anyway, I was the third person to go.&nbsp; Even though I am a very quiet, introverted person of few words, in my last job I frequently had to present in front of groups of adult learners.&nbsp; So I feel fairly comfortable with it.&nbsp; And before I walked up to the front of the classroom, I wasn't nervous.&nbsp; (well, not nervous about presenting it to the class.&nbsp; of course I was obsessing about the assignment.&nbsp; it's worth 25 of the 100 points, and damnit, Ms. goody two shoes wants an A)  So i waltz up to the front with my little mariachi music playing and my brilliantly prepared materials all organized and in a row, complete with note cards that tell me exact what to say, when to say it and when to show which visual aids.&nbsp;  Everything seems great, but then I begin to speak and my voice is  shaking.&nbsp;  Like a lot.&nbsp; I was thrown back into high school choir days when we had to sight sing for a grade.&nbsp; (they just gave us a piece of music we'd never seen and we had to sing it.&nbsp; usually we just sang into a recorder, but still, my fucking voice would shake.&nbsp; i couldn't figure out how to make it not do that.&nbsp; it was such a pisser.)&nbsp;&nbsp; Same damn thing today.&nbsp; I'm telling myself to stop the shaky voice thing.&nbsp; I even clear my throat, but fuck.&nbsp; It still shook.&nbsp; I was SO EMBARRASSED!!!&nbsp; good god.&nbsp;  But afterwards a woman came up and said 'oh, i loved your presentation.&nbsp; you class is gonna be fun'.&nbsp; Then after lunch a woman who was in my first class said that I did a great job.&nbsp; She said that she was thinking during my lesson "shit, kim knows what she's doing.&nbsp; i'm gonna go up there and fuck it up."&nbsp; So maybe it wasn't that bad or noticeable.&nbsp; Maybe they think that's just how my voice sounds.&nbsp; Maybe they think i'm like 66 and that's just the way your voice sounds when you get old.  A tall, very soft spoken man in my group said he didn't even notice that my voice shook.&nbsp; But then he did live in a retirement home for a while.&nbsp; (he has a master's degree in gerontology)  So, i'm almost through!&nbsp; 3 more days!!!  There is so much information floating through my head.&nbsp; It's crazy wild.&nbsp;  I adore my instructor.&nbsp; She's fantastic.&nbsp; Super organized, interesting, motivating...I'm so lucky.&nbsp; Some of the other professors completely suck.&nbsp; People are sitting in their classrooms silently reading.&nbsp; I would be so pissed.&nbsp;  I had my fake nails taken off by the way.&nbsp; (cultured nails, whatever the hell they're called.)&nbsp; I was sick of them.&nbsp; I'm not a girlie girl any more.  &nbsp;   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So the Mr. and I went to see Farenheit 911 while Em went to Shiner with Grammy.  We saw it in a packed house in one of the larger of the 24 screens out here in the burbs.  I thoroughly enjoyed it, although I bawled my eyes out.  All that guilt I feel every time I think about the fact that my country just went over and demolished those peoples lives.  And all those young men and women who will be fucked up for the rest of their lives and will be the ones under the overpasses holding signs.  It kills me and I feel at least partially personally responsible.  Perhaps becuz it's the first time I really paid attention to what was going on before it happened.  I just did not imagine that we would do it.  I spent most of March 2003 in this horrible fog.  I never really caught up on my caseload after that.  Somehow it all seemed far less important.   I didn't pay much attention to the Gulf War even though I knew it was gonna happen.  I was talking to some classmates the other day about a possible draft.  They were freaking out because of course they don't won't their husbands and fiances to go.  It reminded me that my first crazy thought was "if he has to go to war I have to have his baby."  Why the hell does that thought pop into women's heads???  Insanity.  It's got to be some crazy weird biological response.  Of course I did come to my senses and realize the absurdity of having some dead guy's kid.  (i think that's when i started pushing the idea of canada.)  In any event, my best friend was in the hospital dying when it all started and I don't remember any more about it.  The movie just hit on every single one of my issues.  Seeing those poor blue collars folks preyed upon by the recruiters, watching the grief of both the Iraaqui and American moms.  It was shear torture.   Oh yeah, and then the whole stolen election thing.  I remember being fairly sure that we would have some sort of "civil" internal war over the whole thing.  And one day in December I heard all these sirens wailing and thought that it had started.  It turned out to be the annual light parade with all the fire trucks.  I was so surprised that it seemed that no one gave a shit that an election had been rigged.  We all just accepted it.  I was so glad to see that that was not the case and that the shrub didn't get to take his little walk.  Was that reported?  I sure didn't see any coverage of it.   Anyway, I loved the movie.   My favorite line: "Even Ricky Martin couldn't fly."  And there flashed Ricky across the screen with his big smile.  Michael Moore rocks.  But what to do about it all??  Therein lies the issue... We went to see a fireworks display at the Katy Mills Mall rather than drive into town.  We decided to dine al fresco at Jillian's where they were having a luau buffet complete with live band.  Very fun.  They set up a watermelon eating contest and no one would come up.  The prize was to be a $50 game card.  When Em and Zoe heard that, they ran up to the table.  Trevor is lookin at me like I'm gonna go up and eat watermelon in front of a crowd of people.  Hell no, i'm not.  I'll charge up $50 b4 I'll do such a thing.  So he went up and joined Zoe.  They had one minute.  Three other groups were there competition:  a little old lady and her maybe 6 year old granddaughter (clearly no way), a man and his say 8 year old son (looked like they might be competitors), and a 10 year old boy and his like 15 year old brother (i seriously thought the boys would prevail).  But when they got started, Zoe chomped into that melon.  When they said 30 seconds left, the announcer yells something about group 4 having their heads buried in those melons.   And they won!!!! The fireworks display was totally awesome.  And we were right next to where they were setting them off so it often appeared that they were coming straight at us.  Super cool. Then we went back to the game room and the girls played games for like 2 hours.   For some reason Zoe chose four back scrathcher as her prize.  But Em did get a new deck of cards out of it.  Perhaps now we can not use the deck that she and Trevor had to change hearts into spades on some of the cards!!!  God save the queen.      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I passed my Texes Content exam with flying colors!!!!  I am now "highly qualified."  HAHA  To the one who made fun of me being "HQ"--lick my chakra.   No class for 5 whole days!  It looks like we ain't goin to Shiner in this weather, so I wonder what we'll do.  We still haven't been able to ditch the kid to go see Farenheit 911.  (no more R rated movies for that child for a while)  Where are her little friends when we need them? So I was thinking that Monday was like the suckiest day in the world ever.  First--the weather.  Then I had to be partners for my science project with this woman who is very, very nice, but is completely and totally clueless.  I feel so bad for her.  I seriously doubt she passed that test.  She was in our study group and it just didn't sound good.  Anyway, the other woman in our group has somehow gone AWOL.  And she was so cute and bubbly.  Maybe she got a different job or something.  Her job at the zoo was eliminated, that's why she was going to teach; but she loved that job.  Maybe they found the funds or something.  Hopefully. So I'm stressed about making the experiment work properly.  I got some tubs at the 99 (there is no little symbol for cent) store.  And some bamboo skewers to use as markers.  So I get Em and we trek through the damn dreaded grocery store.  I get ready to pay and realize that I don't have my little coin purse.  Em runs out into the rain to see if it fell out in the car.  Meanhwile the people behind me are looking pretty pissed.  The checker boy is very nice about the whole thing.  And why wouldn't he be?  He gets to just stand there and do nothing for a bit.  Of course the little round plastic orange purse is not in the car.  Checker says no prob, we'll just "suspend your order."  He pushes the cart aside and goes on his merry way. We find said coin purse at Grace's, then have to return to the miserable store.  Of course it's still raining.  And I truly want to just forget about the stinkin groceries, but I feel bad that the stuff is just sitting out in the aisle. Then the manager lady makes this huge production of "Oh YOU'RE the ONE with the suspended order, right?"  Thanx, lady.  I coulda  just waited in line.  But it is kinda cool that they can do that. I get home and Em says i'm grumpy, but that i'm always grumpy after school.  That makes me grumpier.   The experiment is not working properly.  My objects are not heavy enough and the tubs are too shallow.  ARGHHHH.  And I refuse to prepare dinner becuz the kitchen still hadn't been cleaned (sorry T, I just had to throw that in there, but it looks very nice now).  So we go eat and when we return I decide to go get some deeper tubs.  I scrounged around and found a whole bunch of rocks to use instead of the toys.   Number 3.  As I am backing out of the garage I hear this huge crash and awful noise.  I notice that one of the bicycles has fallen and when I look at my car I note that the passenger side view mirror has been knocked off and is dangling by a wire.  Now I'm fucking livid.  I storm inside and cannot locate any of the half a dozen or so flashlights we own.  I sort of tell Trev what happened and demand that he go out there and see if he can frickin fix it (I'm trying not to use the f word any more, but it was just workin out to be an f word kinda day.).  We locate a flashlight and as he's lookin at the car, i just about loose it.  Turn the car off, scream that i'm just gonna go take a f'in shower and go to bed, storm into the house and slam the door (i never slam doors.  i hate that shit) and give Em a hurried good night.  She's just lookin at me like I'm nuts. I asked her the next day if I scared her or anything and she first said no, then added something about being a tad bit concerned that her mom was trippin out.  It was really funny, but I can't remember her exact words. So the next morning I rose early and got the new tubs and the experiment went perfectly.  The teacher complemented us on tying in literature with science (oh yeah, the partner decided she wanted to read the book.  What?  IIII wanted to read the book.  I love that book.  But there is no I in team, so damnit, she read the book and even though I told her several times how to pronounce the man's name, she still said Mr. Archamedas instead of Arkimeedeez).  I almost pulled my hair out.  And then the teacher complemented me again when I said to pull out your science journals.  Haha.  I'm great.   So here's where things get sad.  I'm thinkin I'm having this shitty week when Elizabeth, who lives on a ranch in Brookshire tells me that they had to shoot their mule.  The mule wasn't eating and would stand all the time until he fell because when he would lay down he couldn't get back up.  So they found him laying there with his head all beat up and bleeding because he was trying so hard to stand.  They gave him some tranquilizers and dug a huge hole to bury him in ( i think she said he still weighed 500-600 pounds).  They managed to get him up and he walked into the hole and was still standing when they shot him.  For some reason that seems so fitting to me.  That he was able to stand while he took his last breathe.  I'm sure that he was so thankful to them for shooting him.  I only hope the same will be done for me if I ever find myself in his situation. ( but hey, i'm still able to get up on my own and I don't have that much insurance, so don't be getting any ideas, mr. C)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Emilie drove for the first time, all  by herself,down the dirt road to the ranch this weekend!  Very exciting, scary and super sad.  She's not a little girl any more (well, at least not half of the time).  She looked so incredibly mature sitting behind that wheel with her hands at 10 and 2.  Trevor got out of the front seat of his now shiny Maxima.  (it wasn't so shiny then, remember the dirt.  but he snazzed it up when we got home Saturday.)  Em slid onto to the black leather driver's seat, eased her way up and up and up.  Not quite enough up for her to reach the pedals comfortably, but close enough.  She put on her seatbelt and took off.  Now she has been driving on dad's lap for quite some time now.  I think since preschool.  And it seems like maybe we let her near the pedals once b4 with him in the seat.  Anyway, I stayed in the front seat so Trev could be a back seat driver.  (imagine that ;-)  Everything went great.  Just a couple of really wide turns that didn't even come that close to sending us into barbed wire or tree trunks.  The gate was open so we sailed through.  Em says, "i don't want to park.  i don't know how to do that."  Trev says to just drive in and stop.  Well, all the dogs were running around the car giving us their usual enthusiastic greeting.  We drive past the house to the area under the trees in front of hot tub.  Trev is saying, "turn, turn!"  It is at this point I notice that we have not really ever fully described the whole hand over hand turning procedure.  Em's arms are all twisted up because she's turned as far as she can in the 10 and 2 position.  The Australian Shepherd, Sydney, is right in front of the car and the tractor is very very quickly approaching on the right.  Now I start yelling "stop, stop!" and I think mr. C is still yelling "turn, turn!"  Poor Em is just so worried that she's gonna hit the dog.  "Squeeeeek!"  She does slam on the breaks at the last second and we miss the tractor tire by at least 12 inches (maybe 8, but you have to round up in that case).  Trev and Em are arguing over what should have been said, done... and suddenly, just as soon as the adrenaline is back to normal levels, I need to burst out laughing.  I aplogize to Em, but I simply can't help it.  It was funny.  Really funny.  And kind of exciting.  The most exciting thing that's happened to me in a while in any case.  I just now asked her if she thinks it's funny yet.  Eyes bulge out of her head, "uh, NO.  What could be funny about that???"  Give her another coupla days. So the reason for our trek to 3Cranch while it's 95 degrees outside was to go see Little Women at a dinner theatre in town.  Very quaint sweet place.  Gaslight Theatre I think it's called.  We sat with a couple from somenear near Yoakum.  They have 40 acres and a garden with lima beans, cucumbers, tomatoes, eggplant and squash.  I'm so jealous.  He bales hey or something and well,  I forget already.  I just want a garden.   I couldn't hear the other two women at our table.  I think they were from near Yoakum as well. Forrest got stuck sitting at a table with some people and their white haired children.  The man was I guess my age and apparently thought he was going to see Grease.  haha.  He was not happy.  He was appalled that an outsider would be sitting at his table (no offense to you sir, but...).  So they left after the first intermission.  Forrest moved down with us.  It was really cute.  Em fell in love with the girl who played Amy.  She was really good.  Very animated.  I bawled my eyes out when Beth died.  Why do I cry every time she dies?  I know she's gonna die, yet still the tears. Forgot to mention that Em redeemed herself with a flawless driving experience on the way to the show.  (just down the dirt road, not the highway!!!) We have bagworms in one of the pecan trees and in that tree in the front that I don't know what it is.  I cut off the ones that I can get to.  I don't know what bagworms are, but I don't think they can be good.  They're like that scene in Lord of the Rings when that gigantic spider wraps him up in that coccoon thing.  They just wrap up little sections of the tree.  I'm gonna research them now and figure out what to do.    
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>