<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A churning and foul haze has descended upon my realm like the stench of some god-awful landfill during a heat wave, long past its capacity. It is the oily and thick air of disgrace and of falsity that permeates humankind and pervades my daily life. I frown upon such things like one would an unexpected virus one attains quite suddenly one morning. It is an attack, unwarranted, unjustified and contrary to the rules of engagement. It is an act of war.  In the depths of night, when you experience moments that seem to just stand still, there, if only for a brief second, exists a moment where you can become 'at one' with all else. In the cool breeze of the night and in the bask of pale moonlight, or even in the rustling of leaves, for a moment, nothing else exists. If you are fortunate enough, at that moment, no other living person will enter your mind and nothing at all will seem to creep into your mind. It is a proud and solitary moment I experience continually and always have.  For you see, I came to such stark revelations when I was merely young. Here we all are, cosmic pool balls on the vast plain of existence, colliding and rolling towards destiny. Predetermination? No. There cannot be a path in random events, such as chaos has no structure. We live in chaos guided by rules, but there is no guarantee that rules always apply to everybody and everything. People are uncharacteristically precocious, more often they are synonymous with crude and distasteful idioms. I cringe at such endorsements, but to cringe is to set apart and apart am I.  An ash is a fragment of something that was whole, now separated through immense heat and completely removed from the whole. I am that wayward cinder, an ashen nomad amongst the smoky winds of a crumbling and dying system, a muted knell at a funeral and the sweet smell of smoke, alarming...or perhaps tantalizing.  Optimism is for those who have no really lived. It is for those who have acquired enough to make them happy, but did not acquire them on their own merits. Somewhere overhead a bird circles looking for prey, high in the air, far removed from its preys habitat. While far below the prey watches and waits for the time to move. While the bird remains instinctually optimistic, the prey remains involuntarily reactionary, a victim of the whim of this world.   Funerals for extinguished systems are an eye sore. Cry me a river for the departed and drown in the ocean such sorrow can only bring about. I sometimes feel as though I was born at sea and I have always know I will die there.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Existence on such a level as the one dark plane on which I traverse is one of tedium and great misunderstanding.   Oh woe to the misunderstood and woe to those who would seek out such a notion, if only to pounce and interject their banal and rudimentary observations on such a view. Nay, charity and pity are too empathetic to belong within these writings. They belong to the bleeding hearts of those who ignobly waste their efforts of the sour contingent of the masses. Laughter is the best anecdote to the feeble and inept squint of this world, berating their own kin to adjust their seat higher up on their self-made thrones.   And so begins the new realm of words and alphabetic characters, like blood and sinew, working as if some faulty gears in a synthetic dream, a dream one would mistakenly call beautiful, only to come to the realization that beauty is naught, and the dream is a fiery grave. Hopping from one foot to the next have I been in perpetual shift, ceaselly turning my back on foes and embracing new plateaus of dark imperialism and undivine heavenly propaganda. My agenda lies in the realm of all that is typically either ignored, or hunted as witchcraft. It is as arcane as people would like to make it out to be, that is, when the breadth of the level of comprehension has been stretched to its apex, my words and my apparitions will remain misunderstood. I find some comfort in that, the reaching out in obscure tongue and the attempted piercing of my heart by those not able to merely open their eyes and 'understand' my system. I have seen too many weeds growing out of the cracks in my sidewalks, only to be trampled upon by foreign insights and the credentials which I have garnered through my existence. Faceless do I remain and unmerciful have I been to those who have scorned me. They exists in plentiful splendor, yet their infamy will live on in their own hearts, not mine.  I am unapologetically for my candor and I am unmoved by any attempts of rekindling. Instead, as I have also lived by, "imbibe the sorrow from such divergent human dead wood and use their truncated intellect as kindling". I have existed in the space between the spaces, the shadow in the light and the silence amidst the static. I have always been here, just as you, the reader have always existed in your space. Lead me not to the kingdom, for I have no need for feudal kings and the puppets who dance upon strings who follow their ways. I eat from only one table, and it is decorated and prepared by my own hands. I dine as I live, carnal and thorough. I worship that which only those who have spilled blood and spoken the names that I have, can. I am here and I will continue to remain so. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>