<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you have a school you love? For what reason?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you have a school you love? For what reason?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you have a school you love? For what reason?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you have a school you love? For what reason?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you have a school you love? For what reason?
     
    
</post>


<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight I was training one of my beginning students, and I told him not to be too 'martial-artsy'. I've said that before. But what did I mean by that? I didn't want him to inappropriately apply tension to parts of his body because he's trying to do a karate type move. I think beginners need to get gross motor coordination going; applying light force to moves and trying to get a fluidity of movement. To extend that analogy, I don't want water splashing, sometimes I want there to be gently ripples. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thought it was a good idea to see what martial arts books you like. Here's  urlLink my martial arts wish list , compiled using Amazon's wishlist service. For a list of martial arts books available at local libraries in Western Australia [ urlLink click here ].
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got the following inquiry off our website. The potential student had a lot of pertinent questions. In fact, all the questions I'd advice someone to ask. How would you ask the same questions? How would you judge responses by the martial arts instructor? How would you answer this?   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's always discussion on the relevance of kata in relation to the applicability of martial arts. The first post is a section off a book I'm working on relating to kata bunkai, and the second is a post I made on the karatetips forum.   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Outside a very formal dojo, not many people think about the responsibilities that come with attaining a certain grade within the martial arts organization. I in fact have seen no dojo with such responsibilities written down or used as a way to judge performance within the martial arts school. The following is a post I wrote for the karatetips forum.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got the following email and thought it was something that could be used to develop a greater offering to teach philosophy through the martial arts school. The framework sounds like Six Hats. Anyone like to add further thought to this?
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Discussion on martial arts is always incomplete if you don't touch on the topic of self defence or women's self defence. The following is part of a dialog I had with a local reporter exploring the subject.   For more info, check out  urlLink Worldwide Self Defence Directory .
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Interesting requirements. How does someone make the grade? Is MA just time and effort? We can take some ideas for our own syllabus.   urlLink ultimateblackbelttest.com 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Martial Arts Websites  urlLink Hikaru Dojo   urlLink Karate and TKD in Perth   urlLink Worldwide Self Defence Directory   urlLink Martial Arts Schools I Love   Discussion Forums I participate on ...  urlLink IAOMAS   urlLink Karatetips   urlLink Hikaru Dojo Online Forum  (My School's)  An affiliate program I'm linked with ...     urlLink Click here to discover strategies and tactics  as used by world class competitors that you can use to   quickly improve your fighting skills  ...         urlLink Click here to learn dozens of tips to improving your basic technique and kata . Learn how to   punch harder and with more power than before  ...                Discover 43 ways to improve your karate ability...  urlLink click here for more info   
     
    
</post>



<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Articles off email newsletters and websites.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Resources available off various websites.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Building and development- status and issues
     

    
</post>


</Blog>