<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

                          Interesting article below on ad impressions made while zooming by at 60x speed. Maybe it's time for agencies to experiment with optimizing ads for high-speed scanning. A persistent banner, perhaps?    urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

                          Heavy content sponsorship by Ford targeting Hispanic small business owners:   On April 29, Ford Motor Company and America Online launched the first-ever Spanish language community hub for entrepreneurs. This hub, called Mi Negocio -- which means "my business" -- is designed to be a one-stop shop for Hispanic small business owners, featuring live chats, in-person forums and informative articles from Fortune Small Business and Business 2.0. Mi Negocio is powered by AOL Latino, one of the largest Internet service providers for the U.S. Hispanic population.      urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

                          "Ugoff," Burger King's follow up to the  urlLink Subservient Chicken , lacks the simplicity, innovation and creepy darkness of the original.  Site:   urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

                          We've all heard it and it's worth repeating and advertisers are scrambling: "Videogames have become a media force on par with the television and motion picture industries."  Listen: integrated advertising (billboards, etc.) is an easy start, but this will end up having the same minimal effectiveness of Web banner ads in the end. The real solution lies in the games makers and traditional media finding the right integration to leverage the powers of both. Stay tuned for Armchair Media innovations in this area...  Story:    urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

                          See the latest Armchair Media launches:   urlLink  The Jetsons  on ING MoneyMentor    urlLink Iceland's groundbreaking Visir.is    
                      
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

                          Nice to see Time taking a look at the movement. Granted, there are a ton of useless blogs out there, but if you get hooked up with the right ones, you'll find reporting that is more targeted, intelligent, personable and relevant than a good percentage of major media.   "Meet Joe Blog":   urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

                          This piece from TV Week shows how ad agencies are grappling with branded entertainment. They even go so far as suggesting a CPM model. I agree that some measurement is needed, and although  exposure  is relatively simple to gauge, how can you measure  engagement  for successful projects like  urlLink BMW Films  and  urlLink ING MoneyMentor ?  Story:    urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

                          From ClickZ:  "If only one essential online marketing tool exists, it has to be the Web site. Everyone who's anyone has one. In corporate circles, they're likely to have cost a bundle.  Developing a dazzling online presence is great, of course, but you'd be surprised how many massive enterprises disregard some of the most basic rules of corporate site design, neglect to update material and contact info, or feature tools and forms that fail to perform. Such faults not only reflect poorly on the business behind the site but also do wonders for its competition.  Smaller businesses are fortunate because they're less likely to have a network of local or international subsites to monitor and manage. But the big guys have no excuse. Today, a Web site can't be treated as an afterthought. A company's online presence is vitally important to its corporate image. Large companies just can't afford to make mistakes online.  Of course, small businesses, ever on the lookout for free education, are thankful they do."   Full Story:   urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

                          This study goes a long way in explaining why P&G and others are spending more in the beyond-the-banner interactive space.   urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

                          The auto industry has been one of the biggest drivers of innovation in the interactive marketing space over the past several years. From BMW Films to Buick's Tiger Trap, car makers have been at the forefront of creatively capturing users with engaging content and unique opportunities.   iMedia Connection has a nice overview of some recent tactics employed by automakers:   urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

                          A lot of e-mail blasts I receive -- even the ones I actually subscribe to -- are greeted with an instant delete. But here are some examples of promotional e-mail that I actually love to get. How are these different? Solid design, not-too-frequent updates, and above all, great content.     urlLink Design Within Reach  Design Notes     urlLink  The Other Music Update     urlLink Wells Fargo  Small Business Roundup      
                      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

                           urlLink 2004 IDEA (Industrial Design Excellence Award) Winners   Although not directly human-computer interaction related, these industrial designs combine innovation, aesthetics and functionality resulting in a great user experience.  Some of my favourites include:   urlLink Circular Printer    urlLink DEVO Underwear & Packaging    urlLink Weight Forward Hammer    urlLink Ensalada    urlLink "Audiopad"      urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

                            urlLink Linked here  is an important Business Week cover story that details media fragmentation and the resulting shift to micromarketing that is quickly redefining advertising. The story is important because it's the most comprehensive article written on the topic by a widely distributed and respected source. Of course, this is the stuff we've been preaching for years, and we're excited to start seeing huge marketers like P&G, Coke and others not only deploying innovative campaigns but seeing much more cost-effective results.   Some highlights:  "You find the people. You are very focused on them. You become relevant to them" - P&G  "We are a big marketer. We are not a mass marketer." - McDonald's  "They are spending about the same money and getting three times the lift." - Banc of America analyst  "The Internet has shaken off the effects of the bursting of the dot-com bubble and now is rapidly coming of age as an advertising medium. The crude banner and pop-up ads that initially defined online advertising are giving way to larger and more refined formats." - BW Download our case study on  urlLink ING Moneymentor (pdf)  to see how Armchair made this work for them, or go ahead to the Business Week article:    urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

                          Congratulations to our Swedish friends at  urlLink North Kingdom , their groundbreaking  urlLink  Vodafone Future   website just won 2 'Cyber Lions' at Cannes. Design-wise Vodafone Future is a fantastic example of an experience website. It's a dynamic brochure with incredible production and guts behind it.       urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

                          Here's an interesting article at eMarketer.com. While having the top position in paid search is clearly valuable, note how fast the value drops once you reach just the third or fourth spot. Definitely food for thought for companies considering a paid search strategy.   Perhaps more cost-efficient methods exist such as search optimization. And undoubtedly there is another way to capitalize on subject matter that could deliver more bang for the buck. The first company to bring it to market can certainly use this data as a selling point.  Story:    urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

                          A furor has arisen over the rollout of a new form of audience measurement for television. The flap concerns so-called "Local People Meters" being deployed by Nielsen Media Reasearch, the ratings people, in Los Angeles, New York and other major cities. Critics complain that the new computer-driven technology undercounts certain viewers compared to the old paper diary system. In reality what is happening is that for the first time an accurate measurement is being recorded and interested parties are fighting to keep the status quo. Put another way, television networks that have earned staggering sums off the old system are fighting being held accountable to their advertisers for the first time.  Most of us would argue that being accountable is a good thing. We, like advertisers, would like to think we're getting what we've paid for. That's why savvy advertisers have already pushed for greater accountability, not on television where too many technological barriers exist, but in the interactive advertising arena. Ad spending online is moving away from scattershot approaches such as banner ads and pop-ups, to targeted, immersive experiences that offer numerous user metrics and ultimately, accountability.  Armchair Media has helped pioneer this concept in its work with ING. If you're not already a fan, please visit  urlLink ING MoneyMentor  to see how we've executed the concept of Brand Enagagement for ING. We think it's indicative of where most interactive advertising is headed and feel proud to be held accountable for its success.  Story:    urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

                          Our neighbor over at Brighthouse says ad agencies should stop giving ideas away and start holding out for the big money. That's  the real value agencies bring to the relationship.   "Advertising agencies have become an antiquated broker business, selling space to clients with creativity thrown in for free. The result is a marketing world that is ad rich and idea poor. Consumers don't want to be bombarded with ads -- they want to be inspired by ideas that will change their lives."  This reminds me of the  urlLink Steve Heyer soapbox  a couple of years ago. Traditional agencies haven't changed since then, and I doubt if they will now. You tend not to expand creatively in times of fear.  Story:    urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

                             What an interesting concept. Capture your shoppers on video, have them create a profile. Internet users all over the world can then view and write messages to the shopper. Shopper checks back to the store, or logs in from home, all nicely wrapped up in the retailers brand.  After mastering  urlLink 'shock marketing' (link to Olivero Toscani's controversial 80's campaign  using traditional media, Benetton makes quite an impressive attempt at new media marketing.    urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

                          Dying for that new one with "...and all I got was this stupid T-Shirt"?  -- An interesting article on the progress of wireless wearable displays.     urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

                           urlLink   18-34 males are now more likely to go online or play video games than watch TV, and Wired has  urlLink a nice analysis  of how companies are changing ad spending to engage them.   Highlights:   "Used to be, TV was the answer," proclaimed the president of GM North America. "The only problem is that it stopped working sometime around 1987."   [They] share a hunger for "authenticity." If the ad message doesn't jibe with the brand's image, forget it. And say good-bye to the hard sell as well.   The lessons for Madison Avenue are clear. If you want to capture this demographic's attention, be prepared to entertain and don't be afraid to polarize the audience.    "They have a total ability to block out anything they don't want to get through. From an advertising standpoint, that's what makes this animal so scary."   "We're eating the networks' lunch!" crows Jeff Brown, EA's vice president of corporate communications.   "When people used to say, 'We'd like to do guerrilla marketing,' that translated to, 'We don't have any money,'" quips Andrew Gledhill, president of the LA-based ad agency Ground Zero. "When they said, 'We'd like to do something viral,' that meant, 'We really, really don't have any money.'" No more: Ground Zero recently won a $10 million viral-marketing account from Toyota.  >  urlLink Full Article  >  urlLink Stat Page     (thanks to  urlLink Skylab  for the link)    
                      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

                          From the "it was just a matter of time" department, a  urlLink new study  shows that more people are shopping remotely via the Web than catalogs, direct marketing and telemarketing.   (thanks to  urlLink MarketingVox  for the heads up)   Story:    urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

                             One of those simple ideas that I just love. -- You're going to want this!  Go to Kyauei site:   urlLink Link    
                      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

                           urlLink Here's  an nice breakdown of the complex alternate-reality game (ARG) created to promote the upcoming Halo 2 game. If you don't know about ARGs and how they mysteriously connect with users and build edgy buzz, it's time to start reading up.  >  urlLink Gamespot analysis  >  urlLink www.ilovebees.com    
                      
</post>


</Blog>