<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      See, I reckon you're about an eight or a nine, Maybe even nine and a half in four beers time, That blue top shop top you've got on is nice, Bit too much fake tan though, but, yeah you score high.  But there's just one little thing that's just really really really annoying me about you, you see, Yeah yeah, like I said, you are really fit, But my gosh! Don't you just know it?  I'm not trying to pull you, Even though I would like to, I think you are really fit, You're fit, but my gosh, don't you know it?  So when I looked at you standing there with your hoard, I was waiting in the queue looking at the board, Wondering whether to have a burger or chips, Or what the shrapnel in my back pocket could afford, When I noticed out of the corner of my eye, Looking toward my direction your eyes locked on my course, I couldn't concentrate on what I wanted to order, Which lost me my place in the queue I waited for, yeah.  I'm not trying to pull you, Even though I would like to, I think you are really fit, You're fit, but my gosh, don't you know it?  Whoah Leave it out Are you smoking something? Leave it out Mike, just leave it We cannot have that behaviour in this establishment It's not worth it, Mike Leave it out, Just leave it Don't touch me Don't touch me, I'm alright  For a while there, I was thinking, yeah but what if..? Picturing myself pulling with bare white hearted wit, Staring at you standing there opposite, Whether or not you knew it, I swear you didn't tick, And when that bloke in the white behind us lot queueing was clocking onto you to it, I had to admit that yeah, yeah, you are fit and I do want it, But I stopped sharking a minute to get chips and drinks.  I'm not trying to pull you, Even though I would like to, I think you are really fit, You're fit, but my gosh, don't you know it?   Oi, just as you started to make your big advance, With the milkshake and that little dohnut in hand, I was like, nah, I can't even, no you look grand, But you looked sharp there, smiling hard suggesting, and, Leaning away with your hearty hearty looking tan, But I admit the next bit was spanners to my plan, You walked toward my path but just brushed right past, And into the arms of that fucking white shirted man.  I'm not trying to pull you, Even though I would like to, I think you are really fit, You're fit, but my gosh, don't you know it?   What do I give a fuck, I've got a girlfriend anyway, Oi, we're all a bit drunk, we've had a few, fair play, I've got this stella I bombed from that last cafe, This night's not even begun, Yes, yes, oh yay.   I did fancy you a bit though, yeah I must say, I would rather I hadn't mugged myself on display, But this is just another case of female stopping play,  In an otherswise total result of a holiday.  I'm not trying to pull you, Even though I would like to, I think you are really fit, You're fit, but my gosh, don't you know it?    God BLESS Mike Skinner! 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ahem. I have become  so  camp in my choice of music lately. Diana Ross & The Supremes, Madonna, Kylie and Steps all feature in my music collection. Hmmm. Must be hanging around the poofs too much. Which reminds me, Andy's got a new fella who I spoke to on the phone the other night and he sounds  lovely . Gonna go and meet him on Sunday methinks.  Yeah, so music. I'm still loving all my dykey indie and old stuff though. Liking Motown stuff at the moment, especially Jackson 5 and Stevie Wonder.   I took a Sociology exam today, it went pretty averagely I think, you can never tell though can you?! We shall see... no exams for a week and a bit now, and I swear to God I'm going to get my arse in gear and revise properly for History and Spanish!   I spoke to Sarah before, we're gonna go and get pretty drunk on Saturday, which should be interesting as I'm meeting up with the QYA gang that night too... David, Michael, possibly Nadine & Katie and maybe RiotGrrl, HoobaciousPixie (who is rather fit!) and a few others too. That could go either way really. I will most probably want to spend all night with Sarah and James, if he's there. Which could make me eager to leave the QYA gathering, which I don't want to be apparent cos I actually really like everyone. Hmm. Not sure the QYA lot will mix well with Sarah and James. Especially if Nikki, David and Carlos are there. Oh well, let's just see what happens shall we?  My little sister has just got home in tears, she says she's being bullied by her whole form at school. I remember what that feels like and I really do feel for her and want to help. The trouble is I know how arrogant and cocky she  can  be... Just a bit brash and loud really and I think that could get her into trouble.   Another thing today, after the exam I went into Bolton and bumped into  so  many people... Suzanne, Danny Fay, Gem, Rachel Scudder, Vicky, Harriet, Leanne, Alex, Clare Gaffney (who talked for ages!), Clare Bleasedale and some other year 10s on work experience. It was nice really, just chatting randomly to everyone. Isn't it funny how easily you can talk sometimes... yet other times I find it really difficult to keep the conversation flowing. I was speaking to this girl on the net today (katieactually) and she was really easy to talk to... we were chatting about Python hehe. When I think of people who I can chat forever to, I can't help but think of Katherine. We get on so well it's not funny! Michael reckons there is a lot of sexual tension there which might possibly be true! Shame she lives so far away eh?   Right, enough... I'm sure I have better things to do. :)   xx
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "GUEST = Is there anywhere they do French food? BASIL = Yes, France, I believe. They seem to like it there. And the swim would certainly sharpen your appetite. You'd better hurry, the tide leaves in six minutes."  "BASIL = You'll have to forgive him, he's from Barcelona."  "O'REILLY = Well, let me tell you, if the Lord had meant us to worry, he would have given us things to worry about. BASIL = He HAS! My WIFE! She will be back here in four hours and she can kill a man at ten paces with one blow of her tongue! How am I supposed not to worry?!"  "BASIL = I'll ruin you! You'll never waitress in Torquay again!"  "BASIL = Don't touch me! I don't know where you've been."  "BASIL = Is something wrong? GERMAN = Will you please stop talking about the War? BASIL = Me? You started it!  GERMAN = We did not start it. BASIL = Yes you did, you invaded Poland!"  "GUEST = I expected to see the sea. BASIL = You can see the sea, it's over there between the land and the sky." GUEST = You call that a view? BASIL = Well perhaps you should consider moving to a hotel closer to the sea. Preferably in it."   "GUEST: Could you make me a Waldorf Salad? BASIL: Oh, ... ah, ... wa? GUEST: Waldorf Salad? BASIL: I think we are just out of Waldorfs."  "BASIL: Oh, you're GERMAN! Sorry, I thought there was something wrong with you!"  "BASIL: I'll put an ad in the papers. Wanted, kind home for enormous savage rodent. Answers to the name of Sybil."
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A rather fabulous line from a great film... Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind. It kinda resolves all of Jim Carey's previous sins in one big, warped, hallucogenic fantasy. And Kate Winslet is great in it.. and so, so attractive. Although she quite aptly illustrates the kind of girl I'fe really been trying to get away from... Childish, demanding, fluctuating kind of fucked up character. Hmmm.   Oh Jesus, I have an exam tomorrow and it's making me feel sick. The only exam I'll pass in my current state is one on procrastination. I've spent the entire day chatting to lovely girls on gaydar that I'll probably never meet or fall in love with and suffer embarssing humiliation and sitting in the garden reading crap magazines. How constructive. Oh, now I've made myself feel guilty I'll go and get on with it and return later to ramble some more... :)
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       So, maybe you loved me and now, maybe you don't. And maybe you'll call me, but maybe you won't.     Fuck. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oooh Kath says she might come to Manchester today. I bet she doesn't, but how nice would it be to wander round my city holding hands with her?   *daydreams*
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ugh... just woke up to three text messages....  One from Michael - he's cured his crabs. Rejoice.  One from Katherine - she can't sleep. She wants me. Why isn't life simple?  One from Sarah - Hey how are you? You out this weekend?   Ok, so you might think that that was somewhat promising, bearing in mind that Sarah almost NEVER texts me first. And then two texts later, after inviting me out, she tells me that, actually, she's going to Blackpool with Nikki this weekend. Riiiiight. So, what do I think? Is she just bored at college? I think so. Damn. Anyway, can't think too hard, not awake.  x
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oops, where to start?  Well that Saturday, we all went out. I met Sarah and David and there was mass flirting going on between the two of us... much arse feeling AGAIN. We all got on really well and had a fabulous night, resulting in everyone being really drunk and then that was that. I never managed to meet up with David and Michael or fit Lisa, but I did bump into Katie and Nadine. Then after work on Sunday, ugh, I'd rather not think of that actually. To cut a long story short, I ended up on my own for quite a while pre going out and then me and Sarah barely said anything to eachother all night.  Well then I did the sensible thing and didn't speak to her for two weeks. :S Hmm then I got my new phone and suddenly had an excuse to text her, so I did so and we went to Homiesexual on Thursday night with James. She was practically begging me to come out and I though, yeah ok, we'll have a really good night. But then by the end of the night, she was being a bit cold with me again. Do you reckon it's the drink that makes her like that? Why won't she just let me know where I stand and then I can either get on with it or get over it? *sigh*  Meanwhile, I've been doing my usual paranoia thing with Katherine as well... I mean, I just think she has too many girls and I think she could be like this with all of them... I just dunno, because it's got to the stage now where I actually do care about her. I think. Plus she's a really horny minx! Haha.   So other stuff that's been happening in my life... I failed History. I answered the wrong FUCKING QUESTION. How moronic is that? I'm rather furious with myself! Ugh, I can't be arsed going into the rest of everything now, I'm not even dressed yet. Ciao x
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So much has happened since that last post, it's strange. I must update this thing later this evening so I can remember everything in times to come!  Hmmm... but for now, revision!  x
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, fuck everything!  I haven't been here for a while... and for good reason. It has come to light that Katherine is a manipulative, scary person and I was thoroughly duped. So get over it. All that's done now, I've moved on completely. I haven't been here cos I thought it would remind me of all that shit... which is just embarassing really. But I really am a stronger person than that, cliched as it is. All that happens when I think of Katherine now is that I feel a little sick at what she gets away with time and time again. Since then, I've been to America and had the time of my life with Phil. Then I went to Wales for the weekend, on a white water rafting experience thing. That was one of the best things I've ever had the fortune to take part in. Scary, exhilerating, euphoric.... and all those kind of things. Also, I really fancied the instructor! ;) Yeah, so that has completely rekindled my enthusiasm for stupid sports... I'm looking into windsurfing lessons at Salford (after doing it by trial and error, I think it's time I developed some skill) and I've decided that I definitely want to take a gap year. Either becoming a ski instructor with the assistance of a career development loan or getting some watersports qualifications. I don't wanna spend the rest of my life in an office. I'm going to do something I enjoy and I'm more determined and motivated than ever now. All these people who are fucking me off can have their comfortable, well paid jobs in the suburbs. I'm gonna have some fun. I've also come to the odd realisation that I'm actually fine without a partner at the moment. No seriously, I'm ok! I still fancy Sarah, and she remains a good friend, but thinking about it, I wouldn't want to get into a relationship with even her at the moment. Cool. So overall, I'm happy. Or I will be when I get my tax money sorted out! But that's a minor quibble. Life is good, and I'm gonna live it. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>