<Blog>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      At last...I have my own blog. Now I can become obsessed with low-level sex scandals and talk about Lindsay Lohan's breasts and talk about how I saw some guy who's in publishing who only 50 people in Park Slope has heard of at some party for some magazine that 25 people on the Lower East Side will read before it folds.  And I can waste more time at work.   This shit rocks.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, I just read that escort services and strip clubs are flying extra girls in to work the Republican National Convention, and I think that I might sell myself, just during the convention because it would be fun to get paid for sex with a Republican who just sat through a day of speeches about family values. And also it would be great to make money off of a Republican. And also, I could go down on him, and bite a Republican's dick off. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have a thing or two to say to the crowd at Madison Square Garden on June 23 to see Madonna. You suck. Especially the 2 girls sitting in front of me. You appear to be 20 - 22 years old with no obvious handicaps. You have spent $150 to see Madonna, and you can't stand up and shake your ass a little? The least you could do is applaud when she plays "Like a Prayer", losers. And to the rest of you...look, I know it's Wednesday, and I was feeling a little out of it too, but for Christ's sake, can we get a little excited that Madonna is playing "Express Yourself" with a military theme? I know half the people there were boyfriends who got their tickets through PriceWaterhouse or something and were just bringing their girlfriends, and were just there to drink beer as they would do at any MSG event, but really, wouldn't you still get laid if you just gave the tickets to her and a friend. It wasn't all bad of course. Major props to the family of 5 to the right of me who were getting down and having a good time. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      JACK RYAN ON THE DEFENSE OF MARRIAGE  I believe that marriage can only be defined as that union between one man and one woman, and the other man and woman you are having sex with in public, and another man who is watching. And another woman with her finger up your ass. And cages hanging from the ceiling.. I am opposed to same-sex marriages, civil unions, and registries 
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>