<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fox News aired some footage of a protest demonstration today from the middle east.  It showed children burning the flags of the U.S. and Isreal and the burning of a likeness of George Bush.  When I was in school, I don't recall being taught a doctrine of hatred towards another country or being encouraged to do violence on others.  We all feared the Russian nuclear threat, but none of us were taught to hate and to act violently on that hate.  How can there be a peaceful settlement to the endless turmoil in the Middle East when the youths there are taught to hate and destroy?  I'm the same religion as my parents because that's the way I was raised.  I like the St. Louis Cardinals, the Los Angeles Lakers, and the Miami Dolphins because those were my dad's teams.  I raise my children by the same example set by my ministers, my teachers, and my parents.  We are all a product of our early teaching.  If the teachings of those children in the Middle East are so hate filled and self-destructive how can they ever break free of this mad downward spiral?  A lot of brilliant minds have been working on this global threat for a long time and we have seen no lasting progress.  Will it take an American flag flying over Mecca to free us from this threat?
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pretty funny stuff, watching Miller and Budweiser square off in this ridiculous battle.  The Bud ads in response to the Miller spots are the hands down winner.  Here's drinking to the continued hostilities and to future humorous ad spots!       urlLink Link   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm having a little trouble getting this to actually post.  Nothing like spending 30 minutes typing an update only to lose it.    Spent the weekend with the kids, had a great time.  Brianne had a T-ball game on Saturday morning.  At her level, the coach pitches three to the kids and if they don't make contact, they tee it up.  She got ahold of pitches on two at bats.  Could be a budding star at the plate.  She'll need to work on her concentration in the field though.  Likes to sit down at second base and talk to the opposing team's base runners a little too much.  Typical six year old I guess.  After returning from the game, we set up the swimming pool in the back yard.  By the next time the kids are here the water should be warm enough for a weekend of swimming.  At about 5:00 p.m. yesterday the rains came.  Had quite a thunderstorm with a lot of local flooding.  Seems to be the routine for the past couple of weeks.  After moving inside to escape the rains, we all set down for the Return of the King.  Brianne promptly fell asleep, but Morgan and I watched it.  He kept getting reassurance that the good guys would win and he loved the movie.  Frodo's late departure kind of bummed him out though.  I tried to get him to believe the film was over when the hobbits returned to Gondor for Aragorn's crowning, but he knew better.  No outsmarting that one.  This morning was beautiful out so Morgan and I went to the driving range to hit a couple of buckets.  He selected a nice little set for his birthday and this was the first time hitting real golf balls.  We practiced with the nerf version in the back yard when he got the set, but he was dying for a try with the real thing.  Fifty to sixty yards and straight after about a dozen balls.  The kid is a natural.  I spent the time spraying my shots all over the range and in the process, I broke the head off my driver.  Finally, a decent reason to buy a new one!  Brianne spent a lot of the weekend tending to her mice and chasing bugs outside.  She's fearless and always full of mischief.  She's going to be a handful...  Lisa came and picked up the kids for the trip back to Atlantic.  Her and the kids have their last week of school coming up.  I know they are looking forward to the summer off.  After quite a few years, I got a call from Jake today.  It's pretty cool to be able to pick up the phone and talk like we never lost touch.  Thanks for the call, I won't go that long without touching base again.  Mom and Dad went to the lake to get everything prepared for our imminent arrival only one week away.  Dad's getting the boat serviced and I'm sure Mom is busy washing the linens and plotting the week's menu.  They have a great setup down by Truman Lake.  The house sits on a semi-private lake and is only a few miles away from the big lake.  We can fish from the dock, swim, and paddle boat in the small lake and head to the big lake when we want to catch a mess of crappie or striped bass.  They have sure earned such a place through all the years of work and tireless effort they put into raising us kids.  I spent some time this morning before the kids got up reflecting on Memorial Day.  It's impossible for me to understand the horrors of war or the courage it must take to know that what you are doing could get you killed.  Our lives are made safe by the actions of a very small group of determined patriots that deserve nothing but our support and gratitude.  My grandfathers both fought in WWII and witnessed things unspeakable and both came back changed men.  I'm not sure that I could do what they did and see what they saw and still be able to function upon my return.    The Army has said that Pat Tillman was most likely killed by friendly fire.  Regardless of how he died, he and his family are owed a debt of gratitude.  His status as an NFL player brought his story to the limelight, but he is just one of many that died protecting us and our way of life.  These men and women deserve our thanks and our support, regardless of how we feel about the reasons behind why we are there.  The decisions to be involved in Iraq and Afghanistan were made by people desiring the safety of   all   of us.  Not just in America, but worldwide.  We are doing what many would not, even though their people benefit from the safety we are providing.  The cause is noble and just and they have my support.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Most of you that know me and a little about my younger days, know who Jake is.  Here is the link to his blog.  urlLink http://jakester.blogspot.com   Crazy day at work, had to go twice.  No one was there to let in the team at 3:00 a.m. so I got the dreaded call to come and open up.  Tried to come back home and catch some more Zzzz's, but couldn't really fall back to sleep.  Life of a retail manager, I guess.  Trying to prepare a 300,000 sq. ft. store for a visit from the honcho is a little trying, especially after the flooding we experienced on Monday.  I think we're about as ready as we'll get though.  I'm really looking forward to the weekend!  I get my kids for a couple of days and they always brighten my day.  No plans except a haircut for my son, so once again the kids get to plan our itinerary.  I see the zoo and Chuck E. Cheese in my immediate future.  Morgan will also want to see the Return of the King.  I've always been a bit of a fantasy buff, so it's great to get the chance to share some of the things that I loved as a boy with my son.  He loves all The Lord of the Rings films as well as the Star Wars flicks.  Just two more weeks until the kids get out of school for summer break and we take our first of two vacations.  We'll be heading down to the folks house in Truman Lake for some fishing, boating, and swimming.  Really looking forward to the trip, I could use the time with the kids and I need a break from work.  Completely different topic...  I have a little desktop calendar with funny quotes for each day and I have no patience so I skip ahead to find ones that make me smile.  Here's a few to leave you with.  "When you locate your congressperson's office, remember that, because we live in a republic, it's really   your   office.  Feel free to use the phone, rearrange the furniture, help yourself to office supplies, or leave your kids with the congressperson while you go shopping.  Your congressperson is there to serve you!" - Dave Barry  "When you have money, you become your own color.  Money transcends race.  Everybody hates the rich." - Cedric the Entertainer  (My favorite one) "People like David Duke and Louis Farrakhan are head and tail of the same bad penny." - Baxter Black
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lazy day off from work today.  It took me until 4:00 p.m. to make it out of the house and that was just to hop in the hot tub.  Oh, the life of a king...  Weather here was horendous yesterday.  Saw water shooting up through a man-hole cover (person-hole cover for you PC folks) about 15 feet.  Looked like a tiny Old Faithful right there on Saddle Creek road in Omaha!  Could have taken a canoe down the street.  Didn't take long for all that rain to make it's way into the store, we had an area about 200X50 flooded.  Today, on the other hand, was beautiful.  At least it was for the 30 minutes that I spent outside...  My brother-in-law is recovering nicely from his heart attack.  Two weeks off from work, a revised diet, and he should be back in the game.  Kind of scary when someone that young (37) has a heart attack.  Time to re-think eating and exercise habits.    Last month, both kids had their birthdays.  They both got some birthday cash and decided to buy...MICE.  My son picked a female and my daughter picked a male and they both settled on a nice mottled female for me too.  Oh yeah, the female that my son picked was already pregnant.  I now have 11 mice and my mouse is pregnant.  Back to the pet store to sell my babies soon.  Hopefully they won't all be snake food.  I'll tell the kids that they are joining a mouse circus (Stephen King readers of the Green Mile can relate).  Time for some dinner, pizza or fish sticks, hmmm.  So much for life as a king.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just found an old buddy of mine via blog and have spent the last 2 hours reading his archived posts.  Cool stuff - missed talkin' to that guy for the past few years.  Kinda like the older brother I never had.  After I packed up the family and left the Northwest, I lost track of him.  Wish I would have been a better correspondent.  Coulda used some of his advice.    
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The weekend with the kids was great, they spent most of their time playing with Jazz and man, was she was whipped Sunday afternoon. We got some park time in, some swimming, and some evening Yahtzee and Uno games. It sure is hard to put the kids back into the car to go to their mom's. The next visit I've promised to take 'em to Chuck E. Cheese's, heaven help me...  ===================================  Today is turning out to be a beautiful one. After mowing the yard and getting a haircut, I'm off to the golf course. Tonight, I need to prepare for some interview sessions. In late July, I'll be interviewing for a promotion and I begin my practice sessions tomorrow. Need to get some answers prepped so I'm not fumbling for words and generally making an ass out of myself.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a day here in Omaha yesterday!  A high of 78 degrees, sunny, light breeze.  One of the 14 or 15 days of good weather we get every year!  I left work at about 11:30 a.m. and came home and got Jazz out for her walk.  I can't believe how lucky I was to find her at the pound.  She's been with me since Friday and has yet to make a mess in the house, even when left alone for 10 hours at a stretch.  She sits, stays, heels, cooks, and cleans!  She slices, she dices and she makes the perfect dry martini!  She's also a little under the weather.  She got a case of kennel cough from being at the shelter for so long so I took her to the vet on Monday.  She got an antibiotic shot and some cough medicine.  Hopefully the meds will take care of her discomfort.  After her walk and playing fetch for about 20 minutes in the backyard, I went out to the driving range with a new employee from work.  This guy played 5 years of golf in college.  I mentioned my need for a lesson from a local course pro to cure my slice and add a little distance on my tee shot.  He said he'd take a shot at helping out before I spent the money.  Within 1 bucket of balls he had diagnosed my problem and had me hitting straight.  Next time we're doing something with my grip to add some length.  All this coaching and advice at the incredibly cheap price of a Corona.  Perfect timing since I'm playing in a company sponsored tournament today.    Work has been fairly stressful recently.  I'm interviewing in Kansas City for a promotion in late July, I have 5 new executives that I'm training, and I've been put in charge of our annual executive outing.  Trying to entertain 100 people over two days is pretty tough.    --------------------------------------------------------------  Anybody pick up Clinton's new book "Pack of Lies"?  What drivel.  I refused to buy a copy, but I didn't mind sitting down on break at work and reading through it a bit.  The book is just like the man, the right will hate it, the left will love it.  Clinton will always be remembered not for the good things he did (see, you can't remember them can you?) but for the abuse of his office to get an easy woman.  Oh yeah, and then lying about it while under oath.  That is his legacy and no book-writing, spin-doctoring ploy will change that legacy.  He'll always be the guy that cheated on his wife with an idiotic slut that was too young and too dumb to keep her mouth shut both during the event and after. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to the local animal shelter and picked me up a pooch yesterday.  Man, did I pick a gem!  She's a 3 1/2 year old Australian Shepherd/Blue Heeler mix and she is great.  She's housebroke, she sits, stays, and heels.  Very affectionate and good with the kids too.  The dog's name is Jazz.  Not sure if Jazz fits her or not.  If you change a dog's name after that long, will it give her issues that will result in pooch counseling?  I think the plan is to come up with a new name and write in on a piece of paper, then write "Jazz" on a piece of paper.  We'll put a treat on each one and let her pick her own name.    The mice all go back to the pet store on Monday to become snake food or pets (or circus performers if the kids see this).    -------------------------------------  The College World series is in full swing (sorry about the pun).  It's the one time of year that Omaha is a cool town.  I'm looking forward to catching some games and hitting the night life over the upcoming days.  -------------------------------------  Father's Day is tomorrow, don't forget to call!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Oakland A's had won 8 straight games and were flying high on the streak.  The had scored 10 runs in 5 of their 8 wins and their pitching was extremely stingy.  Then they went to St. Louis.  My beloved Cardinals swept them in a three game series including a sweet ninth inning comeback last night.  The A's scored a combined 10 runs in the series and the Cards now have a 2 game lead in the NL Central.  This recent surge by the Cards came despite injuries to Albert Pujols and their gold-glove catcher, Mike Matheny.  Check out Yadier Molina, the 22 year-old call up from the minors.  The kid can catch and has been wielding a decent stick...  Now for the hard part...my Lakers.  What happened?  The Lakers were outplayed in every facet of the game.  In fact, they should have been swept.  The team that was predicted to challenge the 72-10 record of the Bulls was miserable in the Finals.  No team chemistry and a dismal coaching display led up to this.  Seemingly no adjustments were made to the game plan and they looked progressively worse each game they played.  I should have seen it coming.  The Pistons were just better than my Lakers.  Now, the team will be dismantled.  Maybe it's for the best.    Hey, how 'bought them Cards!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sadly, this is the last day of my vacation.  The kids and I just got home from the lake last night.  We all had a great time!  The kids both got to drive the boat and got to go swimming in the lake every day.  Morgan also spent a lot of time fishing.  My niece and nephew were there also so the kids kind of ruled the roost for the week.  I took down my PS2 and a Tiger Woods golf game for use on a rainy day.  My dad is now hooked on video games and will be getting a PS2 from mom for father's day.  I'm not sure mom knows what she is starting here...  ----------------------------------------------  The golf tournament on Friday went pretty well, we finished 4 under on a pretty tough course with some pretty average golfers.  I didn't hit a decent shot until about the 6th hole, then finally got my short game working.  No trophies for us on our fourth place finish, but one of the guys on the team won a pin prize, I won a raffle prize, and the dinner was great.  The proceeds all went to support a little league team that a friend's son plays on so regardless of the outcome, it was for a good cause.  ----------------------------------------------  Mice, mice everywhere!  Man, do these things breed and breed fast.  We're up to 42 mice after starting with 3 on May 2nd.  I've informed the children that we will not be keeping any of them.  They sharpened their negotiating skills and worked a trade:  No mice remain and we get a dog instead.  Pretty good trade for me; dogs are cool, mice are so lame (and everyone makes fun of me when I put on their collars and take them for walks).  Off to the pound today, I'll keep you posted... 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I returned the driver that I picked up last week and took out another today for a trial.  The results were much better, good news since I'm playing in a mini-tourney on Friday.  A quick plug for 2nd Swing Golf -- they let you buy used clubs and try them for three days, if they suck like your old clubs and don't fix your game, bring 'em back for credit.  Pretty cool, huh?  I even like their signing in the store, "It's not you, it's your clubs".  Unfortunately, the used driver that I initially tried was $19.99.  The one I picked up after the trade was $119.99.  Of course, can you really put a price on hitting 250-275 straight everytime?  I would have paid more...  Two more days of work left before vacation!  Golf on Friday, then Bree's dance recital on Saturday.  She's doing a tumbling routine, ballet, and tap.  Should be quite the gala event.  I'll buy my roses to throw on stage following her performance.  Typically, that is only done for the graduating seniors at this dance studio, but it's my daughter.  She's getting roses every year!  Sunday we're off to the lake.  It will be great to spend some extended time with the kids.  Morgan is starting to enjoy baseball a bit more now.  He's been a lot more successful hitting pitches off the machine.  Success makes things so much more enjoyable.  Time to go watch the Lakers, they better not suck tonight like Sunday.  Shaq and Kobe scored over 70% of their team total of 75.  Derrick Fisher made 1 shot in 9 attempts, exactly one better than my dog would have done - and I don't even have a dog.  Anyway, they better not suck again.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally get a day off after six straight days of working at 3:00 a.m.  Man am I whipped.  Tuesday off with nothing to do but play a little golf after sleeping in as long as possible.  I'm sure it will rain or something...  On a more positive note, I just finished the new Stephen King book from the Dark Tower series - "The Song of Susannah".  It's book number 6 in a series that King first starting writing in the early seventies and didn't release the initial book until 1982.  Rarely does something keep my interest for more than a few days or weeks but I've been lusting after more books in this series for over 20 years!  Fans of fantasy tales (think Lord of the Rings with a Stephen King twist) would love this series.  The first book's title "Dark Tower I - The Gunslinger", instantly makes it sound cool and like my kind of story.  The "dark tower" implies something foreboding and a little scary and "gunslinger" makes me think of a western and of shooting, of course.  The main character, Roland, is the last gunslinger.  He's a kind of wandering diplomat, knight-errant, and the last defender of the "white".  The white is basically the force of good in the world.  Oh yeah, he also carries two big .45's with sandalwood grips that have been passed down the line of gunslingers father to son for centuries.  Anyway, if you haven't already discovered and enjoyed these stories, you should give 'em a read.  The last book in the saga will release in the fall of this year after 22 years since the initial release.  King received a letter from a fan after a long period of time had past between books.  Enclosed in the letter was a Polaroid picture of a stuffed bear, gagged and tied to a chair.  There was a gun to the furry bear's head.  Written below the photo was the following: "Release the next Dark Tower book or the bear dies".  How cool that must be to have people enjoy what you create so much.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When Ronald Reagan took office after the landslide defeat of Jimmy Carter, the pundits said it was just business as usual in terms of the presidency.  Four years and out was to be the norm for our country's leadership.  President Reagan changed that through his natural gift of being able to relate to all people.  He was a great galvanizing force in America, bringing people from both parties together without ever compromising his principles or ideals.  Despite the democratic majority in congress; things happened, things got done.  He was a leader in the best since of the word - people followed him because they believed in him and because he was so charismatic.  We need more Americans like him.  He'll be missed and never replaced.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So much for the new driver delivering an improved golf game.  ^%#$% piece of crap!!!  On a brighter note, my Cardinals are finally on a tear.  Six wins out of the last seven and only 2.5 games behind the Reds.  Yes, the Reds.  Come on Cincy, wake up!  You guys suck and you know it!  It's only a matter of time.  As long as the eternally cursed Cubs continue to find ways to keep their starting pitching injured and the Astros (who have never won a playoff series, never!) realize the folly of actually wasting a playoff spot, my guys may have a chance.  By the way, Albert Pujols (league leading 17th HR yesterday) is the best player in baseball right now.  Any disagreement??    Now to my basketball team: The Lakers look poised to win yet another NBA title, giving Phil Jackson a record-breaking 10!  Can this guy pick a decent team to lead or what?  First the Jordan's, I mean the Bulls and now the team with the two best players in the league on it.  Give me these guys and I could have won a couple, right?  Detroit isn't as scary as they were with Dumars, Thomas, Rodman, Laimbeer, Vinnie (the microwave) Johnson, and John Salley.  Sure Ben Wallace is a great player, but come on, let's not forget that the Pistons come from the EASTERN conference!  Lakers in 6.  That just leaves my Dolphins who haven't seriously challenged for league dominance since the mid-80's era of Dan Marino's hayday.  Well, we'll see, maybe this is the year.  Why shouldn't I be optimistic?  Our new quartback is A.J. Feeley! Sure he didn't even start in college, but he's got skills.  Right?  Doesn't he?  Hey, how 'bout them Cardinals!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Work is done for the day and it's time to play!  I've got a full afternoon planned: hit the driving range with my new driver (new-found driver, new-found skill, right?) then off to the gun range to fire off some ordnance.  What a fine afternoon!  Hopefully the rain will hold off long enough to allow me to stay dry while I fire 300 yd. drive after 300yd. drive.  Well, it  is  a new club, right?  Speaking of the weather, it's been crazy here.  Rain, flooding, tornados, thunderstorms, and hail.  Maybe Al Gore is right.  We  are  all doomed to a disaster-movie death.  We  are  destroying the earth's delicate equilibrium by driving our gas guzzling trucks and SUV's.  No wait, I just realized something.  I said Al Gore may be right and that just can't be.  If the ecological situation was so dire, he wouldn't have made it worse by riding around in a motorcade complete with like a billion Chevy Suburbans would he?  And wouldn't he have spent the time he devoted to "inventing the internet" doing something to save the planet?  I guess it must just be a typical spring season here in Nebraska.  I added some links to the sidebar courtesy of my friend  urlLink Jake .  They are good ones for us right-wingers.  Enjoy!  Kevin
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The above is a link to a great site.  This guy can really write and shares most of my same views.  I say most because I'm not sure that Lara Flynn Boyle is really a cannabil, but I've been wrong in the past.  If she is, in fact, a cannabil, wouldn't that be the hot new fad diet for the ultra thin Hollywood types and super-models?  Anyway, I hope you enjoy it as much as I do. Kevin
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trust Kerry?  Read  urlLink this .  That's all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow's the day! I fly out to Minneapolis early for interviews tomorrow and Wednesday. It's a little scary to know that I've worked four years to get this opportunity and a poor showing in the interviews could push me back 6 months or so. I've been prepping and practicing though, so I think I'm ready. I'll keep you all posted...  The roomie is up in Sturgis for the week. I'm looking forward to some cool photos and some interesting tales. She went up last year and came home with gifts for the kids, a shirt for my daughter and a skull cap for my son. The skull cap read "It you can read this, the bitch fell off" on the back. Not real appropriate for an 8 yr. old - so she cut the verbiage off and left the Harley emblem. He looked pretty cool in it after the removal. My ex-wife's boyfriend rides a motorcycle so I thought about giving it to him instead, but in the interest of maintaining the peace, I decided against it.  Talked with Jake in WA. yesterday, glad to hear he is doing well. I'm going to find the time to get out there soon and see him. I miss hanging out with him and I miss the Seattle area. It would be relaxing to spend some time up there again. Shooting, shooting, talking about the old days, and maybe some shooting. I don't know how it's going to work out, but I'll get back there soon. When Lisa and I initially moved out there in 1994, we rolled into Everett, WA to find Jake watching the O.J. chase through LA on the tube. I'll never forget that day. We lived for about 6 weeks at his place until I found work and we found our own place. During those 6 weeks, Jake gave up his bed and even welcomed in Lisa's sister from Iowa. Oh by the way, his place had one-bedroom and was about 600 sq. feet. We also had two cats and a dog. And Lisa's sister was pregnant. Wow, thanks again Jake. That must have sucked! Anyway, we lived in Seattle for nearly 6 years and Jake was there when our family grew both times. He got to see Morgan and Brianne both on the day they were born.  I could devote a posting every day for months telling stories about what we did over the years. The trips on the Cascade Loop, driving the Mazda to the Grand Canyon for spring break, driving that same Mazda into the Pacific Ocean, football Sunday mornings at Sporty's Beef & Brew, driving to Kesselring's to see Bob "the gun pimp", replacing the alternator in Jay's car at the rest area and the ensuing "cat fiasco", Thanksgiving dinner with Socrates and Ripple, shooting at the Kenmore gun club, Christmas mornings in Seattle when our families were in the Midwest, playing pool with the old men on Father's day at the house, sitting around lamenting about the trouble with women in college, and after college, and yesterday... Check out his site  urlLink here .  Anyway, gotta go pack for the trip.  Take care. - Kevin 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Really funny stuff over there at  urlLink IMAO!   Know Thy Enemy: Facts about Democrats is one of Frank's best -- enjoy! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, it's been awhile since I've been able to use my computer for anything other than holding down papers when I've got a fan on.  I had so much crap on my hard drive that my system was constantly crashing.  I have very little computer know-how (I can turn it on and deftly maneuver a mouse, no more) so I had to call in a friend to bring the wood to the virus infection.  My browser was being "hi-jacked" and I kept getting redirected to some stupid "home page".  No matter how many times I changed the internet settings, it never went away.  I finally gave up, deleted internet explorer and installed netscape navigator.  So far, so good.  If I ever meet the idiot that wrote that crap, I'm kicking him in the junk.  If it was a female writer, I'll just call her nasty names and tell her she looks fat in her outfit.  Anyway, it's nice to be back.  Lot's of stuff happening now at work, I fly to Minneapolis on Tuesday for my final round of interviews for a promotion.  Politicians don't go through this kind of scrutiny, but I'm enduring.  If I get through this one, the rewards will be sweet.  My roomie is recovering from her surgery quite nicely and is itching to get her energy back.  I think that's a good sign.  Initially, she didn't even  want  her energy back, so we're improving.  Jazz has made herself a part of the family.  I've taken her with me to the folk's and they're quite smitten with her.  The kids are gearing up for school and I think Lisa may even be ready to get back to teaching.  I'm looking forward to seeing Morgan and Brianne this weekend and hitting the zoo.  If you've never been to the zoo in Omaha, we've got a great one...  Anyway, that's all for now.  Barring a renewed assualt from the virus/spyware clowns, I'll be writing more frequently.  Go Cards! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>