<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Giggle Dwarf, (n.): If you want this definition you will just have to ask me. I promise that you will be greatly offended if you are any sane person.  So what do I have to talk about today? Naught much I am sick and really freaking tired. I am stressed out worrying about things upcoming in the move that I will be doing next week. I am running around trying to clean my house so that I do not get charged $800 when I leave. I am watching my bank account dwindle away as unexpected expenses pop up and take a chunk out of it. I worry about what I am going to be doing with my children during the time the movers come and pack stuff up, Wednsday, and when I am putting them on a plane, Friday. I do not know where I am going to let them sleep, their mother is worthless and it seems unable to help, and I am afraid that I cannot afford a hotel room anymore. I do not want to impose my children on anyone else, so here I am. My friggin back muscles and shoulder muscles are killing me due to the stress, and if I could get a good massage I would be all better.  Ok enought whining on my part, I just wanted to get a few things off my shoulders and try to relax a bit. Normally I used to be a rock upon which insane happnenings broke themselves onto. I would stand there and look as drama unfolded in front of me and I would shake my head and say to myself. "Man I am so glad that that crap is not happening to me.". But I guess I need to open up my eyes because it is happening to me, and has been for some time. If anyone out there feels that a girl leaving them is the end of everything, then I am here to say this. Fuck em! Sure it is American to the core, but let me tell you something my friend. Women are fickle and never know what they want, and if she leaves you don't whine over spilt milk. Sure you may feel some feelings of rejection and "losership", but hell your supposed to you are a friggin human being.   The worse thing a man can do is stay with a woman who doesn't want him. Case in point look at me, mine lied to me the entire marriage and cheated on me behind my back at every oppurtunity. Then she up and left me with the children to go live with her new man, who then promptly dumped her after the divorce. Now because of my children I have to deal with her all the time. You men out there who lose a girlfriend and thats it? Shut up and say "Fuck em". At least you don't have to have small talk with them ever again and you can move on with your life. Besides you never know if the great cosmic forces that be fiddled around a bit with your life so that a few months down the road you meet the girl/guy your supposed to meet. (Threw guy in there just in case you decide to turn homosexual!) Ok well I hope this small bit of wisdom from a raving madman helps you all somehow. Just remember, some people have it worse than you do!  (Case in point my female friend who beats me. Her husband left her to go live with a hooker and smoke crack all day. That left her without any cash or a place to live with her little boy. She cried and cried until one day she woke up and thought, "what the fuck am I doing? If I don't snap out of this my son will suffer." A few years down the road after she got her life back on track with the help of friends she finally met her man. Now she is happy.)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my first post and I feel that I should speak of many things. What should I start with? Knowledge that I have learned or maybe a good anecdote? Oh well, let us start with I am a man like many other and like millions I live in the United States of America. I have lived a life full of joys and sorrow and even now I am continually walking down the path of life. Many people have I found to call friend, but only a few have taken a residence within me as true friends. I do not have many enemies because I do not care to make them. Goodness this is starting to get all serious and stuffy sounding, nothing like my normal self that I show everyone. I guess that’s what these blogs are for however, to show others your inner self.  I am a very serious person, almost too serious, and sometimes I look at the world around me and do not like what I see. People are foolish and fickle that populate this world, and it is leading to quite a large mess. I am only twenty four years old, yet already I am a father of two young children and I am their only source of life. I may be young yet already I carry a heavy burden. Often times I get oppressed by what life has thrown at me and often times I wonder if there isn’t something else I should be doing. However now I feel complete once again. Things in my life recently have changed and I feel more at peace with myself and the world.  Have you ever read a really really good book that was so wonderful and entrapped you so well that when you finally finished it and put it down you were left in a daze? That is how I feel right now, caught in a half dream that I do not know if it is real or just fantasy. I only hope that the veil is not ripped from my eyes to show a world of nightmares. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>