<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Lesson ended at 9am and we(my class) have to start cleaning the classroom. Well, it doesn't seem like a class effort to me. Only part of the class was involved or should I say, took the effort to help out, while others just idle around. Anyway, more pairs of hands hastened the process and I must say, the boys in my class took the initiative to help out. To me, that was something irony. In about one hour, the classroom was sparkling clean!=) good job 4/3!!    We were dismissed at 10 plus and I went out with my good friends, Kyah Hwee and Miao Hui. The three of us took bus 502 to orchard road, went cineleisure whereby we took neoprints twice!! It has been a real long time since the three of us hang out together. I still remember the happy times we had when I was in Secondary 2/2. Back then, we would always hang around together. In a sense, the three of us form a clique; a group which wasn't too big or too small. However, we got separated from one another after the sec 2 streaming examinations and I really mean separated. Miao Hui, Kyah Hwee and me got into 4/5, 4/4 and 4/3 respectively. Since then, we started to have our new circle of friends but nevertheless, Miao Hui and I still go out together after school. I think the words which bonds us as good friends is "Similarity" The three of us have quite a few similarities, we love cute stuffs, love to joke around, hate the same people etc. As for Miao Hui and me, there's even more! We are both cowards, hate people who smokes, hate proud people and the most distinct similarity is that we are both humans without any sense of direction. That's why we can't go to orchard road with each other; we will get lost for sure.     Friends play a very important role in my life. They are the ones who encourage me to go on and the ones who share my pain, sorrow and joy. I'm glad to have such wonderful friends who are always willing to listen to my troubles and to help me get on with life after a fall. To all my friends out there, a big "thank you" for being such great buddies!=) Cheers~      
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      An Angel  In the years I’ve known you time has passed Things have changed but friendships last You we’re sent to me to be my friend If my heart was broken you’d help it mend  If there wasn’t a smile but a frown on my face I could count on you to put things back in place If ever you’re down and need a hand You can count on me to understand  If you need a break to get away from it all If you need me there just give me a call I’ll be there for you like you’re there for me When ever you want like a best friend should be  If you need a hug, I’ll give you two And if you need to talk I’ll stay with you If you need a shoulder to cry on, I’ll be here To make you smile and wipe away that tear  I promise if you need me right there I’ll be To do all these things like you have for me Thank you for being my dream come true I’ve been sent an angel in the form of you  adapted from http://www.friendship-poems.com/poems.php?id=101732  I was searching the net for some nice poems to post them here and this is one of the better ones. Well, to me, it somewhat brings out the message which I would want to tell all my friends. So, To every single friend of mine, this poem is specially dedicated to you! And to the choir members whom I dearly missed, you people have been a great bunch of friends...all the best for those participating in the Jubilate Festival!!=)      
     
    
</post>


</Blog>