<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Angry. Irate. These 2 words are not even close to describing what I'm feeling now.  Went to school for tutorial.. Well we're supposed to show the tutor how much progress we made for a project we're supposed to do in a week. After so much hard work and heartache, my fellow teammate did not bring our project. He did not even tell us that beforehand!! Fucking bastard. The entire team was in shock when he told the tutor he COULDN'T bring the project because it was on his desktop. I could have brought my notebook for presentation, and instead he kept quiet and caused the entire team to lose marks for 'not showing progress' when we worked our asses off.  Stupid china man.  This is the first and the last time I'll EVER want to work with a China man. He'd better not be lying about not bringing our project.. He may have been slacking off for all I know. Lamer. I suspect a coverup. I bloody hate this China man.   Burn in HELL!!    Did I ever mention that he's a sexist too? Because I'm the only girl in the team, he thinks I'm there for the free ride and I'm a bimbo who knows nothing about computing and stuff. True, I may suck at it but don't treat me like an imbecile. Throughout the entire semester he ignored my suggestions and effort. When I talked to him, he bloody looked elsewhere at other non-speaking teammates. When I wrote a proposal, he bloody ignored it and wrote another one regardless of what I had to say. What the fuck. I hate China man. No wonder birth control is strict in China. They produce too many shitheads.  And after a very HORRIBLE tutorial(we got scolded. I bloody wanted to stab the China dude.), I went to collect my skirt from the drycleaner. The fucking drycleaner charged me $47.60 for cleaning a bloody skirt! I demanded to see the price list and the guy gave me a lame excuse about charging more for cleaning the skirt manually. You mean to say that manual labour for cleaning   ONE skirt is worth $30  !? Fucking ripoff.  I hope the drycleaner closes down. And I hope the China guy dies a horrible death. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Guess I've been blogging a lot, judging from the frequency of my posts but who cares. I just happen to have plenty of things in my head, and I made it a point to jot it down on Notepad before posting them all at once. HAHAHA... so one day when I'm really bored, I can sit down and read my posts, laughing at what the hell I was thinking before.  My assignment is killing me. I've debugging it the entire day and it's a miracle my notebook can stand my abuse. Good ol'    IBM    makes durable stuff. It's not even heated yet. ahahaha... Anyway this assignment betta get good grades, otherwise it's cheating me of my precious time.  Teck is being hilarious again. And Teck if you are reading, you will get your  raspberry filled Krispy Kreme doughnut  when you get here. Anyone who reads this will become your witness, and that's if I don't remove this post. Haha.. This guy was literally drooling all over his computer screen when he checked out the Krispy Kreme website. I'm not sure if the franchise is available in asia yet, but if it is, I don't think it will make it big since everyone in Asia is so bloody  body conscious . The stick thin folks think they are overweight and embark on this "wellbeing" journey that guarantees that they can fit into kid size clothes after that. People get criticised for being fat, and are not valued for their talent. Try offering a doughnut to people around you, my friends in Singapore. You will either   a)get punched and shunned.  b)hear the following: "Do you know how fattening a doughnut is?! If I eat a doughnut, my six pack will be gone! God forbid that I lose them. How am I going to face the world?! I won't be stick thin!"  c)all of the above.   Crap. As if you go around baring your six packs to everyone on the street. That's of course if you dress like Britney Spears who leaves nothing to the imagination. It's great to have a fantastic bod and congratulations if you have one. But don't get so hung up on it. Have one doughnut, hell maybe two. Stop if you are reaching out for your forth one. ^___^ I love my doughnuts. Yum. And pass those yummy bbq chicken wings over here.  On a lighter note, the author of this blog is contemplating a noticeboard/chatboard thing. Still undecided about that. I mean, who is going to write on my noticeboard anyway? Not many people read my blog too, much less leave a comment or leave me a message... *sob* Hmm... Noticeboard? Pending approval.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Some people say that house moving is  one of the most traumatic experiences  in a person's life. It ranks somewhere after childbirth and death. Guess what? I think I'm moving soon. My friend, Junyu, is moving to a bigger place and I'm going to take over his 1 bedroom apartment! So happy..I will no longer have to pay double rent for a room that I don't stay in. Basket... waste my money only.  Ok, back to the  traumatic  part. Can you imagine the amount of stuff I have to pack!? Clothes, books, stacks of paper that can qualify for a skyscraper easily, the pots and pans, the bloody washing machine, fridge, and bubblewrap each piece of fragile stuff manually... you get what I mean. And the excruciating wait to cancel/move the phone and gas. And not to mention changing mailing addresses, starting from the bank, uni right down to eBay sending address. $%&*^*$#  If only there's some professional packing company that handles all this crap.  But maybe after moving, I can go play golf with Junyu and co. Gotta work on my swing. The last time I played was my first, and god, I looked awful trying to swing like a pro. *weeps*    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Something struck me recently and I don't know if I'm just being silly or what.  Whatever happened to just plain old-fashioned relationship between a couple?  My friend just got attached recently, say approximately a month ago. Of course, being new in a relationship he would tell me situations he got into and asked me for help, ie. what flowers to get, what she's trying to say, is she playing with words etc. However one day he dropped the bombshell. He did it with his girlfriend.   Maybe I shouldn't be making a fuss since this is the 21st century. Is there a need to tell me that he did it, and the fact that he discussed it with many other people what's the norm these days? *shocked* Then he asked me how my sex life was. The answer is: nonexistent. Yes, don't be so shocked, it is nonexistent.   Why must people assume that being in a relationship means that sex is involved? Is it the definitive sign that 2 person are in a relationship? It's not that I'm against sex. It's just that I don't want it to be something I will regret later.   Couple can talk. Couple can watch tv. And yes, couple can do boring homework together. Does it make their relationship any weaker than those who have had sex? I don't think so.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Had a chat with 2 of my oldest friends today. One of them in America, the other in Singapore. Let me count...right. We've known each other for 7-8 years now, and they have been through the good and bad times with me. I even went through a rough patch with one of them for quite a while, but everything's ok now and we're better friends than before. We talk about stuff that people don't usually share with their friends or therapist.  Somehow I feel so envious of my friends. They seem to have it all, a life outside of school and things they enjoy doing. While I for one remain stagnant for ages; no life outside of school. To be frank, no life at all. =..( I have so many other things to worry about, and I somehow do not have the luxury of having a life, much less an interesting one. No point whining since it's not going to change anything.  People keep asking me where I will go after graduation, even though I won't be graduating till next year and that's if I don't screw anything up. Personally, I don't know. I don't want to stay here in Sydney because I would like to be with my family. But going back to Singapore/Malaysia is not any better since most of my friends have moved on with their lives, and it won't be the same as before. There's no way I will go Hong Kong either; it's too unfair to my parents. Sigh.  But one thing is for sure: I am determined to change myself. I'm so tired of me now. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Was trying to find out the actual aussie release date for Spidey 2 on the web when I stumbled across this flick called "The Prince and Me" and "The Princess Diaries 2". Such flicks are generally targetted at kids, well girls below the age of 14 and people of my age are supposed to turn up our noses and ignore these releases totally. Why do we do that? Is it because we've finally realised that fairytales and their typical "happily ever after" endings don't really exist? Or is it because the plot for these flicks are generally predictable and shallow? Let's assume it's the former so I have something to rant about.  Maybe the majority of us, ok GIRLS mainly, realise that we will not meet a real life prince, let alone marry one within the next 10 lifetimes. Or have some stranger come up to you and say "You're actually the heir or missing prince/princess to  fill in country >." It's already hard enough to meet a decent fella to have an intellectual conversation going, what are the chances of meeting a prince? Almost zilch. That is, unless you are some powerful socialite or linked to some politicians of course. Chances of that happening to YOU: ZERO. ZILCH. NADA. FUGGEDABOUTIT.  Whatever.   Anyway if such fairytales are virtually nonexistent, it explains why the whole world gets riveted to the tv when a royal wedding takes place. And this year, 2 took place. For those who don't know which 2 countries, it's Spain and Denmark. *I watch the news ok..* Ahh.. what luck. I can picture millions of little girls sitting in front of their tellys, wishing that they would grow up to be real life princesses. Sigh... Good luck girls.  If I have my way, I'll bloody declare myself one instead of waiting for someone to make me a princess. HAHAHAHa... HRH Symin. I'll declare all sorts of things. Beware of what I can do. *evil grinz*  On another note, I can't wait to watch Spidey 2!!  Another incoherent post. What's new. And if you don't like it, sod it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "All my life everyone keeps telling me you're a shoe, you're a shoe. But what if I don't want to be a shoe? What if I want to be a hat? I don't want you to buy me a hat, I'm saying I am a hat. It's a metaphor, daddy!" -- Rachel Green (episode 1)  Hmm..the above quote is correct, well that's what I remember anyway. quoted offhand. I want to be something different, someone whom no one expected me to be. Oh, and I did a Friends quiz. Lo and behold, what a surprise.     urlLink      I'm Rachel Green from Friends!   urlLink Take the Friends Quiz here.      
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Somehow this pet project has erupted to this full blown case of blog addiction. I keep thinking of things to add to my blog, instead of other things such as my assignments. I need to go cold turkey, AFTER I add a new entry. *grinz*  I want to read about other people's blog too. See what people actually put down in their blogs. How 'interesting' can it be. Bleah....   Actually I do have something to say. Is it right for a person to feel desired? As in knowing that some people(besides your bf/gf) are actually feeling something for you? Sounds weird but it's a kind of ego booster and it puts a certain spring in people's steps. I guess it's alrite to have this kinda attention. *shrugs* =/ The sad thing is I know of a person who is no longer feeling something, and this makes me kinda sad. It's like knowing that you have lost an appeal/X-factor/special connection with someone. CRAP. There goes my ego booster/spring in my step. What the hell...  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hmm.. supposed to be doing my assignments. However, I've found myself devoting most of my time updating and sprucing up this blog thing, and hence the topic.  The tv is blaring behind me, some silly show called "Big Brother". A whole load of crap. Just listed down my preferred thesis topic, but I'm not sure if I'll get what I'm interested in. Hmm =/  Anyway I will try and do my work. *Concentrate* And if this blog gets more updates and new links, it just means that I'm doing stuff I'm not supposed to. We shall see. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I finally did get my hands on those fantastic, melt-in-your-mouth    Krispy Kreme    original glazed doughnuts. The queue to get those doughnuts can put the queue at your local supermarket to shame. It was down the block and the queue never stops. And for those who don't think one block is a long way, believe me, it is LONG. And ridiculous just to get yourself some world famous doughnuts.  A long lost friend, ok not lost but not really kept in contact with, suddenly sent a msg to me on msn. I have not seen her in 3 years and she informed me of a primary school gathering that's going to happen tomorrow. Too bad I'm on a totally different continent. Ahhh primary school. Those were the days that you can get away with anything. I haven't met up with most of them, and I just found out someone is now known as Timothy, previously known as TH. It's a little like "The artist formerly known as". Oh well.  p.s I got my curry stained kilt to the dry cleaner. They told me it's going to take them a day to clean it. Hope they don't lose it or add more stains to it. *cross my fingers*
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sigh... As much as I don't want to admit, I've caught on the blog bandwagon. HOLY CRAP. Perhaps it's a way I can fully express myself without really giving a damn as to how others think. Things that are posted in the blog thing are unfiltered, and sometimes incoherent since everything that comes to mind gets typed down. People who are easily offended or don't see eye to eye with me on some issues, look away. =)  Anyway I've plenty of things on my hand.. I've got 3 assignments due next week and 1 major presentation that's gonna determine if I pass or fail that subject. So now you have an idea of how's life like in my pathetic worn out shoes.   I had a dream. It was nice and it was of my friends in Singapore right now. How I miss every single one of them! You know who you are, if you decide to read my entry. I realise that they are the single bunch of people that are my 'final' group of close friends. It's hard to explain, but being in uni doesn't really mean that you are constantly surrounded by people whom you would call friends. I miss my friends, and the jokes and the verbal 'crossfire'. It's this casual talk and 'debates' that hold us together. I'm getting over-emotional/talking too much mushy yucky stuff now.  Gotta run. Will update whenever I can. This will BECOME my pet project. =)
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm terribly overwhelmed by work. =(  And because someone, ok El, said my blog entries are way too long, I shall keep this one short and give it to him in point form.  - I have so much to study. - I'm having really bad thoughts about a certain teacher.  - I'm quite broke. - I want a holiday.  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Years ago it was "Clueless" that brought my attention to life in the fast lanes of Beverly Hills. I was thirteen then. It left me thinking when will the kids here get to bring cellphones to school at age 15, or buy Dior couture at age 15 as well.  Lately the content in the recent well-received movies and tv series has changed to a more dramatic tone sans the comical aspect of life in Beverly Hills. It's more like grownup "Clueless" without Cher's goofiness. I'm still interested but no longer unfazed at how 'unlikely' it is to happen around us. Life in the fast lane has finally arrived to our part of the world. Maybe not not as exciting but we're catching on.  After watching the OC and the trailer for "Mean Girls" that is playing on tv, I can't help but feel that this is just everyday life for many of us. Maybe not as filthy rich or good looking as the characters involved, but the overall feeling of the popular  (ie. the jocks)  pushing people around, the rich  (ie. old money)  looking down on everyday kids, the beautiful  (ie. the REALLY beautiful ones AND the self-presumed "beauties")  strut around like god-sends. Somehow we are lucky in a way because of mandatory uniforms, otherwise we will have fashion wars as well. Hypocrites pretending to like you, and the minute you turn your back, they backstab you. The ongoing competition of getting the 'IT' items at the moment. The wild parties. The categorisation of rich: old money, new money, not enough money, how you get the money. It's another world.   How 'unlikely' this is to happen in the sunny little island that is Singapore. Hmmm... then why are these scenarios so FAMILIAR?  Sigh, I don't know.. Just feel like writing these down since I feel like it suddenly.   Anyway, about the rich kid syndrome. Have you ever have the feeling that some rich brats have all the things that money can buy and their behaviours are nothing short of atrocious? Go watch the series "Rich Kids" or something like that. Forgot the name. Ally Hilfiger, daughter of Tommy Hilfiger, and I think some guy who really belongs to the OLD MONEY, think Rockerfeller clan, are in the show. Ally spends thousands in one afternoon in one of her 'normal afternoon day out". The guy who threatens another with one POWERFUL sentence,  "Shut up. I can buy your family. Now fuck off."  Wow. Classic. There is also an article called "Park Avenue Princesses" on   urlLink MSNBC   that goes on to show us the normal folks a day in the life of a park avenue princess. The expensive tea parties for 8 year olds, designer gifts for baby showers and so one. It's as if the rich are royalties, except without the title.  Can't keep my thoughts coherent. Don't think I have to write anymore since everyone knows at least a little about the rich kid syndrome or at least some rich brats among us.  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My property agent called me 4 times this morning, just to show me how inefficient and dishonest they are.  First call: they told me they couldn't find my deposit for the new apartment, even asking if I have paid or not. I told them I even got a receipt.  Second call: they told me they found the cheque, as it was filed under the  FORMER  tenant's name. Stupid people.  Third call: told me that the kitchen in my previous apartment wasn't clean enough and there were damages to the blinds. Either I fix these problems myself or they will ask someone to fix it, where the charges incurred will be deducted from my bonds. What the hell.. The blinds were already broken when I moved in! Had to shout over the phone to tell him that it's not fair that I have to repair someone else's damages when I did not cause them. He even dared tell me that he's not picking on me. Well it's his fault that he didn't know the previous conditions of the apartment! By regulations they have to conduct a 'condition report' of the apartment when I signed the lease. They did not. And I wasn't aware of such a check till now. What a ripoff. Now I have to go 'clean' the old kitchen in the middle of my exams.   Fourth call: asked if I have returned the keys when I already did. Better communication with your colleagues people!! Stop harassing me.  Curse these property agents.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tried the Go-Quiz again just to see the different results on my name. Haha..     How to make a symin        Ingredients:  5 parts jealousy 5 parts courage 3 parts leadership        Method:  Stir together in a glass tumbler with a salted rim. Add a little cocktail umbrella and a dash of lustfulness        Username:    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just woke up not too long ago, say 11.30pm. Downloaded a french song called   Irresistiblement   by Sylvie Vartan because Desmond recommended it. Very cheerful and old school pop song, circa 1980s. Copied the lyrics below from Desmond's blog. Didn't even ask him. Haha.. Des, don't be mad ok?  as copied from Des's blog:  here are the lyrics and translation to this french song from the ost of waterboys the movie. fucking nice. go download it from kazza or somethin'.  Irrésistiblement sylvie vartan  Tout m'entraine, irresistiblement vers toi comme avant Tout m'enchaine, irresistiblement a toi je le sens  Comme le jour revient apres la nuit Et le soleil toujours apres la pluie Comme un oiseau qui revient vers son nid Vers mon amour je vais aussi  Tout m'entraine, irresistiblement vers toi a chaque instant Tout m'enchaine, irresistiblement a toi je le sens  Comme la mer qui frappe le rocher Obstinement sans jamais desarmer Par le malheur on est souvent frappe Mais l'amour seul peut nous sauver  Comme la joie revient apres les pleurs Après l'hiver revient le temps des fleurs Au moment où l'on croit que tout se meurt L'amour revient en grand vainqueur  Tout m'entraine, irresistiblement vers toi comme avant Tout m'enchaine, irresistiblement a toi je le sens.  translation:   Everything carries me Irresistibly to you, like the wind  Everything ties me Irresistibly to you, I feel it  Like the day rises after night And the sun always follows rain Like a bird returning to its nest To my love I also go  Everything carries me Irresistibly to you, at every instant Everything ties me Irresistibily to you, I feel it  Like the sea batters the rocks Persistently, without cease We're often hit with misfortune But love alone can save us  Like joy follows after tears After winter returns the time of flowers When you feel that everything is dead Love returns the grand victor  Everything carries me Irresistibly to you, like the wind  Everything ties me Irresistibly to you, I feel it    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       FINALLY. One of the hardest papers is over. It was Electrical Engineering stuff. I hate electrical stuff. Stupid op-amps and transistors. I hope I pass. I'll do anything to pass this subject.  I'm writing a piece on something, which will probably be finished after my exams. I've started on it and it's going ok. I will compile this piece(s) throughout my ordeal (exam season) and let's see how lengthy this piece(s) will be.  Just watched the FIRST episode of The OC. Great stuff. Gonna download it.  I'm so tired. Gotta sleep.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm broke and my purse is dirty. You heard me right. I don't use a wallet. I chucked my wallet somewhere because it's too bulky and opt for a little purse.   Just had a peek at my purse. It has lost some of the  girly pink  it had when I first got it. Oh my poor Coach purse. Shall clean it after my exams. I must take good care of it since it was a birthday present from a dear friend,  Setsuko , who is in US. I don't even know when I will see her again.  Strange that my purse weighed so little. Did I just use all my coins? Hmmm... Took another peek inside my purse. It's frightfully empty. I've got a 10 dollar note and 3 coins to be exact. I'm so poor... Shucks.   Why am I writing a blog entry about my purse?  It's about time I stop neglecting my md and record something. It's been some time since I've last recorded anything worth listening to. Still remembered how thrilled I was when I first got my md. It's white in color. Totally rare. But it's been so many years (4-5 years ago).   Just tried to download some songs by Yellowcard on Kazaalite. When I tried playing those songs, they were all the same tune repeating for 10 secs despite being different tracks! I suspect it's some anti-piracy thing. Crap. And  some mp3s are actually corrupted files.  They will play until a certain extent and this period of scratchy sounds will take over. Eek. People should be  BANNED  from sharing these kinda files. A waste of time. Inconsiderate people.. Tsk tsk tsk. Listening to  "This Love" by Maroon 5.  I had to download this song  7 times  just to get the right uncorrupted copy. Damn those users who share corrupted files. And despite the frustration from downloading this song and the repetition, it's pretty catchy. Hahaha...    Anyway Rick Dees do have a great list of what songs to download. I think he meant for people to go buy their cds but haha.. Kazaalite is the antithetical solution. Doesn't it prove that a performer is popular/talented/doing-something-right-at-the-moment if their songs are widely sought and downloaded off the P2P network? Encourage P2P file sharing! Hahaha... campaigning for the "P2P Movement". I bet everyone has downloaded something (mp3s, movies, sitcoms etc.) off the P2P network at some point in their lives. Good on you.  This particular blog entry is just my random thoughts. They are not coherent. I just type something whenever I feel like which explains how fragmented it is. I think I probably typed a little something (takes about 5 minutes) every 1 or 2 hours. Let's see how much I can write. I'm suffering from a bad case of zits. Having 5 of those  red little painful bumps  on my face. I haven't got them since the last exam. =( Depressing. I've been plagued by these buggers since sec school and they just won't leave me alone. Basket..   Enough rambling for a day. Surprised at how much I can put down in words. 5 minute sessions. Amazing.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I realise that in some small ways, I'm actually quite lucky. I'm sort of going through a rough patch, the kind where things are going topsy turvy when they shouldn't be. I always thought my friends are too busy with their stuff. And when I'm depressed (sort of), they are actually talking to me about it, asking me if I'm feeling better or offering me advice when I least expected them to. Thanks peeps, for being with me. You don't know how much this means to me. You know who you are and I won't name names. =)  Put up a tagboard for fun and hope that this blog is more active. Haha..what a reason. I feel like putting up more links and stuff but I don't really have much time to fiddle with my blog. Wait 3 weeks and I shall try to revamp my blog. Watch this space.  Bloody neighbours... painting their house or stuff. Now the entire house smells of paint and it's making me giddy. Going to suffer from lead poisoning. =( I know this because I took a course this semester on safety,health and environment. It deals with the hazards around us. Fascinating subject. Don't ask why a computer engineer has to know all this. I know for a fact that most of the things around us are poisonous. Take your drinking water for example. The lead in it from your old lead water pipes are actually 'activated' when you boil your drinking water. And you thought boiling water makes it safer for drinking. I'm digressing.. but I'm very sure I'm going to have a headache soon. This smell of paint is driving me mad. Bloody neighbours.   Still studying my electrical stuff. Paper on the 22/6. Why is that I fully understand the lab work and I can put in resistors and what not with ease and be  CORRECT  about it, and when I have to do the exam I blank out  TOTALLY ? Must calm myself down and continue muggin'. Must call upon the rote learning skills I picked up during my education in Singapore. Hahaha.. Oh the regurgitation. I love my jc days, it was the best time ever.  Red ,  blue  and  gold . I'm so fond of my school colors all of a sudden. Somehow.  I realise that support comes in so many ways. Firstly I would like to thank   IBM   for making such durable notebooks. I abuse my notebook and it's on 24/7. It's Sooooo stable, and thank god for not dying on me during the exam season. Secondly the reliable microwave for heating up my meals ever so efficiently. Haha..I'm going mad. Seriously speaking I want to thank my friends who are with me during this incredible period. Those who aren't, take note and start feeling guilty.   I'm such a selfish brat but I don't care.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Not very motivated on my studies at the moment. I guess I'm tired of revising. What's new. I have to go back to my studies in a moment, even if I don't want to. Don't really want to disappoint my family by screwing up this subject.. Sigh.  Just talked to a friend. Casual chit chat. He has come to the conclusion quite some time ago that my boyfriend and I are not meant to be together. Our personalities are so different and I sometimes feel suffocated in this relationship. He suggests a breakup so that I can move on and find greener pastures. He feels that I deserve better.  The thing is, my bf is a nice guy. He's the goody guy that your family will accept. He thinks everything is all peachy between us. Maybe it's the difference in personality that is causing me to reconsider, or whatever you want to call it. The thing is, I can't bring myself to breakup because basically he has done nothing wrong. Breaking up with someone when he has done nothing wrong doesn't make sense. Sigh... Dilemma.  What am I to do? Am I supposed to change myself, or just give up?   I don't know.   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I hate to sound all whiny and deranged but I think I am suffering from a bad bout of jealousy. I'm jealous of so many people. It's not something that I can even be jealous of in the first place. Somehow the resident editor got really affected and started imagining things. I seriously need to go see a shrink.  Jealous over someone else's attention and words simply spell lunacy. I get jealous and envious because he loves someone else more that he loved me, that's if he loved me in the first place. Does that make me inferior or something? Why is it that I'm not as loved? What did I do wrong?  And another claims that a girl has made him so happy and his life more wonderful than it ever will be, just because she's there with him. So does it mean that I don't bring joy to people? I wreck people's lives? What's going on?   I don't expect people to really know what's going on, or what went on ages ago to understand the situation. And seriously I don't expect people to do anything in return because there is no need for any return. I just, have this ability to think too much. People will say I have way too much time on hand. The thing is, I don't. Somehow these things just seep into the small crevices and present themselves to me when I least expect it. The confusion these little scenarios bring, makes me really upset. I feel so small, so insignificant and so unimportant. From a shrink's point of view, I may be suffering from either low self esteem or lunacy. Frankly, I think I am going nuts. Not suicidal. Just nuts. I should be concentrating on my studies and the upcoming exam, and not hallucinating on the what-ifs and whys.   Why is it that it's easier said than done?
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Decided to drop off an entry on Harry Potter 3 before I get some shut-eye. I feel that it's a letdown, despite all the rave reviews about it being the best in the 3 Harry Potter franchise. Alfonso Cuaron did not do justice to the twists in Harry Potter 3. A lot of details from the book was left out and throughout the movie, there was a lot of repetition in scenes, which gave the movie a 'low-budget' feel. It's as if they can't afford to get better places or variety of places to showcase the intricate details as mentioned in the book, and Columbus succeeded where Cuaron failed terribly.   If you have watched the movie, you might remember the 'wooden' bridge scene. It appeared so MANY times. Why? Hippogriff was fine and the Patronus Charm was not as fantastic as I have imagined. The ending was crap. Ended with a screaming face of Daniel Radcliffe. Tsk tsk tsk. Very 'low budget' feel again. And what's with Malfoy? The sleek untouchable and sinister feel to him is gone. Now we have a blonde boy with a bad haircut. Sigh.. I thought he's supposed to be a 'prestigious' pureblood?! Where has the stuck up well-groomed bad boy gone? Sigh.  The lack of details in Cuaron's version made movie watching bad for me. Victor doesn't read anything other than comics. He doesn't touch books if he can help it, let alone read one. Throughout the entire bloody movie, he kept asking me about the details. He was fine for the first 2 because they were so idiot proof that no one would miss out anything if they haven't read the book. Thereby proving my point. Sigh.  J.K Rowling's creation is so successful because the readers can project whatever they want the background and settings to be. In the first 2 Harry Potter, it was almost everything I had imagined. The 3rd is a waste. Columbus should be back for the rest of Potter because he created everything from scratch. He would have a better idea and direction of how the feel of the movie should be. Since it's Cuaron, the resident film critic (me) give it  2 popcorns out of 5.    The film critic has decided to go sleep, and forget she ever set eyes on Harry Potter 3. She sincerely hopes that Spiderman 2 is not another over-hyped and disappointing movie.   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It has been a nightmarish week. The mother of all nightmares. I think people who are reading might have thought that I've given on up blog, or perhaps got kidnapped by aliens. Well none of that happened. I was just plain busy. Although my notebook is on 24hours a day, I didn't have the time to write anything unrelated to work. Let's have a sneak flashback:   Monday   :   Rushed Elec assignment. Officially signed the lease to my new apartment.   Tuesday  :   Went for Artificial Intelligence tute. Started on my AI assignment.   Wednesday:   Still doing AI assignment. Packed up some of the stuff in my room.   Thursday :   Still doing AI assignment till about 12am. Submitted it and started on my SESC1001 assignment, which is due friday midnight.   Friday   :   Began typing as soon as I pried my eyes open. I had been typing so much that my fingers became stiff. By the time I submitted my ENTIRE assignment, I was 5 minutes late. F*ck. 5% penalty but who cares.   Saturday :   Went to watch Harry Potter 3 to reward myself. Went home and regretted like hell cuz I've got loads to pack. Thought that 2 little drawers of toiletries and some kitchen appliance weren't a lot to pack. How wrong I was. The itty bitty stuff took SO LONG to pack. Packed till 4am.   Sunday   :   D-Day. Movers came 2 hours earlier and I wasn't even finished yet. Packed my entire life, ok 3 years, into the back of a van and moved to new place. Spent 6 hours doing that and the boxes are still unopened. =(    I'm so tired. Never have I EVER had to do so much manual labour in my entire life. I moved so many boxes today and they were not small or light, mind you. Also regretted in my head that I bought so many little stuff that made today hell. My friend, Luke, was supposed to come and help me but that bugger did not appear or take my phone calls. I'm so going to scream at him later. If he don't want to help he can just tell me and I will get someone else. BUT HE DIDN'T. My poor poor hands. I've got many cuts and it hurts like hell when I wash my hands. Basket.  I feel so weak and whiny. Hahaha, complaining and complaining about stuff. Oh well, it just so happened that there's a lot to complain in my life recently. *grinz*  I've got so many little zits just waiting to pop out. I'm a psychic in this field since I've battled these little irritating things since forever. *weeps* And I'm bloody flaking. What the hell...  Has to start revising for exams which starts on next Tuesday. My worst subject Elec. Study, mug, cramp, and just 'vomit' everything during the exam Singapore style.   Shall write later when I'm awake. Going to sleep like there's no tomorrow.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I self-declared a holiday for myself today. Just because I needed it. And seriously, I did not do a single constructive thing today, other than getting food and remote control. And that's if you consider these things constructive.  Had not felt this well rested since the bloody holidays. That was about 3 months ago. Slept as if in hibernation and did not budge or crawl out of my warm warm blankie till I felt hunger. Warm warm blankie...  Read some interesting blog(my bro's and a friend's) and watched some junk on tv today. Can you imagine I sat through a fishing program, a home renovation program, Gilmore girls, Saturday movie:Men of Honor(bleah..), and late night news? And now infomercials are blabbing away. I could have gone out and bought something(part of my prescribed retail therapy) but I didn't because I feel immensely guilty about moving house. My parents have to fork out so much more for rent and we're not exactly filthy rich. *whimpers* Decided to be the grateful and filial daughter by sparing them from further monetary problems from my 'therapy' session.  Did a funny quiz too. Try it!     Magister Mundi sum! "I am the Master of the Universe!" You are full of yourself, but you're so cool you probably deserve to be.  Rock on.     urlLink   Which Weird Latin Phrase Are You?      Added the link to this quiz website on the side. Explore when you have time.   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today has got to be one of the WORST day of my entire life.   Went to school for presentation. I was so terribly nervous that I had a speech written so that I wouldn't get tongue tied. Agreed to meet the rest of my team for a final meeting before the presentation. As usual the China dudes arrived late, leaving us with 10 minutes to prepare for our presentation instead of the proposed 1 hour. If that was not enough, the smart alec changed the   ENTIRE   project without Victor's and my knowledge. Everything was NOT GOING as our initial structure!! Both our codes were  unused . Then why the fuck ask us to debug till the wee hours in the morning?!   All our effort went down the stinky drain because of that son of a bitch. During the presentation he showed the examiner our 'working' program. And when the examiner asked us to show him the basic requirements of the project, the program did the following:   a) crashed and burned. b) did something entirely different that asked, eg. undo the WRONG thing. c) did something entirely different and THEN crashed.   Only a few of the requirements worked. And that's  BAD . And since I was sitting next to the examiner I could see his marking sheet. It was VERY BAD. And I noticed that under the 'peer assessment' ( they said I did NO WORK!?  Being the sarcastic me, I voiced my opinion about this injustice to the examiner. He then proceeded to ask everyone what each did and awarded 5 to everyone. Fucking Chinamen, trying to screw my marks. I hope they fail their honours program and get deported back to Mainland.   In the end, my team got a  6/20  because the smart alec changed the entire program. And he DARED TO SAY THAT IT DIDN'T MATTER BECAUSE WE WILL STILL FUCKING PASS.  He isn't the least bit sorry.  I am so going to make him pay for it. 6/20!!!!!!!! Can you imagine how BAD it is? This project goes towards 40% of our final mark. and out of 40% i got 12?!?! He made me fail. *fukin' hoppin' mad*  This is so unfair. Victor and I worked like hell to get everything working. Just because of this China man thinks he's the smartest gift to mankind, he had single-handedly caused us to fail our project. If only he let us know what he had been up to. NO WONDER he didn't reply to the group mails and inform the rest of the progress. HE MADE ME FAIL.  I AM SO MAD. GONNA DEVISE SOME PLANS TO MAKE THEM PAY FOR THIS INJUSTICE.   I HATE CHINA MEN. MAY THEY BURN IN HELL. SUFFER FOR THE REST OF ETERNITY. AND I'M NOT SORRY FOR CURSING THEM. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm so done with China men. My group is due for presentation and the stupid china men just replied my mail that they are NOT ANYWHERE NEAR COMPLETE FOR THE PROJECT. #$%^&*   They don't want to 'tell' us because they think we WON'T BE ABLE TO UNDERSTAND THEIR LOGIC. They are so going to make me fail this subject. I want to kill the 2 china guys now.   Pissed off.  DIE AND BURN IN HELL!   I hate China guys. SO ANGRY.  I was rushing another assignment just now. Some AI stuff. Why is the computer so damn stupid? I have to write a program that recognises English grammar and understands a passage. But this cranky thing only works whenever it likes!! It's already past due date. I guess I'll work on it and get whatever works best. =/ Things are NOT looking up for me.  Went to the agent's office this afternoon regarding the apartment thing. It's confirmed. I'll sign the lease next Monday and I'll be moving next weekend. I'll be extremely busy so I'm not sure if I can post anything. But then again I always manage to post something. Hahaha blog addiction.  And since it's 1.36am now, I have about 12 hours' time till my project presentation. I hope the 2 Chinamen finish the project. Otherwise I'm so going to skin them alive, and send them back to China. I'm actually quite nervous about the project. Failing or not doing well for the project would mean that I fail this course. *sob* I don't want to fail, and certainly not because of the 2 China-mama.  I hope everything goes well for the presentation later. *fingers crossed*
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It is set.  I'm moving! It's confirmed. Going to tell the agent I don't want the apartment anymore tomorrow. And hope he doesn't tell me there's a 1 month waiting period. I don't have that kinda money to pay for 2 places. We shall see how things go.  Just completed my share of the project, except for 1-2 small problems so I guess I still made some progress. Enjoying my  banana  +  strawberry  smoothie now.... Yum. How I wish I'm at some tropical resort now. I need a break desperately.  And since I'm on the topic of moving, I'm thinking of what furniture to buy. Maybe I'll get a dining table since my ex-housemate took the dining table, actually the entire living room. Now that I'm moving, I'll probably go  urlLink   Ikea    or  urlLink   Freedom    to get some cool lookin' furniture. You guys can browse the website and help me pick something! Leave a comment to let me know what you pick. Hahaha.. I regret not being the interior decorator I wanted to be. I'll be the   urlLink  Queer Eye for the Straight Guy    dudes all rolled into one character, but I won't be a guy and I won't be gay. Ok, maybe not all the Fab Five, since I can't really cook and I'm not exactly the culture vulture.  For those who are not sure who the Fab Five are, you've missed out on the best show you can possibly watch. It's educational(guys learn that they are not the only slob around), and with some major makeover and cleaning, both the guy and his den can look showroom perfect, with character and culinary skills to match. I don't think they show this in Singapore or Malaysia, since everyone is not ready to accept that homos dwell among them and being gay is morally unacceptable. I mean, that's their personal life and no one can criticise their choices. It's not as if you have to join them. It's a bit like religion. No one should judge a person because he/she chooses something different from you.  Going to do some furniture browsing. =) 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just watched   Shrek 2   on pirated dvd. Saved $10 on tix. It's quite cool, and funny because they make old stuff cool again. The music from the 80s, famous scenes from movies from the early 90s till now, ie. alien protruding from guy's stomach. It's good.  This week has been quite tough... lessons went on and on and we are already having tutorials and lab work. Bleah.. I read people's blog and sometimes I find that a lot of people seem to have pent up rage and angst. Always cursing and swearing to jab a knife into someone. The entire blog is full of these violent  "stick-you-up-you-lousy-stinkin'-maggot"  entries. I mean,  is life really THAT bad ? Ok, life sucks and shit happens. Complain a wee bit and move on. Reading some of these entries make me think of these people in a whole new light. It's like watching a psycho stirring in the dark, waiting for the right moment and finally unleashing his wrath one day. Hmm.. very cinematic description isn't it? I should work in that industry.  Oh, saw this  Takeshi Kaneshiro  poster on my way home. I think he has a new flick with Andy Lau and Zhang Ziyi. I don't watch Chinese flicks because I just think the plot is contact lens thin, not even paper thin. And they always put whoever's popular at the moment as lead actors even though they can't act. Think Twins, 2 HK girls with 0 talent. How revolting is that? I prefer Hollywood and European flicks anytime. One has great SFX and the other has great storyline. Well, I like the Takeshi guy. *Swoons* He is JUST so gorgeous... Now I'm publicly displaying my affection for him. Hahaha how embarassing.  Anyway my aunt and uncle are coming to visit me! I'm really looking forward to it. It's better than staring at bare walls in my apartment. I can't wait to see them!   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It seems that I can never ever escape the clutches of China men. Yesterday was&nbsp;the first day of my semester and I went to my first TELE lectures. And the lecturer was a China guy with a serious English problem. His English made Singlish sounds like British English. I couldn't help but laugh when he spoke. I looked around to see if I was&nbsp;the only one laughing but I wasn't. Many were hiding their heads behind papers/school bags/jackets/friends and you could tell they were laughing because their shoulders were shaking.&nbsp;  Let me give a brief guide on his pronunciation:    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Word&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; China guy Pronun.    1. purpose&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;per-puss    2. with&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; wi-sa  3. randomness&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;run-dom-mi-ness    4. analog&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;as-sa-log    5. exemption&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; es-sum-shen    6. radio&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ray-sio    7. analysis&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; e-na-lis     &nbsp;  I can't remember all the words he said but you get the idea I guess. How am I to handle one of the toughest subjects with this kind of teaching!? I am not against China people, in fact I have China friends. Ok maybe just 1 or 2, but I love them all the same. But those who shove their hands down their pants to scratch their itching butts in public, I condemn.   Some China people should be deported back to their motherland and just be farmers or something.   &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Added a little something about me on the sidebar.    What I'd want to be.    Actually I want to be someone who releases cool games or a behind-the-scenes crew on a movie set.  Nothing would make me more happy than to see my name&nbsp;on the&nbsp;credits when the show/game ends . That's the sole reason why I took computer engineering. Some people say I'm nuts&nbsp;after hearing my reason. But  wouldn't you feel so proud  when you see your name on the big screen?&nbsp;   Well, at least I took a step towards my dream.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I have been  in school most of this week  despite it being the holidays, trying to fix my enrolment, thesis topic and of course my result.   I went for the thesis informal interview on Wednesday and the lecturer is such a piece of shit. I came up with this proposal of doing an interactive internet game for my thesis. The game I designed was&nbsp;something like&nbsp;GunBound, with shooting and all. But the stupid lecturer&nbsp;asked me how is this game interactive. Hello? Playing a game with 8 other people is not interactive enough for you to see that point?! If he doesn't know anything about interactive games he shouldn't have been the lecturer in charge for this topic at all. Bastard. Even then I could tell he wasn't interested and yet he told us to wait till Friday before he gave us his&nbsp;decision. Of course he rejected the proposal thing. BASTARD.  One day I will release this damn game&nbsp;and show you that I'm a millionaire&nbsp; because he has no foresight.&nbsp;Anyway I'd like to  thank all of you  who have contacted me via icq/mobile phone to give me your ideas on the game. I will try to make the game when I find the time. Maybe after my graduation and be a millionaire. Hmm.. what an idea.   Sigh I have to schedule another interview with other lecturers in charge to get a thesis topic. The next on my list is doing something  GSM/GPS  nonsense. I don't even know what's going on. Bleah. Has to go see the program director sometime next week&nbsp;for some enrolment crap because I intend to overload this coming semester so that I can graduate in time.  The only thing that&nbsp;I'm looking forward to is my  Cirque   Du   Soleil  show this August. I got seats to go watch it and I can't wait. I just caught a Cirque show,  Alegria ,&nbsp;on tv and I believe it's the one my ENTIRE family watched when I wasn't around.&nbsp;Simply can't wait to watch Quidam. If anyone reading hasn't been to a Cirque show, I suggest you should try it once in your lifetime.  It's one of those things you should do .   It's the 2nd last day of my hols and I feel so crappy. School's starting soon and my workload is going to be overbearing. Not too sure if I can update my blog often. But then again I may have a lot of things to complain about. Haha..   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Alright, I'm currently writing a proposal for my thesis interview tomorrow. I am so keen on writing an interactive internet game. However I am considering what type of game should I base my thesis on, hence the headache.  &nbsp;  Basically there are those that have no storylines and those that have.   Gunbound and CS have no storyline  while  Ragnarok Online and Final Fantasy XI have .&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Therefore I would like to use my blog as a broadcast medium to conduct a short survey.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Would you guys prefer a game like GB and CS, or RO and FFXI? Or better yet, you  can suggest the KIND of games you like , ie. having great graphics with no storyline or  whatever combination you like . If you don't play any games, maybe you can suggest a game you would like to play but it's not on the market. Any input is better than none. =)&nbsp; All suggestions are welcomed.  &nbsp;  I don't think many people actually read my blog. For those that do and  YOU know people who are hardcore gamers, please direct them to this blog or you could ask on my behalf and post your feedback as comments!  Ahh... fantastic. =) Please do help me out on this. Perhaps this game will see the light of day and  YOU will have a chance to play it ! When that time comes, you can  slime me for NOT using your ideas , or you can  bug me to add your name when the credit rolls .  Seize the moment, people.   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I just knew the results of 3 of my subjects. I took 4 subjects this semester fyi. The good news is that I passed all the tough ones. The bad news is that I flopped my most confident one. =( I don't know why but I had sent an email asking for a review of my marks. Why does such shitty things happen to me? I took this subject with 2 other friends, Junyu and Victor. And all 3 of us failed abysmally. And all 3 of us sent strong emails to the lecturer. Hmmp.   I'm keeping my fingers crossed for the 4th subject. It's the one that got screwed by the China guys. I think I pass but then again, I better not be so sure just yet.   I feel quite upset because my efforts have gone down the drain once again. I just don't know how to break it to my parents, and disappointing them is the last thing I want to do. It makes me feel really bad being the bearer of bad news to them.   Called my brother and had a chat with him. Sigh.. It's good to have someone to talk to, since the 2 of us are quite close and we share a lot. At least I share a lot of stuff with him. =) I would have gone mad with sadness if I keep everything to myself, especially on such a sad day.   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The title basically sums up today. It was raining and it was far too cold to go out. Don't really like getting the hem of my jeans wet, quite yucky.  Reading Dan Brown's Digital Fortress now. I'm quite a Dan Brown fan, judging by the fact that I have all 4 of his known printed works in my collection. Hahaha.. Read his "The Da Vinci Code" for starters. It's fascinating, the details of it are so mind blowing. It's conspiracy + history + art + puzzle solving. Totally riveting.   Anyway my bro will be leaving for Melbourne later tonight and I guess the house is getting very quiet without us around. Sigh... he asked me about bringing cds to Australia and restrictions etc. I don't think there is much of a restriction though, just as long as you don't bring suspicious amount of cds like a few hundred. 10-20 is fine, just say you are a student and they are blanks. I guess that works. I don't have trouble bringing cds over. Hmm... 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ahh..the holidays. It has been a week since my last entry and I have been enjoying, or rather, sorting out a few things. Australian Idol is on tv right now. Some of the contestants can be the next William Hung. Try a search on the internet for this guy called Flynn.. forgot the last name though. Not that it's a bad thing to try, but don't people know their own capabilities? Some should keep their singing inside the shower, just like me. Haha.. Anyway here is a rough idea on how things went the last week:   Wednesday - Day 1   Well, I went to buy some furniture and electrical appliances at the furniture mall. I had no idea a simple vacuum cleaner costs $140, or some Ikea stuff are actually quite expensive. One book shelf costs $50+ while a similar one costs $25 at the store opposite Ikea. Thank goodness I went looking around.    Thursday - Day 2   Then I spent another day assembling the furniture by hand with only 1 pathetic little screwdriver. It sounds really tough and actually it is tough. The dining table is so bloody heavy and I have to assemble it (and its 4 matching chairs) from scratch. Although it's not rocket science, I feel damn proud of myself. Hahaha..    Friday - Day 3   Continued assembling furniture. Wiped down the entire place as well. At least I had a clean place now. =) I'm actually quite meticulous about cleanliness and tidiness. Magazines or paper strewn all over my table makes me irksome. So do towels that are not hung up properly, as in corners of towels not matching. You get the idea. I don't think many people know about this, unless they actually have lived with me.    Saturday - Day 4   Went out for some shopping!! But sadly I didn't get anything, not even the book I wanted. Not at the right price though. Bleah.. and why are clothes so expensive? 30% off and it's still above $60. I'm so broke right now and I can't really afford anything fancy now. *sob* Also found out that I can't go whale watching because we don't have enough designated drivers. This entire term break is going all wrong.    Sunday - Day 5   Went to yumcha at 10am with all the grandmas and grandpas. Ate so much that I didn't eat anything after. And I bought my book at $16!! It retails for $20. I know it's not much difference but I'm on a tight budget.    Monday - Day 6   Went to explore Bondi Junction. Wow..the new Westfield complex is massive and well-furnished. Very modern look and feel to it. And they have got so many selections! I'm getting excited even as I type. Haha.. I can feel the inner shopaholic emerging once again.    Tuesday - Day 7   Today. I woke up because some idiots were doing some drilling at my place at 7am. I have no idea what they are doing it for, but they are drilling all over the building. Above my apartment, outside my apartment and I was under house arrest for a couple of hours from the noise and dust. Their equipment were blocking my door and I could not even get out. I complained when I got out and neighbours were out confronting those people as well. And they told us apologetically it's going to take 2-3 weeks doing the stuff they are doing. CRAP. How can I sleep man?   And I have been weird lately. I sleep at around 7-9pm and I wake up at 7.30-9am, early enough to catch the morning news program and cartoons. Hmm... I'm so bored and maybe I will get around to organising something for me to do. Watching the OC now. Why is The Catillion so much like a wedding? Everything is so grand and beautiful looking. But what I wouldn't give to attend one.. *sulk* I didn't even try on my prom. The regret.  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My exams are FINALLY over!!!! So so so happy. No more mugging, no more instant noodles, no more screwed up sleeping hours, no more ink stains on my hands, no more breakouts.. the list can go on and on.   Came back and slept. Missed O.C. =( going to get some furniture tomorrow. I'm so happy now. I still feel tired. Sigh.. will go back to sleep when I really can't find anything to do later. It's only 3am now. Crap.  Trying to organise a short trip to Port Stephens for some whale watching action. Thinking of swimming with dolphins too! So excited.   I am so happy I can almost sing out loud now.  P.S. What's with blogspot these days? Always get popups and Cannot Find Server error. Bleah.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just had a chat with my good buddy, Corn. He just told me he went back to Singapore. Now I don't have anyone to call and disturb. =( And after looking through his photos, I realise that I'm so tired and I haven't really put my camera to good use this semester. The last time I took photos was probably in January. How sad. I so want to go home this winter break. Extremely sick of life here in Sydney since I'm such a no-lifer. =(  But I have this feeling that SIA is already fully booked. Crap. Have to discuss this situation with Mom asap.  On the other hand, if I don't get to go back this winter like I have hoped, I would go on a short trip to Port Stephens for whale watching!! Better not miss this opportunity since there's no freakin' free-willy-jumpin' whales in south east asia. If Victor doesn't want to go with me (his financial reasons.. blah blah) I will go on my own. Can't stand having my plans disrupted by him anymore. Bleah.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I find the song "Honey and the moon" by Joseph Arthur nice. Trying to download some of the OC soundtracks. I can't really concentrate on studying. Sigh.  I hate exams.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Went to catch Spiderman 2 this morning, that is Wednesday morning at 11am. I caught the 2nd screening because I couldn't make it for the 10.30am session. Oh what the hell. At least I beat the crowd at 11am. Spidey 2 is probably the best sequel to anything movies that have sequels/trilogy. You don't even feel that 2.5 hours passed while watching the flick. Very good film, great action sequence and the plot was moving along nicely. Tobey Maguire can act! His inner torment and conflict were so convincing that you actually feel sorry for Peter Parker and wants him to quit being Spidey altogether. The resident critic gives it  4.5 out of 5 popcorns .  I'm not quite excited about Star Wars 3 though, since Episode 2 was such a bore. How the nicest kid turned into the evil Darth Vader wasn't really explored. I'm not really convinced that George Lucas is going to do that in Episode 3, since he's quite focused on being out the CG effects. If he is, he has a lot to do. Why good guy morphs to evil guy, evil guy takes over entire galaxy, evil guy loses family etc. Since Anakin is going thru a rough patch, let's see Hayden Christensen do the Tobey Maguire/Spidey inner torment look. Hmm..  Got a haircut too. Not very happy about it. Not happy about a few things lately, besides my haircut. The exams are a pain and it's so tough. Sigh. And oh, JK Rowling's 6th creation will take the title "Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince". Wow.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My aunt and uncle were to visit me on Monday. Went to pick them up from the airport and spent the next 2 days with them. It's great to see your family when you are stuck in a god-forsaken place and you badly need to see familiar faces. I stayed with them at the hotel and it was alright. They just dropped me back home before heading to the airport. *sigh*  We ate so much these 2 days. I think I gained some weight. I still feel full now. (12.32pm Wednesday) Anyway it was good seeing them again. My aunt kept asking me if I wanted to buy anything, but funnily I said no. I really really couldn't think of anything to buy. Usually I would have jumped at the chance. Great chatting and catching up with them.  I miss them already.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I was in the hospital for the 3rd time in my whole life. This doesn't include the times I went to visit, only the times I'm there for medical help. =( First being the day I was born, and second being the time I had my back problems checked out.  I was crippled by severe stomach pains this afternoon. I couldn't walk a few steps without feeling the life sucked out of me. I wanted to throw up but I couldn't. This went on from 2pm to 5pm, when I finally decided to go to the GP on campus. The stupid nurse then told me the clinic was closed and I had to go to the hospital. I could hardly walk man... Called up a few friends to come drive me to the hospital. A few students who saw I was in pain stopped to help me too. Thank god for them.  Anyway I waited for my turn for 2 hours at the emergency room. And some trainee doctor jabbed me 5 times just because she couldn't draw blood. Later when a senior doctor came to see me, he told me the blood test wasn't needed since it couldn't be appendicitis or anything. =(  Told me it's just muscle pain. How could it be!?!? Anyway the jabs were painful... Was put on a drip and now I'm home. Was told to go back tmr if pain persists or worsens. And it's 12am now.  Going to sleep. I feel so terrible at the moment. Sigh.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just feel like adding one more entry.  I've got people on my icq, msn and truth be told, I don't usually talk to most of them. I'm always on invisible and it's not that I avoid them, it's just that I have either too much work or I don't know what to say to them. =/ Some of them have abandoned icq altogether and haven't been online for the past couple of years. Some, well, think that if you message them out of the blue, you are a   stalker/psycho  . People read too much into things. It doesn't pay to be friendly I tell you. Sigh... I think they have forgotten how we have got onto one another's icq/msn list at all. We used to be friends and we wanted to keep in contact. Now look at the situation. Message me, tell me about the weather or what you ate for lunch.  Aren't we all friends?   I miss my friends, even if we don't talk at all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, just got back from the school. Met with 3 lecturers to dicuss my thesis topic and enrolment issues. FINALLY things are starting to look up, well, a bit.  I got a pretty interesting thesis topic. It is no longer the game as mentioned earlier, but I'll be doing something on GPS/GSM  and server stuff on fleet management. In simpler terms, it will be like monitoring where delivery trucks are using the satellite. Sounds pretty good actually. At least I'm doing something interesting.  Next off I went to see 2 stupid CSE lecturers who finally allowed me to overload this semester. Usually people take 24 units of credits, but this semester I'm taking 30 units so that I can graduate in time. The school director (1 of the lecturers)  was actually advising me against it because the chances of failing is higher when you overload because you cannot cope. But if I don't I will stay another semester, which will make quite a scene at home. =/ What choices do I have anyway? Anyhow he said I could overload and it's my choice, so if anything crops up ie. fail, it's my own damn problem. Bleah. When is it HIS problem anyway?  Anyway I'm doing 30 credits, and that's 7 subjects. I feel the noose around my neck tightening.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am really quite bored today. Too poor to go out so I spent the entire day at home, tidying up stuff and stoning. Waited till it's 6pm to catch something funny on tv. Simpsons was funny as usual, so was Newlyweds. 7.30 to 8.30 was Australian Idol and frankly, I don't like that program.  I was pinning my hopes on 8.30pm movies when I found out that out of the 4 watchable channels, 2 were horror flicks (The Others and Ring 2), 1 was some footie crap and the other was fuzzy. Sigh... nothing to watch on tv. I don't have the guts to watch either of the 2 horror flicks on tv. Facing Sadako or that ghostly trio in the others simply makes me wanna crawl under my blanket and hide.  I shall hide now, for Ring 2 is quietly playing on my tv screen.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>