<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lately.. I've been thinking about happiness and what it really means. Whether it's something attainable or simply just a state of being. But then the more I think about it, I look back at my life and ask myself whether I really am happy. For a few days, I had been confused. I just wasn't sure whether I really was happy, trying to be or plain unhappy.   Luckily, I was able to overcome this big fuss over my own happiness. I thought to myself that I shouldn't be thinking of myself all the time. I mean, I need to be at least a little selfless at times and quit thinking of my personal pleasures by trying to look around my environment and see if they're also happy. When I said my environment, I didn't mean just anyone. I had to start with the people I knew. Is my family happy? They seem okay but you'll never know. So I thought about doing something to cheer them up a little. I sent my mom a little sweet quote just to tell her that even though I'm quite far away, I still do remember her and appreciate everything she's done for me. Then I thought about my friends, I had a lot of acquaintances being disguised as friends but to those people whom I can really call "friends"... well I can name a few. How are they? Are they alright?! Well, good thing I went bonding with this friend of mine last week. We went to the gym, then we ate at her place. Anyway, I haven't seen her in quite a while and it's nice to catch up on things. It's ironic how opposite the two of us were during the first semester, we sort of had a little indifference because we didn't have much in common, but now, we even go to the gym together.   Anyway, I've learned that when we talk about happiness, it doesn't have to be you alone. I mean, a bunch of cash and a new cellphone would make me happy.. but I've realized that a day with my "G" in Greenhills just browsing around the tiangges is even better.   You see, money or material things could never ever replace happy times with your family, loved one and friends. And now that I've checked on everyone I care about especially my "G", I know there may be problems once in a while, but the fact that I've showed them that I'm just here no matter what and that I will try to make them happy, that also makes me really happy.  I don't have much money right now, actually, I'm more than running out.. but the smile on my face couldn't be much bigger because "G" is making me so happy these days.   So I would rather cry a thousand times and be happy afterwards with the one I love. Rather than to smile when I want to and cry in the end. I know it's not only me who wishes that.   Happiness starts from you, but it doesn't have to end there.. it goes around and is being shared by more people.  I hope I made sense. If not, let me make it short.. I really am happy now, and I hope you will be to. Take care.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trust had been such a big issue with the relationship I'm having right now. You see, when we were just starting, I had already gave my trust to him. Sadly, he had broken my trust. What's more sad is, it had happened too many times. It's partly my fault because I allowed him to toy with my emotions, and I didn't punish him for breaking my trust. But you see, it's not that I'm being such a martyr but a matter of not giving up. I never gave up on him and our relationship no matter how many times he had hurt me. I still tried to look on the bright side and I didn't lose my faith in him to change.  Fortunately, I see a big change in him right now. I know it has to be a two-way thing. Actually, I hope he really does trust me as much as I trust him because that's going to help a lot. Lately, he had proved to me that he's trying everything he can not to hurt me anymore. And I'm so happy for that. It is indeed a wonderful feeling that I simply could not trade with anything else.  So I keep on praying and hoping that my trust in him will not be put to waste. I see his efforts so I really wish he would keep it up. Because if we only try everything we can not to break each other's trust, there wouldn't be a problem.  It's just so nice to have someone to love, someone to trust. :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, I had been robbed while I was doing a little shopping at the "tiangges". Its was partly my fault, I have to admit. Because I already knew that the place was dangerous for a girl like me to be roaming around alone. And yet I still went there, alone. So, I had to learn my lesson the hard way.  Though I lost my money, like what my loved one told, it was only "money" and not my life. So I had to be thankful that nothing more dangerous had happened to me. As for the love of my life, well he scolded me for being stupid. But I know he means well, I deserve to be scolded. It also means that he really does care for me. I felt so bad that I had lost my money because I also felt so stupid. So I asked him to fetch me, and he came. My savior! Hehe. I felt like a damsel in distress waiting for my knight in shinning armour.  Anyway, I must be really lucky that day because nothing more dreadful happened to me. It was a lesson learned.. I had to pay the price, but as they say, no price is expensive enough because at least I was safe. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Something keeps me smiling all day long.. I don't know why, maybe I do It doesn't matter as long as I'm smiling... oh baby, I love you It's really not a matter of what makes me smile... but who makes me smile It's my baby, he makes me so happy.. that I can't help but smile  Sure sometimes, he makes me frown a little.. but nevermind He makes me feel a lot of thing.. it's coz he's always on my mind I know we're going to last forever and that really makes me smile We're not one of those couples who would only last a while  Baby I'm so thankful for the smiles you give to me Even though you're not around now, I wish you could see That this smile is because of you, you make me smile all day I simply am thankful that you're here with me everyday! :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Today, my pride within me was tested with my loved one. I need not relay the whole story, but the incident that happened to us today had proved a lot to us. Not only to our relationship, but also to how much pride I am willing to swallow for my loved one. I'm not saying that someone was right with what had happened, no one has to win the argument. So I just tried my best to fix things as soon as possible so that it wouldn't grow into a bigger argument. I wasn't trying to escape the long dreadful argument that was yet to happen, but I was trying to look at things on the brighter side by swallowing my pride and see where the argument might lead. And just like that, things got better. If I had not thought of a more peaceful way of solving things, it really would have gone worse. But that would only be useless if there really was a better way. So as I've said, today my patience and my pride was tested, and I think I aced the test. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Relationships need to be conventional. True, everyone might be vying for that stage where in everything seems to be at the right place and time. Yet, wouldn't you think it'd be boring that way? Believe me, if keeping a relationship with someone or being a good partner was so easy, love wouldn't be that special. It'd just be like, mineral water or jello.. no offense to jello lovers.   My point is, when you and your loved one has been given this title of being unconventional, as long as you two still love each other, there is nothing wrong with that. Because it may only mean that you're keeping pace with each other in this fast-paced world that we're living in.   * I have no idea why I had felt the sudden urge to write about unconventional lovers tonight. Though I'm still proud to be writing about love. As for my personal relationship with my one and only "G", I think our relationship may be a little bit unconventional. But that's what makes it more exciting and that's what will test us to be stronger each day. *
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If he wasn't here with me right now, I'd probably be dead. No kidding. Before I met him, my life had been filled with false pretentious and superficial happiness. It was like I was stuck into the hellhole and there was no way out. Yes, my life was sad. Meaningless. It looked fine from the outside, but from the inside, it just wasn't good.   Before, love wasn't much of an issue. I mean, I have loved before but at such a young age, I had been fooled and hurt too many times that I thought "true love" really didn't exist anymore. Pretty mushy huh? But when it comes to me being in love, there is no limit to how mushy, dramatic or sensitive I may become.   You see, there are a lot of things I can say about the love that I have right now. One of them is when I consider love as an art. Like a sculpture being made just for me. My love for "G" is truly an art. He is my masterpiece. And he saved my life!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>