<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I must show my respect to two fellow fellows whom have taught me much with their websites. I have already recruited them and have showed them some of my more in depth plans which i may someday post. Visit my fellow Llama friend at http://www.llama7.blogspot.com/ and my fellow snoof friend at http://www.hamsters4me.blogspot.com/
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well in my various adventures today, i fell inlove with a great gal. I plan on "going steady" as the hip young term is used and perhaps someday even having a cohort in my nefarious plans for the domination of France! You people out there probably think it rediculous that the great genius that i am even has emotions, especially since i am part llama, but in-fact snoofs are quite intelligent and very developed mentally. So, if you are reading this, know my love is for 783742643, written in phone dialect, so if you waste your time figuring it out, good for you. Anyway......... I will continue with my usuall banter tomorrow, though at the moment i must act smitten.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I made an interesting revelation today about the wonderful internet system called "eBay". I have heard many stories of its great amount of ludicrus items, scuch as selling a town, though i had not really belived them until today. I saw for sale a BROKEN camera priced at $26.50. Now, i know you may by stuff on eBay like a used wedding gown but a BROKEN camera? Maybe i am overreacting, but i would like if all you people could write in with your weird eBay stories.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Another idea given to me by my "friend" "Wayne" is a new WEAPON OF MASS DESTRUCTION. It is kind of primative yet seemingly would be very effective. He thought of it when we where discussing the war in Iraq and there WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION. He felt all the hubub over Nuclear weapons was irrational along with genetic weapons. He posed the question you all have thought yet simply not expanded on; Why not just use a giant mustard gass filled log? You would simply fly it in and drop it on a hill above what you want to destroy. If anything cuts it in half, you have two slightly less giant logs to deal with AND a field of mustard gas. i am open for suggestions as to how you can make this great destructive item even MORE powerful. Please post comments with your ideas.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, i was watching Lord of the Rings: Return of the King woth my "friend" at http://www.llama7.blogspot.com/ when he brought up an interesting idea; what if the nazis joined up with the nazgul? Well, upon thinking about this i realized, they would form the ultimate war machine; both are completly souless and evil. I have decided that i shall start to biogentically culture a DNA strand of a nazgul using the vast amounts of information the LOTR club has about them, along with finding the remains of Adolf Hitler and his nazi hordes. I shall create this freaks of nature over the next 10 years and by the time they are created, humans will have decayed so much physically due to a lack of movement in general, created by the vast use of machines, and i will finally be able to take over France.  SO if you know any LOTR geeks, please contact me for their information, also if you are or know any nazis, please tell me where you live and any information you may have on the location of Hitler's corpse.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, it is late at night but i am dedicated to you readers. At my physical training class (also known as Tae Kwon Do) i was beating up on one of my foolish enimies when all of a sudden my robot body froze up and randomly started shooting lasers. I compleatly eraticated everything around me and then shut down. I had to pry myself out of it and manually repair it. i then proceeded to come up with a reason as to why the school suddenly dissapeared. I came up with this "..." nothing, thats right. i finally decided what i would do, I blamed it all on my FRENCH neighbor The Count DeMourdry. So, that news story that everone is hearing about will do something good for me, and that is bring us ever closer to war with the Frenchies.   As i note i don't really hate the french so no offense..... unless i say i mean it! 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was born in the suburbs of a small country called Turkey, which is itself a truly horrid name for a country, and was the son of two most bizzare animals.... A snoof and a llama. I am the first of a great race which i shall build and dominate called the Slamof. I was born in a cabin made entirely from turkey feathers, which is the tradition in Turkey, you can see the coorilation, and was raised by the various woodland animals attracted by my shelter. I suppose i should hate them, for they killed and devoured my parents........squirrels dining on the flesh of humans, a sight i shall never see again........... yet they raised me as there own and for that i love them. When i reached the age of 10 though, they realised me for the freak i am and cast me out of there society. I was found by a dull minded native and thought to be some sort of exquisite new breed of poodle. I was captured and forced into numerous dog shows which i won, not out of honor, but shame. At the age of 12 i broke away from him and travelled to the Americas, for i heard there they hated the french, the people whom sponsered many of those dog shows i was put through. When i reached there i quickly obtained various metal scraps from a junk yard and built myself a robot body in the shape of an average human. Since then i have been living an inconspicuous life under the name Nick and have gathered much information about the human race by going to school. I have made "friends" and many other various alliances through kindness, bribery and blackmail 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have started to gather my army, and none shall opose me! I now have not only a legion of rabid hamsters with laser beams, i also have many varieties of leprechauns who have risen againt there oppresive lord who have taken an aliance with my new enimies, Snoof and Llama. Not even there mighty legions and hordes can defend against my power. I shall sweep over them and France like a horde of locust, devestating all in my path! My genome warriors are complete and i have been gradually converting all forms of animals into my minions. The sad stroy of the octpus which i told inspired me because it showed that even the stupidest of animals can help. I have made all the waters around the coast of France impassable with my "suicide" whales who will destryo any boat on command, along with other annoying sea creatures who can be equally devestating. Also, i have blocked of much of air transport by convincing birds of all sizes and shapes to join my battle. You may all be sceptic as to how i can do this, but i respond with a name: Doctor Dolittle. I have harvested his brain and vocal cords and have amplified them into a radio transmission device. Now the wildlife itself shall rebel against armies opposing me! Along with my animal advances, i have built and launched 24 more sattellites into orbit, and the newer versions not only have lasers nukes and free cell phone service, they also have missiles, giant blocks of lauchable cheese (as a destraction to my cheese loving enimies), and really big anvils, like in the cartoons!  As a final note, i welcome your opposition Llama and Snoof, it will make my plans of conquer much more interesting. To provoke you further, i must tell you something, I DO NOT LIKE CHEESE! IF you dare to continue to make futile attempts to stop me, i shall not only use what i have revealed thus far, i shall also use my hidden weapons and arsenals, and i don't mean average things like Stealth Blackbirds and F1 Abrums, but the nastier stuff like EMPs (Electro Magnetic Pulse) and pulsating earthquake generators or PEGs.   RESTST ME IF YOU DARE FOOLS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I must appologize for my last few posts, i have had a multiplicity of stupid things braking out of my brain. i have secessfully beaten them all with a very large stick and they are temporarialy sedated. Well, on to more domination plans. For those of you who don't know, go to http://hamsters4me.blogspot.com/ and read of leprechauns powers. I have already captured an intire clan and have midget informants living with them. Though they do make excellent decorations, they have othere uses also. I have found that i am able to imbue there magical powers upon peolpe by sucking the leprechauns soul out and transferring it to the person. Along with superpowerful magic though, they gain an irrational addiction to either opium or wax of any kind. And if they are unable to continue to consume at least 5 kg daily, they go into a berserker rage and turn everything around them into the desired substance. i have a problem about building fleets of them because i am often unable to supply such vast amounts of opium or wax, and thus they are constantly turning eachother into the afore mentioned substances. Along with this plan, i have aquired the giant magnet i needed, success being brought to me by an anonymous sender who i thank, whoever you may be. It has allowed me to get the space shuttle i needed and have sent my satellite into space, so know, not only do i have a very precise laser defense sateliite, i have a nuke and free cellphone service.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday i was out terrorizing the nursery down the street as the bogeyman when this strange creature resembling a giant muffin loomed in the shadows. It started talking a deep and melodeous voice, telling me to leave this nursery which he was gaurding or he would be forced to inflict forbidden ninja arts upon me. I of scourse was having fun wreaking havoc to the FRENCH children's nursery and thus told him to bug off. I should have considered the fact that my robot body was at the cleaners being refurbished and that my poodle like true form is actually quite weak. I was of course, forgetting temporarialy that i was a master of the Voodoo arts. As he attaked, I barely got to the side in time and plucked a piece of his deliciously moist exterior. I then created it to a likeness of him and ate it, thus eating all of him at once. I should of considered his size before doing this, but i was savoring the wonderful flavor, blueberry! Well, anyway, since i had just swallowed a muffin the size of a few 6 foot tall men, i became very fat, and thus tayed in the bushes hidding nearby for a few hours until it got out and then rolled home to my liposuction. I had decided to purchase it after this had happened the fifth time, and i had gotten tired of getting rid of my fat by removing it with a laser.  Well, i am hopeful that none of you think of me a monstetr for eating the poor muffin, but we all make mistakes, i just make the same ones frequently, because our world is filled with these large muffins. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I heard a story recently that warmed the very soul of my souless robotic body. It was a tale of great sadness and loss. The protagonist of this paticular story was a very disoriented octopus that was picked upon mercilessly by all of the other sea creatures, especially the clown fish, for though there name suggests a kind hearted and funny creature, they are actually supercondensed wads of pure evil, bent on causing utter havoc and displeasure. Anyway, the octopus, henceforth to be called "Larry" as to not divulge any personal information, was a lonesome nerd whom nobody liked at all. His parents had both left him shortly after his birth, unlike those whale children whom he loathed, and for some odd reason, he had been born with a deformity, this deformity being that he sent out pulses every few seconds which made this whole story possible because it caused fish to think in the exact same manner as him, what a coincidence! Well, to start the story, Larry was going to visit his "aunt" the senile starfish "Selma" when he was confronted by numerous Jellyfish, who not only constantly insulted him, they used wonderful insults such as calling him the "spineless blob". They started to say such things to him and zap him, so he of course had to spray ink into all of there faces and run away. Now this may not seem strange to you, but it created an interesting problem for Larry. This problem was of course that he was charged with littering by the mentally altered swordfish police and fined 100 pieces coral. Now, of course he did not have anyware near this much currency because he was constantly paying his neighbors for ink stain damage. So he was of course detained and taken down to the nearest sea anemone jail and put there over night. It actually was many weeks before he got out of there though, because the local shark suffians had decided to eat the police officers. During this time Larry fell in with some of the local criminal Clown Fish, whom were mentioned earlier, They accepted him because they thought that he had done something totally wicked like those totally radical whale punks who had gone and punctured the Exxon Valdez a couple of months ago. Well, to get back to Larry, he learned a few tricks with the Clown Fish, like how to harvest a swordfish's sharp blade and create a very deadlty impliment, along with how ot use his tentacles to pick a lock. After using his lock pick skills, Larry proceeded to the swordfish's remains left by the sharks and harvested there blades. He then paid some various ocean life and thereatened some others into diving down and harvesting some various explosive gases at the bottom of the bottom of one of the gorges, such as methane. After collecting this, he hired a walrus by giving him the souls of the clown fish who had been in jail with, if they even had any, and had the walrus go on land and kill a nearby stone age fanatic who was carrying some iron pyrite and flint. After collecting all of these items, he went into an underwater cave nearby and killed all of the whales nearby by shooting the swordfish blades into there hearts, that and shoving large amounts of stolen corral into there blowholes and harvested their blubber. He took the flammable gases, the bluibber, the iron prrite and the flint to the afore mentioned cave and commited a suicide bombing by lighting the blubber on fire by striking the iron pyrite and the flint together and then put the large amounts of methane gas he had earlier decided to store in the air bladder of a fish into the flame. This chemical reaction caused a catistrofic explosion which caused 15 vlocanoes to simotaneously errupt, three of which where super volcanoes, and not only did this cause the sun to be completly blocked out, it also caused the poles to melt and covered the whole planet in water. Larry died a happy fish whom had gotten his vengance on the world and all those who had teased him.  This was sort of long and very wierd, but the one who told me it said it has a very good morale to it, good writers all have stupid ideas, it's just the ones who have enough free time to look over there work and change it to make it better who do well.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I write to them with my grivances, for they are my heroes who weild lances. They are the knights of the past, with honor and a code held to the last. I admire them for their resolve, and the problems for which they doth solve. I also glow with pride, at their help all other through scout and ride. But most of all i like them not for there great deeds, but for the money i inherited from their will and other type of deeds.   I know it is stupid, but i don't care. If you want real poetry write your own in the comments section 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sorry it has been a couple of days, i was in white sands for a while inspecting there military base (New Mexico). Well, anyway, i found out it would be an excellent site for my first military instilation in the US. I have already hired 50 highly radioactive, rabids gerbils with plasma cannons to take out their defenses. The problem with my deal with the gerbils is i told them they could rule there for me until i raised enough money for there 1 million dollar fee. So, i am asking you all to donate money to help with my conquest of France. Don't worry though, when i have finally obtained France, you will recive a pencil for every dollar, a rubber parrot for eery 10 dollars and 1 acre of land for every 100 dollars. Finally, then person who donates the most money will recive the remains of the Eiffel Tower (meaning what isn't destroyed in the attack). The sooner the donations come in, the faster my plans will come into effect. Also, if you have any profoundly large magnets lying around (10 tons or more) i would be glad to pay you for them, i plan on taking over one of the space shuttles that NASA sends into space for some of my later plans needing it to transport my laser sattelite into space. Next order of buisness, my human genome project is getting underway and i need all the volunteers for testing that i can get. It pays great dental, $6 an hour, and you get to keep all the mutations that may occer (you lucky dog you, i have always wanted tentacles). My condolences to those who lose there mouths, but don't worry, only 8 out 0f 10 have had this happen
     
    
</post>


</Blog>