<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What is LOVE exactly to you? Many people would usually say LoVe equals to RomAncE... Well, in certain angle is rather true but then who on earth has tasted FOREVER tasty and everlasting Loveship? LoVe has on its own its bright and dark side. Couples are seen quarelling over the most senseless thing on earth and also splitting up for the "stupidiest" thing.  People may be together as a couple or husband and wife for years...but have they really ponder on this question: DO I REALLY LOVE HIM/HER? That is the question to asked yourself when you decide to get married with your so-called LOVED ones. Query yourself and think over it seriously as whether you and your partner can walk the rest of your life together. A couple has got to give in and take. There is seriously no such thing as one partner does it ALL and the other party just sit down and relax.   Well, I do have friends who are facing with these problems and empathize with them. They are pathetic and trapped in this web called LoVe which can literally torture them. The other party are not realizing the problem but needs to reinforce those ideas to them to let them know what is the issue here.   As mentioned in the first edition, LoVe is like a jigsaw puzzle and it is scattered all over before we enter into a relationship. When we begin that love life of ours, that is when we start to pick all those little puzzle to pin them together in hope to complete the whole entire thing. To me, LoVe consists of these factors: Trust, Tolerance, Forgiveness, Love, Care and Concern, Open-Mind...which can be more but these are the main factors that are the ones to hold the relationship together.   That is all my oneself's perception, hope I did not offend anyone and everyone of you who has read it. Thank you and see you next time in my next edition...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Have you ever thought what kind of life you are having? Be it Good or Bad? Well, realize that our life can be either so simple or complicated which can be of two extremes. Personally hate to see people whom I know departing from this world and friends betraying me etc...It is quite contradicting though but that is life, full of UPs and DOWNs. Can we control it? In a way I guess but it is all fated and destined. 2 people from different location can just meet and fall in LOVE, just like a jigsaw puzzle. Until you get married and die, you will know that the partner you have is the last MISSING piece to that unfinished puzzle that you have been desperately searching for.   Humans take LIFE for granted...How many times do we take notice that our two feets are on the ground and transporting us from place to place. Do we ever appreciate them? OR the little flowers on the roadside or parks that we zoom pass so fast that we miszed the beauty that they possess. We often take our parents for granted and thinking that they can be there each and everyday to guide us...  Well...this are all based on my own perception to LIFE...What about yours? Post in your views and we can share your side of stories too...Till then, we will meet!
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>