<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey 'sup people, it's me again. Who else would it be? just to let you know something else about me, i can be very random. so if i skip from one subject to another, don't be surprised. I think in a very weird way. I don't think anyone else sees things the way i do. I try to be a very positive person. I've never been that popular, but i have a group of friends and they rock! Got to go, catcha later!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi everyone out there. whats up? i can't wait for summer vacation, it starts in 1 week and 1 day! I can't wait to get out of here! i'll be free, like the wind! ok, i am a little weird, sorry. well anyway, i am 14 and i like the bands Evanescence, Blink 182, and Simple plan. There are many others, but if i wrote them all down it would take the whole page. i love to sing, and want to be a singer except i don't know if i'm good enough. my friends think i'm good. i also write a lot of poetry and some short stories, and i write my own songs. I like to express myself as an individual, and if someone  tells me i'm weird i take it as a compliment. The worst thing for me would be being normal. Why be normal? it's no fun.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi, one of my favorite songs is "If I Ain't Got You" by Alicia Keys. What songs do you all like? Music is pretty much my life right now. My hobby is listening to music, and when no one's home, i sing along. one time, my mom walked in and is like, "Thank you for the amazing performance, Kate." i waz like "oh my god, how did you get here?" she thinks i need voice lessons, but she listens to classical music, so what would she know? well, i shouldn't say that about my mom. besides, she likes Suzanne Vega, Tracy Chapman, and the Dixie chicks. and they aren't that bad. but she still thinks I can't sing. it's weird, my friends are like, "oh my god, you have the best voice, you should be a singer." and that's my dream, to be a singer. but then my mom says "You have a pretty voice, but you could use some voice lessons." sometimes I want to kill my mom, (especially since she's so overprotective) but i don't know what i'd do without her. I make her sound really mean, i know, but she's actually one of the smartest, nicest people i know. and being overprotective? it's probably for my own good. But i still wish she would let me get a second hole pierced in my ear. Oh, speaking of earrings, they are my favorite fashion accessory. I wear the biggest earrings in my class.I have one pair of hoops i can stick my hand through. people say they make me look slutty, but if they think that, it's their problem. well, i'm out, time for gym class (yay! not.) 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is the last full day of school!!! i am so excited. we have school tomorrow too, but that doesn't really count, as it is a half day, and we have graduation rehersal. it's weird, but it doesn't feel like the end of the year. probably cause it is so cold! (this is vermont). well, i'll write some more later, gotta go!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me AGAIN!!!!! 3 more dayz of school left!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi, haven't written in a few months.&nbsp; it is so hot, probably 85! (i live in VT, so it seems hot). So bored. My 2 best friends, one is @ camp, the other is in Washington. I'm dying from not talking on the phone. None of my friends are home. Ok, sorry I keep complaining, probably PMS. So anyway, I've gotta go see my grandparents next week, and get the whole "Look how you've grown" ordeal. Oops, waz that a complaint? Sorry. I'll try to say something positive. Just a fact about me: i've seen Titanic 6 times. Another fact: I can be very random. wazn't that random? I'm not making much sense, but it's summer and my brain kinda isn't functioning right now, so I hope you will forgive me. I have Avril Lavigne stuck in my head and it's getting on my nerves. I like listening to Avril, but they keep playing this one song over and over and over. SORRY about all the complaints! here's something positive. I'm going to high school in the fall. I'm psyched! Does anyone have any advice about high school? I mean, social life and so on? please, i need some advice, i have no idea what it's like! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>