<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, as you may can tell... im back from the beach, and toasted like a burnt peice of toast... heres how my weekend went...  friday - went shopping with my mom to get a swimsuit and all that other yummy stuff... then on the way home, kaycee called and told me to be at her house earlyer than we had planned, and i still wasnt packed all the way... so me and my mom are running around the house like crazy ppl to get ready... then later, i got to her house and we had to wait for donna to get home from work and kevin to get there... an hour later, heres donna and me, kaycee and kellye went looking for kevin all thru liberty hill... we finally gave up and were pulling into the drive way when here comes kevin, pulling out... so we talked to him, and he had let someone borrow his car and they had wrecked it, so he couldnt go. then, we're off to the beach! few stops here and there......... gerald had alot to drink so he kept having to pee... so we finally get to galveston and we get all situated at john's house... we met john's wife's daughter named stephanie... shes the most annoyest person i have ever met in my entire life.... i wont even get into that... later that night we just chilled on the dock by the canal in john's back yard.... sleep....  saturday - we all were in the living room sleeping and someone called kellye back at 5 in the morning... woke us all up... then later at 6.30 gerald couldnt sleep so he decided to be so loud that no one could sleep.... so everyones up by 7, besides stephanie of course cuz she stayed out til 3.30 and was whining... me, kaycee, and kellye are all ready to go to the beach by 7.30 and we have to wait for beth and john to get back and then we had to unload all the fishing crap for gerald... then we all set off for the beach about 9... we stopped at a corner store and i got a camera and a mag. w/ avril lavigne on the cover cuz shes pretty sexy ;) hehe.... we all went a beach shop so donna could get a swimsuit and everyone else just got shirts for friends and all that juicy stuff.... alright, so we're at the beach finally... and stephanie is already complaining about how she wants to go home... we played in the water for a while then i wanted to get buried in sand, so they covered me from my neck down all in sand.... we took pictures :) if their cute, i'll show yall... but anyways... we played some more, ate sandwhitches, and got some boogie boards to play on.... then a few hours later, me and kaycee were feelin all sticky and salty from the water so we went to the showers with stephanie and cleaned off.... that was soooo nice, it felt so good... then we walked back over to where all our ppl were.... and they had already packed up all our towels, shoes, clothes, EVERYTHING... and we were leaving... i was kinda sad, but i knew i was already getting burnt... so we went to the store and kaycee and i went in and got a bunch of junk food... goooooD stuff... went home and chilled by the dock, played in the canal, took pictures... then we all took showers and realized how burnt we realy were so we all layed in the living room and watched Blue Crush... donna put aloe on my back and little gerald tripped over kaycee and landed on top of me... it hurt so bad i cried... then we layed...after a while we went to sleep.  sunday - woke up to gerald having a hissy fit... turns out little gerald slept in the chair and peed in his sleep... hehe.... i had to pee so bad, and gerald was in the bathroom taking a shower so i had to go downstairs and that was locked so i went back up to kaycee coming out, going over to the neighbors house... i was so dizzy i thought i was gonna barf, i guess it was from being under the covers and my body temp is way hot or something... i was good after i got something to drink... then we ate some sugar doughnuts... drank some more water... got packed up and left...  well hope i havnt boreded you too much lol, if u wanna see the pictures tell me and i'll show you when i get them scanned :) later days  i miss brent... :(
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys, this is my new blog... and im happy hehe :) ... i always hate starting new ones bc i dont know what to say first... but i just got out of school today, so thats exciting hehe im a smore! yay! and im going to the beach this weekend so i'll update when i get back on monday and tell yall about it!   later days
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this songs called "holdin' you" by gretchen wilson.. heh i just like it, it sounds super too...   I dont need whiskey to drown out the pain Or some old umbrella to hold off the rain Dont have to cross over a river of tears All that i need is right here  Holding you holds me together When holding on gets just a little to hard When this tight rope i travel Begins to unravel and i feel like Im falling apart Holding you holds me together  You know lifes a freight liner on A runaway track But ill take the ride knowing That youll bring me back No fates too uncertain no distance to far As long as your here in my arms  Holding you holds me together When holding on gets just a little to hard When this tight rope i travel Begins to unravel and i feel like Im falling apart Holding you holds me together  Whener i hold you tight This crazy world of mine falls right in place Whatever the trouble is You find a way to give back what it takes  Holding you holds me together When holding on gets just a little to hard When this tight rope i travel Begins to unravel and i feel like Im falling apart Holding you holds me together  ..i love you brent..
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was interesting...  i woke up at 7 am this morning like my dad told me to, and he wasnt done w/ his shower yet so i couldnt start getting ready, therefore i went back to sleep for about 15 minutes... then i got ready, we went to Hobo Depot for breakfast... i had a biscuit... then we went to acadamy or w/e... and looked at guns, left there... went to downtown austin for my dads hearing test and i read a few magazines... blah... left there and went to find Austin Plumbing down on Burnet Road just so they could tell us "you cant return parts after 48 hours".. so im like blahhh... we left there and met some of my dads ex co-workers at Lubys and i had some good green beans... so about an hour later we left and went to walmart by Lakeline and took freaking forever to find some place to park w/ a tralior...they didnt have what my dad wanted so we went to Lowes and got some pipe and something else and then went to H-E-B for beer heh, and then the other walmart by H-E-B... they didnt have what dad wanted either, but we looked at guns... i saw Jerry and hes like "hey grandma!" lol... so we left and came home :) mom called right after i walked in and said that we have to go to the school tomorrow to get a form so i can get my permit... then dad left to go drop off the tractor at horseshoe village... so i cleaned my room, its all purdy now.. so yah hehehe....  i tryed the new Coca-Cola C2... pretty tasty...  bye for now!  ps... hope yall like my new skin :-p its kinda cute
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yah yah, i know... i havnt updated in a while, heh! well it turns out i havnt gone to get my permit yet, but im supposed this friday, along w/ getting my hair cut, yay! finally! heh... well, im trying to find a cute skin for my blog, i'v only found one site, tell me if ya know of a one with some good skins... well im out for now... later
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hummmmmm  today was pretty fun... me, sara and tarna went to gtown and then to cedar park/leander and idk about them but i had a blast hehe...  nothing much really to say... just talking on the phone with brent :D  BYE!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      guess what guys!!!! TODAYS BEEN GREAT!!!!!!!!!!!!  brents back, and dad let me drive to his friends house and i did PERFECT! oh it was sooo great, all my stops and starts were exactly how they should be and i did grreat in reverse and all that juciy stuff! hehe i like this truck alot better now that i can drive it good! :D  I LOVE YOU BRENT!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      brents back!!!! :D :D :D :D oh wow, im so happy... a week and two days it just too much lol...  well yesterday, me and my mama we're bored so we went to gtown early and just went everywhere possible for 2 and a half hours, then we went to gtown hs for my cousins ged graduation, lol my cousin was crying the WHOLE time and she went across the stadge and she said something in the mic but who knows what she said, she was crying to bad.. haha goofy kid... but i got in charge of taking some pictures, so if u wanna see my beloved cousin, ask hehe :) .. after that me and my mom went to heb and while she went to look at something i went to the photo center and was looking at the one hour stuff... and the guy told me to write my name on the envolpe and i TRYED to tell him i was waiting on my mom but he took it from me and my camera and filled in everything for me lol... i was like "uhhhh... :/ hum..." then we wandered around for an hour, saw another cousin... they talked about her daughter that got into the alcohol stash at a friends house hehe she got sick :-p .... we finally left and went to kaycee's house.. i was SOO bored, kaycee wasnt there bc she had to work and everyone else was old or a baby.. josh finally showed up with his gf but he only talked to me for like 10 minutes... he looks really happy with her, :D ... but yah, everyone was teasing me and wouldnt leave me alone, so i was kind of mad at me dad, since he made me go..... went home and i talked online for a lil while and then went into my room and painted my toe nails lol and went to sleep...  todays gonna be boring... lates  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry i didnt get to update yesterday... i was gonna do it after i watched blue crush but i fell asleep and the storm kicked me offline... but i'll tell you about yesterday hehe...  my mom woke up at 6.40 and told me i had to be ready by 7, so i was running around and u know... we went to her doctors appointment and i got to read an old issue of Elle Girl lol... then we headed into Round Rock bc we were gonna help my gma set up for this thing at the senior center, but she wasnt there so i had to CALL her and figure out where she was, she was still at home haha, so we went to her house and i played yahtzee on one of those lil hand-held games that my aunt has... hehe i got 370 :) ::cough:: anyways... so, i got a sprite out of my gmas fridge and we left to go to the senior center about 9 and we got there i had to help move a bunch of crap and then finally i just stuck to the clothes... there was TONS of them, i got bored after a while so i made my mom help me and then this old lady came to help us, hehe she was cute... then we got hungry so we set off to Sonic for food, came back and ate and then my mom said we were going to leave at 2... an hour later i was playing games with this cutie, hehe... he taught me how to play poker and 21... and then we played tetrus on my phone 'n just chilled on the couches that they're selling in the attic sale thingy... hes really neat... anyways then about 5 he left, i was still there... blah.... we left at like 5.45... then we took off to walmart and i got a milk shake from mcdonalds and i got Blue Crush, and some club crackers! yum. then we went home and me and my parents went out to eat at hobo depot. i ate a whole tator tot.  yah lol stupid day... i know.... but today my cousin is graduating something... she got her GED 'n such, so we're going to that at 2 then we're going to Kaycee's house later tonight and we're gonna barbeque or somethin... well im out, later gator
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      good news and bad news and good/bad news...  good news - i learned to drive my truck!... its a standard u guys, iv never driven one before.... heheheh :D  bad news - i got stuck outside almost all day today in the heat... bored.... it sucked, but i did get to see a bunch of the bikers that were going to the biker rally in austin! VROOM VROOM!  good/bad news - i went out to eat this morning with shawna and her mom... i had pancakes and tator tots, it was good... i couldnt eat it all tho... but yah, it was nice to see shawna and actually talk to her... her mom seemed kind of annoyed with me or something, i dont know... but i was sitting there, sloshing my pancake in syrup thinking about how im not sure if i wanna do this all again... i dont mean to be rude, but, you didnt say those things bc u didnt mean it shawna... :/ i really do miss having you always with me and always there to talk if i want... but i dont miss all the fights... i dunno what to do anymore......   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ::cough::  shawna IMed me this morning, she said sorry and a bunch of stuff... i feel bad, cuz i told her that i didnt wanna be close to her again... which i kinda do, i miss all the fun we had and all that good stuff... but i also dont wanna go thru all that again, it made me realize that i'd rather have no friends at all then have to go thru that more than once... i dont know what to do...  on the juciy side... I GOT MY TRUCK! :D yay! its a lil S10 blue and silver truck... all i gotta do is get my permit now, and that'll happen either this month or next month.... CHA-CHING!  ....still no word from brent..... i love him, u guys.... i miss him so much. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      feels like  wind: have fun with shawna? X007biznatchx: ya i guess it was pretty cool X007biznatchx: speaking of shawna can i talk to u about her?? feels like  wind: i guess X007biznatchx: ok feels like  wind: what about her X007biznatchx: ok would u ever be friends with her again? feels like  wind: no. X007biznatchx: ok because she was talking to me at my house and she started crying.... X007biznatchx: because we where talking about cheril and how she makes u do bad and weird thing well  X007biznatchx: she told me that she never ment to be mean to u she just had alot of anger to take out on cheril and it happened to the wrong person and she really misses being ur friend   well..... yah, i dunno what to think about THAT. lol.   today was pretty cool... i woke up thinking i wasnt gonna do nuthin today, but tarna came over and we went swimming... came back and i made some mac and cheese :) and then we went to marble falls to see Raising Helen and then came back and went swimming again... this time with steven... tarnas like in love with him.... THEN WE ATE PIZZA!   brent went on vacation last saturday... he said he'd call me :( he hasnt yet.  well... nothing much to say really... i wanna sleep, goodnight
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, saras on her way here right now... moms bring home subway yumm... and tomorrow, we're going to round rock for the express game, it shall be fun... but yah... hehe i'll update later
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    heh! thats my puppy layin on the floor :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      those are the pictures from San Antonio... i messed up on the caption for the first picture, it was me and kaycee in front of this huge building lol idk what it was... but yah...  i went to the mall and round rock with my mom yesterday... it was fun, heh... then last night we went and picked up rebecca and she stayed the night :) twas fun... we went swimming and there was a buttload of people down there having a party but no one was swimming so we just went anyways... and yah... weve been up since like 10ish but too lazy to get out of bed... just laying there lol... we watched the perfect score last night... it was kind of losing my interest so i was falling asleep and my dearest brent called :D so i talked to him for a while.... mmm i love him :-*  welp, gtg.. shower time, later days
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    hotel&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    comfy chairs...mmm&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    kayc on the riverwalk&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    me after swimming&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    on the trolly outside our hotel&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    kayc in the elevator&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    kayc sleepin'&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    kaycee in our bed&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    me on the second story of our hotel&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    me in the elevator at our "rich people" hotel, heh&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    me and kaycee at the alamo&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    us at the alamo again&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    pictures from san antonio&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok... i admit it... im kinda being immature about the whole shawna/colin thing... but i dont like being told im a fuck up more than one time a day... not even at all... but you know... :/  today i woke up early and went to my moms doc appointment w/ her... and then we went to my grandmothers house... we werent there for long and one of her dumbass senior citizen friends showed up and was having a hissy fit... so me and my mom went into her other living room and filled out paperwork for my permit... and after that we took off and went to Lowes and got some stuff.... looked at stuff.... then we left bc we were going to pick up my gma for lunch and all... but renee, dillon, and dewayne(all cousins...) were there... so of course, my Nana didnt come with us... but me and my mom had forgotten to get keith(another cousin) a birthday card for his 11th bday... hes grown 2 inches and gained 6 pounds this last year!!! :D hes still 40 something pounds tho... and short... ::sigh:: ... so me and my mom left there and went and got our hair cut and then got food in gtown, then went to the DPS, hehe! i was SOOO nervous... i kept having to sign my name and i could bearly write at all.... but i took the test and i thought it was kind of dumb... but whatever... and then the guy graded it (he was kind of mean...) and i missed 6 questions... but i still passed!! :D yay! so... me and mom went to H-E-B and then she let me drive from leander home, heh my first traffic light!!! lol so we just chilled while we waited for my father to get home, and then i got to drive to margaritas and we ate lots of gooooD food... i didnt get to drive home bc it was getting dark and such.... my father told me that i was a fuck up and that its all my fault that bad stuff happens.. and im no good... so whatever...  i just found out 2 people i know died this past week... and one got in a car wreck at seward junction.... :( ... later days
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      forget everything iv said about colin and shawna lately... their both hypocrites... shawna  is all this talk about how she wants so badly to be my friend again... if you want to be my friend so fucking bad you wouldnt call me a fuck up twice in one single day... or maybe at all...? ever think of that? guess not...  another thing... if your going to fucking talk shit about me... do it to me, not someone else...   im tired of putting up with everyones shit all the time and then being depressed over it... then i forgive them... oh guess what.. so and so just did it again! SURPRISE! everyone that im close to told me not to forgive her for all that shit shes done... all the times shes lied to me.... well guess what, im a dumbass... twice so far this summer... HAH SILLY ME!   go ahead... kill me....  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      thirteen random things i like: 1. BRENT! heh.. (: 2. sugarless gum 3. poptarts 4. taking pictures 5. letters in the mail from your favorite person ::COUGH:: 6. music, lots and lots of music 7. playing with rollie pollies 8. my cheeto :/ hope he comes home.... 9. aim 10. phones 11. leafs 12. turtles... RIP eddie... hehe eddie was my pet turtle back in the day 13. rocks?  twelve movies: 1. night at the roxbury 2. the other sister 3. finding nemo 4. legially blonde 5. airheads 6. thirteen 7. the new guy 8. half baked 9. dazed and confused 10. bubble boy 11. billy madison 12. blue crush  eleven good bands/artists: 1. staind 2. the used 3. seether 4. yellowcard 5. coldplay 6. nirvana 7. avril is a hottie 8. fall out boy 9. blink 182 10. three days grace 11. trust company  ten things about you - physically: 1. blonde hair 2. blueish greyish green eyes 3. freckle on my pinky :-p 4. not-so pale... (im super pale to begin with... but im workin on a tan) 5. long blonde eyelashes...grr i hate them 6. freckles here and there... not much tho 7. long hair 8. 5'5 AND A HALF! yay! 9. ::does dumb dance:: 10. lalalala  nine good friends (this is in no order): 1. brent  2. justin 3. tarna 4. sara 5. sarah 6. rebecca 7. tom 8.  9.   eight fav. food/drinks: 1. sprite 2. enchaladas 3. tamales 4. strawberry smoothies 5. orange juice 6. apple juice 7. grape juice 8. any kind of juice! lol  seven things you wear daily: 1. flips 2. hair tie 3. shirts 4. jeans/shorts 5. bra 6. underwear 7. ...my teeth?  six things that annoy you: 1. mean people 2. girls that try to impress guys 24/7 3. people that brag 4. my father 5. when stuff messes up (ex: my camera fucked up this morning) 6. chain letters  five things you touch everyday: 1. keyboard 2. shampoo and conditioner 3. cds 4. blankets 5. my cell phone  four shows you watch: 1. full house 2. the simpsons 3. that 70s show 4. the simple life 2  three celebrities you like: 1. ashton kutcher 2. julia stiles 3. ben stiller  two people you have kissed: 1. sam 2. david  one person you could spend the rest of your life with: 1. brent      (how do you feel today?) pretty much the same as always... it could be better  (how did you feel yesterday?) i dont remember  (what's tomorrow look like?) theres gonna be a BIG rain storm and Jesus is going to come marching down talk get take my pillow....  (who annoyed you the most today?) my dad  (who made you happy today?) brent, colin and shawna...  (what did you do today?) went to the high school to get a TEA form for my permit and then sat around... i shaved my legs! yay!  (what is in your cd player?) a mix i made  (what cd do you want the most right now?) coheed and cambria  (what song most describes you right now?) uhh? i dont know  (what is the last movie you watched?) calendar girls i think  (what is the last thing you bought?) a C2 coca cola  (what do you like most about your body?)  my hair i guess...  (what do you hate most about your body?) alot of stuff  (which friend do you lean on the most in troubled times?) brent  (what was the last thing you laughed at?) colin... his computer sucks, heh!  (what is your favorite t.v show?) simpsons  (what is the last thing you ate?) a poptart  (what is the last thing you drank?) milk  (what is the last thing you said?) that i have a bored-ness disorder...  (who is the last person you hugged?) hell... i dont know, tarna?  (who is the last person you kissed?) .... sam... while back  (what is the weather like right now?) sunny and humid i think  (who is the last person you called?) brent (have you noticed hes my favorite? lol)  (what is one thing you can't do that you wish you could?) spin around like spider man  (who is the one person you wished you looked like?) mmm... avril, shes a total babe lol  (what animals do you have?) well... 2 cats (baby and cheeto) and some stray cats blah... and then 2 dogs (tippy and shadow)  (what do you think of this filler-in?) kinda... interesting i guess....
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, yesterday colin called me up and said sorry for everything, that was great... it meant alot... later i talked to brent on the telephone :D then talked to colin some online and went and watched The Simple Life 2... i had to record it cuz my mom doesnt like them lol she says their trashy....anyways... so i watched that and then the new Bug Juice on disney... then went to sleep....  then this morning i was supposed to wake up at 7...but i woke up at 7.15 and dad wasnt done w/ his shower yet, so i went back to sleep til 8 and then hes all bitching at me cuz i didnt wake up at 7... yah i bitched right back :) so then we went to up the high school to get the TEA form for my permit tomorrow... and now im stuck here at home alone... yay!  me and shawna are doing good again... i miss her like crazy even through everything.... heh, i told her a secret! :-p
     

    
</post>


</Blog>