<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, the summer has already started here, and my children are already bored, and its only been like 3 days home!! Oh Boy.... I'm not sure how it will be after months. Maybe they just need some time to adjust to being home.   Tonight we are grilling with some friends, hotdogs, sausage, chicken, pork etc...I'm also going to try my hand at making Margarita's for the first time. My friend gave me her special recipe. After this week of moving to the new house, it will be nice to sit down and relax for a bit!!  A picture of my husband and I on our wedding day.    
     

        
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, I am new to the world of blogging, and really not sure why I am doing this. Perhaps time will tell. 
     

        
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hayden has gotten his first tooth!! Its not all the way in of course, but its completely broken though now.   Well, Hayden's shots went well. I really hated going to do that, but its one of those things that must be done. He did a lot better with it this time. He had 3 injections, and on the first one he did not cry at all. He just watched. He started crying towards the end of the 2nd one. It did not take him long and he was happy again. Just as if it had never happened. He is back to his normal happy self today.   Brock has his last ball game tonight. I'm going to take my camera and get some pictures of him playing. I hope I get some good ones. Its been a lot of work for him, but he has really enjoyed himself this season. He really loves his trophy!  I think I'm getting a cold. I keep sneezing, and my head is hurting with that heavy feeling. I hope I get over it fast.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      June is really flying by. I'm not sure where the last 8 days have gone to. It seems like Dave, the kids, and I stay so busy.   Brock had his baseball swimming party yesterday, and they were awarded 2nd place in the league. They received a nice shiny Trophy with their name on it. He had a lot of fun. His last game of the season is on Thursday the 10th.   Hayden is having his shots tomorrow, so he will most likely be very fussy tomorrow.   Hayden has been having a bit of a rough time with this tooth coming in. We checked it a few days ago, and a very tiny corner of the tooth had broken thru. Today I checked and a bit more is thru now, but its still not the whole top of the tooth thru yet. It wont be too much longer now before its completly broken through, and I know he will feel better after it does.   We grilled on our new bar-b-que grill on Sunday, and Davey has really gotten good at grilling chicken. It was scrumptious! It was nice and relaxing, the kids and I all went for a walk while Dave was getting the grill started. Its a nice neighborhood for walking, and we enjoy it.  
     

        
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, It rained again on Wednesday night, and it was beautiful to watch as Dave and I sat outside watching the sky light up. You can see a lot more at the house than you could at the apt. We are further out, less city lights. It didn't rain last night, so it was "only" 6 nights in a row!!  Davey had yesterday off. The kids got to go swimming with him at the apartment. I stayed in the apartment fed Hayden, and packed some things up.   Last night Davey grilled on our new grill. Burgers, sausage, and Cajun Boudain. Yummy!! I let the kids make ice cream with zip lock baggies, and today we made orange pineapple slushies. Mallory enjoyed hers, but Brock turned down the idea of juice down. Can't slip anything past him!!    
     

        
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wow! Dave has been here since October, and We have not once had Thunderstorms like we have had this week. For the past 5 nights after we have gone to bed and fallen asleep; the bottom has dropped out of the sky, and the thunder has been tremendous. Once the day is here again though, its full of sunshine. I think the ground is saturated now though, can't really hold much more than this.   Hayden is 6 months old today!! I will be taking some pictures of him a little later on. I think I am caught up with having all the recent pictures up on my fototime site, but not yet on my homepage. I'm having some difficulties with my coffeecup builder. Not sure what is up with it.   It's amazing to think that Hayden is 6 months old now, and last year at the time I was....Lets not go there, this year is way better :D   His 6 month old picture...   
     

        
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      test 
     

        
</post>



</Blog>