<Blog>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i snatched up a peacock feather today. they're actually quite dull in reality, contrary to the popular opinion given by most peacock media outlets. several of them in overlay would work for the good of the people, i suppose, but with american civil liberties the way they are i wouldn't push for that anytime soon.  oh, and the reality of the many slogans of the snickers corporation is finally sinking in. snickers really satisfies. hungry? grab a snickers. packed with excitement. always low prices, always snickers. enjoy snickers. simply the snickers. the list goes on and you know it.  signing out for long weekends away from civilization, this is captain boo yeah and the anti-fraction.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i just wanted to say congratulations to myself.   nathan you are a special person.  the kind that is dedicated to writing things down even when no one will read them. the kind so vein and self-annointing that you would join the masses conceition and dedicate parts of your life to writing about yourself, even after you've spent so much time in front of a mirror visualizing a similar aspect.  congra-tootles-lations
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      all the time i walk around this sit down campfire lusting life and picture tale the cotton sails that may have former use in time the reminisce comes splosh splash splish and happy fills the heads of every one of these circlers, a fire for their interest  so silent in the sunk and slosh that captures every day we tread our feet as heavy as the grass permits an indent lay and simple sicked up nowhere rhymes and tickle round our tongues until the rain comes hailing sounds to bless us, every one...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so here i am getting back into the blogging world thinking that someone somewhere will be interested in what i have to offer....
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         So this is Tristan in full fledged rocker status. With hair like that who needs a proper speech pattern?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      there's a woodchuck parading around in my field of vision. he has origin issues. he spends his days rooting around looking for sustenance, every now and then looking up quickly and intentely to determine if i'm a threat or not. or to ponder how his mother being a gopher and his father a beaver will affect his adult life. the toiling of a woodchuck is complicated, at best.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i find myself in new music and hah hah sunburns. wearing a mesh trucker cap backwards will leave the most interesting of speckles on a man's brow.   i am a son of Ares, born in the time of the ram and filled with the spinning chase of the two fishes, living a life of fortune cookie creativity and unprecedented boon vs. bust. when the big god of war shakes his clutchy fists and even Zeus doesn't mind to turn the blind eye as the thunder comes crackling through the cool blue sky of this northern home i find myself prone to, well, no one minds all that much attention, but I know who he shakes his fist for.  still, i do a lot of sitting slouched and flecking my lungs with tar and dismissing all of the healthy dark green veggies and high fibre living that i do otherwise.    the sun is always coming. and i suppose i'm always waiting for it. every any day, but in particular those sparkling lens flare pumpkin hue mornings, when i step outside into the morning glare leading me out of the driveway and a big picture frame window cropping out my own little part of the forest. i'm just another child of the whole, a real People of the Sun. we're all just  urlLink People .   good luck.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So...i went to this comedy club in my own newly claimed hometown, that's erie pa for all of you dedicated listeners who don't front on the old school rap. anyway, comedy comedy comedy. that's funny stuff. here's the wrap up:  comedian one: made a joke about mexicans (keep in mind the entire audience [nearly let alone erie's population] is white) and then went on to racist black jokes. now i'm no racist, but i love racist jokes. white, black, mexican, negro, nigger dare i say, whatever. racism is so unrealistic to me at this point that making jokes about it is the only proper way to go about life.  comedian two: a woman. hah! funny in itself, you say, and i agree. i know, i know, there's nothing funny about women, but this girl sounded like she was a dislexic reading from a cue card, but her jokes were so funny it shone through. is that how you spell shone? as in "shown": hah again.  comedian three. too funny. that's all. hilarity about cops and killing deer and he was on jay leno, which makes him cool, because whatever anyone says, letterman isn't the top spot. old people like jay, or so i hear, but i grew up through college on jay, so that's that.  so i was with three others, and when the show was over, and i'd had five or ten beers, i suggested we continue this raunch at calimari's, some little joint with an outside drinkery in the port town, and no one was up except the least likely of suspects, linda, who i barely knew. so we went, yada yada yada, talk shit on people at work, and we each had a drink. then i ordered a second and started drinking it when everyone was like - hah! we're leaving sucka chump foo. so there i was, alone, drinking, smoking, looking good in my hat.  the end came i left and now i'm typing. see the previous audio blog for info on the hooker i ran into...  later.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i don't know what to think about that 70's show. sobre, i find it to be drab at best but droll at worst. on a more intoxicated note, i seem to think that it is incredibly horrible and amazingly hilarious all in the same bit. and then i go their website and read some of the most aweful hubbub ever.  and laugh tracks, those are horrible. dead give away for a good wave.  lates.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      mmmm...stale generic nilla wafers and monday evening chill factories marching out that old gray good time blue sky no worries for here in the big time, babies. playing short games of pickup, baseball, swinging on tires and hammocks and smokes and a cold one and generally enjoying the summer life. there's a world full of waste and we're nowhere near it.  there is a big pink robot out there but i've got someone to save my ass...whew...and that's the best it gets.  let's talk about things.  like...favorite movie ... favorite chicken .. favorite other things.   well, my favorite other things are smoking while drinking and sitting around a table generally conversing from stupid to dummrest, staring into camp fires full on wine and potatoes or possibly sleeping late and wrapped up in t-shirts and suntans on the forever pale. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my teeth are rotting out in anticipation and under immense turmoil from the smoking community surrounding my usual actions. soon i'll be a million miles from anywhere and under skies clear enough to see the stars and laying on sand steamy enough to curl my pigs. i'm going to sleep now.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      [edited per my satisfaction]  urlLink The hall where they played  ended up being a very narrow and long room that could hold maybe 100 people tops, the stage not more than a 4 inch riser at the end of it all. We managed to walk right up and plop down in the front row, and weren't further than a stone's throw from intense facial expressions and amazingly dexterous fingering of  urlLink guitars  and  urlLink harps.    At some point I was able to talk to Joanna for like all of 5 seconds, and a guy named Kevin was shooting their shows on this tour for some future documentary I suppose, so I talked with him awhile, as well as one of the guys from Vetiver. All of whom were very cool and not at all rockstarish or out of touch with us wee folk in the audience.   A woman probably my age or a few years ahead of me, capped in 3 foot dread locks, the kind dirty white hippie kids have, colorful and ribboned, walked around with her daughter, who couldn't have been any more than 4 years old, with an exotic name I can't manage to remember, stamping herself all over her arms and hands with the doorman's stamper. And outside I chatted with a girl who was all about downloading things from the Internet, as far as I could surmise. Hilariousness and warmth abounded, at least from my chair. Perportedly, not a seat away things were filled with contempt and angst and some oddly placed hatred for things unknown...which continued over coffee and my final cigarette. But all in all, good times for everyone.  I love being alive in this world. I'm doing a good job and the world in general, at least in my immediate surroundings of thick forests kissing the monotonous highway repitition, is doing the same. Soon is good. Sooner is best.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been awake for a long time. Well, it wouldn't be very long to some people, college kids, rock stars, artsy next big thing wanna be types who bartend a few nights a week and blow coke into the earlier hours of  urlLink Morning Edition . But to me it's been a pretty long time. I'm smoking again. Not full fledged, but only when I drink. I've been drinking regularly. Draw your own conclusions.  I'm giddy for the  urlLink Joanna Newsom  /  urlLink Devandra Banhart  concert tomorrow. That's Pittsburgh PA. Some place called the  urlLink Garfield Artworks .   The  urlLink Mattress Factory  was cool by my standards, for an arthouse and all. I'm not a big fan of looking at paintings hanging on walls. That's not what MF is about. I live in Erie. That's cool for now, I suppose.  Two more years and I'm still here, well then we'll have to think about getting our life back on track...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'll be leaving Erie PA on a Friday. Gloom and doom or bright and sunny, the highway and I will play leap frog to Pittsburgh and I'll meet up with J.H. the secret agent fellowshipper who'll accompany me on this wonderful tour.  Next stop, Terre Haute IN, then onto Oklahoma City, Albuquerque NM, and then to spend a few days in the desert near Flagstaff. Good times I surmise. Though i'm no fortune teller, I'll find myself inclined to state, but who would doubt?  Anyway, I'm thinking about Mr. Mojo Risen and how he might find me dancing there in the desert. I'm sure we'll find our own thing, though, as emulating the past isn't precisely prime rib on my plate.  I'm thinking of sleeping in tents for most of our journey, but I here the Grand Canyon International Hostel "is centrally located in downtown Flagstaff 1 1/2 blocks from Amtrak and 5 blocks from Greyhound." So that should be useful.   Next stop, San Diego - maybe a daytrip into Mexico. HAH! That's hilarious. A day trip. Wank on.  Finally onto Incline Village to see an old friend and live life on the good beautiful lake i've heard so much about.  That's a precap. More to come after the excursion.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         A few of my traveling companions and I made our way to this little island south of Ocean City, MD — a state park named after the Indians who once lived there that, get this, were driven off the island by some settlers. Read all about the Assateague Indians  urlLink here , or the island itself,  urlLink here , or even about the wild horses that don't so much roam the island as wait by the road to be "killed by kindness," as one flyer put it,  urlLink here.   As for the real deal, well, we left the fine state of PA for this island Thursday, June 03 and docked up in some chain lodge that night, then made our way to Assateague the next morning. A good arch of a bridge put us over the bay and a merry old site of canoes and a some sort of sea fowl's nest perched on a miniature lighthouse-looking thing coming out of the water. These wild horses, which weren't as much wild as they were homeless, I would say, were shitting all over the road and in the swamps, and not minding one bit. You could tell they were just hanging alongside the pavement, waiting for some poor sucker to come along and give them a snack, which would inevitably lead them to continue this method of panhandling until one gloomy night an unwarry traveler would smack a horse dead on in the middle of the road, which actually happens, and when such an occurance took place in 2000, they drew up a special flyer with the headline "Killed By Kindness" which was simulatenaously hilarious even surrounded by all the standard bummer feelings one might rouse up at the thought of a dead horse who probably had never even got to star in his own porn.  Anyway, cloudy skies and warm weather, sitting with feet dangling out of some decent tents, beers and fruity drinks and the feeling that everything around you is foreign and perfectly naturally home all at the same time, sand in your shorts, in your slippers, in your drink, smoke on your lips and a foggy mind to keep everything wonderfully out of perspective—the work world a million miles away and when night came crashing over us in thundering stormy reality I was suddenly humbled and empowered by the fact that I was sleeping on an island far from home with nothing separating me and a night in the rain but a tent that we'd put up ourselves and were now as close to real as I'd been in a long very long long time. An early morning skip to the beach before we left where I sat by myself letting the water dance around my toes and somehow getting the feeling that as mighty as the ocean is it was showing me a bit of respect and allowing me to think that I had some control here. So much of our time was spent just living in this martian locale that we only headed into Ocean City once, for about an hour, to do the whole crab shack thing and Shawn kept reminding the rest of us that we were in effect eating something similar to a giant insect, while he no doubtedly dined on beef or steak or sirloin or some part of a cow. A real meat eater, you could say. Hilarious, what with my knowledge of him. But you'll never know, seperate are the reader and the original thought and all I can do is try to suck up some life now in the between of this adventure and my next, a cross country trip with my girlfriend, Jill, to the desert, California, Lake Tahoe and possibly a quick jaunt through Mexico...  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i think i'll go back to kindergarten.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      that old familiar orange glow comes crashing across my world a patented distinguished set of glasses rest upon my nose and all the librarian girls let down their moppy hairs until just me and the music are left to analyze just how much they're in the know  i make a simple statement and you guesture accordingly we touch hands awkwardly and you're smiling endlessly for all of these moments we have within these sheltered walls someday never comes and we're left to perfection's visual  i'll spin you all around in a sun dress and similar day watch the world get dizzy and blur into green and unafraid let you go just in time to fling your soul into the air and we can get caught up in treelimbs and dance our way back down from there  but until then lets wicker whittle wither away time lose the hair from my head and grow the lines under your eyes and we'll see how beautiful we become just before we die holding hands and peddling humor in the wake of the divine
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Intronet is a word that I think is funny. Like when you call a guy named Jake the J-Man or J-Town. Wait, I guess it wasn't as funny as I thought.  Anyway, here are three killer websites that everyone should enjoy. (No one is reading this, Nathan, you, and millions of other blogging idiots like you, are completely insane. Not like 13 year olds playing D&D by themselves insane, but really in italics insane.)    urlLink "Typer Shark"  Think Jaws the video game for the original Nintendo meets all the fun of typing!   urlLink "Super Funny Linux Joke"  More Flash - key for any supergeek trying to rule the world.   urlLink "The Beaufort Drinking Scale"  This is a little Flash comic strip from those crazy Brits with their dry wit and skanky humor.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my son's name is tristan. he is a two year old rock star. if you have a baby, i just want to say i'm sorry that your baby is not as cute or cool as mine. he called me tonight to say "i just wanted to call you because i wanted to say goodnight."  that's a cell phone commercial in the works.  good night tristan.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       traveling west by foot  a thumb to the sun and a smoke in the breeze a dozen cars pass, maybe more, before any launch can be made wondering how or how not friendly this leadfoot will come off disappearing out the door at the first stoplight ready to roll buying cheap wine and sitting by myself in the woods just away from the road watching headlights make their way around the world and imagining the conversations i would have and probably be uncomfortable having with the drivers   urlLink nanty glo goes worldwide  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     So my adventures around the world have officially begun before I began this ol' blog thang, earlier this year, with my traveling companion extraordinaire Jill Henkel/to Canadia, home of the freeze, land of the grapes.   The occasion coincided with February 14th, which coincidentally rummied alongside a little known holiday wearing a nametag labeled "Hello, my name is Valentine's Day" but on more official documents labeled St. Valentine's Day. Also, in Niagara-on-the-Lake, the hyphen-happy little villa we stayed in, they were celebrating Days of Wine and Roses, which sounded like a sparky ol' jovial time to me on the way up, though we later realized that it meant not much in a town where the latest shoppe is open only until just past 5:15. A lovely locale, really, but for hearty wanderers such as ourselves, we needed some substance, something more dirt and gritty, a place that might actually have a population of homeless people.   So we gathered ourselves in a local bar and asked around, discovering that while you weren't able to smoke inside any public place in the Niagara region, there was a little diddy of a shuffle that you could make by motorcar and find yourself arrived in a small city known as St. Catherine's. Blah blah blah blah blah. My story goes too long and so I'll make the point snappy and clean: we stopped in a wee coffee shop where our waitress wore her hair in silly sexy beads and lanked her way over to deliver us our ordered drinks, chai for the lady and some sort of green tea with the word "dragon" in it for this rag tag exchange for a gent. After pursuing her interests we discovered that a little place known as  urlLink the NAC  would be having a cheesey high school dance sort of blast and we should stop in.  So we did.   At first site it was too 10th grade for reality, and no one was there yet, so we turned tail and found the second of two bars that you could actually smoke in, where we played pool with some friendly Canadians who were adament about the fact that "the States" were a bore and Canada had the cheap weed, which I found entertaining that people might think of me as the sort to partake in such events. They generally tended to say things like, "Oh, you're from the States? Well, that's okay with me, but they're a bit of a drag. I do like the (insert hockey team), though." Stereotypes are a beautiful thing. Roundabout storytelling and all, we got back to the NAC and there we met a happy bunch of misfits who called themselves (though not to our face) the Suitcase in Point. They invited us to a private showing/critique the next day of a play they had written, starred in and produced called "Be Wearing Wolf," a truly wonderful display of insanity and humor all wrapped up into a flabbergast of intellectual hilarity. And you can quote me on my hairdo if I'm wrong. So check out the website and then go to Canada on your next lunchbreak via your local magnetic train. Ta-ta.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         urlLink Christian Debt Removers   Wow - check out that Proverb - "the borrower is a slave to the lender." - nothing like dropping in on my inbox to find that I very well may have been using pagan means to eliminate my debt in the past. Whew - salvation at last.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today I roll over 300 miles to see kith and kin.  urlLink Charles Ingals  would have been planning this for weeks, months maybe. He'd need a cart full of supplies and two or more good steeds. Ha. All I have is a (running down) old  urlLink 2000 Neon  (sounds cooler if you say  urlLink Neon 2000 ) and the sheer will and determination of a nation gone wrong.  Lovely.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The ranks of disheveled waywards has been lifted as I storm into the depths of my basement in search of but one, lone sock. Clothes have been disappearing from my abode in a matter fit perhaps only for the old MTV Oddities or maybe Ren & Stimpy, Season 1.  To work I say, offward gone!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      An old friend gave me a call on the telephone last night. I was sleeping, so he left a message, and he says to me via that machine:   "You want to know what my books about? It's about how when you're a kid you think that your boys will always be your boys and then when you grow up you realize they have lives of their own. When you're young you think everyone's just a minor character in your own story, but then you realize that they're all major characters in their own thing and you're just one of their outgoing characters."   That was tight, I liked it alot.   My girlfriend pointed out to me the other day that I'm still friends with the people I knew in high school, even though I'm 25 now and we've all moved in and out of a dozen different towns all over America. Good for us.   urlLink Jet Screemer plays rock n' roll. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         There are six locations—that I've been able to find—in Erie where you can sit down and Wi your Fi off.    Borders  near the Mall&nbsp;     Kinkos  on&nbsp;Upper Peach&nbsp;  Pilot  is a big trucker stop on Perry Highway&nbsp;   Starbucks  downtown on State Street   Hampton Inn  on Old Oliver Road&nbsp;  UPS Store  on Upper Peach  Cornerstone Bar & Grill  on 38th  And then best of all, there's a free hotspot at  7th and German&nbsp; that I've just gots ta check out.  Well, killer diller ya'll&nbsp;and do enjoy.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      former lovers have secret spies to monitor my moves kings and pawns and dj babies sneak into my room all i want is time travel to feel the way i don't feel anymore through a simple word or a moment i've learned can we lose the intelligence and just knock straight onto doors? 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i've been to heaven, i've been to the beach but anymore, i mostly just go to sleep first i wake up, then i do it again i wake up once for every time i go to the sleepin' i live up herein a far away land where the milkmaids and the engine drivers they all up and ran and sure i've got friends here and again but i go home to an empty house more nights than i don't and it's gettin' a little tiresome and a little out of hand and i just want to wake up somewhere other than Erie, PA a desert sunrise, new york minute or the crystal bay i wanna be back there in diapers running around my farm but i can't so i could settle waking up in your arms and it's clear to me with crusty eyes so tired every morning getting up before my time and when i see my son and do my routine that i'm no kid anymore but i walk around amongst the living blah and they do all their things but they don't do much so it becomes so clear to me my talents are my faults and in a million years i'm no fucking adult so i don't know where i should pretend to fit in i guess i'll buy myself a motorbike and write MOM across my skin................ 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The color of today blows up in drab contrast to places I've seen and been in recent weeks. Trees, though more assorted than in other realms, seem to blur together in a splotch of green and grey and brown and silent barks that make me want to roll around in the dew that, though up in these mountains, is completely free of high fructose corn syrup. I'm trapped back in the box, work, eat, sleep, etc., but life is definitely renewed. Vacations from the cycles we wrap ourselves around are often followed by a change of heart, a determination to reinvent our lives, and I fear I am only riding on that wave as of now. I play daily with my son, take long walks and have quit smoking, started riding my bike with frequent turnaround and am loving the eases of ignoring all the money I don't have. Today I'm a happy cat, lazy and laying on a fence somewhere with other happy cats, laughing over simple jokes and magic tricks. Tomorrow I might slip closer to the alley floor, once I need to start scrounging for the scraps again and dipping my paws into the neighbors milk. But for now it's all analogies and metaphors until a smokey green haze takes from the west coast burnings comes my way to remind me why laid back is so much good good times. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Beer + My Brain = Back to Smoking    urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So here are some nice things I discovered on my ways today...   The Dungeons & Dragons Complete Elven Bards Handbook presents  urlLink Devendra Banhart  live in concert.  worth checking out even if you completely despise devendra and mock his bitter voice on a daily basis.     &nbsp;  It's fun to look at&nbsp;human faces. Some people look more interesting than others.  urlLink Punk rockers  often look more interesting than the rest of us.  clicking the names of the bands on the right is what you'll want to do.     &nbsp;   urlLink This  makes me smile for reasons not necessary to be divulged but perhaps appreciated by the only one who matters.  this link will go bunk in approximately 48 hours.     &nbsp;  Please, party people, do feel obliged to comment here. There could be no larger a rejoice in my soul.   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here and there I take a tic or toc to ease my mind Early days away from 5:00 deadlines and landmines I like to make a couple words to spin into a phrase So everyone can read along and lots of happy days and other such things. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I'm getting seriously into riding bikes. I'm getting a new mountain bike either next week or the one after that. Sponsored by My Mother, Inc. Every rider needs a sponsor, hell, we can't keep ourselves in diapers and new tires on a graphic D's salary.  So my plan is to next year ride from Erie, the Flagship City of PA, to Flagstaff, AZ. According to MapQuest, it's something like 2000 miles via major highways. A straight line connecting Pittsburgh to Flagstaff, plus the 124 or so miles to Erie, is 1400 miles. So my actual length will be somewhere between that.   I plan to take 4 weeks off of work, which might be difficult what with reality being a factor and all, but I think I can pull it off. So 4 weeks = 30 days with the extra initial weekend. The ride itself will take place over 23 days, and it'll take 2 days to get back on a Greyhound, which leaves me with 5 days to kick back and enjoy Flagstaff or take breaks along the way if need be.  Basically that means just under 75 miles per day, so at 12mph each day it&nbsp;would involve about 6.5 hours of riding.    Do I really think I can do that?    &nbsp; I don't know. I've quit smoking, it's only been a few days, and I quit and start up again all the time, but I'm feeling some extra dedication right about now. As for riding, I went two miles in fifteen minutes today, on a 20" bike at that, and was feeling okay when I got back. So I'll keep working on that until winter and we'll see how everything's going.  lovely. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a bit of research I've done, via the internet and my extensive career in the field, on good ways to get over a hangover.&nbsp; Why am I writing this? I don't know, go ask your dad.    Drink lots of water.  Alcohol is a diuretic, which means it sucks the water straight out of your cells. Chug a glass or two after all the beers gone. I like to fill an empty bottle up with water, that way it seems like I have one more beer. By that time you tend to be so shmaced that you forget it's water halfway down the drain, anyway.   Gatorade . Drinking also sucks out potassium and salt from your body.&nbsp;Gatorade, or it's dark nemesis, Powerade, will get these back into ya.&nbsp;From personal experience, I usually wake up, my stomach feeling like shit, and chug down a glass of soda, then maybe a milkshake or something,&nbsp;all types of strange cravings which basically always just make me sick. But eventually I come around to&nbsp;gold old orange&nbsp;Gatorade, or the orange flavored clear Gatorade, man, I mean that stuffs just sick.&nbsp;   Fill up on fruit juice.  Word on the street, though none of the streets I've lived on, is that fruit juice gives you a boost of energy and also cleans out toxins from your body. Bod man. That's a funny commercial.   Cappuccino drinks . Alcohol makes your blood vessels swell, which in turn leads to a real throbber of a head syndrome. Caffeine combats this like Yoshimi could only dream. But on the other hand, it also sucks the water out of your body, so keep it light. Starbucks isn't keeping it light, but maybe a cup o' Folger's homebrew will do the trick. Personally, I only do the fake cappuccino drinks from 7/11s.   Eat some food.  Eat before you drink, and light goods in the morning. Unless you're a senior in high school or a freshman in college. Then, I'm assuming you're looking to get shlammered, so your best bet is to eat lunch on Thursday, and then proceed to compete in chugline after keg stand after whiskey shot for the next five days. I'm sure you'll be sufficiently comatose by Saturday morning.  Well, with that I've officially become gay. Bye. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The world hates me with tortorous devotion. Laughing at every little reward it throws my way, rewards meant to encourage enduring the rest of the sap that comes with the everyday sickness known as school and work and death, the new cycle. &nbsp; On one of the bonus notes, though, I struck upon  urlLink this little girl . 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
          "The role of Superman, which has reportedly been offered to Brendan Fraser, Paul Walker and The Rock in the past, remains uncast."   Now, after spending the last few weeks under the big black night sky of far off regions and the enchantment of life without schedules, toppled over with the fact that I just watched Spiderman 2 last night, I find that life in general is a difficult droll of being late for appointments and nodding your head in agreement with the scurvy masses, or at least those sketchy minority reporters who call themselves Bossman.  It is with great displeasure that I present to you the hilarious shortcomings of what could have been the greatest neo-superhero movie of our time. Superman was originally going to be directed by Tim Burton, no doubt with Danny Elfman on the music scene, and Nick Cage was going to play the man of steel. That's all over, and rumors abound that Encino Man himself, possibly the worst actor ever, might have a shot at the role. HAH!   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
             &nbsp;
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
            Don't bother listening to this post. I was half-cranked on liquors and good times galore but not precisely in a state to make loud conversation into a cell phone as the rest of a sleeping house went numb into dreamland.
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
             Here we were sitting ontop of a roof that we'd crawled out onto through the window of our non-smoking room. We did drinks and general good times all into the night and I ended up singing. The hotel was completely packed with a giant family reunion.  We weren't invited.
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
             Here we were sitting ontop of a roof that we'd crawled out onto through the window of our non-smoking room. We did drinks and general good times all into the night and I ended up singing. The hotel was completely packed with a giant family reunion.  We weren't invited. 
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
             
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
            With a surprise appearance by Julius Sumnermiller!
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
            Countless slop troughs passed off as bathrooms dot the back end highways of America's Main Street, the former Route 66. I don't tend to disappoint myself with high hopes when trailing into a gas station lav, but now and then, coupled with intense heat and a smoking addiction, I find myself weathered.
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And they are indeed. Clear blue unrealistic skies once you cross into the Central Time Zone, and the clouds just thin from there. Giant burning clouds of smoke interrupted the scheme in Arizona, yesterday, on our way into Flagstaff, caused by wild fires all over the open prairie range. They were miles away from us but could at any time destroy this entire town. Maybe they would feel the same about a thunderstorm. Living in them all of your life you lose interest in the fear. I am living. Awake before the coffee shops this morning and watching the people, bums, junkies, hippies, businessmen who don't quite dress like businessmen. This town is free of a lot of the social structure that Western PA feels the need for. This is the my first time in front of a computer for days, and in my world, computers dominate every minute of my working day and much of my down time. Feels strangely good. I want the freedom of nature and travel, but I still love the benefits of technology.  I think I'm getting a tattoo soon...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      time is slow and suddenly realized as just another aspect of space. so the space/time continuum is basically just the space continuum. however you want to look at it.  anyway, my adventures in no work world have thus far gotten me bitched at by an antsy neighbor, painted as a passing blur in a comical artists corner setting, led me through the halls of the andy warhol complex, where the soup cans are kept in the storage room, right behind the dolly full of garbage.  shawn makes music. beer consumption is contemplated. i'm alive and free and have no reason to feel otherwise for the majority of this month. blogging on the road will be intrepid but incredibly desirable, like finding a slice of pizza exactly like your hometown pizza shop in a town a dozen thousand miles away.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, you should definitely like this urlLink phone  if not i suppose you may want to re-evaluate the circumstances under which you're living.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Okay, so like, oh my god - cell phones are soooo cool!  is perhaps the main reason why cell phones, digital or otherwise, are supergay.  On the other hand, beautiful magical capabilities available to us in the future that is now here (you know, the one they told you would come along all of these years), like  urlLink this one  and possibly  urlLink this  as well, make me dive into my phone at all possible moments. well, a few now and then anyway. note the decension from capital letters to anti-cap. anyway, this is a hilarious comment from a web page talking about it's new slide phone:    The SL56 is  designed for desire.  It's an incredible phone; it combines a flashing design with innovation and all the features a state of the art phone should offer. Smaller and lighter than ever before, it reveals its inner qualities when you slide it open and discover the faceted keys. They flash like jewels in a treasure chest, it's a unique phone to hold.  You will love to display it and hang it around your neck.  SL56 is too beautiful to disappear in your pocket.   No explitives necessary folks, this is the real deal. Check it out  urlLink here  if you'd like, 'cause i'm near to certain there's more...let's find out shall we urlLink >> 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Hello and do welcome yourselves to the homepage of one Professor Julius Sumnermiller. I will at times be confiscating this blog to express my opinions on the state of scientific matters and how they are affecting the everyday lifestyles of the human populace.    For example, the average person has no idea as to the resulting pandamonium that would happen if I dropped one cigarette, brand: Misty Ultralight, into a cup of your average joe, precisely the kind filling this styrofoam container. Madness I tell you! Please tune in soon for more wacky exploits from myself and my friends, Grampa Grayscale and his three insane children.    urlLink Visit the official Experiments of Julius Sumnermiller Webpage! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So today was somewhat fulfilling.  For one, I was contacted by the good people at  urlLink Suitcase In Point  and we'll be shooting our movie/documentary sometime in September. That's very cool. I've seen these guys do their thing and they amazed me beyond words. Hopefully, the project will be a success, and by that I mean that hopefully we'll finish the whole darn thing and be able to translate what works so well live into a (the dreaded words) TV show.  Also, I watched  urlLink The Last Samurai . What a great movie. Forgive me, but my honor dictates I follow in the way of the samurai and not reveal much of anything else to you, but go watch the movie - quickly now!  And finally, my training in the way of the bike is coming along quite nicely, though perhaps not as progressive as I'd like. This is partly due to the fact that my new bike hasn't come in yet, but also to other major contributing factors in my life like my baby and the fact that I'm often times lazy.  So I rode 7 miles today in 45 minutes, so I'm going about 10mph. That's on a little kid's peddle bike, at night and on the sidewalk. Tomorrow I'll go at it again, 10 miles in the same time, though. Then next Wednesday I ride home from work, which is only 9 miles but hella hilly, as opposed to the relatively flat landscape I've been working with. My plan from there is to ride to work the next day, see how it goes in the early hours of the wee morn. Then to Edinboro PA, which is about 20 miles away sometime next week.  Before the end of the season, I want to ride all the way to Pittsburgh. That's over 125 miles - I'll do it in two days, I suppose, arriving just in time for beers with Webstar. But that's for the future and now on to the special features on The Last Samurai.  Late nights to all  urlLink my peoples on the west coast. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i hope someone searches for that someday.  anyway...here goes:   mike williams:  Iam looking for any info on the penny family from tredegar mainly from twanaback any info would be greatly appriceated or the  urlLink granvill family  of ebbw vail thank you    janice webb:  I have a query relating to my 2 x great-grandmother (Elizabeth LITTLEY) who died at Tredegar on 25 April 1859.  Her death certificate is very difficult to read and I cannot make out the name of the parish where she was buried.  It looks as though it may be Penmorth Tirhoroy, Tredegar,  urlLink Monmouth, Wales . Is there such a parish?  Her husband, John Marshall LITTLEY (born Ottery St Mary in Devonshire) was an iron mine worker at Tredegar.  I believe that several of his children (including my great-grandfather - Edward Littley) were born at Tredegar.  Unfortunately, none of their births were registered (Civil Registration). Therefore, I need to know in which parish I should be looking.    mike williams:  Iam looking for any info on the penny family from tredegar mainly from  urlLink twanaback  any info would be greatly appriceated or the granvill family of ebbw vail thank you    sara:  Hi everyone, I am trying to find my ancestors who came to PA from Wales. I have sort of narrowed the search down to Tredegar from some info I found at familysearch.com. I am looking for  urlLink Charles  &  urlLink Elizabeth  (Nash) Tilley and their children.  urlLink My great-grandfather , William Tilley was born 12 Feb 1851 in Wales. According to his obituary he is one of 20 children and his parents are listed as Charles & Elizabeth. William married Elizabeth Steele. William's siblings that we know about are Charles b. Mar 1850, Harriet b. 1856, Albert b. 30 Jan 1859 and Samuel b. Nov 1865. In a book someone wrote about this line is written that in 1861 they lived 121 Scwia Road, Duffey's Upper, Dukestown, Llandunider, Wales and next door to Charles was Alfred Tilley & wife Amalia. I located this Alfred & Amailia through familysearch in Tredegar. Of the five obits I have Samuel's states he was born in South Wales, I also have his natualization showing they came to the USA in 1865 fro!  m Liverpool.  I would like any help/leads to locate the other 15 children and possibly get birth/baptism certificates for the children. It is possible that Charles' first name was William, that is what is shown on the marriage certificate. Any help greatly appreciated.     urlLink nathan :  and by this, reader, do i mean what?   reader  ( urlLink that's you ):   why did i seriously read all of that?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      seriously bro - you should've read your email by now.   if you haven't.  well then. stop. read your email.  okay okay.  so you're back.  alright man, well - here are  urlLink my short term plans.    1. get the R.L.P. CD. I believe it's called PUNX AIN'T STOPPIN' with a picture of Mr.  urlLink Nicholas  "The Cars"lisi (most notably of "The 4  urlLink (Later Known as 5)  PunX)and load it into our sophisticated  urlLink WQLN-FM Q-91.3  software and make a somewhat decent CD out of it. (though i'm certain  urlLink wild cat city , my best tune, will still sound like a shit mix)  2. get the video of us from up at the skatepark from Steve Havener. nothing more to say there. just all burning rip ass DVDs and whatnot as similarly and formerly noted with my powers of tangibility.  3. come to Jersey. halloween. you should call me about this.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i spent the last few minutes talking to my best friend about the death of his dad. he's handling better than anyone has ever. "handling" isn't even appropriate. he's living in the reality, more adequately related. i aspire to achieve his disassociation with the really real.   i spent the last hour calling old friends and leaving messages on their machines. saturday night at 10:00 isn't a good time to hook up with twenty somethings.  i spent the day getting drunk with my boss and two.5 year old son.  i'll spend the next few minutes getting leafy green and smoking camels quenched in miller light.  have fun.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So yeah, I'm 25 years old and this shouldn't be the sort of thing that I'm laughing about now - but the number listed above connects you to a chemical company. Fartman. Chemical company. C'mon. Hilarious. Just listen to the post...    urlLink   
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I try to dwell as little as possible on the dark lords running the big rusty machine that gives this otherwise splendid country it's horrid name, but can anyone else see the hilarity in the way that the first Bush lost his shot at a second term by focusing on Iraq and not the economy and now W. seems to be running the same route.  urlLink Electioneering.   Then I think about how this is funny to me. And how I make jokes at work about processors and  urlLink targa sequences  and I realize I'm a horribly  urlLink giant geek  (24.0916% actually.)  Other than my  urlLink supercool factor .  On the other hand,  urlLink Jazz & Blues festival  is tomorrow so I'll sip a few beers, eat a few free slices or sandwiches, bullshit my boss and coworkers and hang out with the TanMan.  Oh, and zebras are the punkest animals out there? Am I wrong?   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Morning shimmers through the houses and chain link fences and ungroomed trees blocking me from the horizon, it shines all over the dew licking the grass and my dirty bathroom window. Relief. I look outside and then down, down at the swirling goodbye to last night's beverages.   Is it no coincidence that humans are 75% water just as mother earth is? I think not. We all spit out from our mothers, who were the same mix, who in turn came from their's and so on and back forth until one of our great grandmothers (yours and mine both, I surmise) were sprung forth from the ground. Eve or otherwise, let's get hippy love all over the place.  I'm buying  urlLink a new bike  today. Still in training for next summer.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay so three or more things...  One,  urlLink Burnination  can be yours with  urlLink this super cool game.  Think  urlLink King's Quest 3  and email me if you have any idea when to feed Manannan the cookies in that game.  Okay part C:  urlLink Jason Mraz  is coming to town and while some of my friends might think he's weak and without purpose I find him utterly groove-tastic. So hopefully I'll be there.  And furthermore,  urlLink my baby is a superstar.  Click there and you'll see what I mean - oh, but then he got bumped because he wasn't  multi-racial  enough. That's bullshite. What can you expect though? The white man's always gettin' held down, you know?
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      where passion and life are concerned often times you'll hit doubts when i was a kid i could deal with things  but now that i'm all alone in the big grown up house i find it harder to look on the sunny side of the egg  here and there i go walk clear a head and a mind straighten my posture sort out my time  if a friendly man dies through no fault of your own know it's just a real life and at times life's postponed.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>