<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was a fun day. I went to Reading with Amy, Kaz and Avril Lavigne girl. AL girl has been renamed to Kazzy's girl, because she didn't like the old name, and calling her Laura is just too difficult. I bought leopard print trousers! And they're a size 12, which is admittedly disgusting, but I have ways of making them fit. I also bought a PWEI record, Throbbing Gristle CD, New Order CD, Joy Division CD, and Kazzy's birthday present. It was pretty hilarious, because Amy and I are doing a little matchmaking to help out AL girl. I mean Kazzy's girl. I mean Laura. Anyway, we basically injured him a lot when he refused to put his arm round her and stuff. He deserved it though, he's so rude. We were harrassed by pikeys, which was quite funny, but then quite boring. I'm a little upset though, as there were no Psychic TV or Babylon Zoo CDs anywhere, which says rather negative things about their popularity. But I found a PTV record, which I intend to eventually purchase. Oh my God! Today I saw the R2C video!! Basically, I used to go to this Christian youth group thing, and the church it belongs to put on this huge Christmas concert. And our group decided to do some stupid rap, and me and Amy and Matthew volunteered to do solos because we thought it would be funny. We totally spazzed out, because we were on a sugar high at the time, I mean we were air guitaring and disco dancing and everything. It really was quite sad. Anyhow, I saw the video today, and I can't remember the last time I laughed so hard. I'm not sure I've ever looked so stupid in my life. I really must do stuff like that more often! Anyway, when I got home, I went up to my room and... My Dad had tidied it while I was out! IT'S TIDY!!!! Well, much tidier anyway. I can now find my guitars, and my bed and stuff. Another interesting piece of news is that apparently, I do actually have a carpet underneath all that crap. It's very awesome to have my room that tidy, tomorrow I'm gonna finish the job. It's quite weird really, how one day can be so fucking awful, and the next day can be so much fun. Gemma has got considerably less interesting. She didn't seem to have much to talk about, except when she was crying (how emo!). The rest of the time, she just repeated conversations she'd had with various people, while I was like "uh huh...yeah...right...ok...mmhmm...". She told me all these stories that didn't go anywhere, I was bored out of my mind. For example - "The other night, yeah, I was at Stuart's house, yeah, and like... Ah, Stu's music is so great, all his cool pikey music...Anyway, yeah, I was at Stu's house, and like, I tossed him off, yeah, and like... Ah, Stu has a fucking Empire State building, he does...Anyway, yeah, like I tossed him off, and we were lying in bed, yeah, and like, my phone rang. So I answered my phone, yeah, and it was my Mum. So I was like 'Oh hi Mum' and she's like 'Where are you Gemma?' and I'm like 'I'm at Charlotte's house for the night' and she's like 'Oh OK, have a nice time' and I was like 'Yeah thanks Mum, I will' and then like, we both hung up, and like... Yeah I always tell my Mum I'm round Charlotte's house, she totally trusts me, and I actually go out and get pissed. Everyone says I'm well nice when I'm pissed, and like, yeah, that phone conversation with my Mum was so funny though...". And then she starts laughing, and looks at me and expects me to laugh, but I'm too busy being in a coma to notice, so she gets angry at me and asks annoying questions. When she isn't telling crap stories or repeating conversations, she is asking questions. "When's the last time you washed your hair Laura?", "Why do you like that weird Pop Will whatever band?", "Do you remember when you used to be really nice?", "Do you reckon you'll ever be normal again?" etc etc. She's always pretty damn rude to me, which pisses me off. She is so incredibly bitter about breaking up, and I don't see why it bothers her if she hates me so much. And she has such a problem with Alex, it's pretty amazing. She can literally spend hours bitching about him, even though there really isn't anything to bitch about. And she lies so much too, half the time I'm talking to her I have to humour her, because she is blatantly talking shit. There's something very wrong with her, I think she needs to see someone. I really wish I could just ignore her and totally cut her out of my life. She really is nothing but trouble, I just regret going out with her so much now. Right! Enough bitching about Gemma. She isn't that bad. Let's be more positive... I have an entire leopard print outfit now!!! Tis even cooler than the zebra outfit! AND I have a tidy room, most excellent indeed. Apparently I'm going to see some shitty Christian band tomorrow. That should be a good laugh. Or incredibly boring. One or the other. Damn, I can't believe I missed Gavin at R2C!! That would've been so fucking funny! Ah well, tis my own fault... Anyway, I think it's about time I stopped writing in this thing, perhaps I could do something useful instead. Like....................Play with selotape! Peace out xxx  PS I finally worked it out! Grass is a rather peculiar shade of blue, it would appear. How glad I am to make such a great discovery. PPS The grass is always bluer on the other side. PPPS Except in Winter, obviously, because I guess a lot of grass dies then, so it sort of loses its colour. Everything is grey in Winter. So, to summarise, the grass is always bluer on the other side in the summer. PPPPS But not reeeeeeally blue, like sky blue. This is a special kind of blue, PPPPPS The other side of what?
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well firstly, I didn't have time to check out the whole grass thing. But I will. Secondly, the exam was...interesting. Except halfway through I got really scared, because there was this plane going overhead, and I thought it was going to bomb us. Luckily, it didn't. Thirdly, today I met Gen. It was very cool to meet him, and he asked me to marry him. Actually, I'm lying. But I listened to PTV, which is kinda the same thing. Sort of. I'm so bored... Hence why I'm writing in this. It's quite useful for wasting time really. I'm going to Reading tomorrow, which is always good. If I don't buy any TG or PTV CDs, I will hang myself. Although I guess I could maybe forgive myself, depending on what I bought instead. If I bought, like, something really crap and stupid, then... Haha, that reminds me of when I bought a scourer in Camberley. I looked so cool wearing my scourer. I looked like a washing machine or something. Except I didn't look cool, coz I was hanging out with Nathan. In Camberley.  I feel a bit miserable tonight actually :( I saw Gemma today, which is fairly self-explanatory. And now I just feel sad and lonely... And also, reeeeally tired, coz I had less than 2 hours of sleep last night, which probably isn't enough. On the bright side, I got Gavin's e-mail address, which should be pretty hilarious. Apparently he came to R2C today, and they talked about suicide so he was spazzing out. Tis pretty annoying that I missed that, I coulda brought the camera. Wow, I've written loads in this. Tis a bit sad really... But it's quite therapeutic methinks. But maybe playing with the selotape will be more fun. Peace out xxx
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ...Grass isn't green at all. How peculiar! After I fail my English Lit paper tomorrow, and before Gemma comes over, I shall devote some time to studying its real colour. This is a momentous discovery indeed. Ah crap, tomorrow will be so humiliating. I wish I'd actually annotated my poems, instead of writing PWEI lyrics round the edge of them and 'editing' the pictures of the poets. And I wish I'd done at least one practise essay. Nevermind... It's impossible to fail, right? Bloody hell, it's 12 already, guess I'd better go. Stupid English... Peace out xxx
       
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Rule Number One - Pity is for losers. If you pity anybody, you will end up in terrible situations that you don't want to be in. Instead, try hatred. Remember that weak people aren't there to be helped, they're there to be despised. Rule Number Two - This is one of the most important rules - Do NOT, under ANY circumstances, develop emotional attachments to ANYBODY. Rules are made to be broken (except these ones), and the same seems to apply to hearts. If you are stupid enough to care about anybody, whatever happens is your own fault. It's not worth taking the risk. Rule Number Three - Everybody is lying except you. Your loved one tells you they love you? They're lying, retard! Your teacher tells you you're capable of better? Wrong! People only tell you things so they can manipulate you. Nobody tells the truth, except for you. You never, ever lie, and you are right about everything. Rule Number Four - You are a God, perfect and underrated, and society should recognise you as such. Anybody who doesn't totally idolise and worship you can go to hell. Rule Number Five - When referring to yourself, there is no such thing as a bad attitude. Everyone else's attitude is bad, yours is perfect.  Rule Number Six - Don't delude yourself. Your friends and family don't really care about you, they only want to hurt you. Don't even bother pretending otherwise, because they'll prove you wrong every day of your life. But remember, they are only jealous because you're not foolish enough to believe that people care about you. Rule Number Seven - Your idols will never hurt you. Rule Number Eight - The more you care about somebody, the less they will care about you. The less you care, the more they will pretend to care. Rule Number Nine - Always ignore Rule Number Nine. Rule Number Ten - Anybody who is stupid enough to break The Rules will live a meaningless, empty, ignorant life full of pathetic delusions and vacuous nonsense.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Uh...um...well...no. I can't really remember what I've been up to. But anyway, I'm very excited. On Thursday, I finish school and exams forever!! No more compulsory education!!!!!!! Amy and I have a great celebration planned... On Friday, we're going to Thorpe Park. On Saturday, we're going to Guildford, where I will get my nose pierced and Amy will get her ears pierced. And then I'm dying my hair purple. And on Sunday, we're going to Camden. That should all be very fun indeed. Tomorrow I have no exams, which is nice, so I'm going into town. And I was kind of thinking it might be a bit boring by myself, because I never was very independent, but now I'm seeing Scott, which is good. Scott said something very sweet today. He was asking what I think of him, so I told him, and then I asked the same thing, and I thought his reply was very kind. He said "i think your great, scary, but great, i think your intresting kinda hyperactive but generally realy cool to talk to, i think you got a great personality even though some people don't think so, i think your pretty and all in all a fantastic person". And despite the lack of capital letters and full stops and proper spelling, I was very flattered. It's very rare that anybody says anything nice about me. And so I agreed to see him tomorrow, which I guess ties in well with job-hunting. I might make up a fictional time I have to be home by though, because he never strikes me as being too fascinating. Oh and other slightly but not very interesting news is that I'm talking to Tom C again. But he's the only person I know who has even heard of Wumpscut, let alone likes them. And he actually agrees that Nazi techno is awesome, so I guess I'll carry on talking to him. Recently, I have been such a damn poser. I'm wearing sunglasses all the time!! But understand, these are the most amazing sunglasses EVER. Also, I have even been thinking about what to wear on the first day of college. First impressions count! But I have been doing other stuff too, like good stuff. Reading and stuff... And sleeping and eating, which is good for the health. And also... thinking about revision. OK, I just took a Zimovane, I'd better go now before I start talking crap.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I thought I should write an entry about the onion, seeing as the whole incident was rather humourous. Basically I have a horrendously bad sleeping pattern, which is reeeeeally inconvenient. So I have to take these sleeping pills... The fun part is, they seem to make me go a bit mad (as well as making me stagger a lot, hmmmm). And mostly I just talk nonsense, but last night was, in retrospect, pretty damn funny. We have these red onions in the kitchen, so I got out a plate and very, very carefully dismantles this onion. It seemed extremely important at the time, and I took it very seriously. My mother was the only person still up, and I don't remember this but apparently she asked what I was doing and I said I was eating an onion, and then I went on for ages about its great significance so she went upstairs and left me to it. Anyway, I obviously ended up with a plate of pieces of crappy old onion, but I honestly thought it was the most beautiful thing I'd ever seen. So beautiful, that... I had to do it again. I dismantled it differently this time, and ended up with these two pieces of onion which for some reason I decided were husband and wife. So I tore them apart, and put them on either side of the plate. But then I took them apart too, and there was a mini version of the wife inside her, so of course that was the baby. And then I reunited them all on the plate, which was so wonderful it nearly moved me to tears (I'd actually only just stopped crying, but that was because of the onion, not emotion). Anyhow, I then arranged it all very neatly, and took pictures. Equally fun is the sign I made to accompany my 'masterpiece' (I seriously did think it was a beautiful piece of art). In demented, scrawled handwriting it says: "DON'T TOUCH THIS  - It's my art Laura Why Hi hello Hello HELLO"  So of course when I got up the whole house stunk of onion. Yuck! Anyway, that's it really... Peace out xxx
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today Amy and I went to Reading, originally intending to shop for a while and then go to the cinema. Well the cinema thing didn't work out at all. We bought tickets, but we turned up late and there were no seats left! So we got refunds (after having spent about 10 minutes wandering round in the dark, much to everyone else's amusement). The more exciting part of the day was before that, though. We went past Supercuts!, and decided to get impulse haircuts. Which doesn't really sound that exciting, but it was so much fun! I guess my hair isn't really that much shorter now, but it still looks quite dramatic to me. And Amy now has a side fringe, which also looks awesome. Except my damn hairdresser was really bitchy, and DELIBERATELY covered me in hair. Ummmmm... I don't remember what I did yesterday. Hey, something just occurred to me. Why am I describing the details of my day on an online diary? It isn't interesting to anyone but me. Actually, it just isn't interesting to anyone. And does it really matter what I did today or yesterday? No. But on the other hand, it's quite fun to pretend it does matter, so I'll continue in that manner. Well I've fiiiiinally started to read The Republic, which is good, because I kept being too lazy and too busy with other stuff. Although I guess I should actually be reading my biology and maths textbooks... But never mind! I'll learn more from Plato than from whoever it is that writes the bloody textbooks. The thing that sucks is that I can't read for long without headaches and crap (maybe my eyes need testing?) and the dialogues are so damn long, I can't read an entire one at once. But I guess after the next 3 weeks, I'll have the whooooole summer!! Except that I reeeeeally need to get a job. And of course, I don't just want a job because I'm a greedy money-loving consumer. No, I want to feel that I'm contributing to the sustainment of this country's economy, and that I am earning myself a place in society, and that I have a responsibility of some kind. Or if I'm honest...I just want to buy all these CDs and records that I so desperately need. And weird impulse haircuts don't come for free, y'know. Hmmm... I guess that's all the mindless droning I have to spare for today. Peace out xxx
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So today, I had Amy over, and then Kaz and AL girl. It was pretty uneventful really. It's weird, I'm not getting up till like 3, so I don't really get any more time than when I was in school. It's so annoying, I still haven't done any revision. And I promised myself I would this half term, but it's so hard to make myself do it. I really just generally feel like I'm fucking things up for myself. It's like, I just feel like I'm never going to get anywhere in life. Oh God, and now I sound like a whiny emo loser! Also, I found out that on the back of my college letter, I should've have a letter from my personal tutor telling me which tutor group I'm in. And the fuckers left it out! So now we'll have to call the bloody college. Stupid stupid stupid. My parents have decided today to not go away after all, which is very annoying. I think it might help me if they'd just fuck off for a bit. Oh well, I guess it doesn't matter, because I'll be revising! Yes...Of course I will...Most definitely... Bloody exams. I wish I could just be smarter for a month. It's strange how much I've been seeing Kaz lately. I think it's because of this whole matchmaking thing. I don't really mind though, it's not half as bad as seeing Thee Evil One. I think Alex gets back home tomorrow, which is good, because although it isn't really that long since I last saw him, it feels like ages. I miiiiissss my lovely friendy! I don't miss Thee Evil One though... She's coming over on Thursday, I must cancel. That reminds me... She's been getting people to spy on me!!!!! What the hell is wrong with her? I'm really getting fed up of her and her psychopathic tendencies. Grrrrrrrrr!!!!!! On the bright side, I got a Genesis album today, and it's great =) Peace out xxx
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I went to Guildford on Tuesday, to check out all of the Charles Dodgson stuff, which was very fun indeed. I saw two Alice statues, Charles' old house, and his grave. The statues were beautiful, as were their locations. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The Chestnuts (Lewis Carroll's house) was nice, but there was some work going on there, so the noise pollution was a bit off-putting. I had to walk up a huge, steep old hill to get to Mount Cemetery, but it was well worth it. Dodo's grave was next to this lovely big tree, and although you can't see in the picture above, the sun was shining onto the white cross. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I took about a thousand pictures, so maybe I'll put them up here some other time. It was such a nice day out, though, especially since my Carroll obsession has been growing a lot lately. I'll probably start visiting those parts of Guildford a lot more. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          I kind of feel like I'm living in Limbo at the moment. This is probably the only time in my life where I'll never  have  to do anything. No school, no job, no family of my own, or even a girlfriend to keep me in check. It's very difficult to make myself do anything, and although I still enjoy seeing friends and stuff, things feel very weird.     I seem to be spending a lot of time lying in bed, playing all the albums I haven't heard in ages, which means my days are just this passing blur of Pink Floyd and King Crimson. I'm not even playing guitar (no band to practise for), I'm not reading much (too exhausting), and I have to remind myself to eat and sleep. I forget to wash my hair, forget to get dressed... I guess you could say I'm a bit of a mess really.     But it's not entirely my fault. Nobody seems to care much, and nobody is encouraging me to sort myself out. And I know I shouldn't expect them to notice, because I obviously don't tell them any of this, and I know I should be responsible for myself, but it isn't that easy. Well my parents do nag a bit - "Take your sleeping pills", "Get up before 2", "Go out and do something", but they don't really care that much. They have their own problems to worry about.     Wow, this all sounds very negative. Things could be much worse, you see. I just feel very lost, and I feel as separate from the physical world as ever. I'm stuck in my own bizarre little microcosm, and it's starting to feel a little stuffy. It'll get better with time.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I must say, I'm very glad I haven't done the teenage thing with this blog. Everybody else I know let's all their friends see theirs, and I'm glad I never did that, otherwise I'd have to censor what I say. I'm very pissed off with most people at the moment. The only two people I'm not angry with are Amy, Sarah and Julia. Everybody else can just go to hell, they're all a bunch of assholes. They're all shitty in their own unique ways - some are egotistic posers, some are selfish neurotics, some are stuck-up bastards... You get the point. The latest person to add to the list of the despised is Gemma. Or geema, hahahahaha. And yeah yeah, I know I already despised her for ages, but this time I'm actually finished with her, totally. I don't need her for anything anymore. I hate her so much it surprises even me, and it's funny because I don't think she even knows. Yesterday was meant to be my thing, and fair enough she paid to go too, but she completely ruined my day. I mean yeah, I still enjoyed it, and I felt much more comfortable there than I do with lots of straight people, but she made so much stuff very crappy. I didn't want to dance or anything, because she's just so...I don't know that there's a word for it. An essay would explain it but I can't be bothered. Sometimes I wanted to just sit and watch the main stage, which I thought was originally the plan, but she kept dragging me into the shitty tents to listen to the crap music that she likes. I missed all of the acts I wanted to see, which isn't exactly fair. When we actually did watch the main stage, she kept complaining and being her usual shitfest self. And if I didn't talk for a couple of minutes, I was being moody, and if I did talk I was being argumentative... There's no winning with that girl. When we were at Waterloo, something snapped in her and she just went crazy at me. She bitched non-stop for ages and ages, while I just had to stand there and take it. And I don't care when pikeys and people like that slag me off, because I'm used to it and they don't even know me, but I did care on this occasion because she does know me, and she said a lot of extremely hurtful things. And I tried not to pay much attention, which just didn't work. Anyway, when we were on the train she was still going, so I just fixed my eyes in one place and focused on not crying or thinking. And the dumb bitch was saying "Why won't you look at me? Oh, so you're in a mood with me now?" blah blah blah, while I was thinking 'No, you fucking prat, I just don't want to cry'. See I couldn't speak, 'cause I knew my voice would come out all weird. Anyway, eventually the tears just started pouring out, and I was really really crying, and I guess she felt guilty. She kept asking me to hug her and shit, because she probably didn't want to feel guilty all throughout her sleepover. I did in the end, which sucked. I shouldn't give in next time, she doesn't deserve it. At first I was worried about people noticing, and about making a scene, but I just thought what the fuck, and cried as much as I liked. Stupid geema then starts trying to convince me that I'm not a total shitfest, which really didn't even help. She starts blatantly lying, saying how much she likes and respects me, etc etc. It was such obvious bullshit. I checked on her online diary today, haha, which mostly consisted of bitching about me. So I was right, basically, she was bullshitting. And if I'm honest, the stuff she said was only half the reason I was crying. But let her feel guilty, she deserved it. Having had so many friends slag me off recently, I'd just had enough. And I know if I was reading this, I'd think 'Haha, I doubt it's all her friends that suck, it must be her'. Well maybe that's true, but it's kind of irrelevant because I can't just decide to be someone else. And I don't want to die until I finish my book, because that needs to be written. I can't rest in peace otherwise. Anyway, she e-mailed me today, it was about how we should still be friends, and all that shit. Well fuck off Gemma, I don't want or need 'friends' like you. Seriously though, my fucking patience is running thin. I actually think I'm going to end up dropping out of college because I'll be too filled with hate for everybody else there. I wish I had a writing career, the kind that lets you do nothing but write novels, and gives you lots of money. The kind hat lets you isolate yourself from the rest of humanity. Still, I had some real insight into the DT today, so my book is now going to be written, finally. Still thinking about the L-Room go. Well, I'd better go now, I need to remind my parents that I haven't eaten. I think they must be getting senile. Auf wiedersehen xxx
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>