<Blog>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

						
						   Mood: Furious  Secularism is an inadequate and incompetent word. Other day, watching a group of India's high profile people from various sections of the society, arguing about the true interpretation ('cause it doesn't seem to have its own true meaning!) of the word, i seed them fail miserably. Its quite obvious that people who have their own agenda and goal will never agree on something that is contrary to their basic ideology. You don't need a expert psychologist or psychiatrist to understand that.....  That said, shall we try to first establish the need / end result, of the notion "secularism". All this talk about secularism is the direct consequence of the carnage and trouble brewing between people from different ideologies. I deliberately did not say religion because language, caste, culture and even race are a equal reason for all this trouble.  What is that, the lofty minds had in mind, when they framed our constitution and made India a secular country?  1. Did they want the people of India to recognize and acknowledge the ideals of all religions and coexist happily? 2. Did they want the people of India to be a-religious and coexist happily?  If they had wanted the first... they, it seems did not grasp the fundamental concept of religion and people's psychology. They had underestimated or over trusted religion and its fanatic proponents. Did they not know that accepting all other ideologies is in truth, the dilution of ones faith?  Or is it like - i will believe my own faith, but for the sake of everybody's good, i will act as if i acknowledge all other faith.(which translates to- i am holy; you r an ass, though i wont tell you that...) Obviously this will not last long...one small spark and all this hidden and repressed contempt will burst out. Let us accept this simple reality, even though it is a slap in the face, can anybody define god, religion and faith from a universal point of view and getaway with it without objection?. can everybody change his ideology, (which he believes like a fanatic) is the truth, even if it is cannibalism? Fanatic ideology is the part where man chose to remain an animal.  So... secularism is, for the religious, a euphemism to saying "you don't cross my way and i will not cross yours, for heavens sake!" for others it is a dilution of faith.  And the problems arise because there are more people of the former than the later, today. if you think, you can keep your faith strong and intact and also acknowledge whole hearted the truth and essence of other religion...please. don't deceive yourself again and again.  If you argue that all religions say to love everybody and it is those half baked people who fight. I accept, with the warning that, 99.9 percent of people are half-baked, then. For, it also says cows are holy and you should not kill it, and your neighbor has it for his dinner everyday. What do you do?   If you accept it you have diluted your faith, if you fight him you are a fanatic. Dilution of faith and its effects are.... much lesser considering that, the faith can be put into a less harmful sphere of bonding...but alas man always trusts what he does not see more than what he sees. It is true that a person will trust the unknown good rather than the supposed evil. he will trust god to any human any day, at least god is not supposed to harm you.  What if your parents taught you that you should kill your first child to please the god and get the blessings for the family and the society? What if the society around you acknowledged that as righteous? What if you were told that the sacrificed child was in fact god's child and that it is right that it should reach him soon? If you are pious and orthodox, you would do it, without guilt and celebrate the murder of your own child. If you suddenly feel that it is meaningless because no one is sure what happens after death, except the quack who calls himself the priest, you will talk about the human right to live and the horror of killing a just born baby.....and you will be branded as atheist, an outlaw and even be ostracized from the society...how much ever you shout no one will hear. What we are talking here is faith too, and such killings are not exaggerations, as even now we do have human sacrifices in the name of god. Take an analogy of a cultural faith- sati. Today sati is banned by the state, after making people realize the stupidity of it. That means there has been a dilution of faith, right? So all those woman are outlaws who don't do sati, among the orthodox. But as a modern (that is what some people. call themselves) man and maybe from a different faith, you might accept this correction in culture as good.   How much more modern do you need to get before realizing that cow slaughter (vegetarians pardon me) is not a sin which is going to anger the god and that you should wipe out those who think otherwise. How much more modern do you need to get before realizing that the true essence of religion is to ONLY ensure peace and to provide a guideline for a trouble free society.  How much more modern do you need to get before realizing that ultimately it is your fellowmen who are providing you your food, saving you from illness, creating wealth and also doing crime, and that there is no invisible entity governing the lives of the billions of humans on this earth.  That is the question.... how much more modern??? How much more time and more importantly how many more lives? If you can tell me how much more time you need then i can tell you when the world will be totally safe ......... and secular, if you please..  

						
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   As of this writing, the gulf war II has begun.   	I'd like to compare the world nations to a children (surely, you jest if you say it is not an appropriate comparison! ). I see america as a rich but insecure child (Rich - no doubts abt. that ; insecure - because it had taken a beating recently -sept 11). Now it wants itself to be safe using its might. This, against the opinion of people allround the world. Now imagine the other several poor children (third world - as it is called) , who have squabbles among themselves.  They have also been subject to the extremes of terrorist acts. They have also taken several beatings in the past. India, for instance, has been a victim several times and whenever the tension with its neighbor reaches critical state, we had uncle sam making peace talks. But now the uncle is crying foul. It is like only uncle sam knows where the root cause of all trouble lies !   	 I hope the readers know of the middle east mess and its cause.(That is a entire disscusion in itself). Going by history, i think, by the time america feels secure in this world . . . . . . very little would have been left of it. Hey! u might say- 'survival of the fittest'.  Unfortunately, all our lives have been reduced to just that.  	If america wants, like how bush spoke before the war - to fight this war so that we dont have to fight it again in our cities with firefighters.; then, sorry America  this war is not the solution. What will be result of the war is obvious to all. Not the victory of america, but the birth of a new generation of terrorists. Yes.  already after the Taliban war, we lost hold of bin laden. Now he is safely tucked somewhere, forming another generation of terorists, most possibly from the orphans of the people we killed in the preceding war.  	Now it is sadam's time...... much depends on what america has in store for iraq and its own agenda after the war.     the war might be won, but the battles will be fought.   forever... and it will be difficult to win that one because it will be fought in our backyard.... and we will not know who the enemy is ..... and we will be searching for the next scapegoat.  my best wishes, and load of luck to all ! --------------------------------------------------- (follow up...)  tim, glad that you got to agree about the the most vital fallout of this war - 'new generation of terrorists'.  --  I never condone war; however, since our --  coutry has chosen to force I must stand in support instead of protest.  The sad truth is that nobody has any other option. Protest - is the maximum, we ordinary people can do, to show our detest, 1. in the hope that our voices might reach those who matter. 2. to tell the innocent people under threat that there are atleast some souls around the world, who do understand their plight.    what i feel is that you think war is an 'extension of state policy'.  That was the thought prevalant at the dark ages of europe. If it is still popular.... we have reached nowwhere in terms of civilization.  I do think and hope saddam is gone by the end of the war but, I also thought and hoped that bin laden would be gone, sometime back. ugh..  war is not what we see on tv and say  tch.. And it is definitely not something to be supported because it has begun. i think you will agree that all of us have only one life, and every one is entitled to think that it is meaningful.  hey btw, i can assure you something, the end of the world is not near.... atleast as long as we protest and keep the ray of hope shining for the millions who are and will be affected by war.  

						
</post>

<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

						
						   Mood: Pensive  .We do what we do, to do something for us. .Even those that we do for others, is for the intrinsic satisfaction that we get by the "feel-good" factor that comes with it. .Accepting the above is not a pessimistic attitude. .Once we accept that fact we all fall under a common denominator. .How much physical gain you want and how much spiritual/mental gain you want, are the main constituents of one's character. .What one wants is so unique and varied that all of us are unique. .Money has become a universally accepted "credit card"(!), that most of our wants are determined by it and we aspire mostly not in terms of our wants but in terms of money. .This misleads us into thinking that when we have more money our wants are satisfied. .This explains the classic "what have i done all my life earning this money?" syndrome, because at the end of the day we realise that somewhere down the line we forgot our wants in the search for the means to satisfy our wants. .We need to keep reminding ourselves where we are going 'cause we tend to forget in our hurry where we are going. .Since the destination is our choice, we can stop anywhere and retire. .But if our destination is fixed strongly and we stop in the middle our journey seems incomplete. .Most people let others choose the destination for them. .Individuality is the highest form of religion if one realises it truly. .Life is cruel - because it is a sexually transmitted disease.  

						
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    "I have forgotten this before"  It happens to us all at one time or another: deja vu, that uncanny feeling of having experienced something before but being unable to recall exactly when or where. The term comes from the French for "already seen," and is defined by psychiatrists as "any subjectively inappropriate impression of familiarity of a present experience with an undefined past." But that clinical description hardly does justice to the eerie sense of mystery and unease we feel during such an episode of inexplicable recognition. ~ The Times ~ 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    	 		 		 To start at the begining... 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink vandiyathevan 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink nlym .			 		 	   

						
</post>



</Blog>