<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        You can call me jesus christ superstar, there are a dozen roses simple reasons and no answers whatsoever.   The yellow road paved with indescriminate illusions to your destination, hardly subtle or surprising.   The games were starting and frightning they were, filled with boundless energy and an all consuming fear, a terror with many a name yet no substance. The opening gambits were foolhardy and shameful yet still strangely enthralling and most entertaining.    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I finished the grapes of wrath, it was quite a good read, interesting philosophy and politics. Although the book, in my not so humble opinion, suffered from the all too clever "leave it to the readers imagination" ending. If I wanted to imagine a story why would I waste my money on a fucking book?   I'm still at war with certain unnamed factions, it's a pitifully pathetic and childish war but I feel it to be necessary. Although hostilities with these factions are not unheard-of, this particular instance seems rather more prolonged and less susceptible to an amicable or early conclusion.   The main problem is that war was declared against all factions simultaneously, meaning that a third party mediator can't be used to build a bridge between the warring factions. Also external forces that usually seek to create harmony within the group seem unwilling interfere in this conflict. Finally, I am usually the person who offers to mend any broken fences and as I'm currently in a less than positive state of mind as well as feeling that I had just cause for the commencement of hostilities, there seems to be no one else willing to take that crucial first step.
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I'm in the middle of reading grapes of wrath, which is a pretty decent book even if it is kinda slow paced. It has lots of interesting observations, reminds me a bit of george orwell but less depressing.   The fear is getting to be monumental, it makes it harder to breath, to think, just to be... This cant be unusual, this fear that spreads like posion and grips with the presistence of quicksand. What makes it ever more terrible, is that there really is nothing to fear other than the "fear", just an insane void waiting to pull you into its less than loving embrace. I need, I must, I will learn to dull the senses, to control their errant wanderings into uncharted unfathomable space.  FOCUS. I just need to focus.    Here is the quote that I never promised you:   "...fear the time when Manself will not suffer and die for a concept, for this one quality is the foundation of Manself, and this one quality is man, distinctive in the universe."   I fear apathy has overcome me once more, I must bid you farewell dear fictional reader.  
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Boredom, I think that more than anything else is most likely to wipe out humanity. Everything seems to be tailored to stave of that terrible, unspeakable thing that is at the root of all insanity, all madness. Boredom, all that we do, all the many terrible and good things that we do,&nbsp;are simply for a little bit of entertainment, a little bit of joy to escape from the incessant wail of a Mind, that has simply outgrown its humble origins.   Of course it could very well &nbsp;just be me; I have been so bored for so long its almost become a way of life, I would sell my soul ten times over for some relief from this purgatory, this prison of&nbsp; my own making, this terrible meaningless pitiful existence. Anything to quench the never ending wail of a helpless Mind, that seeks questions that can't be answered, meaning that was never intended.   Oh ye gods have mercy on my soul....     
</post>


</Blog>