<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is me enjoying my vacation in Chicago back in 2002. Well my favorite team in ice hockey is the Detroit Red Wings and well you see those nice blue shades, i gave it to my cousin the next year. The Michael Jordan i just gave it away hehehe. Basically im not really a very trendy person. For me what's important is person inside and not the way the person looks. "DON'T JUDGE THE BOOK BY ITS COVER!"&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
                    Green Arrow "You make me sick! What kind of a man are you? The whole city needs your help,not just the Nice Section!". Hal Jordan, Green Lantern replied "Get off your horse Oliver! I'm helping who i can, as i can order of their innocence in these fires! Those slugs downtown want to burn their homes, i'm not going to let innocent people suffer for it!". "You sound just like the lily-white Fat cats who've been straggling donwtown to death! They can't be left to die just because their protests got out of hand!". Green Arrow answered while pointing an arrow towards Hal whil replying meekly and helping innocent bystanders from the inferno of the city "You saw them Ollie! Heard what they said to me! What they accused me of! They started those fires! Started the mob violence, adn if they don't want me there--FINE!". Shooting the sleeping gas arrow towards Hal Green Arrow answers "You're not listening you dope!" and hal while catching the arrow and instantly blows in front of his face "More violence! No wonder you love these people--You hypocr--Hggk!" Green Arrow now helping Hal to his knees says "They've been trained to hate people like you and me through all the abuse this city's given them! Sorry they hurt your feelings but GET OVER IT!". Hal replies "They brought this on themselves. WHY SHOULD I HELP?" Now enters Tom Kamalku Green Lantern's sidekick and replies softly and directly "Because you're GREEN LANTERN!!! Because Green Lantern would never hold a mistake against somebody who needed his help!". Hal freezes and looks towards Tom who added "The fires are getting worse." Immediately Green Lantern summons his ring to make thousands of buckets and gets water over the sea to put out the fire while saying "Not for long, they're not.  Coast City will be saved today. All of it!"                        Well this was one of the most appealing and owe inspiring contexts i've read in the comic book LEGACY: The last Will and Testament of Hal Jordan written by Joe Kelly in 2001 published by DC comics. My tears instantly fell from my eyes the first time i read this book. I cried not because never in my life would i have the powers of Green Lantern has, but the point and somewhat the message this particular 3 page scene is giving to us was really true. Let's face it in all of us people, there is a hero in us in some ways. People tend to forget that in some ways, big or even little ways we can contribute in helping for the improvement of the lifestyle of people in these world. Giving donations, helping people with their problems, giving advices, being a good example, and many more. In short let them be inspired! We have the power, all of us! Yet somewhat I still think our world still has a long ways to go. People with power in governments instead of helping the less fortunate ones they tend to corrupt the money of the country for their own selfish needs. People resorting to violence in settling the score on some enemies. The cycle will go on and on, and until some of us realize these nistakes, we will be still where we are right now. War among ourselves and peace still very far away from our grasps. Lifestyle of poor people are still the same. And yet i still believe there is still hope. As what they say "the only constant thing in these world is change". Change for the better or worse? A small sample of a good change towards other people can spread like forrest fire in an instant. As long as no one relenquishes it. Well kidding aside a small thing can touch other people and hopefully it will become bigger and bigger until all of us people realize, we are a small world after all, and if improvement and peace should be given a chance we should start with ourselves helping others with the best way we can. As i said, its either you're a member of the Green Lantern Corps or not? What will it be?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                Well nowadays you see in the news when you turn on your tv sets late at night, mostly their reports for the day are either violence, and some even more violence. People think that by resorting to these ways they can achieve their goals in life. But isn't this wrong? I don't know about you but if i can remember correctly when i was still a kid and watched early mornings shows like Super-Book and Flying House, aren't these signs that we may be nearing the end of the world as we may know it. War, violence, immorality, killings, nature's destructive powers, are now prevailent in our days now. Movies being made now are much more connected with the with these realities in which subconsciously is trying to bring a message to the people that if we do not change the way we live our lives right now, the end is really near. It's already knocking at our door for some time now. But still some movies and other form of media communications like tv try to show inspirational movies. Movies like recently Bruce Almighty and my favorite The Passion of the Christ. These movies try to give us a positive message that there is still hope of mankind and that God is always there for us, its up to us if we will embrace Him with open arms or not.               After having said that i would like to go to the message i want to point out to all of us. Basically right now, the movie industry are making a lot of investments on superhero movies. Comic book characters are being made to life in films. Their popularity have really risen above any expectation and the comic book medium has even been popular to a lot of people. Young and old alike. What i'm trying to point here is that admist all the violence and sufferings that is happening in our world, people try to look up on icons, someone they want to believe in, someone who could give them hope in their lives, their superheroes. And what better superhero is there than the real people depicted in the bible. Jesus Christ the true superhero. Our God Almighty. Its just a vague suggestion but its a way better alternative to the violent and adult related storyline we have in our comics today. Great writers and artists should give this a little chance. Make an on going series making the bible stories in our modern day comics. It will be a sight for sore eyes for avid fans who likes the art of pencillers like Jim Lee, Mark Silvestri, Alex Ross to name a few, and the writings of Jeph Loeb, Stan Lee, and Brian Michael Bendis for that matter. It can be successful if made the right way plus its a good way to give the people the chance to discover the Holy teachings of God in the Holy Bible. Well its kinda weird having these ideas but its worth a try. Any kind medium to just and make a difference in this world is a good thing for me.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Grass Valley, Sacramento. April of 2003. Well i was here because i helped my newly found friend in San Francisco, which was my original destination, to locate her hospital she was planning to work someday. This was the first time i went to the States all alone, i mean i stayed in California for days in a hotel all by myself until i met my nursing friend 5 days after. Had also a great time sight seeing and discovering the beauty of the place, and more importantly having the greatest freedom of all for the very first time. Wooohoooo!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is me having a diner in Boston Lobster Feast in Orlando Florida with my uncle back in 2002. I had the best time back there, well kinda having been to Universal Studio for the first time, having seen Marvel Comic book attractions back there and many others. I'm kinda dark skinned in the picture because sad to say i was walking all day long for 3 days i stayed there under the scorching heat of the sun. Well it was worth the effort, i did lose a couple of pounds.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                  Well basically i'm a part time local comic book writer, and having read some and collecting comic books from popular foreign comic book publishing like Marvel, DC and Image i somewhat came up with my very own, up to my own knowledge of the subject matter, unique storylines for some popular comic book superhero characters.              First of all is the Dark Knight himself, BATMAN. Well if you are reading his line of comics, me well i have a collection of trade paper back comics of his, you may encounter storylines like him having broken his back and left for suspended animation for sometime but eventually came back a year after when sales of his comics went down dramatically when the storyline was about the new BATMAN he appointed to take his place. Another storyline is that of having a virus plague Gotham City. Then there was rebuilding the whole Gotham city after it went to ruins when it had an earthquake. Then BATMAN, aka Bruce Wayne became a fugitive when he was framed for the murder of his girlfriend. Another was that a long time friend of his became one his dealiest enemy. All this storylines was already been made and they have all the same conclusion, BATMAN always won in the end and he was still, basically all his life, a very rich person. My own unique storyline is that what if the Wayne enterpises went bankrupt and eventually Bruce had to give up all his belongings and even to the point of stopping from doing his job as BATMAN because of lack of funds. Wouldn't it be a walk in the park for the villains? I know there are a lot of flaws in these but still its a good concept.             Next is that of the Fantastic Four, one of my favorite comic books. My unique storyline here is that, well we all now that the heart and soul of the FF team is Reed Richards. The genius behind all the machineries they. Their leader, the Plasticman of Marvel comics. His wife Susan Richards, aka Invisible Woman. Her brother Johnny Storm, aka Human Torch, and finally Ben Grimm, aka The Thing, the rock hard solid behemoth of the team comprises the whole Fantastic Four. Well i just gave a brief description of their team, some of them i need not to describe as with their names you could already know their abilities. Now here's my concept what if Reed Richards went insane because of a successful plot by Dr. Doom, their arch enemy, against him. Who would lead the team to victory and who would eventually defeat Dr. Doom if your leader is already useless and a big hindrance to your team?           Ah well i did say some, well about 2 concepts but the point here is how did i come up with this concepts? Well for beginners let's just say place your frame of mind in a way of having ideas in "The WHAT IF SCENARIOS?". You get what i mean folks? Basically its coming up with plots or storylines with the what if this thing or that thing happens concepts. Like what if Captain America never believed anymore in the American dream, to the point he is now killing people and is working for the mob? In short he becomes a villian? Another one is what if Jean Grey married another X-man besides her two lovers wolverine and Cyclops, let's say Iceman? What you think will happen to the whole team and what will be their reaction? What if the New Green Lantern had the choice to leave behind his duty being a Guardian forever to save the life of his girlfriend and the countless people of New York?           These simple plot lines are the starting points for all people, beginners in the genre of comic book storytelling. I know its easy at start but wait until you submit your concepts to the editor, that's where the fireworks start coming. Trust me, at first you should accept every mistake you made and all the advices they tell you to refurnish your storyline. Eventually after a couple of returns and edits, hopefully you'll get the right concepts and the storylines editors would like to have for that character. Try and try until you succeed. That's a good motto for me, it really works to tell you frankly. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                  The title of this article says it all. My whole life has been a combination of ups and downs. Basically all of us people have this same kind of feeling. Not a soul in this world could have not felt this kind of life before, and if ever the person says he or she hasn't it's obvious their lying!               Trials and obstacles always come in our lives and it depends on us how we can handle them. Whether you be a rich or poor person, handsome or ugly, these things will eventually come and disturb us with our everday life. I was once a medicine student. Well one thing is for sure that i could say to you, and this is a fact, if you don't like what you are doing, you'll never ever be successful in it because your heart wasn't into it. Your dreams are not in it. For me, my med school years where both the best and worst part of my life. The best because i had the chance for the first time in life to live away from home. To have my own time and to do whatever i wanted to do. And basically because i was somewhat forced to take up medicine by my parents it's kinda obvious what i did back then. Absences were very frequent and going out in malls, night bars and casino was very often. I would sometimes go back to my dorm with the sun already shining. And to think i still passed my tests and still made it to second year. God really works in mysterious ways. But still time catches up with you, let's say in context the law of averages will eventually come into place. My lifestyle at first was really bad and well basically i had given up trying to pass some subjects and well i just gave up. Kinda bad because i failed my parents, it was the first time in all my life i failed to acomplish something. It was really one of the worst part of my life. The dark days was already coming...               And yet i didn't give up. My friend there who is now a junior intern once told me, "Jun always remember not all the time we are on top of the world, sometimes the worst things comes into play. Always remember that its not how many times you fall down, its how many times you get up." So i was there beside him remembering those exact words, 2 years later am already starting my master's degree in arts, and hopefully with the help  and support from my friends, relatives, loved ones and God, i can finish this course and become a successful comic book writer in the future. Follow your dream, as long as your happy with what your doing, you'll do fine. My friend was right with those sayings. So as a conclusion, its really up to us to what will happen when trials and obstacles come into our lives. Its like what the basketball analyst once said, the ball is round sometimes your on top, sometimes your down. Wouldn't you agree?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                  As was having a conversation with my gf yesterday about the great empires that have ruled and controlled many countries during their time. Well its kinda obvious right now who are the dominating nations ruling us, the US and UK. We may call them the anglo-american powers. But comparing them to the previous world powers namely Egypt, Persia, Babylonia, Greece and Rome to name a few, basically they still have a long way to go when it comes to the time of rule they have in our world. But enough about that, what really was the focus of our conversation was that "What if we had the power to change time, well having a time machine what period of time would you like to be in?".               First and foremost my gf is a very religious person and me somewhat having been a sacristan in our church for quite sometime right now. So my first answer was that if its my choice i'd rather go back in time, to the time of Jesus and somewhat bring a stop to His crucifixion. Basically for me having the time machine is like having the chance and the ability to go back from time to time not only by yourself, hey why not bring the whole artillary. Hehehe....kinda weird but i do like things to go my way, and if its going my way, its got to be the easiest way. And in having to try to accomplish my first goal to stop Jesus from dying, i would have to conquer the world power during his time which is Rome. And having the right machinery, personnel and artillery well basically i could be king in that nation in no time. Jesus would have been saved and everybody happy. Easy isn't it? But remember what's written in the Bible has already been foretold and should happen said my gf so the scary thing that will happen there is that even though i maybe the King during that time, wouldn't Jesus approach me and tell me right in front of my face "I know who you are, I know where you came from. You are not from this time. And you know what is the thing for you to do..." I told you i'm somewhat of a religious person and having thought of that i had goosebumps all over my body. So  the next thing i did was change the timeline. Hmmmm....the best timeline should be the time after the whole bible was written. That's the best for me so that what's written in the Holy Book should be as it is.                So end of story i will rule during that time, but....it went also to my mind, i have the time machine, why waste time in conquering only a single time period where you can rule for the rest of your life. How is that? Well for me it's kinda tricky but fun though. i would rule only for a year during that time i'll assign a designated person to rule in my absence and i will fast forward to a couple hundred years to see my progress. i can go back any time i want so long as there is consistency in my rule and so to check if my hired servant is doing his job. I may age a year or two but still for the people during the times i conquer i maybe considered a living legend. An immortal. Nice isn't but we should snap back to reality and remember that tampering with time will cause a great disturbance in future generations and in the first place we may never in all possible ways have the ability to make a time machine. And if ever hopefully it wouldn't be the end of the world. So for now it's really nice to sit back, relax think for a moment and ask yourself that same question, "Of i had the time machine what time period would i have conquered?" 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>