<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It just tickles me pink.  Here I am bitching about how much I hate Walmart and Costco and at the top of my blog lies an advertisement for Costco and Walmart, who are probably sponsors no less.  Corporate whores.  I suppose I'm biting the hand that feeds me.  Well care loads.  Walmart can still eat it.      
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is an actual testimonial of a conversation that took place between two student assistants somewhere in an office at the local state university in San Diego, California.  Troy*:  "What are you reading?" Sydney*:  "The Teachings of Don Juan." Troy:  "What's it about?" Sydney:  "It's about a Yaqui Indian from Sonora who takes a young man under his wing as his apprentice on a spiritual path in search of personal power and a deeper truth.  It's pretty good.  You should read it." Troy:  "No thanks.  I don't like Indians." Sydney:  (at a momentary loss for words) "You don't like Indians." Troy:  "No, I'm not really into that whole western frontier stuff" Sydney:  "This isn't about cowboys and Indians.  It's about a Yaqui man who lives in Arizona during the sixties." Troy:  "I still don't want to read the book."  later that day....  Marciela*:  "I'm having trouble trying to find someone with the right availability to fill the receptionist position.  The only people that seem to be applying are of Indian decent.  I wonder why?"  Sydney:  "Probably because the job posting board is in the engineering department.  I've noticed that a lot of Indians are engineering majors.  (Trying her best to be PC) Not to generalize or anything."  Edna*:  "It's true.  There's an upscale neighborhood up north that is densely populated by Indian people who are all primarily engineers."  Troy:  "I've never met an attractive Indian."  Marciela:  "Most people would just think about something like that.  But only Troy would just go ahead and say it."  *-some names have been changed to ensure the privacy of those involved due to the sensitive nature of this topic  **************************  Though some of you might be slightly horrified by what you just read, in a twisted way it's somewhat funny.  There really isn't a moral to this story, which actually happened.  This is more of a tribute to my old job, from which I was fired.  You see, I was a bit of a loose cannon; a real spark plug, as opposed to Troy* who was a real butt plug, and it cost me my job.  Luckily for me, I've found a new job.  But wouldn't you know it, Troy continues to work there.  Well God bless America.  In parting I say, so long, little office located at the local state university in San Diego, California.  So long Troy, you jackass.  You won't be missed.        
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took my grandma to Costco today.  And to the Bodega. Oh yeah and to Save A Lot too.  As if Costco on a Sunday isn't already hell on earth.  Ok I'm sorry, that's an exaggeration.  Walmart on a Sunday (don't ever go to Walmart again btw) is hell on earth.  Walmart  on any given day  is hell on earth actually.  Yep, there's nothing better than topping off a few treacherous hours at Costco with a couple more trips to other supermarkets for a particular item that wasn't available or suitable from Costco.  That's always fun.  Dealing with situations that include overcrowding can be particularly frustrating.  That's my beef with Costco.  I didn't exactly dig the vibes I got at Save A Lot, either.  The misery just hangs in there like a horrible stench; so thick you could cut it with a knife.  Once I almost slipped and ate shit on some cow blood that was spilled on the floor in Save A Lot.  It was from a package of beef in the meat section.  I don't think they cared either, because they didn't clean it up and I know they saw it.  You might not know this, but they actually have a section in the back corner of the store that is a "clearance section" of sorts, where they sell packages of opened or damaged food at discounted prices.  You know, you have a box of ho-ho's with a couple missing; they're still good though...that's the thing, most stores would throw an item like this away but not these guys.  They have some good deals though.  I must give them that.  Anyhow, that's why I avoid grocery shopping like the plague.  I loathe grocery shopping.  Although, I like Trader Joes.  They don't have a Trader Joes in Chula Vista.  I loathe Chula Vista.             
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is it a cultural thing or are all humans inherently antisocial?  You've experienced it, you're walking along minding your own biz and you spot someone you once knew, or kind of know, went to school with, whatever.  Point is you know them.  You may not know their life story, but they're a notch above the average passerby.  So how come you both walk by each other without saying a word, pretending not to see each other?  It's a cute little game we play; you stare at the ground and they try really hard to look preoccupied, straining to find that someone who really isn't there until you pass each other, for fear you may ( gasp ) make eye contact.  Then you might even have to say hi to them.  That would be the worst case scenario.  Not only is it rude, but it's so darn awkward too.  I say it would be better to just say hello.  It takes way more energy to go out of your way to avoid the person.  Why not just smile and say, "Hi, how's it going?"  You don't have to have an hour long heart to heart with them, just keep walking.    I mean it's one thing if that person really doesn't see you or you appear busy and they don't want to bother you.  Aside from that, people who pretend not to see you are lame-O.  There's this biatch that I always see at the gym who I was friends with in high school, whom I haven't spoken with since, who does the whole "I don't know you anymore" routine.  How self involved can one be?  Anyone who thinks they are too good to acknowledge another human being is seriously confused about their shit and the fact that it stinks too.  It doesn't mean you have to be phony about it either, just polite.  Just be polite.  Is that so hard?  Well biatch at the gym, is it?!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently saw the movie, Saved!, which I found to be quite entertaining and humorous.  This may come as no surprise, since I already made my disdain for organized religion known.  What really struck me though, were the previews.  Man, has the movie industry continued to sink to new lows.  What a bunch of crap we have coming to a theatre near us.  These new movies include a lot of overly-dramatic pseudo soul searching and recycled themes.  I mean how many Victorian era themed movies do we need to see?    The old, "simultaneously flash a bunch of images in the most rapid manner possible" method is widely popular on the big screen, but that doesn't necessarily make the movie appear to be less sucky.  I suppose all those enticing images are intended to evoke some kind of emotion, but NAY.  I'm not fooled.  No siree.  I know I'm not the only one either.    A lot of these new movies seem to be composed of a lot of presentation, but no substance.  I know this isn't a ground breaking discovery considering that's the basis of pop culture, but it's just such a travesty when considering the money that's spent doing these films.  Who approves some of these flicks?  For instance, I saw the previews for one that was particularly awful; Will Smith leads the battle against robots gone berserk.  Wtf.  Robots?  Will Smith, you are a tool.  I don't respect you.  I want you to know that.    Summing up the robot gone bad movie would go something like: bad plot, bad acting, plenty of action, great special effects.  Empty entertainment, that's what that is.  Kind of like empty calories.  Those special effects must have cost a pretty penny too.  What a waste of money.  On top of that, I bet that navel gazer Will Smith got paid lots of money.  That makes me boil.  Which brings me to my next point, why do actors get paid so friggin' much?  Why do athletes get paid so much?  The entertainment industry as a whole gets paid way too much.  This ties into the distribution of wealth being grossly disproportionate as a whole.  People with more important roles in our society who contribute to a greater cause don't get paid squat, yet cokeheads like Ben Affleck have a summer home in Georgia and a Manhattan penthouse and yada yada yada.  It just aint right.    How can this be explained?  The water-diamond paradox.  How is it that water, a resource which we cannot live without costs a dollar per bottle and a diamond, which we can go a lifetime without, costs thousands?  Scarcity has a lot to do with it, since water is far more abundant than diamonds, as you probably know.  Perhaps this may not fully explain why actors get paid more, because they certainly aren't rare.  They come a dime a dozen, in LA at least.  One thing does hold true in regards to the water-diamond paradox however; most of the actors and celebrities out there, despite their net value, we definitely  can  go a lifetime without.       
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The other day my mom came into my room and asked me if I could come downstairs and watch my sisters baby while she went and picked up her other two grandkids at school.  This was something that would only take about 20 minutes max, but those 20 minutes were pretty hellatious, let me tell you.  Picture scraping feces out of the crevices of a screaming child's rear, which was pretty much what my little babysitting adventure entailed.  This made me wonder why so many people longingly aspired to have children.  Why?  Why do people want to have kids so bad?  I know there's benefits to having children, but there's also a good chance that your kids will hate you no matter what.  Scraping feces out of the crevices of my children's asses does not necessarily mean that they won't resent me in the end.  If that's the case, then where do I sign up?  And to think people keep popping out those suckers like they're going out of style.  Don't get me wrong, I am not a child hater.  Kids are great; I want kids someday.  What I really hate is the people who have kids that are not fit to.  Some people just shouldn't breed.  But it's the people that shouldn't breed that happen to be the ones that breed the most.  Like my sister for instance.  She's a sucky mother, which is ironic because she has three kids.  They are always sick, aren't fully potty trained and were pretty much raised by the t.v.  Why deal with the kids when you can just pop in some Disney?  Disney is crack for kids by the way.  The kids can't read for shit, but they WILL recite  The Emperor's New Groove  to you word for word.  Then those kids grow up to be retards like their parents.  And the cycle continues.  It isn't their fault.  But it's not mine either and I'm paying for it.  We all are.  The population is exploding as it is, we don't need more useless human beings around taking up our precious oxygen.  The philosophy on having children should be comparative to that of obtaining a drivers license; it's not a right, it's a priveledge.    Not too shabby of an idea, eh?  Competency tests would be required prior to engaging in procreation.  Those who pass can freely have children and those who don't can have, for instance...a gold fish perhaps.  They would be free to retake the competency test and their progress on caring for a gold fish would be observed by the people from social services.  Then if they improve they can upgrade to a mammal.  And so on and so forth.  That would make the potential creators of pathetic human beings think twice about, well, creating pathetic human beings.  That or just sterilize everyone.  Whatever's easier.             
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of life's biggest problems.  It seems to seep its way into every arena.  Even academia.  The university system is inherently evil nowadays.  Well, I suppose it's always been inherently evil.  It used to shut out minorities and women in the past and  it probably still does.  It's becoming more of a profit making scheme than anything; a very lucrative business.  It's a darn shame though.  We're paying quite a chunk of change for it...take a look at the skyrocket in tuition, out of state fees and private school costs.  And what exactly is the difference between private college and state college, besides the price tag?  Why is private school much more expensive?  I've got a friend $100K in the hole because of private school tuition.  Is she worried about finding a job?  Absolutely.  I don't think she should be feeling that way.  At that amount of tuition she paid, there should be an included guarantee of employment upon graduation.  Doesn't that sound fair?  Nevermind.  That's a stupid question, I'm sorry I asked it.  I will say though, that private school kids are not guaranteed success with the amount they shell out, but I'm sure they're receiving better treatment.  State schools are so overcrowded since not everyone can afford or is not willing to borrow money for private school (rich getting richer, poor getting poorer) so that pretty much means special treatment is out of the question.  My school is a dog-eat-dog world because of high demand and low supply.  Administrative attitudes are so impersonal and cold.  If you come to them with a problem, their way of solving it is to redirect you somewhere else.  There are actually two main phone numbers to the school which everyone gets filtered through and if you listen carefully, each will tell you to call the other number for help.  I see students AND teachers around me getting screwed over all the time.  For example, some fee increase proposals and ideas are put out to the student body as a choice, in the form of a popular vote.  Majority rules, end of story.  However this year, the president of our school decided to overturn a vote for NO increase on a fee that would contribute towards the budget for the athletic department.  Hello, uh, I didn't think that was allowed.  Though I suppose since he  is  the president he has that power, because he is  God himself  lest you forget.  It's also a little uncanny that he chose to overturn a rejected fee increase for the athletic department of all departments.  Why not overturn a rejected fee increase for the art department or something we're actually good at, because it is my understanding that my school sucks at sports.  It's not that the athletes have it bad either; I've seen their weight room and it's not too shabby.  Wanna know why this happened?   Corruption , that's why.  Pressure from the athletic department, a payoff perhaps (these are all just theories, not all theories pan out).  A vicious cycle.  But I firmly believe that the people will prevail.  I still hold on to my copy of the "Kiss My Aztec" as hope, which is a mock rendition of "The Daily Aztec", our school newspaper.  A handful of censorship bandits pulled the greatest stunt and handed out oodles of this literary masterpiece on the free speech steps.  It was quite vulgar, politically incorrect, raunchy and completely hilarious; a 1st amendment lovers paradise.  It included letters sent by the Kiss My Aztec staff to the Daily Aztec staff, about the opinion editor, Joe Zarro.  It went something like this:                Dear Daily Aztec,   Joe Zarro sucks donkey dicks and fills his lame fedora full of donkey cum and that's why he's such a fucking donkey fucker.               Sincerely,           The Kiss My Aztec Staff  The newspaper also included a free self addressed cut out post card, which they discouraged you from cutting out and mailing, that included a picture of President Weber's head superimposed onto Da Vinci's statue of  David .  They cut out the part where the penis was supposed to go and proposed a "Draw Weber's Cock Contest" which you were, once again, discouraged from cutting out and mailing.    Thank you Kiss My Aztec staff, for pioneering the revolt against censorship, complaisance and all things corporate.  Hooray for solidarity!  We will prevail!           
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know for sure that you're at an all ages show when you look at the audience and see kids making out during the band's set.  Ah, to be 13 again.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I started my new job last week, which is at a center for international students at school.  I've met quite a few foreign students since I've started, which can get pretty interesting.  On my second day, I witnessed the most pitiful of instances, involving a couple of Japanese kids and a used car purchase gone bad.  Apparently, the sales guy at the car dealership smelled naivety all over the obvious out of towner and decided to bend him over and do him dry.  Long story short, the Japanese kid bought a car that didn't have one functional seat belt in it.  When he noticed (after he got home) he decided to immediately go back to the dealer and bring it to the attention of the salesman, who told him that it wasn't his problem anymore.  Unfortunately, our foreign friend bought the car "as is", for a lower price.  Well now you can imagine the predicament this guy was in; he was pretty much screwed.  He had no one else to turn to but the advising center at his school...who has nothing to do with his problem.  And you should have seen the look on his face.  When explaining his story, he was so nervous and flustered that he couldn't get out a complete sentence.  It was hard to watch.  His roommate, who was more fluent in English, had to step in and take over explaining what had happened because it was obvious the other guy was struggling.  The saddest part of all:  he told the car salesman that he was going to tell his advisor.  "I'm gonna tell"; quite the threat.  That would surely instill fear into the heart of any car salesman.  As pathetic and humorous as that is, it melted me.  Poor little guy.  The innocence of this kid, exploited and manipulated by some greaseball trying to push bunk cars off his lot.  What a way to start his visit here.  Welcome to America!  We suck young blood!  I suppose that's the way the whole world works, not just exclusively the U.S.  Every community, whether it be the animal kingdom or human society, is composed of predator and prey.  Everybody has their turn to take and be taken.  All we can do is try to break even in the end.      
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now that I'm out of school for the summer I can do all those things that I wanted to do but never had time to.  I've been thinking recently about one of those things, which has been a long standing project; to make a t-shirt that says    I survived catholic school   .  When I mentioned the idea to one of my heathen friends, he suggested that I add ... let's fuck  after the I survived catholic school bit, which IS a pretty good idea, except some tool who sees me out there will probably think I really want to fuck him.  And we can't have that.    Not that most catholic school survivors wouldn't happily oblige to such things.  However, if the stigma attached to catholic school girls being skanks is really true, I can say that I am the exception to the rule (for the most part).  Although, I can attest to knowing several peers from catholic school who were total sluts.  I basically grew up going to catholic school, which is pretty much why catholicism has become the bane of me.  I went for all of my grade school years, except for 2/3 of the year in 6th grade.  My experience with public school ended when I was told that I could not go to 6th grade camp unless I went to the catholic school across the street.  I guess my mom couldn't risk me coming back from public 6th grade camp "knocked up" or anything.  Especially since I still played with dolls, had not graduated from an undershirt to a bra, nor could I even begin to fathom what a clit was...until high school at least.  Anyhow, there were still plenty of girls that I went to catholic school with who pretty much had their placentas dragging on the ground.  And who can blame them?  All that oppression has to manifest itself one way or another.  Catholic school can only drive one to such limberness.                   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bars...ah what a genius invention.  A business that specializes in getting people loaded enough to send them into a drunk and horny frenzy, thus allowing them to hump like apes.  The dim lighting, which helps make everyone there less unattractive and the deafening music saving you from pathetic conversation.  What a magical combination!  A real recipe for success if you ask me.    Sure it's easy for me to bag on the bar scene now, but I am actually quite the attendee.  I've been going to the same bar for almost two years now and I swear I'm the grand caca because I know all the people that work there.  I think anyone would at that point.  But by that logic, that would mean that Norm and Cliff from Cheers were lame-o's.  In the real world (and by real world I mean Norm and Cliff's world      outside    of cheers) I'm sure Norm and Cliff were losers.  Cliff was a postman for godssakes.  However, once they entered cheers they were the coolest.  And that's what my bar is to me.  It's the place where everybody knows my name.  And of course, they are always glad I came.     Anyhow, I don't go to bars to get laid believe it or not.  And girls like myself have developed a tactic to avoid people who do.  I call it the "buddy system" but its also more commonly known as "cock blocking" amongst men.  For instance, a few weeks ago a friend of mine and I were making our way through the bar and a young man decided to pinch my friend's ass in order to get her attention.  He succeeded and began to divulge in some small talk with her (what's your name, what's your sign) that the music failed to drown out.  It was then my job at that point to drag her away, suggesting that I "spotted" our friends or something urgent caused us to leave immediately.  In my opinion that's the easiest way to deal with the situation.  Just bail.  However it's not always foolproof, because it wasn't long after I began to yank my friend in the opposite direction that joe donut shouts, "Why you hating?"  Right in my face.  Just like that.  I couldn't even begin to know how to respond to that seeing as though he gave both my companion and I douche chills.  Incredulously, in addition to being reprimanded for "hating" on this guy, his friend demanded that I give him some respect.  That just knocked my socks off.  In any case, we escaped them, but not for long.  After the clock struck two and everyone scrambled outside to attempt a last minute hook up or to simply just talk, we interfaced with our gentlemen callers once more.  This time they sent their friend over to ask us, "Are you two lesbians?", to which I simply answered by laughing boldly in his face.  I suppose the crude laughter stung the ego a bit, so joe donut blatantly added, "They look like lesbians."  I laughed some more.  Oh the humanity.  You see, I'm all about loving thy neighbor and treating others like I'd like to be treated, but for those who are asking for it, there is no mercy.  So I walked over to the first guy I saw, nudged him and told him, "Want to hear something funny?  This guy just asked us if we were lesbians!  I guess that's how he justifies us not being into his shit", and just cackled like a hyena.  I don't think they liked that.  Then I proceeded to demasculate them as much as I possibly could.  I think I succeeded, because they left with no digits, no love and their fruit of the looms all in a jumble.  yay.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw Anchorman recently, which was pretty ridiculous and absurd, though it had a few laugh out loud moments.&nbsp; Though the movie had its borderline tardo moments, it made me realize I just can't proclaim my love for Will Farrell enough.&nbsp; He is one class act, I tell ya.&nbsp; Timeless.&nbsp; If you ask me, who do you consider a&nbsp;funny guy?&nbsp; I say Will Farrell hands down.&nbsp; He's one of those people that I wish was my chum, my compa, my wingman.&nbsp; To be friends with Will Farrell...ahh to&nbsp;be so lucky.&nbsp; Hell, I'd even marry him for the laughs.&nbsp; Wait a minute.&nbsp; No, I wouldn't.&nbsp; I was being hasty there.&nbsp; But I&nbsp;sure do wish he was my friend.&nbsp; That would be something.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The sadomasichistic cult that everyone calls Christianity has claimed another victim, a person I once dubbed as 'pretty cool'.&nbsp; But no longer.&nbsp; Tear.&nbsp;   You see, this story goes back; way back.&nbsp; Joser was a boy that always took the latest trend&nbsp;and just  ran  with it.&nbsp; Not too many boys that I know are really at all concerned with fashion, (although this new&nbsp;metro-sexual queer eye for the straight guy nonsense will make short of that) but Joser is one of those guys that is.&nbsp; And he doesn't like penis.&nbsp; So one minute he's a rastafarian vegan, sporting dreadlocks and always getting stoned.&nbsp; Then he was one of those 'The Strokes' type pseudo hipsters with a mullet.&nbsp; Then he became a hardcore surfer.&nbsp; And so on, but he would just jump from trend to trend.&nbsp;&nbsp;He wouldn't just jump, he would dive in.&nbsp; Head first.&nbsp; I actually started calling him poser instead of Joser.&nbsp; Not to his face.&nbsp; So when Joser and&nbsp;his girlfriend of a couple years broke up, he was completely devastated.&nbsp; There was huge void there, because she had been his  life  up&nbsp;until that point.&nbsp; That's when it started to get scary.   So I saw Joser for the first time in a few months at a friends house last week.&nbsp; He had a shaved head and was dawning a new tattoo.&nbsp; It took up his entire back and was an image of an angel of Christ&nbsp;or something and it&nbsp;cost him well over $700.&nbsp; A tattoo of "The Last Supper" was also in the works.&nbsp; Then he started&nbsp;talking about his religion.&nbsp; He informed&nbsp;us that he had gone to church that day from 9 am to 4 pm.&nbsp; I don't know&nbsp;about you, but I would&nbsp;not volunteer&nbsp;my entire day to be spent inside a church.&nbsp; How deathly boring.&nbsp; Then he started explaining that humans are inherently evil and that we are born wicked and there's really nothing&nbsp;we can do about it.&nbsp; He kind of started ranting and&nbsp;raving.&nbsp;   "We're&nbsp;sinners and that's it.&nbsp; It's human nature.&nbsp; The only way that&nbsp;we are going to&nbsp;save ourselves is to be in the church 24/7 everyday.&nbsp; It's the only way to get into heaven.&nbsp; You know?&nbsp; I don't&nbsp;trust myself even.&nbsp; I don't.&nbsp;&nbsp;You know, I stopped smoking weed and I had a really bad trip the last time I did it, and I was like ok God.&nbsp; This is how you want it to go for my&nbsp;last time?&nbsp; Alright.&nbsp; Then so be it.&nbsp; And that's why I changed.&nbsp; I am just dedicating myself to my religion.&nbsp; I want to start new.&nbsp; That's why I shaved my head today... It was like a cleansing... I just wanted to shed everything, shed all the impurities away.&nbsp; I don't like who I was and where my life was going.&nbsp; That's why I've taken Jesus into my life and I don't want to go back...I just can't be that way anymore...I just can't...I don't want it."   FYI there was nothing wrong with the way his 'life' was going before, except for the whole poser thing.&nbsp; The scariest part of all was that everyone grew&nbsp;awkwardly silent and he just kept on talking.&nbsp; Not only did he continue, but he started getting really flustered and neurotic, finicky almost.&nbsp; It was difficult to&nbsp;watch.&nbsp;&nbsp;I was really disturbed and frightened.&nbsp; I really hate organized religion as it is, so&nbsp;Joser was like the antichrist to me&nbsp;at&nbsp;that point.&nbsp; I was so traumatized that I had to leave the room.&nbsp; It was like a bad scene out of the movie, Saved!&nbsp; Imagine&nbsp;you knew someone who was totally normal and&nbsp;chill, then you see them a couple months later and they are totally transformed into&nbsp;a bible toting psycho.&nbsp; Pretty scary, huh?&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  For a second&nbsp;there&nbsp;I was going to interject and inform him that everything he was saying was BULLSHIT, but I didn't want to get hurt over it.&nbsp; Who knows what that wannabe pious freak was capable of when his religion was insulted.&nbsp;&nbsp;Anyhow, it pained me to see such a lovely fellow&nbsp;get brainwashed so badly by those Christian fuckos.&nbsp; I suppose they saw that him at his most vulnerable and sucked him right in.&nbsp; Bastards.&nbsp;   I remember at my old community college&nbsp;legions of bible thumpers&nbsp;were found in swarms, hunting&nbsp;down the next new victim.&nbsp; There wasn't a day where one of those&nbsp;holy rollers&nbsp;wouldn't approach me.&nbsp; And believe me I avoided them like the plague.&nbsp; But they would always get me.&nbsp; And DAMN were they pushy.&nbsp; It was always some girl, who claimed that she was a real trifling whore back in her day...that is  before  she found Jesus.&nbsp; But now that she found Jesus her life is  so  in order, and&nbsp;goddammit she's never been happier.&nbsp; She&nbsp;always insisted that&nbsp;I come to the bible study, which was so fun, because they really explored the bible in depth and learned the real truth about the bible.&nbsp; Though&nbsp;I assured her that it sounded like a real&nbsp;scream, I wasn't interested.&nbsp;&nbsp;In one particular instance the&nbsp;girl got&nbsp;real nasty with me when I turned her down and&nbsp;asked me if I wanted to go to hell.&nbsp; I told her that I already was in hell, but thank you.&nbsp; She was a little&nbsp;taken aback by that and left me alone&nbsp;after that.&nbsp;   Seriously though, I'm not buying the heaven and hell tactic anymore.&nbsp; If they think I'm going to behave to avoid going to "hell", they've got another thing coming.&nbsp; What  is  hell anyway?&nbsp; I burn forever?&nbsp; Whats going to burn, my body?&nbsp; Because I thought that got left behind.&nbsp; Then if my body isn't present, where does the pain come from because I thought all the neurons and whatnot played a part in feeling physical pain.&nbsp; Ah, what the hell do I know anyway?&nbsp; All I know is, if there actually is a hell that we go to after already living in one here on&nbsp;earth, God is cruel indeed. &nbsp;&nbsp;  Moral of the story:&nbsp; Don't let them (the Christians) take you.&nbsp; They see you sad, alone and with your pants down.&nbsp; Then WAMMO!&nbsp; Right in the butt.&nbsp;   Down with organized religion.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just found out that Martha Stewart has been sentenced to prison and&nbsp;I can't decide whether I'm&nbsp;elated or sympathetic.&nbsp; Martha Stewart always gave me that&nbsp;'evil bitch' vibe.&nbsp; I've read&nbsp;a thing or two about her and how she can be, ummm, intimidating.&nbsp;&nbsp;A modern day Joan Crawford, if you will.&nbsp;&nbsp;And&nbsp;I know you will.&nbsp; So when this whole&nbsp;scandal started and she had to go to court,&nbsp;I was kind of hoping she&nbsp;would go down in flames.&nbsp; I thought to myself, "It would&nbsp;be nice to see that whore Martha Stewart go to prison.&nbsp; That would be something."&nbsp; Wouldn't it?&nbsp; Well&nbsp;now it's a reality.&nbsp; I don't really feel that satisfaction that I&nbsp;thought I&nbsp;would feel.&nbsp; What is wrong with me??&nbsp; Has the hater in me subsided?&nbsp; Or maybe...  &nbsp;  So it got me thinking.&nbsp; Perhaps Martha Stewart gets a bad rap for being a&nbsp;ball buster, super anal, driven and&nbsp;all that good stuff even more so because she's a woman and she's successful.&nbsp; She really just knows what she wants so we&nbsp;deemed her&nbsp;a "bitch".&nbsp; That's what we call most intelligent and assertive women.&nbsp; Like Hillary Clinton.&nbsp; She's a "bitch" too.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Even so, Martha&nbsp;Stewart still really just seems like a bitch.&nbsp; But that's not my point.  &nbsp;  This whole trial is revolving around an unethical and illegal move made by&nbsp;Stewart , but&nbsp;it&nbsp;couldn't be any worse than what the Enron guys did.&nbsp; And&nbsp;then you may remember our old pals OJ and&nbsp;Condit.&nbsp; Sure&nbsp;Condit was never deemed guilty, but then again neither was OJ, so go figure.&nbsp; Killing is ok, but cheating in the stock market is baaad.  &nbsp;  Five months in prison is&nbsp;pretty short, but it's just long enough to take any bit of the tender ass left in her&nbsp;OUT.&nbsp; Imagine Martha&nbsp; after  prison if you thought she was scary now.&nbsp; I suppose there will be plenty&nbsp;of jokes we could make about her stay in prison and how she&nbsp;will&nbsp;keep herself busy in there with&nbsp;arts and crafts.&nbsp; I wonder if they would let her continue airing Martha Stewart&nbsp;Living live from prison.&nbsp; What a hoot that would be.&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  "Hello everyone.&nbsp; Welcome to Martha Stewart&nbsp;Living, the prison edition.&nbsp; Today my bitch and&nbsp;I will be showing you all how to transform&nbsp;this ordinary toothbrush into a weapon.&nbsp; We will also be making&nbsp;homemade tampons out of paper mache and cotton.&nbsp; And in the last segment of our program,&nbsp;we will&nbsp;show you how to store and&nbsp;smuggle the&nbsp;unthinkable in your vagina."&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Good times.&nbsp; Hey, Martha said she'd be back.&nbsp; I believe her too.&nbsp; See you in five months Martha.&nbsp; Stay&nbsp;strong girl.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What ever happened to Shaundra Levy?&nbsp; Remember her?&nbsp; She mysteriously disappeared a while back.&nbsp; There was speculation that she had been involved in a torrid love affair with Gary Condit.&nbsp; Gary Condit was even starting to become a prime suspect in the case of her disappearance.&nbsp; On that note I must say, Gary Condit is the luckiest fuck alive.&nbsp; Ok, I take that back, O.J. Simpson is the luckiest fuck alive.&nbsp; But lets pretend he's not for a minute.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;Timing is everything.&nbsp; For Gary Condit, the 9/11 tragedy COULD NOT have come at a better time.&nbsp; Up&nbsp;until that fateful day in New York, news coverage was beginning to focus heavily on the disappearance of Shaundra Levy.&nbsp; Condit had a nice steady flame right under his ass at that time.&nbsp;  I  even felt the heat.&nbsp; Then, bada-bing bada-boom, a couple airliners go slamming into the twin towers and everyone goes apeshit.&nbsp; I suppose that's a pretty good reason to forget that&nbsp;GARY CONDIT IS A PHILANDERING MURDERER!&nbsp; Does one tragedy cancel out another?&nbsp;&nbsp;I didn't think so, but&nbsp;it seemed to happen anyway .&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;   We have&nbsp;short attention&nbsp;spans don't we?&nbsp;&nbsp;Analogy-wise, if&nbsp;our attention spans were comparable to dick size, we'd&nbsp;all be hung like a light switch.&nbsp; Shaundra Levy's&nbsp;missing...oh shnap!&nbsp;&nbsp;The twin towers were attacked.&nbsp;&nbsp;Get&nbsp;Osama Bin Laden.&nbsp; Ok forget him then, get Saddam Hussein instead.&nbsp; We got Saddam Hussein?!&nbsp; Yipee.&nbsp; Ok now what?&nbsp; Lets take him to court.&nbsp; Yeah. &nbsp;  &nbsp;   Out with the old, in with the new.&nbsp; We just want to be entertained.&nbsp; We want to sound informed.&nbsp; Give me scandal, give me a juicy story, give me, give me.&nbsp; Stimulate my peanut sized brain.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   How come we aren't really talking about Osama Bin Laden&nbsp;in connection to 9/11&nbsp;as we&nbsp;were before?&nbsp; Has the search for Bin Laden subsided?&nbsp;&nbsp;Has the focus shifted to hunting down Saddam because curious George W.&nbsp; had beef with&nbsp;him since he tried to whack off his pop?&nbsp; That sounds like a personal problem.&nbsp; No need to drag the rest of the&nbsp;country down with you on this one.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    I digress...  &nbsp;  So Gary Condit one lucky fuck.&nbsp; He's stoked.&nbsp; Terrorism came in real clutch and saved his ass from further scandal and possible prison time.&nbsp; Everyone just plum forgot about that measly disappearance.&nbsp; I haven't forgotten, Gary Condit.&nbsp; I know what you did last summer.&nbsp; Intern killer.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Speaking of disappearances, whatever happened to the sporty and scary Spice Girls,&nbsp;Al Gore, Ralph Machio (Karate Kid) &nbsp;and&nbsp;those kids from Dawsons&nbsp;Creek?&nbsp; Or all those canceled WB shows&nbsp;for that matter.&nbsp;&nbsp;     
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the first time in my life, I was a first-hand witness to the process that takes place when one of your own friends gets married. In addition to making me&nbsp;aware of&nbsp;my accelerated aging process, attending this wedding helped me realize that&nbsp; white people are drier than a day old piece of bread .&nbsp; Especially old white people.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I went to the&nbsp;wedding shower too.&nbsp;&nbsp;That experience was very much like watching paint&nbsp;dry, to be honest.&nbsp; The only good part was that I got fed&nbsp;(potato salad and some m&amp;m's) and I got to go home with a fabulous gift bag that included a magnet with a picture of the lovely couple.&nbsp; I haven't quite decided what to do with it.&nbsp; The worst part was when we had to play ridiculous games, like quizzing the bride to be&nbsp;on her fiancee's likes and dislikes and&nbsp;for every wrong answer&nbsp;she had to stick a piece of gum in her mouth.&nbsp; Pretty wild.&nbsp; It was difficult to sit through since I really don't give a rats ass whether&nbsp;the groom&nbsp;likes creamy or&nbsp;chunky peanut butter.&nbsp; After that, then&nbsp;we got to watch her open cards and read them.&nbsp; It was sheer torture.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  In contrast, I went to a Mexican wedding shower and&nbsp;they had booze and&nbsp;even this homoerotic dance troupe, which they call SOS.&nbsp; These guys basically go&nbsp;in there and drag all the yenta women out onto the dance floor, then lead them through a series of dance routines which everyone&nbsp;is supposed to do in&nbsp;unison.&nbsp; It's pretty freaking queer, but at least it's fun and light hearted.&nbsp; The point is, every Hispanic wedding I've been to is relatively lively; the reception is all about drinking, dancing and good times for all.  &nbsp;  So my friend's wedding, which was largely made up of anglosaxons, was pretty damn dull.&nbsp; Coincidence?&nbsp; I think not.&nbsp; For one, the DJ was playing country western.&nbsp; Not only was the choice of music terrible, but the ultimate wedding reception faux pas was committed.&nbsp; They played the chicken dance song.&nbsp; I was horrified, more so because I jokingly predicted that they would&nbsp;play the chicken dance and they did.&nbsp; And people danced to it.&nbsp; Well, the bride and groom and maybe&nbsp;two other&nbsp;people, who were pretty much the only people dancing the entire&nbsp;night.&nbsp; And its no wonder why they were the only ones dancing.&nbsp; Music is a key factor when it comes to parties and celebrations.&nbsp; You just don't screw that part up.&nbsp; Anyhow, it was boooring.&nbsp; So it got me thinking, why are white people&nbsp;so dull?&nbsp; Do they have some kind of boring gene that they pass along from generation to generation along with a lack of rhythm?  &nbsp;  I kid.&nbsp;&nbsp;That was a very hasty&nbsp;generalization.&nbsp; Not all white people are drier than a day old piece of bread.&nbsp; Not all...just some.&nbsp; Some meaning most.&nbsp; Especially the old ones.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just saw The Big Lebowski and it was the shittiest movie ever.  The movie was strongly recommended to me more than once, so you can imagine my dissapoinment after viewing it.  I was expecting fireworks and I got a couple poppers.  Maybe not even a couple.  Such a let down. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everybody poops.  Everyone.  You, your sister, your dog and even your mom.  It's not a pretty picture, but we all know it's a fact of life.  I'm not scared of talking about it but it seems like some people are.  It's like we're afraid of letting others know we do it.  I actually know someone who, for many years, didn't think that girls pooped.  Isn't that great?    For a long time I refused to take a dump in a public restroom.  I'm sure there are others out there that can relate.  It can get so bad that people have psychological problems with it, like those people who can't urinate in public restrooms.  Howard Stern had a problem like that during his youth; I believe he called it pee fear.  Now I've been forced to realize that sometimes you just have to get over it and use public restrooms, but the trauma that comes along with accidentally farting loudly or taking a loud shit can be irreparably damaging.  I usually wait until everyone leaves the restroom to do my business.  It shouldn't be that way and I realize that it doesn't have to be.  I just can't ignore society telling me that farting out loud is gross, when in reality, farting in the restroom is fair game.  People who fart in the restroom at least have the decency to fart there as opposed to the dinner table or a crowded elevator.  Give them some credit.   Though I'm not really one to talk.  I always giggle when someone farts in the bathroom.  I can't help it, poo and the like is funny to me.    Maybe people are deathly afraid of talking about poo for the same reasons they don't want to talk about sex.  It's taboo.  Taboo's are stupid.  Labeling these things taboo and refusing to openly talk about them is all in vain attempt to deny our animalistic behaviors.  We need not be ashamed!  These are our basic needs.  It's natural.  It's ok if you have to poop.  Everybody poops.                 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love that my state's governer called people "girlie men" in a public speech.  It's not at all an embarassment, not by any means.  I hate myself for not voting.   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have theorized that men can be placed into two categories: those who wear wife beaters as an undershirt and those who wear wife beaters as attire. I've noticed that men, American men at least, that wear wife beaters on a day to day basis tend to be very particular types of men. Perhaps they are the types that can open a beer bottle with their teeth. Perhaps they are the types that want to show off their tats. Perhaps they are the types that tend to show off their bodies when they really shouldn't. They are obviously too sexy for their shirts, in their minds, so day after day they put on that uniform of theirs. Rain, sleet, hail, snow; it doesn't matter. Wife beater it is and wife beater it shall be.  There's this dude in my social psychology class who wears a wife beater  every day . He doesn't miss a beat. Everyday. He must have one of those Ronald McDonald style closets, where everything is the same but there's about twenty wife beaters to choose from.  The world is the wife beater wearers oyster and they can wear all the wife beaters they want until their heart's content. They just look lame, is all.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>