<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So yesterday I had to yard sale to end all yard sales.... It was amazing the amount of CRAP 2 people can accumulate.... And the worst part is, we had one last year too.... So pretty much over the course of one year I purchased enough crap to make almost 500 dollars...how sad is that? So I have made a promise to myself that I will no long purchase something, just to have it, it must now serve a function or purpose.... of course I will probably say the same damn thing in my blog, one year from know, but what the hell, sounds good right? Well now that we have sold all shit, I am off to go shopping..he he he he  more later 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That is how I feel about all the other blog's I have been browsing.... This really is a world unto itself.... And I must say that i am more than delighted to add my little sparkle of life to it.. So have you ever wondered what it would be like to have magical powers and what you would do with them? There are days when I just lose myself in those thoughts.. And think of different "powers" I would want. Would I want to move stuff with mind? Would I want to be able to control the weather? Would I want to be telepathic? Ohhh what fun I would have. The reason for all of these questions being on the forefront of my mind is because last night I was doing Tarot readings for my partner and a friend of ours. And they always get my creative juice's flowing, so to speak.. Also I should give smoe backround of my family. My father was 100% Native American, and his parents actually grew up in their respective tribes, and my grandmother was the witch doctor of her tribe. And it was said that she had to power of "second sight". I was facinated with the stories of her when I was younger. I use to beg to her about all that she could see and predict... Right before she passed away ( a couple months before I was born), she put her hand on my mother's stomach and said your gonna have a boy.. And everyone else, including the dr's, said I was a girl. So i use to say in someway in that moment she passed something onto me. Do I believe I'm psychic? NO! But I do know that I get "feelings", and when I do they are almost always right. Usually they are out of no-where and I dont know there coming, it's just something that happens. Other times, if I try hard enough I can focus of something or something and get a "reading".  Well I most say good-bye for now, and get back to that crazy thing that gives me a paycheck every week...WORK..... which is a whole posting in its own....
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ohhh, where or where to start  Well I guess I should tell you a big about myself....The names Eric, I am 25 yrs old... I live in a little city in Mass called Pittsfield...I live with my partner of 2 yrs Stephen. We have 2 dogs, Miller, the most stubborn PUG ever, and Kadee the sweetest most loving pitbull/greyhound. We have a good live together, surrounded by friends and family...  Guess that was a good way to start, I am sure there is more to follow because this boy( yes that is boy with a Y not an I, I am sure this is soooo taboo to all the gay "boi's" out there, but ohhh well).... Until next time... smooches
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So this past weekend I threw a party for my best friend and her partner at my house. They recently purchased a new home about 2 hrs away from where I live, and because  alot of their family couldnt travel to their new house, we decided to have the party at my house. So we rented a big tent, invited pretty much everyone their have ever come in contact with, and partied harder than I have partied in many many yrs... now mind you I am only 25 yrs old, which I dont concider that old, but with the way I feel this morning, I feel as though 25 is close to being on my death bed....  So feeling like this makes me think? At what age does one become "too old to do this shit"? so to speak  I mean, my mother is 53 yrs old, and I swear the women has more energy and stamina than people my age..... And I know people who are at least 10 yrs older than me, and can party harder than me by a long shot.... I had all day yesterday to lay lown and nurse my hang over, yet today I am still feelin it.......... So that is my question for today... is there an age when enough is enough, or when the partying gets "old"?
     

    
</post>


</Blog>