<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well,  3 weeks (or is it 2) and then we have tests. Great feeling isn't it. Or should I say freaky. People say review a lot, but when you look at the amount, you go under something commonly notified as 'stress', and as this is our first time the effect is even greater. "But," the doctor says "meditate, perform yoga, and everything will be alright child, but is that really the case?"  No, well see you, sometime next week!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to thesquarerootofnine.blogspot.com. This website was published today, yes, today. Freaky isn't it, how the internet has expanded so much; so much 'free' stuff.  Well, do share you thoughts. Oh, and please refrain from swearing.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Official Omega1989 Resource   This page apparently proves to be a shocker, especially now that it has introduced the rules to "Stealth Chess, Discworld Style", Enjoy! 
     
    
</post>


<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink  Googlism    THE FIRST OFFICIAL POST EVERY HAS HIT THE ROADS TO HEAVEN. WELL I JUST THOUGHT I'D SEND THIS UNBELIEVABLY CRAZY SITE TO ALL OF YOU GUYS...WELL JUST CHECK IT OUT AND IT'LL EXPLAIN ITSELF!  THANKS, BLOG ADMINISTRATOR, SMIK  

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well...This is officially the first post to give this blogspot it's way into the future. Well it's main use is going to be for all the 10th Graders (2004/2005), which includes me. Well for all of you who have a clue about what I'm writting about so far, there's going to be 'radical' stuff happening here, that's as long as you participate. Many articles and updates!       [Some] Grade 9 Students Gather For An End Of The Year Picture Including Me (On The Ground, To The Right)    Thanks To Zahra For The Picture!     

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     It's 11:40pm&nbsp;(DSM time), As Shezeens&nbsp;MSN&nbsp;nickname reads we're "Six days"&nbsp;away from school. For me the feelings great! I actually can't wait...though of course there's going to be a lot of work, dang!&nbsp;I guess this worlds pretty much crazy...   &nbsp;   Somehow I can't resist&nbsp;to say -- "Live Life To The Fullest"   &nbsp;   "On The 16th Of February Penguins Are Going To Fly, And The Square Root Of -1 Is Going To Exist In The Minds Of Many" -- Just Remember That 
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well I will be having my last dinner today before I leave to South Africa. We're going to some restaurant with my Grandparents...I hope the food's good. I've packed all my stuff, at least that's what I thought, it turns out that my mum's complaining about me putting an amount too small to suit the needs of the trip...well I guess that's life. Um... I thought I'd just bring up a current running issue. You see the fact is that I can't run this web-blog on my own because there's going to be a lot of stuff happening next year. So I atleast need one volunteer (who knows how to use blogs) who can help me run this "Grade 10 -- The Garbage" blog. If you are interested in helping e-mail me at  urlLink smiklakhani@zhotmail.com  (without the "z", which is a prevention method used for anti-spamming). If I don't find anyone, I guess I can manage the blog on my own...  Anyway, here's a picture I've been working on lately (using Jasc Paint Shop Pro 7.04) (69.1KB)...        "Matthew Franzen At The Elementary School" 
</post>


</Blog>