<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We need more bars like the Ye Old Falcon Pub in Davie, Florida. It was described to me as a "REAL hole in the wall - a strip mall dump" before we left, so I was already expecting greatness. It's not crowded, you can always get a dartboard, the beer is cold and cheap, and last call is at 4 a.m.... if you ask me, there's not much else you can really ask for in a bar. Reminded me of bars like Cool Beans, Riprock's, and Lucky Lou's that I frequented (sunk my tuition into) in college back in Texas. No pretension, no concern for "image"-- you can wear shorts in there and drink to your liver's content while trolls, yuppies, hangers-on, beautiful people and nerds alike inhabit every corner till the sun's about ready to peek over the Atlantic coast about 10 miles east. My kind of place.  Surprisingly enough, I was the only one walking a (semi) straight line as we rolled out of there. Ah, the burden I must bear.... I've missed bars like that. Felt like college again.  Another warm but beautiful day today. I love the feeling of the first day of a three day weekend... trouble isn't even within shouting distance.  Rim it.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...the Friday before a holiday weekend is great. The phones are dead, problems aren't mounting, and now that the boss is gone, I get to stream my Sirius satellite radio through my computer speakers for the last hour and a half of the day. Music in the workplace should be mandatory, I say. No questions asked. My mood is better, I feel more productive (as you can tell, considering I'm blogging my ass off while Rome burns around me), and life is easier in general.   Love you. Curve it around.   p.s.: Thank God for Uncle Sam. My refund check smells like victory and strawberries. Boo-yah!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's really hard to be at work when it's a beautiful day out. I would think that a corner office with the great view would be more of a curse than anything else. I'd get nothing done. I guess the point is that once you reach the corner office, you've already done it all and you're on cruise control. I'm in a cubicle, but I'm already on cruise control.. see, I'm always ahead of the game...  May in South Florida isn't as hot as you'd think. So far, it's been pretty nice. Dad comes into town in three weekends, which I'm excited about. I'm more excited about the fact that after 8pm tonight, I've got a three day weekend. Rock on, kids. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been raining off and on for three days now. Kind of says alot, really.  Life has been so tinged with sweeping positives and negatives lately, my head has been swimming across the Florida straits just about 24 hours a day. Nerves, excitement, doubt, fear, anger, joy... they're all there, they're all side by side. I swore there'd be no real specifics in this blog, so there's really only so much I can do with this. But I'm trying. I've never really felt so alive and so adult yet so close to being a ghost all at once... but I'm there, somewhere between here and Miramar Parkway. We've got about two good weeks now to survive. We'll see then.  Other than that, with rain comes great humidity. And creatures I've never seen-- bugs, fish, birds, rodents-- everywhere, and I couldn't tell you what in the hell half of them are. The pond around the corner from my townhouse is higher than it's been in the 4 months since I got to Florida, and with the water rising I think every beast in the tropics has emerged upon me... oh well... the sun is still beautiful when it's out, and I've got two and a half weeks to spend at the beach now....  Grip it and rip it,  --P
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm fighting every rational urge to book a 3-day cruise for us next weekend. It's not that expensive, but expensive enough to make it not the wisest call right now. It's like crack. I just have to put down the pipe….  … 3 day weekends aren't what they used to be. It was too hot and it was too short. Amazingly, I was constantly active and had something to do pretty much every hour of every day, but it still feels wasted. The Sunday paper revealed to me that my dream company is having an employment open house next Saturday-- it makes me feel good because I know I'll get the chance to get in front of them face to face, but it makes me feel concerned that they've been ignoring my resume all this time and now not only do I know a guy who got fired from my current job got on there, but that they are hiring-- like mad. We'll see, I guess….
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm really falling behind here. Sorry, blog.   I promise to be more diligent.  Starting tomorrow.  Last night at FtL beach, dinner on the breakers at Pusser's Caribbean, and the new job coming through all in 24 hours. This is one of those upward swings. I'm trying not to think about it and just enjoy the ride while it lasts. It just continues to seem like just when I get kicked in the nuts, a Christmas tree is waiting around the corner.  Of all the things I could have used there, a Christmas tree??? Hmm. What can I say?  More beach tomorrow, and as little work as possible until the 26th.  Land Ho,  --P
     
    
</post>


</Blog>