<Blog>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Survey Your Friends 13  1)Name- Ohav 2)Nicknames- Ohav Tits, Fat Tits, Fatah 3)Birthday- August 18, 1990 4)How old are you then- 13 going on 30... lol jk... 13 going on 14 5)Hometowm- albany, ca but i consider tel aviv my real home 6)Town you were born in- petach tikva 7)What do you look like- a homo sapien 8)Are you hansome/beautiful- nice spelling, yes i think i am 9)Why or why not- i like my body build, and my face 10)Family members- um... in my house mom, step dad, and half brother 11)Fave relative- mom and dad 12)Least fave relative- love em all 13)Is the #13 unlucky/lucky- unlucky 14)What time did you goto bed last nite- u mean last morning?? 2:30 am 15)What did you do yesterday- abso-fucking-lutely nothing 16)What did/you doing today- went to tobys house) 16)What did/you doing today-  17)Fave place to eat- curry in hurry, but it closed... well i think i was their only customer 18)Fave food- too many but if i had to say... lamb curry 19)Fave drink- spicy hot v8 20)Fave numbers- 18 and 29 21)Do you drink- in general? yes. alcohol? on Jewish holidays 22)Do you drive- no 23)If so,what kind of car- no 24)Did you dye/highlight/lighten your hair or anything- no 25)What are you wearing in your school pic- sweater 26)Worst thing you ever did- stole a plastic toy car for 20 cents when i was 4 27)Best thing you ever did- last friday 28)Fave radio station- 106.1 kmel 29)Fave TV show- south park/chappelles show/viva la bam 30)Fave room in your house- mine 31)Fave season- summer 32)Whats on your mousepad- i have a laptop... haha 33)Do you have a scanner- no 34)What kind of computer do you have- apple 12" inch ibook 35)Do you have a mic- built in... haha 36)Do you have ICQ none 37)If so,whats your ICQ#- none 38)Are you wearing nailpolish right now- o yeah 39)If so,what color- no 40)Ever stolen something- that goes back to question 26 41)Do you like this survey so far- very 42)Ok,lets play a game i say a word and u say what u think of- um... 43)chocolate- hot 44)spice- girls 45)taco - bell 46)pretty- nikki 47)hot- chocolate 48)cold- sympton 49)lemon- ade 50)coolatta- what the fuck 51)pink- tree 52)email- check 53)hacker- plasma 54)ocean- blue 55)sun- ray 56)Ok, lets play another game, I say a name and you say who u think of  57)Bob- dole 58)Rose- garden 59)Justin- exeter 60)Delilah- rachel and ross daughter 61)Ricky- douell 62)Jenna- jameson 63)Joe- schmoe 64)Jamie- kennedy 65)Ron- sadi 66)Tabitha-  um 67)Mark- anthony 68)Britney- spears 69)Anthony- um 70)Christina- aguilera 71)Brian- adams 72)Maria- lucy 73)John- kerry 74)Katie- holmes 75)Tiffany- um 76)Shawn- smith 77)Megan- thompson 78)Tammy- arnon 79)Bobby- jones 80)Tim- my ~~~~~~~LasT Time You~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  81)Spoke- 2 minutes ago? wtf?? 82)Showered- an hour ago 83)Ate- 90 minutes ago 84)Cried- thursday... from joy 85)Kissed- my mom?? last night 86)Laughed- all throughout this quiz 87)Wrote- right now!! 88)Typed- last week 89)Studied- dunno 90)Drank- an hour ago in the shower 91)Fought- last night with robbie 92)Ran- a long ass time ago 93)Walked- 5 minutes ago 94)Hiked- tobys house... 9 hours ago 95)Coughed- now 96)Rode a bike- a week ago 97)Rollerskated/bladed- a couple months 98)Iceskated- dunno... 2 years 99)Bought something- um... wednesday 100)Were sick- 2 months ago 101)Tell Me Which You Would Rather in the next questions ok- no its not ok 102)Forwards or Chain Letters- forwards 103)White or Black- black 104)Strawberry or Lemon-strawberry  105)Chicken or Turkey- chicken 106)Red or pink- pink 107)Soda or Pop- what the fuck is the difference? soda 108)Blonds or Brunettes- both ;) 109)Make-up or No Make-up- for me? no make up. for girls? a reasonable amount 110)Straight or curly- both ;) 111)Summer or winter- summer 112)Spring or fall- spring 113)Christmas or Easter- FUCK BOTH OF EM 114)Valentines Day or St Patrick's Day- valentines day 115)Pretty or beautiful- beautiful 116)Hot or Sexy- hot 117)Tall or Short- both ;) 118)Long or quick- depends on the occasion ;) 119)Chocolate or vanilla- vanilla 120)Private or Public School- private 121)Religious or Spiritual- religious 122)Half Empty or Half-Full- half full 123)TV or Radio- tv 124)Walk or Run- walk 125)Drive or Walk- walk for now 126)Crowded or Empty- crowded 127)Lefty or Righty- rigty 128)What was your most embarassing moment- too many 129)Best friends- too many 130)What did you do on New Years- went to mias house... errgh 131)Do you have mIRC- mIRC? what the fuck is that??? 132)Fave car- hummer 133)Fave shampoo- herbal essences 135)Fave colours- black, blue, silver, red 136)Who sent this to you- i found it on chainletters.net 137)Any last words- FIRE!!! hahahaha rofl love that joke 138)How long did this take you to fill out- so far, 15 min 139)Are you glad you're almost done- no 140)Who is going to send this back- no1 141)Whos not going to send back- no1 142)Fave place to shop- ummmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm safeway 143)Do you have an Mp3 player- yes, an old one but im getting an ipod in 2 weeks 144)What mp3's do you have, if so- over 1000... so pshah 145-You're done!!! Good Job!! - what a great question 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Parents are out... This is what I'm having for dinner:    This isn't some kinda bad joke... I just took that picture... I am probably gonna eat two cans of Chef Boyardee with the Enchiladas that are on top mixed with the spicy salt in the front center.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THE BASICS*~  Your Name- Ohav Nicknames- Ohav Tits, Fat Tits, Fatah Birthday- August 18th, 1990  ~*HAVE YOU??*~  Been kissed? Does Truth or Dare count?? No?? Then no. Eaten an entire box of Oreos? The Mini-Oreo kind Been on stage? Yeah Gotten in a car accident? No Death Valley on horseback? No Stayed home? Um... Duh Made homemade fudge? No Seen the Eiffel tower? Yeah  ~*FAVORITES*~  Shampoo: Herbel Essences, Suave Soap: Suave Color: Blue Day: Saturday Night: Saturday Band: D-12 Season: Summer Commercial: The Asian Sour Starburst ~*YOUR FRIENDS*~  Do you have a boyfriend/girlfriend? Dunno Do you have a crush on someone: Yes Do you have a best friend? A couple Do you rank your speed dial in order of favorite friends? No Who's your funniest friend? All Who do you go to the mall with the most? Um... I don't really do that with my friends... Who do you e-mail the most? All of them Who have you known the longest of your friends? I dunno... People in Israel... Who's the loudest? We're all fairly loud Who's the shyest? No one. Whose parents do you know the best? Robbie's  Who do you go to for advice? Lucy?? Depends... Who knows all your secrets? Robbie Who do you get the most surveys from? Myself Who are you jealous of? Toby Who do you cry with? I don't cry with people... Do you?? What is your usual quote? "Oh, pound it!" "Nice, Fatah"  ~*IN THE LAST 24 HOURS HAVE YOU*~  Cried? No Eaten fluf? What the fuck is fluf? Helped someone? Yes Bought something? No Dissected something? No Cut your hair? No Worn a skirt? No Worn a tie? No Been mean? Yeah Been sarcastic? OHH... YEAH!!! Gone for a run? No Gone for a walk? No Gone to the movies? Hopefully soon!! Gone out for dinner? No Been kissed? No Felt stupid? All the time Said "I love you"? To my mom Written a letter? E-mail Written a paper? Yeah Taken a test? Yes Met someone new? No Moved on? Moved on??? Um...  Written in a journal? Blog Watched your favorite movie? No Talked to someone you have a crush on? Not within the past 24 hours Given someone a present? No Missed someone? Yeah Hugged someone? No Had a nightmare? By taking this quiz Fought with your parents? No Fought with a friend? Yeah Been Scared? Yeah  ~*WHENS THE LAST TIME YOU*~  Showered? 10 am Ate a meal? tobys house What are you wearing right now? jeans, tshirt Are you tired? no Are you lonely? very Are you happy? for the most part Are you wearing pajamas? no Are you hungry? a bit Are you eating? no Are you talking to someone online? yeah Are you ready for this survey to end? no How long did this survey take you?  *Do you want all your friends to do this and send back? no  WELL YOU'RE NOT DONE!!!....   >>>>FAVORITE STUFF>>>>   Type of sandwich: turkey Coffee or hot chocolate? hot chocolate Cold or hot? weather? depends Big or little? BIG Lace or satin? um...  Red or blue? blue New or old? new Here or there? always there 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I seriously need to get a life. Nothing to do!!! TV's outrated, so I resort to the internet, however, I went to everything on my  urlLink Bookmark Bar  like ten times... I even looked at stocks (yes, I  am  that pathetic...) I have no idea what to do.  My momma always told me that intelligent people never get bored...  So... I'll think of something to do... Oooh! I'll go find a chain letter thing where it asks you a lot of questions and fill it out, and post it here for the whole world to see!! YEAH!! I am so fucking intelligent.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Came back from Toby's house. Finished book report. Woohoo... I am probably not going to Bay Street, unless something miraculous and awesome happens... So yeah. Noah, Toby, and I worked on our rap, then played Halo, then Risk, then pool, then Balderdash, then Halo. I am home now. Someone call me, you know the number.  -Hoping for a miracle, Ohav  P.S.  56% addicted to Instant Messenger.  How about you? 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So tomorrow I have to call Noah at 10 to see if I can carpool with him to Toby's house where I need to be at 11... Then I might see a movie with Nikki, Lucy and Ari so I have to finish with Toby at like 4:30... Then I need to get a ride back... Then I need to meet them at Bay Street... Come home at like 10 and finish my book report...  so im nervous about 3 things  1. that for some reason noah wont come to tobys house cuz he forgot or if toby forgets... or if i go to the wrong house (his moms instead of his dads) 2. bay street wont work out... 3. i wont finish book report  Hopefully everything will work out.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay... I don't think people actually saw this because it was on the bottom of my entry so here: I made an Eddie Quiz... "Which Side of Eddie Gordon are you?" After you are done, look at all the results... Because they are so fucking funny.  urlLink Eddie Quiz 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Took many quizzes today, here are the results:    You are naturally born with a gift, whether it be poetry, writing or song. You love beauty and creativity, and usually are highly intelligent. Others view you as mysterious and dreamy, yet also bold since you hold firm in your beliefs.     urlLink   What Type of Soul Do You Have ?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      hand holding - you like to be in constant physical contact with your special someone but you don't want to take things too quickly.    urlLink   What Sign of Affection Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla     urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You are Juan Moreno!!    urlLink   Which Completely Random Person Are You!!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Furnulum pani nolo. "I don't want a toaster." Generally, things (like this quiz) tend to tick you off.  You have contemplated doing grievous bodily harm to door-to-door salesmen.     urlLink   Which Weird Latin Phrase Are You?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Casual    urlLink   How's your AIM grammar? (With pictures.)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Seer    urlLink   The ULTIMATE personality test     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      you are the "you're so dumb" happy bunny. you are brutal in your words and enjoy putting others down.     urlLink   which happy bunny are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're the loving smile,the one that is entirely devoted to others,especially that one person.You really can't get them out of your head,but then,you don't really want to.    urlLink   What Kind of Smile are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      PASSIONATE LOVER. You love to love, always looking for a relationship. You cannot live without it. Your lover must be passionate  and you want that you and your partner melt into each other. He/She should not try to take the domination . You dont want a relationship without passion, and the sexuality plays a big part. The first moment you meet him/her is one of the most important. There has to be something between you , you cannot explain. From the first moment on everything must fix. But when this passion disappears you disappear to. For you it is better to leave than to see your love restrained.  PLEASE VOTE, I want to know what you think about my quiz, I worked hard on it.You can always message me or tell me how I can improve that quiz. Ill sure write back.    urlLink   	~THE big LOVE TEST!! What do you need? With PICS! For girls and boys!~     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      You're Gangsta Bitch Barbie.  You're tough and you like it rough, and of course you like to pop a cap in any wiggers ass.    urlLink   If You Were A Barbie, Which Messed Up Version Would You Be?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Aphrodite/Eros    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Your Heart is Red    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    AND LAST BUT NOT LEAST... I MADE A QUIZ MYSELF!! "Which Side of Eddie Gordon Are You??"   You are the EVIL Eddie    urlLink   Which Side of Eddie Gordon are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my computer, on the keyboard you can see (sorta) English and Hebrew.  urlLink Click Here   This is me looking at Nikki's blog.  urlLink Click Here   This is my Bookmark Bar, and you can see that one of my quick links is Nikki's blog, because I am that pathetic, and I read it constantly, I check it on an hourly basis.  urlLink Click Here   Okay... And here you can see the quick link up close... See where it says 'Nikki'... Yeah... Pathetic, isn't it?  urlLink Click Here 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just woke up. I have no idea what I am gonna do today. I have no idea what time it is... No, wait... I have a clock on my computer... 9:57. My stomach hurts, my mouth is dry, and I think I'm gonna take a shower... NOW, unless someone (hint, hint) signs on within the next few minutes.  About that thing yesterday, I am still shocked... But only when I think of it... So I guess it's better now.  I hope I'm gonna do something social today... And if not today, then hopefully tomorrow!  Tomorrow I am getting together with Toby and Noah to work on our graduation rap.  I think we're gonna use the beat of Nas's "One Mic".  Anybody heard that? No? Okay.  This concludes my entry.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      STATUS: Freaked out  I am freaked out...  Just found out something...  Oh. My. God.  I am not trying to act like a drama queen, I am seriously in a fucking state of shock.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quoting Lucy's wonderful blog... I would like to also post another post about Eddie. This is Lucy's entry:  "i shall now tell you who i hate. eddie. Ok, for those of you who don’t know eddie (you are so lucky) he is a guy in my grade. how shall i go about explaining eddie. well, first, he has 3 lips. which is overwhelmingly hot. no, no joke. 3 lips; because he constantly lips above his upper lip, so he has developed this irritation above his top lip, that looks like a 3rd lip. eww. next, eddie is really into dungeons and dragons. which is weird.   but, i mean that’s no reason not to like the poor chap. I don’t like him because he’s mean and annoying. i wanted to pelt him with baseballs. so, when eddie is talk, like, for example in a debate, he can’t talk in a fluid sentence. it sounds like this: “and *moan* that’s why i think *moan* that drug *moan* testing in businesses *moan* should be *moan* *moan* legal.” it’s so gross. and during PE, omg this is the worst; ok, during PE he always tries to encourage the kids on the other team. and be all just when there’s a hard call to make in baseball. and it’s not like he know anything about it, he is the most un-athletic person in the world.  the best was when we started our baseball unit in PE, so we all got in groups and did slow pitch and hit sorta thing. so, i was pitching. and every time i pitched something non-perfect he go “nice pitch LUCY”. and so finally i was just like “NICE FACE EDDIE!!!!!” and he shut up. twas awesome. so yea. i hate him. i want to shove his head up his ass. oh, mad do i wanna do that, g2g"   This is what I think of Eddie: Annoying  I don't "hate" him, per se... I just find him incredibley, amazingly, overly annoying... But I feel bad for him...  Anyway... Everytime any teacher asks a question, he is the first one to raise his hand, and then either one of the following three things happen:  A) He will raise his hand, and if the teacher does not call him within five seconds of his hand being in the air, he will go: "Ummm..." every ten seconds until the teacher will notice him.  B) He will raise his hand, and so will someone else, and the teacher will call on the other person and Eddie would groan in frustration VERY loudly.  C) If he does finally get called on, he will pause for a few seconds, then he will say: "*Laughs obnoxiously* I forgot... Come back to me" or "Dangit!! I forgot! *laughs obnoxiously*  That's Eddie for you.  Oh, and always before J.S. Eddie will read a book. And as soon as Tsipi, the teacher, comes he will continue reading until he is told not to. One time, she told him not to read, and he said: "I'm not reading!!" in his high-pitched voice although his gigantic eyeballs were staring right into his tome. And she said: "Eddie! Put the book away or I am confiscating it!" and he said: "What?!? But I wasn't reading!" and she said: "Don't say 'what?' to me!!" and then Eddie said... "I  will  say 'what?' all I want because this isn't fair."  Eddie spent the rest of the class in the office.  This is a picture of Eddie, courtesy of Lucy:     Yes, Ladies and Gentleman, observe the perfect circle that is... Eddie!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has not been 12 hours of having a blog and I already have 4 posts. Wait, now there are  5  posts on my blog. That means that I posted approximately 1 post/2.4 hours
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to brush my teeth like, five minutes ago, and in my sink I see a spider. This wasn't your  mundane  spider... (Oooh, nice Vocabage!) I had a chance to meet  "El Retardo Spidero" !! 'How was  "El Retardo Spidero"  retarded?' you may ask... Well, here is the story... So I was brushing my teeth, and  "El Retardo Spidero"  was in the sink trying to climb out of it. Anyway, every time  "El Retardo Spidero"  got to a really high point in the sink, trying to get out... He slipped and fell back down. So I watched him for a couple of minutes, laughing constantly... Finally, I felt bad for  "El Retardo Spidero" , so I got a Q-Tip and he climbed on it and I released him right by the sink... Anyway,  "El Retardo Spidero"  clearly did not want to leave his fun time at my sink, so he literally  JUMPS  back into the sink, repeating the process again...  I wonder if he's still there.  Yeah, still there.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay... I promised to explore the fascinating the life of the badger... BUT! Instead of doing that, I decided to "badger" all of you by yet ANOTHER sarcastic post.  Okay, these are other people's blogs.  Nikki: http://metalmouth.blogspot.com/  Lucy H: http://www.livejournal.com/users/yellowstrat/  These are cool pages.  My Raps: http://www.soundclick.com/bands/4/jewishmcmusic.htm  Okay... And now for a funny website: http://www.ebaumsworld.com/  Goodbye.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. As of yesterday, my daddy owns 2% of the Sears Tower 2. Nikki said yes.  Okay... Tune in next time, kids... When we explore the fascinating life of the BADGER!!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey. Welcome to Sarcasm 24/7. I don't think this blog is sarcastic nor am I for the most part, but it sounded like a name somebody who actually knows what they're doing would give to their blog. So... Here is what I did on this very interesting day: 6:30 - Woke up - Took Shower 7:00 - Got dressed 7:02 - Searched frantically for my cool shirt that I wore today 7:03 - Found it 7:10 - Brushed teeth 7:12 - Posed in front of mirror looking tough for eight minutes or so 7:20 - Listened to music on my bed 7:29 - Realized my bus pass is expired, took two dollars from my piggy bank (AT LEAST I HAVE THE BALLS TO ADMIT I HAVE ONE!!) 7:30 - Left for my bus 7:32 - Boarded bus 7:45 - Arrived at place where I connect buses 8:05 - Connected buses 8:30 - Arrived at my destination, Tehiyah Day School  OK PAUSE FOR A SECOND... You may be bored but now is when stuff gets interesting... So keep reading!!  8:40 - Oh, deathly homeroom!! How I despise, thee... But you know what I hate more? Ms. Prowse playing stupid songs (for singing at our Graduation) on her iPod for an hour when we're not even gonna pick them... Then when we FINALLY chose the top four... She nominates "The Rainbow Song", AGAIN... And we all say no... But she persists...   9:40 -  Math class, whoopee!! Copied some things on my composition book and pretended to look interested.  10:15 - Science class, whoopee!! Thanks to the help of Nikki and Emma, I actually did something productive today... (And tieing Gatorade bottles filled with water to Eddie's backpack is definitley NOT productive...) In the middle of me doing that thing I was doing for Mr. A (I had to graph something), Emma asks me if I pluck my eyebrows. Um...  NO .  11:00 - Lunch. Ate Tomato & Rice Soup and Ritz crackers. Oh, and Oreos. Then we played Butts-Up (It's slaughter house but when someone gets out, he/she (usually he) gets on the wall andthe person who got him out gets to peg him.) Fun Fun Fun!!  11:45 - Um... Kabbalat Shabbat... Watched an excellent film on something... Nah, I'm kidding... It was really sad, actually... OH WAIT!! And we sang "I am a Latke" thanks to me!! Fucking awesome!!! Then Rachel told us a story about how she find out that Tsipi and her are  Second Cousins !!! Who would have thought??  12:30 - Physical Education... Dodgeball!! Fun Fun Fun!!  1:10 - Recess... Studied for Vocab 20 (the last one, finally!!)  1:25 - CORE = BORE!!! Took Vocab 20, got 20/20 (fits the occassion....), had Taylor dollars... Nick got one, Nikki got one, and Lucy got two. Then we watched a horrible, horrible, horrible movie on the "Music of the Civil War"... Jesus Christ!! How the FUCK is this in anyway productive to our education?!? All they did was sing "Dixie" and that song that goes "Whooorah! Whoooorah!"... And we all finally saw Ken Burns for the first time... He is younger than we imagined... And his nose kept flaring and moving all over the place when he talked.  2:50 - School is out, finally listened to music (I crip-walked in the bathroom to my rap, scaring the 5th graders).  3:00 - Boarded the bus.   3:30 - Got off at Solano with (Alphabetically by last name): Robbie, Nikki, Lucy and Ari-KH. We went to Cactus Taqueria. I got nachos for 80 cents. Then we told stupid stories about jelly beans, Safeway, Adam and other.  4:00 - Gave Nikki a CD with a song on it. Here is the URL: http://fileserv5.soundclick.com/fastg6\HiD/jewishmc+theheartsballadrevised.mp3 Nice, huh?  4:15 - Boarded bus home, listening to rap.  4:45 - Arrived home.  4:50 to 6:00 - I dunno. Too nervous.  6:15 to 7:15 - Talked to Nikki on AIM  7:15 to 7:50 - Dinner  7:50 to 9:00 - Talked to Nikki some more.  9:30 to 10:15 - Made a blog.  This concludes my day.  Questions, Comments, Hate-Mail, Love-Letters?!? Email them to me at fearlessdeadman@hotmail.com  Thank you.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Muslim song, ladies and gentlemen: http://fileserv1.soundclick.com/fastg6\HiF/jpawz+themuslimsong.mp3 Feedback please
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aight aight... Here's the 4-1-1 for yo bitch ass... I went to see Shrizzek Dos with my bro at Bizzay Street. Shits ill. Pussy pants was phat, yo... Shit was jamming... I then went to the Appizzle store in order to get my... Okay I'll stop with that... I went to get a mini iPod but it was all SOLD OUT FOR FATHER'S DAY. Do people actually buy their fathers gifts for father's day worth $250? Jesus. So I ordered it and it should arrive in 4 weeks. But I bought iLife 04 which comes with Garageband and I am currently making a song about muslims to be realeased tomorrow. Not today because I just finished it and it's too late for me to record. I also bought a protecting case for my iPod. I got My Baby's Daddy on DVD from Blockbuster which I will watch shortly. Oh, on the way back from Blockbuster a cop pulled my mom and I over for going around a U-Turn too fast or something... And my mom didn't have the registration with her in the car!! :-o  My mom paid a $10,000 fine and is currently in San Quentin.  No... Joking... She is currently at home... The cop let her go because my mom is pretty.  Sooooooooooooooooo... What else? Oh, I totally redecorated my room. Whatever. Um... Hmm... Garageband is cool...  I'll post the Muslim song tomorrow... It's funny... It starts sentimental, then it's blues, then country, then rap and then salsa... Amazing.  I deserve a grammy or at LEAST a fucking (insert valueless item here).  Let me check my agenda for what I'm doing the next couple of days.  Sunday: Sit in front of the computer and do nothing. Eat - Tenative. Pee - Tenative. Drink - Tenative. Sleep - Tenative. Monday: See Sunday Tuesday: See Monday Wednesday: See Tuesday Thursday: See Wednesday Friday: See Thursday Saturday: See Friday  TILL NEXT TIME!! This has been another Sausage Fest Production.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Graduated yesterday. T'was good. Then party at Robbie's house. Good. Good stuff. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why don't people update their fucking blogs?!? Whatever. Hi. Picnic was today. Good. Mollie is too argumentative. Um... The picnic was cool. This is what I did in chronological order. 1. Changed 2. Football 3. Pool 4. Um... Ate? 5. Volleyball 6. Dunk Tank 7. Pool? 8. Water Football 9. Some other shit. 10. Left 11. Argued with Mollie.   Bye.  Oh, and by the way... I look good in a wifebeater...  Agreements? Disagreements?  V Comment Below V
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Toby's party was cool. I no longer have a mohawk. School picnic tomorrow. Cooool!! I am hungry. Adios. Oh. And also. I forgot. To say. That. I. Like. To. Eat. Alot. And. There. Fore. I. Am. A. Fatass.  136. Pounds. Is. My. Weight.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my room: This is my wall, with the confederate flag visible. Although I am really a union...  urlLink Click Here   And if you move a little to the right you see...  urlLink Click Here   The other wall...  urlLink Click Here   And if you move a little to the right again you see...  urlLink Click Here   My TV:  urlLink Click Here   My closet... I think...  urlLink Click Here   My desk:  urlLink Click Here   My bean bag AKA the Reading spot:  urlLink Click Here   YEAH  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My new moahawk (sp?) which I shall cut today:  urlLink Click Here   My trophy that I got yesterday for Most Improved Volleyball Playa:  urlLink Click Here  Notice the shit in the background. And by shit I mean stuff, not dung.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another survery!! I'd like to clarify that this survery is from the year of 2001, therefore it has questions about the Backstreet Boys and N'Sync and shit... Okay...  1. What is your full name? Ohav Sean S******y C***n >2. BSB or Nsync? NEITHER, but if I must choose......................... Suicide... >3. Pepsi or Coke?: Pepsi 4. What color pants do you have on right now? Army >5. What are you listening to right now? The voices in my head 6. what did you eat for lunch today? 2 cheese sandwiches >7. What is right next to you now? Um... Pillow, blanket, and my TROPHY!!! 14. Do you like snow, sun, or rain? Sun >15. How is the weather right now? It's night... Cloudless... 16.What did you do last night? Don't remember... I think I did absolutely nothing but I'm not sure. >17. Last person you talked on the phone with? My grandma 18. What did you do today? School, Robbie's house, Athletics recognition shit. >19. What is the nicest thing you find in the opposite sex? PERSONALITY (NOT Sex appeal) >20. Favorite number: 18 and 29 21. How do you eat an Oreo? WHAT'S UP WITH THE OREO QUESTIONS IN EVERY TEST I TAKE?!? Okay, I put it in my mouth and SWALLOW. Couple hours later I... Nope, won't go there. >24. Favorite Song: Too many, my raps I guess, a lot of Eminem, but my ultimate favorite has to be Lose Yourself. >25. Favorite band: D-12  >26. Birth date: August 18 >28. Height?: 5'3  >29. Do you wear contacts? No >31. What school do you attend?: Tehiyah, but it'll be JCHS in 5 days...  32. Who are your closest friends? Too many. But if I must choose... Robbie, KH, Toby, Lucy, Nikki 33. Best advice given to you? Put the toilet seat down. >34. What do you want to be when you grow up? Actor, rapper, archeologist 35. What is your favoritest food? Indian, Chinese, Italian, American, LAMB CURRY!!! >36. Who is the funniest person you know? KH >38. Favorite day of the year? B-Day. >39. Favorite girls perfume? Channel 5 >40. fav men cologne? Abercrombie & Fitch >41. Do you like to dance? Yes. >42. Favorite brand name? Gap, Old Navy, Shady LTD. 43. If you could change your name, what would it be? Dunno! >44. Worst sickness you've ever had? Henna infection. 45. Do you like scary movies or happy? Both, but primarily happy. >46. Night or day? Day 47. Summer or winter? Summer >48. Hugs or kisses? Both 50. If you could change one thing about yourself what would it be? Nothing. I am perfect from head to toe. 51. Do u consider cheerleading a sport? No. >52. What did you think of this survey? I like it. >53. Do you want your friends to write back? NA >54. Who is least likely to respond? NA >55. Who is most likely to respond? NA >56. Your location? Albany, CA >57. Do you care about the way you look? Yes! >58. Do you get a tan only in the summer? Um... I dunno? I guess not... >59. Do you have big ears? No 60. Are you the class clown? I think me and like two others are... >61. In the past week have you cried? Yes, I think 62. cut your hair? Yes >63. worn a skirt?: No >64. Have you lied in this survey? I hope not >OUT OF THE PEOPLE IN YOUR CLASS... >65. Is your best friend in your class? Most of em >66. Is the person you like in your class? Yes >67. Do you hate anybody in your class? Hate? No. Dislike? Yes. >68. Do u loove any1 in your class? Taking this back to q 66, yes. >69. Do you believe in ghosts? Um... what does this have anything to do with people in my class... but yeah, i do. >70. did u enjoy this test? yeah
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just came back from the athletic recognition award thing, which it was... LMAO! Well... I won a tropy for Most Imporved player on volleyball which is fairly apropos. Um... What else? No more Wednesdays and Thursdays at Tehiyah ever again... :( Um... Walt Whitman... Eh... Mmmm... Graduating on Tuesday... SAD!! I am so gonna cry at graduation... :'( So sad... So sad...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am having the worst day EVEEEERRRRRRR!! God, I am so fucking pissed off... AAAAARGHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!! I miss my bus, I lose volleyball game, Lucy gets mad at me (the WORST), then by Hebrew I become totally crazy, and I scream in the bushes and shit... Core!!! FUCKING WALT WHITMAN CAN GO SUCK HIS OWN COCK... I hate him... Actually, I don't... But I'm just mad... Then graduation practice... Whatever... I'm just upset because Lucy is mad at me which sucks... Small... Infected... Hairy... BALLLS!!!!!!!!!! AHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!! BREAK STUFF!!!!  I'm not really that crazy... :-/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry I haven't been on in a while...  Anyway... I am pissed off... I just returned from a celebration of Israel's 56th birthday in Pac-Bell park in San Francisco. Outside the baseball stadium stood an approximate amount of 300 pro-Palestine protestors stomping on Israeli flags, spitting (THEY ACTUALLY DID IN THE BEGINNING, TOWARDS THE PEOPLE COMING) on the people attending the event, and shouting curses at the people.  It's okay to protest, that's one thing. Then it's one thing to protest during another nation's holiday. But it's absolutely wrong to act that way in front of another country. That is just inhumane.  Spitting, acting violent, yelling and burning flags is disrespectful and simply uncool. It's just morally wrong. Especially in the USA.  Fuckers.  Purely inhumane.  Then I met Ari, Lucy and Simone... And Ari and I wanted to throw shit at them, but Simone thought that throwing Hershey's Kisses at them was wrong, but she said that swearing at them was okay.  I am pissed off.   If I were a Palestinian (tfu tfu tfu), I am sure that I could not have picked a better location, and I would be happy that my protesting worked and pissed people off, but because I was one of the people who the protest was directed at, I have no choice but to be pissed off and angry. Woah, big run-on...  I am angry.  It just gave me more reasons to hate Palestine... As if my current reasons aren't enough.  If it took being violent to make the protestors shut up, I'd have hurt them all. Each and everyone of them. Muslim, Christian, and even Jew (there were Anti-Zionist Jews protesting with them...).  I would have thrown stuff at them, even if I got arrested for it.  I was so tempted to hurt them, it was unbelivable. Just seeing the Palestinian flag makes me wanna punch someone.  I hate them. I fucking hate them. All of them. Even the non-radical ones. Just because you're not willing to die to show your hate of a country doesn't mean you don't hate them and want them dead.  This protest made me want to join the Israeli army, as I had doubts about that. I want to be drafted and fight in Palestine, against Palestinians.   I am almost 14, and I will hate Palestine until the day that I die.  If I ever become a millionare, I hereby  swear  that half of the money I make will go to aiding the State of Israel.  Back to the protest, I think some people were kidding when they said: "Let's cuss them out!" or "Let's throw shit at them!" but I was serious. I had a plan to steal the microphone, run with it to the bathroom, and from a bathroom stall yell anti-Palestine chants.  Fuck them all.  Fuck the radicals, the non-radicals, the Anti-Zionists, the Nazis, the Skinheads, the KKK, CNN, Al-Jazeera, the Palestinians, the Arabs, the Muslims, and most of all... The misinformed ones.  FUCK THEM ALL!!  May you die you fucking sons of bitches.  My heart is with Israel forever!!  ~1~    P.S. I bought an awesome shirt that says: "Pro-Israel... Pro-Peace" and there is a flag of Israel with peace signs on it. I bought it to support the greatest country on earth, and I shall wear it proudly tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      GET A PIECE OF PAPER AND NUMBER IT 1-11 (NO CHEATING)  1. Do you have dark or light hair? dark 2. If you were outon a date would you want to go to a party or go out to eat? eat 3. What's yor favorite color out of Pink, Yellow, Baby Blue, or Sea Green? baby blue 4. Pick yor favorite hobbies out of: Surfing, Skating, or skiing   skiing 5. If you could pick a store between Old Navy, Pacific Sunwear, or Victoria's Secret which one would you pick? old navy 6. What's yor favorite state out of Kalifornia, Florida, or Ohio  kalifornia 7. In the summer would you rather go to the beach or go sumwhere cooler? cooler 8. What's yor birthday month? august 9. Would you rather chill @ home or go out wit frendz? depends... but i guess home 10. Name a person of the opposite sex. (confidental) 11. Make a wish..... (confidental)   *ANSWERS* 1. dark- sexy light- fake  2. go out to eat- romantic go to a party- playful  3. pink- cute yellow- loud babyblue- cool seagreen- horny  4. surfing- active skating- determined sking- daring  5. old navy- preppy pacific sunwear- fun victoria's secret- sexy  6. California- you like being around people Florida- party time in the Heat Ohio- quite, likes the cold  7. beach- tan likes the sun somewhere cooler- pale and original  8. january: popualr february: lovely march: loud april: playful may: chills a lot june: happy july: smooth august: fun september: quite october: out going november: pimpin it december: warm  9. home: boring go out with friends: crazy  10. that person will fall in love with you!!!!!  MORE  1. Name given at birth: Ohav 2. Nicknames: Fatass, Fat Tits, Fatah 3. Favorite words: Fyke, Fuck, Fatah (All the F-words) 4. Hometown: Tel Aviv, Albany, CA 5. Current Residence: Albany 6. Croutons or Bacon bits? Crutons 7. Favorite salad dressing: None 8. Shampoo or conditioner? Shampoo 9. Have you ever gone skinny dipping? Yes 10. Do you make fun of people? Yes 11. Favorite color: Blue 12. Have you ever been convicted of a crime: No 13. One pillow or two, cotton or feathers? I sleep with 5 feather pillows 14. Pets? 2 cats 15. Favorite Music: rap 16. Hobbies?? music, friends, movies, acting, tv, internet, too many... 17. Toothpaste: colgate 18. Favorite foods: lamb curry 19. Do you get along with your parents? yes 20. Favorite town to chill in: room 21. Favorite ice cream flavor: espresso, bubble gum 22. Favorite drink (non-alcoholic): v8, coke, vanilla sode, 23. Adidas, Nike, or Reebok? nike 24. Favorite perfume/cologne: ralph lauren's mystique 25. Favorite Website(s): hiphopgame.com 26. Favorite subject in school: core, js, pe and comps 27. Least favorite subject in school: science 28. Favorite alcoholic drink: tequila, bacardi, vodka 29. Favorite sport to watch: football, pool and bowling. oh and soccer 30. Most Humiliating moment: like im gonna share that on my blog 31. Craziest or silliest idea: wtf? 32. What do you look for in a romantic interest? smart, funny, nice, sophisticated, able to talk to and good looking. 33. Say one nice thing about the person who sent you this email: im cool 34. The person you sent this to, that is least likely to respond: NA  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is what I did today, briefly:  J.S.: Debate Math: Sleep P.E.: Kick (Ass) Lunch: Eat Core: Cooked Hebrew: Trouble Recess: Pegged Graduation Pt. 1: Jumped Graduation Pt. 2: Sung  Then I went to Robbie's house. Then I came home.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG! I forgot to say... You know those things where they guess your weight and if they guess it wrong, you win a prize... I did that and the guy guessed 111 (bwahahahaha)!! So I stepped on the scale and saw that I weigh 135 lb. I got a prize for that. Then I went to another place where they had that. The woman guessed 113 (bwahahahaha)!! This time I weighed 137 lb. because I ate Mexican food and candy.  I am a fatass.  But, I truly believe that at least 20 lb. of that is muscle.  I am pretty strong, and buff... Really!!  I am not fat. I really am not... I don't mind being fat, but I'm not. I'm muscular. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Back from Great America. It actually did NOT suck, it was quite fun. Anyway, I of course rode all the scary rollercoasters (Ah, shit... I'm bragging now...) I met Patrick Star, Dora the Explorer, Scooby Doo, and Blue!! I even sat on Blue's thinking chair and sang songs... I got Patrick's autograph as well... But the coolest thing I did was... BUNGEE JUMPING!! Is it Bungee or Bunjee? Whatever. Anyway... Here is a pic of where I bungee/bunjee jumped:  urlLink Click Here  So, they put me on the harness and shit, and I was slowly lifted up until 160 feet, where I was just staring at the ground. Now, instead of them deciding when to let go, I have a pully thing next to me, and as soon as I am up there, I have to pull it... I knew that if I thought about it too much that I would be too scared to pull it, so as soon as I got up, I pulled it and droppeed 160 feet to the ground. I then swung back and forth, swearing in English, Hebrew, and Spanish. Scary shit. I got it on tape. Then I rode the less cool rollercoasters such as Top Gun, Drop Zone, etc *yawn*... Almost fell asleep on Top Gun. Baby ride. I got wet from the water rides though. Which I can still feel on my pruney feet.  I didn't see Alex or Merav during Great America so that's good. Toby, Lucy K and Dylan were there... But they were cool for the most part.  I won 4 things: A picture of Eminem, a monkey, a pig, and a pony. Yay!  So, I had a blast.  Yeah.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         HAHAHAHAHA!!  Thank you deejekyll for the pic... Funny shit.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today we had a 3 hour graduation planny thing... Anyway, I sit down on the table and it like... Almost collapses...  So Ms. Prowse says: "That's what happens when you're such a big guy." And I obviously took that offensively... Thinking she called me fat... She explains to me that she didn't mean it and I insisted that it was fine. Later on she takes a dog biscuit and throws it at Eitan ordering him to eat it as a joke... I take it and I tell her: "Since I am sooo fat... I am going to eat the dog biscuit..." And she pleaded me not to but I almost did... Then we were quiet during something so Ms. Prowse took us to the Kwik-E-Mart... But... Instead of everyone getting a dollar to be quiet, I told her that I wanted two dollars if she wants me to forgive her. Haha, it worked.  I was rewarded for being fat with fattening foods. I'm a Fat Bastard.  Am I fat? Do I care? Do  you  care? I don't think I'm that fat but I don't care either... I think I am very muscular and handsome (and so does Ms. Prowse, she told me...)  Tomorrow we are going to Great America. Yay.  It's gonna suck though, for the most part...  People like Lucy K, Merav, Alex, Toby and Dylan would be like bragging about how much they know the place and all the attraction and be like: "Oooh... Let's go to "Top Gun" or "DropZone" as soon as we get there... Then in the end they'd be like "Well... I went on DropZone 14 times..." "Yeah, well... I went there 17!!" and it's gonna suck because of them. I personally love roller coasters and am not afraid to go on any of them, but if I hang around that crowd it'll convince ME to brag about that stuff and hate myself.  My mommy is coming... I am taking Toby, Noah and Evan in my car. I wish I had different people *cough* but it's fine I guess....  A propósito... ¿Usted todo sabía que sé español fluido?? ¿Usted no , usted? Pozo... Aquí estoy hablando español... La mayoría las muestras vendrán fuera de extraño, pero lo que.    Con mucho mucho amor y admiración,  Ohav
     
    
</post>


</Blog>