<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hi, my new frind. Im a secondary school student in studying Singapore.Its my pleasure to start my own websiteand I wish that I would be able to continue writing here as long as I live ( provided that I do no forget about you).    Anyway, Im a skinny male with a height of about 1.8 metres. Wooooo..... quite tall isnt it? However, this had caused me to be terribly underweight (so sad), leaving my report book with an sarcarstic comment, " Need to refer to doctors for advices". Crap!    Before I stop typing, I wished that I could score an A1 for the coming O' level Mother tongue.    See ya...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Yesterday had finally past. It past like a wind, or like a slght breeze that took years to past by me. It is the reopen of the school, the most detestable place for me since I was in my 'holiday' mood.    The school never stop giving me surprise... Oral!!! It is on the coming Friday! I really hate to say that Im very afraid to face up with this oral. Maybe it is my youth causes. Sigh......Why did I only learnt to speak properly in primary one... I have at least 4 years lesser of years of speech. Even now the past difficulty that I had still exsist.    Looking on the bright side, I have finally finish recording down all the birth dates of 2e4 .....ermmmm.....YuuuuHuuuuu!!!! However I forget to get their add...How can I deliver the birthday cards?
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Socialise ......is so sweet Knowing more people ......is so lovely Playing games ...... is so relaxing What about love? It's fantastic  Love is always bestowed as a gift - freely, willingly and without expectation. We don't love to be loved; we love to love.   Leo Buscaglia   Never convert love into hatred...... you will still be friend
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         The power of love cannot be underestimated. That's all for today.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I just found out the difference of Christainity from other religon; the legends in the holy bible is more interesting than other religions can provide.    However, Im not really interested in all of the story. Im only interested in the stories that I have haven't heard before, thanks to the game 'Vampire The Masquerade'. Cain, Adam first wife are the examples.....Most importantly, I wanted to know what is The book of Nod.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Time flies, now I'm already secondary 4. I have been looking at her back for months, fantasise about dating her. Friends, Im sure that we are friends, but Im cannot confirm that we will be more than  JUST FRIENDS .     "Suffering" is the only word to describe my situation. Ironically, somehow it will become my favourite pastime to peek at her curvature. What is of LOVE? It makes me fells like angel, yet it brought me deeper into suffering. Why do the cell in my gens cause me to fall in love with her? Why!? Maybe it wil be the only thing that will bright up my life, giving me the thoughts of opportunity. Or maybe its a challenge for me to take?
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Im bored today as there is no more vampire the masquerade with me.    In the afternoon, an unexpected just rang. At first I thought that this call will spice up me for a while, but it seems like it had only added stress on me. Sad !!! Now I feel kind of lost and did not know what to do.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What's The Meaning    What is of examination? Is it use to test our knowledge  or is it used to guage us?  What is the education? Is it to be gaining knowledge or is ut to finding jobs or even to please our own parents?  What is civilisation? It is actually settling down of human but it appears it is false in present decades.  What high technology? It is sophsicated knowledge develop by us to serve ourselves, however it is suffocating our motherly planet.  What is of war? It is to be fought by the heroes to protect justice, on the other hand, it is started by the greed and selfishness of the apes. Some huge wars are fought to end all war, but it didn't take much longer for a human heart to fall into path of greed once more. So another misery surfaced to the world again.  A pathetic world indeed......
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hi there, its been a long time since I last write into the post. Im glad that I was freed from the grip of the O'level temporary, on the other hand, I was very worried about m result. Being not sure that I will get a great result make me sleepless for a few days........even though i think I may do quite well......I'll just keep my finger cross until I take the oral, listening, and finally the result in August.    For the solarcar competition, I was relieved that my team's solar car was able to move. In fact we got a C.O.P.    My live changes now. I could not concentrate on my studis because of the post eaxams blue.......saddd......I hope I'll get better when I wake up the next day.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         July......    This month is full of surprise..........I finally got the the chance to go to the stage to receive the solarcar prize.......Hahaz.....    On the other hand my night mare had also awaken. I am doomed in the chinese listening comprehension....about 12/20. However, I should look on the bright side........Cos I got into the band 1 in physics........LOl......:(...the teacher is really boring......and insult me twice in 4 lessons....    Lastly, I have finally going to be passing out soon........yuhooooo!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          The month of August is full of challenge for me, due to the fact that O' level is around the corner and prelim is here. What a life is that? Ireally hoped that This year can end sooner, so that my worries by gone faster. However, deep in my, my feelings contridicts what I had just said, for I will miss my dearest friends, especially the ones whom I miss most.    I will not meet them in the future, will I? Next year, I will be in a new environment, making new friends (I hope). What am I thinking about? I wish I would be able to meet my friends in the future and now, I should consider on studying hard.    Best wishes to everybody for the coming prelim, especially for my dearest friend! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>