<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The first official, ontime (i hope) friday feeling news post. Wel lthis week has been a rather eventful one and so my usual scouring of the web was not as thorough as one would hope but as always I will make do with what I have and hope that everyone saw at least one thing that was new.  These first few weeks im trying out structures for the friday feeling,  sub-headings, no sub-headings etc... so bare with me. This week is a top 3 stucture under each sub-heading      New Animations of the week:   1) Weebl releaces the last of the Pikea Saga. Watch it  urlLink here    2) Rodger Moore, Tony Hart('s music) and eyebrows.  urlLink Bask  in the glory   3)  Well I was going to reccomend watching a homestar runner episode ( urlLink here ) but i just saw a helarious mismatch of badgers and kenya. Go see ...  urlLink NOW!    New Games of the week   1) This difficult, though highly addictive game once you have the hang of it, game involves pendulum swinging and bees. Yes the things that make honey.They're not just the capital of bulgaria it seems. Ver fun so play it  urlLink here    2) Ok this is not a new game but ive been very into Domo-kun very recently: so  urlLink play  the game   3) My third game to play is from ferry halim, designers that have consistently produced the most aestheticaly pleasing games on the net. They do have a newgame that as always is very good ( urlLink here ) but i want you to play  urlLink this  game, it is so simple an idea (that you circle like coloured fles [are they flies] by drawing round them) but is amazingly addictive. With Orisinal games you will never be bored- or stressed    An oldy but a goody:  Im sorry, i have stolen these three links from a b3ta newsletter but it is only because they grouped my favourite videos (which i had seen originaly elsewhere) together. So here goes  1)  This is  urlLink poor mans skydiving   (attempt number 1)  2)  I just loved this when i first saw it: a homage to computer systems of the past:  urlLink hey hey 16k    3)   urlLink underground surfing . Nothing to do with caves   runner up)  Kittens. Motorbikes. London.  urlLink Enough said    Random Weirdness of the week:   1)  This guy decides to draw a thousand characters and  urlLink here  they are.   2)  Ive been told Im lazy (see tests below) so im starting to do:  urlLink webxercise     3)  This is a little animations showing the advantages and disadvantages of robots.  urlLink Enjoy    'Dam cute pics making me well up...' of the week:   1)   urlLink lil' donkeys   2)  urlLink Lil' Otters   3)  urlLink Lil' Kittens    New Tests of the mind this week:  Well these are what people are doing nowadays on the web: Tests. People seem to enjoy knowing more about themselves so they do interesting, thought provoking tests. I cant speak for the mentioned "people" but i can say that every so often i could murder a well thought out test.   1)  This is my favourite one for this week. It's a little bit different (as it is based around what would happen if you were a dragon). Click  urlLink here  I was yellow   2)  This was quite interesting: What  urlLink feeling  do you represent?   3)  The spark always had an interesting test to help you through the day, but now the spark has evolved,  evolved into  urlLink Spark Life . New this week is their lazy test: Are you as apathetic as me? Go  urlLink see     
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      but in the meanwhile i'll leave you with the few links from the main site before the extravaganza of the main post comming to a computer screen near you, on the 25 of June!  The first is a online startegy game that is packed full of wit, plot changes and strange puns: its a murder mystery that will stop everything until you complete it  urlLink Clicky   (please wait for it to load: well worth it)   Here is a site of an artist, please dont turn simultaneously into narcaleptics, which is telling it like it is: Mysteries of the world revealed!    urlLink Clicky 2   This little video is of a frenchman who plays many types of music, but on horns located around his body. Not as strange as it sounds but still pretty astounding and funny     urlLink Clicky 3  urlLink    My last one for tonight i can safely state shows the best guitarist in the world, bar none. Enjoy  urlLink Clicky 4  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ...&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>


<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Im going to start this blog with the review I recently wrote about the new Harry Potter film: Harry potter and the Prizoner of Azkaban. I do know that this was originaly posted on my general thoughts blog but at that point I did not know that I was going to branch out into sub-blogs. So here it is; my first review for the movie rack, but more should come soon...   So now back to the subject of today’s post: Harry Potter and the Prizoner of Azkaban. This is the film that everyone has been seeing this week, and with good reason, and I’d like to see a ticket sale for a different film this week. This film is quite thoroughly amazing to those that are familiar with the books, which is everyone except a couple of Norwegian moles that slept through this best-selling craze because they were too tired (“Please can’t I have another 6 months in bed”) and hit the snooze button sometime in 1998, as well as to those that are not. This review will not cover the plot of the story, I’m sorry a deep sin of reviewing to leave out the synopsis, but hey, everyone knows the storry already (see Norwegian mole comment). I am a self-confessed super-fan of Harry potter and felt very good after seeing a film which was very magical in its picturesque hogwartsy way but I felt rather let down when I saw the second film. The first book had that very cosy fealling to it and so the style of Chris Columbus suited it very well but the second is a much darker film but that is not really shown in the film because the happy go lucky feeling of the school seemed to take away from the dark of the forbidden forest sequence and the final sequence with the basilisk-snake. This film is totally different, but as that very annoying child from the Macdonalds advert has been telling us: “Change is Good”. Alfonso Cuaron has brought to life the film and has changed it from what was seemed to be a children’s film into a film that appeals on different levels to different people: the principal that has made the Harry Potter books world wide best-sellers. I liked the feeling of the last films, ok they were aimed toward the smaller of us, please no short jokes I’m trying to make a point, but the ambience was very idyllic and when I heard that they had chosen a new director and that he was going to change the feeling of the films to a much darker setting I was rather apprehensive because I felt that if he went a bit over the top with the ‘darkness’ it wouldn’t feel like these films are in the same series. I can thankfully report that this is not the case and that the film flows with the new more introrespective feeling but keeps to the magic that is hogwarts, even accentuating it at times with the movement of the setting of Hagrids hut to Scotland for example. This film deserves the caption magical and I advise everyone, and I am not exaggerating, everyone to see it. NOW! 
    
    
</post>


<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   But my first review is coming so be patient. I'll give you the clue that i am reading a couple of bill Bryson books at the moment. Thats all i'm going to say for the mean time but the review should be out within the next few weeks Stay tuned...  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The Curious Incident in the Dog in the night time. Well I’m not really sure how I am to start a review of this wholly strange but compelling book; but to state the facts as the main character of the book would do. He is a young boy that has autism which means he does not understand emotions but it does enable him to be un-humanly logical, even doing his maths a level at primary school. The story is based around his life, specifically an incident, maybe even a curious incident, where a neighbor’s dog is stabbed to death one night. He takes it upon himself to find out who is the culprit and decides to write a detective novel in the process, as he like the logic and progression of detective novels. This leads him to finding out a lot about him and his family and leads us to finding a lot about a mindset that can feel very abnormal and somehow alienating to those without it. This book is written as if it were the detective novel of the boy which can make it a very tiring read, because of the interwoven complexities lingering in every page but even so it is gripping in the way that not many books are nowadays. This book made me think about my self and the world and at some points allowed me to understand to the point that I doubted whether my perspectives are correct. This is a book for everyone’s shelves but unfortunately I have a feeling  that all my reviews will sound a bit like that as I have just bought many books to my taste. My understanding that I like these types of books will hopefully allow me to cast a less biased eye on these books. OK then here goes:      No I just cant do it. Its just too difficult to slag this book off!        this book is so good that It would be Sinful to lay criticisms upon it but  Criticisms there are and  so should be Mentioned .As I have already Said this book Can  be Very tiring in the way and style it is written as you cannot relate to the authors perspective and it can  also be very tiring in the complexity of the logic and the Complexity of the problems put forward in the book. Even my, er-hum, superb intelligence was overshadowed. It made me think which is always a good thing because the worst thing is to let a mind go to waste, especially mine.  Maybe you wouldn't see yourself as an intelligent person but if one thing made you think in a book I would say that it was worth reading and this book has so many opportunities for this that it is unlikely that anyone past adolescence will come away empty from it. It is a great and enlightening read suitable for all, thoroughly understood  and enjoyed by older  readers. This will break the monotony of everyday  life . I myself enjoy reading a Dick Francis novel (I’m using Dick Francis in my analogy because of the shear amount of his novels) as much as the next guy but they can all feel the same, even with totally different story lines. This could end up with a development of boredom for reading which is a terrible thing. Thankfully I read a lot of different genres which helps me to battle  this and allows me a broad knowledge. I seemed to have babbled on a little but I feel the book is worth it. Anyways all this was to say that this is a fantastic book. And even if this isn’t your kettle of fish, I doubt that this is anyone’s usual kettle of fish, I’d urge you to read it. Go on       

						
</post>


<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      At this moment i am waiting for big brother to finish so as to watch the finale of frasier. Frasier has been one of my favourite sitcoms of which my reason for choosing this specific sitcom coming for my likeing of the brilliant sitcom cheers. My brother always liked Happy days but i always found the wit andcharacter of cheers more apealing. Cheers did not develop the character of frasier as far as many would have wanted but with his moving to Seatle saw him faining a sitcom of his own, of his own style. We are now lacking sitcoms in this modern age where the actors perform infront of a live audience. This is what gives the show a freshness with every episode as the actors are not playing to a camera (i know they are but in their minds they are not), ,they are playing to the audience which gives a feeling of truth to the performance. I was very sad to see friends leave because i can probably say there isn't an episode that i haventwatchedbut I am not wholely sad to see frasier go as much of its life on telivision was lost because of curfew. I am not saying that i want the sitcom to end but sometimes it is for the sitcom's good, as it is better to have a good ending (like that of blackadder that sticks in everyones minds) than to drag on losing all the fans it had gained throughout the years. Anyway I was saying about how frinds will become boring because of the amount of times each episode has been repeated, but with frasier i will be happy to watch repeats for many years to come as, for one i havenrt seen many of the older episodes, and two i dont think i have seen any episode more than once so it will not lose its new and fresh appeal for many a year. I hope that frasier will take up the 6 o clock spot of friends on channel 4 at some point as it would be a movement forward that wouldnt feel out of place as frasier has run alongside friends for many a year. Wellthe finale episodes are about to start so i'll wrapup this long-winded waffling post that has managed to spread one point over god knows how many lines.  oh,ive just realised when frasier finnishes (+10min) I'll be sixteen.wow. Oh yes the other thing i was going to add was that the pictures on the site are going to be from my holiday in Amsterdam for next couple of weeks. Hope you enjoy.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Its of the reichstag art museum in Amsterdam, I think. Mum wasn't in focus thou, oh well&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      And have decided to go shopping in York. Hopefuly buy something as it is my birthday tomorrow, nudge nudge wink wink!! The history exam wasn't too bad but the questions are always too detailed in one specific subject. Say i had to speak about the sand creek massacre. i could have spoken about all the battles but getting all the marks possible out of the one subject is pretty hard to do. Im hoping to buy a couple of things while in York. Ther main is the book called The Curious Incident of the dog in the nightime. This is meant to be a very good book from the perspective of a young autistic boy. Im also looking for a side satchel as i think it will suit 6th form better. Anyway i better be going, much to do   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      they cant seem to build their lamposts straight!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      And i've been working hard at the history ofteh american west,  with its vast amount of dates, but hopefully it wont be too hard. I'll do my best and i'll just have to remember to readthe question thoroughly and remember to write in proportion to the value of the question. Well it'llall be over then and i can celebrate my birthday on thursday in peace,not worrying about exams. Couple of friends are coming over and waching a film: starsky and hutch. And i go back to brasilon sunday. We stayin for just under a month which should be great and we are hoping to go to this place called Brotas which is a centre for adventure trype stuff: rafting and the like. I'll update with a great sigh of relief tomorrow when my exam finnishes.  bye for now
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Second Hand Camera, unknown reason for previous owners death &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      And i am exhausted, its not that ive done any vast amount of exercise its just that being on your feet all day is tiering. It was a good day though with sunshine most of the day,except for the last fifteen minutes where it tipped it down and we had to retreat to the food tent. We saw a particularly funny sign while at the show and so took a photo on someones camera phone, but i have yet to get it sent to me, so when i do have it it willbe posted here. It was a large sign on one side of a cow pen with a rather large black cow within. The funny thing was on the sign it said "Tuck into roast beef!" which was particularly funny when the cow popped its head over the fence. Unfortunately the cow might not be seen very well on the photo because of its blackness but you will get the gist. Within this hour that i have  got after the show i've got to prepare myself to go to a concert. Yes Nicholas McMullin at a concert. Its by a guy calledbrian ferry and he seems to be quite famous to the friend i am going with's parents. Should be good, and it is a treat seeing as though im not doing much on my birthday. Oh well i better get back to that preperation i was talking about (and practise that nike ole game so that ii can beat toddy. grrr) Toodles         Edit: Unfortunately the show has been cancelled, laringitus or something, but im still going to my friend toms house. It'll be good whatever we end up doing. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      None of those at the north yorkshire show&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For me and my blog. Today has seen the creation of my sub-blogs, a major development in this site. I am quite proud to be the creator of these sites andif i can update as often as i am planning i will be really happy. Now has come the low after the high of doing many things at once. I'm a bit bored but am looking forward to tomorrow morning because im going to visit the north yorkshire show to give out prgrammes and make a bit of money for the explorer scouts. Should be able to have a look around aswell. Better go now, The Parole Officer is starting and i've heard its quite funny Toodles  (Edit: Sorry this was posted late,i fergot to post it after wachin the film, which i can assure you is helarious-review coming on movie rack-)    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      oooo old picture of me. I have longish hair at this point (it got a lot longer)Sorry about the fuzzyness-camera phone &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Exams are once again upon me after this blissful break, which in reality wasn’t a break because of all the revision but I could, maybe, classify it that way because I didn’t have to worry about exams. I seem to be doing less revision than I may have first planned but, I think, I may be doing my revision beter because I seem to be learning from it/actually remembering it. This is quite a surprise to me, but it seems that it isn’t the quantity, though some hard graft may be needed, of the work, but the quality: setting my mind to work constructively. As I have always said boring your mind with endless hours of reading wont help to revise. I have come back to writing this post after a couple of weeks because of many set backs such as the mentioned exams and the fact that I formated my computer but the show is going on. i am now at the end of my exam period with all my exams except History paper two out of the way. This is quite a relief as history probably has the largest amount of information to learn and understand. My school has chosen to do the Schools History Project sylabus which is probably the most interesting of the sylabus as you get to study the history of medicine (very gory i assure you) and you get to study the cowboys and indians of the wild west but unfortunately they hardly ever met.This is the exam that I am studying for at the moment so i should get back to the revision but all those dates seem to be getting the better of me!      
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Breath Taking: The reason why you should travel if you can&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ive decided to coordinate my blog ideas intoa couple of different sections. At the moment this is going to be a general thoughts page and I am going to have my weekly review of the delights of the web on a seperate page: urlLink The Chief's Friday feeling   I am also going to have a blog for reviews of the books I have recently read:  urlLink The chief's Book Trolley   Enjoy 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I found Nemo!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here's a little update before tomorrows big one, as i thought these two sites deserved a mentioning, and i thought you might enjoy them  The first is a online startegy game that is packed full of wit, plot changes and strange puns: its a murder mystery that will stop everything until you complete it  urlLink Clicky   (please wait for it to load: well worth it)   Here is a site of an artist, please dont turn simultaneously into narcaleptics, which is telling it like it is: Mysteries of the world revealed!    urlLink Clicky 2   My last one for tonight i can safely state shows the best guitarist in the world, bar none. Enjoy  urlLink Clicky 3 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Homers Brain: 'Nuff Said&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As you may well have seen in my previous post I am going to be experimenting with photo-blogging and I feel a photo between posts breaks up the monotony of solid prose s that is going to be my plan. In the future these photos will be recently taken ones but for the mo, I’ll stick with my favourites for you to enjoy.  So now back to the subject of today’s post: Harry Potter and the Prizoner of Azkaban. This is the film that everyone has been seeing this week, and with good reason, and I’d like to see a ticket sale for a different film this week. This film is quite thoroughly amazing to those that are familiar with the books, which is everyone except a couple of Norwegian moles that slept through this best-selling craze because they were too tired (“Please can’t I have another 6 months in bed”) and hit the snooze button sometime in 1998, as well as to those that are not. This review will not cover the plot of the story, I’m sorry a deep sin of reviewing to leave out the synopsis, but hey, everyone knows the storry already (see Norwegian mole comment). I am a self-confessed super-fan of Harry potter and felt very good after seeing a film which was very magical in its picturesque hogwartsy way but I felt rather let down when I saw the second film. The first book had that very cosy fealling to it and so the style of Chris Columbus suited it very well but the second is a much darker film but that is not really shown in the film because the happy go lucky feeling of the school seemed to take away from the dark of the forbidden forest sequence and the final sequence with the basilisk-snake. This film is totally different, but as that very annoying child from the Macdonalds advert has been telling us: “Change is Good”. Alfonso Cuaron has brought to life the film and has changed it from what was seemed to be a children’s film into a film that appeals on different levels to different people: the principal that has made the Harry Potter books world wide best-sellers. I liked the feeling of the last films, ok they were aimed toward the smaller of us, please no short jokes I’m trying to make a point, but the ambience was very idyllic and when I heard that they had chosen a new director and that he was going to change the feeling of the films to a much darker setting I was rather apprehensive because I felt that if he went a bit over the top with the ‘darkness’ it wouldn’t feel like these films are in the same series. I can thankfully report that this is not the case and that the film flows with the new more introrespective feeling but keeps to the magic that is hogwarts, even accentuating it at times with the movement of the setting of Hagrids hut to Scotland for example. This film deserves the caption magical and I advise everyone, and I am not exaggerating, everyone to see it. NOW!  Edit: This review has been moved to my new movie review sub-blog where you can find much more                  urlLink The Chief's Movie Rack 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Just playing arround with photoblog settings so heres a nice one: I know very bad pun&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well to start on a strange note i found this rathert cool site which tells you your battle cries that corresponds with your name so i decided to give you mine and the cries for my nicknames: enjoy (Oh yeh visit the site at: http://bdmonkeys.net/~chaz/battle.php?usrname=&sex=m )  Lo! Who is that, prowling amidst the steppes! It is ***Real Name***, hands clutching a meaty axe! He howls mightily: "As sure as predators devour prey, I hereby snap and go berzerk!!!"  Prowling across the hotel lobby, attacking with a sharpened screwdriver, cometh Big Chief Little Nick! And he gives a spectacular cry: "I'm going to beat the flaming shit out of you!!"  Rampaging over the icy wasteland, swinging a jeweled meat hammer, cometh Adwarfnamed007! And he gives an ominous howl: "I'm seriously going to bruise you like a first grade teacher!"  Prowling over the mini-mall parking lot, swinging a thorned whip, cometh Weespecybloke! And he gives a booming roar: "In the name of Thor the Mighty, I sow darkness and discord with reckless abandon!" 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello everyone and welcome to the blog that is “The chief’s thoughts”. I hope to update quite often, at least once a week but when my exams finish you will feel the strangely nice glow that is the glory of a blog by me, no ego of course. I hope to get some sanity of mind through this, but from the outside it might seem other wise (because I am giving you my insanity buwa ha ha ha!) sobare with me because all will become clear...  (Edit: This, ive decided, is such a great introduction to my blog that it will live on forever at the top of the page in my description)   If you dont know already I am moderating for a really cool forum at http://www.corrupt-system.net but at the moment i am doing the extreme sports sections and well this isn't really my style: as i dont actually do any extreme sports but i am an interested watcher and am an avid fan of all those extreme sports that are a little bit different, see the forum for next weeks review on extreme ironing! Also every fiday I am going to show a true fanaticism of mine off: my love for all things interweb so tune in for the greatest timewasting,funny, interesting or downright laugh your pants stuff from this weeks internet.  If i can get some good comments about my friday roundup it might even persuade demby to get a section on corrupt: nudge nudge wink wink. Well back to the grindstone but more to come soon. Promise         
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Im not as tierd as i was last week because strangely enough i managed to get a decent amount of sleap most nights in the bush so all is well. I am slowly trying to work out what i have missed&nbsp;in the days i've been gone butthis is going to take a while. All sub-blogs are going to be slowly updated, especialy movie and bookreviews, but friday feeling will consist of mainly old news for some of you as i am going to post the best of the weeks i have been gone. If youve got a problem with that i'll be happy to deal with it outside. Oh well. Got lots of photos to show and tell. Will come soon.  byeeeeee&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Will inform soon. Now too tired. Will only post next week. Off Camping.&nbsp; argghh&nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      (on holiday)
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      and i am quite tierd cos i spent most of the weekend journeying back and forth from where wewere staying. My grandad is recovering well from the operation he had so that is good. I spoke to my uncle and they invited me to go over and spend the rest of the holidays with my cousins. im considering this and going to work with a architect, so i shouldnt be bored for the rest of the holiday. Well that is about it for this update. Except that i am looking for a sewing machine so i can get to work on my camp blanket. Nighty Night 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For the weekend. Talk to you soon. toodles 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Two Book reviews have been written and one movie review is nearly finnished. Will be uploaded from the palm top i was writting them on tomorrow, hopefully. It is quite soothing to type on a palm top as you can sit in a comfy arm chair. CYA tmora  Also In other news I need to buy a new phone. Mine has been broken for a while now and it is beginning to annoy me. I was thinking of buying a simless phone, similar to that wat i have but i have been browsing amazon and it seems that simless are more expensive, ,for wat they are. I saw this samsung A800 and it is only £20 more expensive than the other phones i was looking atand this is almost brand new ( i dont mean condition, I mean since this was brought out) where the others i saw are old models from a couple of years ago. I think I might spend it on this better phone and transplant my sim card. Here it is tell me wat you think of it:  urlLink http://snipurl.com/87rs  (OH yes snipurl.com is quite a useful site for shortening long urls to send to people. very useful)  Oh and another thing I have found The complete Monty Python series for 50 quid!!!!!!! That is under half price: because it is 14 dvds. I am so close to buying it but thta would hold back me buying a nu phone: oh well i dontneed a phone that much; it is at   urlLink http://snipurl.com/87sd  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am working on making this blog much more than just a blog. I have aspirations for this blog to become a fully fledged site but this needs me to get to grips with a little more html than i understand at the moment. Posts are on the way for all sub-blogs but even more than that Polls are being added, statistic counters are being added and photo albums are being compiled. I am hoping to nick the source code for a links section on my sidebar so as to list my affliates. Things are changing and the only way is up.  (oh yeh i have this cool little graphich fo when i close a sub site for some reason. see it on friday feeling as a preview) 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>