<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I just realized one of the reasons I've not been going to my exercise classes lately, or making the proper effort to get my son to his soccer practice, is because I have been feeling very anti-social these past several weeks.  I don't fit in well with the soccer mom crowd, although they are all very kind.  I'm just the only single mom, and one of the few who works.  In fact, lately I've had to bring work to do to soccer practice, which is off-putting to some extent to the others.  I'm sure I probably come off like a snob, but my shyness has been rearing its ugly head and making it more painful for me to even make small talk.  I find myself feeling that no one cares what I have to say, and it's even rude of me to force myself onto others, even through mundane conversation.  If they wanted to talk to me, I reason, they would initiate the conversation.  I realize how silly that is, but emotion does not always win out over intellect.  The exercise classes are filled with very fit people who have their clique with other very fit people, with the subset of trophy wives and those struggling not to be replaced by trophy wives.  At work I have only one person I can really talk to.  I can talk to the other women in the office about family things, but there's a guy at work that I can talk to about anything.  It's very refreshing, because we both know we can be honest and agree to disagree without our opinions jeopardizing our friendship.  My ex-husband and I sometimes have spirited conversations, but I can't trust him with my feelings.  Recently it appears that he has reunited with his ex-girlfriend, who is a wonderful woman and a good influence on him, but he's not telling me because he hopes to have a friendship with benefits with me.  That has no appeal for me.  Plus he sometimes is very illogical; yesterday he sent me two chain emails!    My brother-in-law posted in his blog yesterday about an argument he had with my sister regarding parenting.  He is much more laidback, whereas my sister wants to force her opinions on her children; she insists they believe what she believes.  Her children are all teenagers now; they are not going to agree with her 100%, especially since most of her views are quite conservative and not always based in logic.  Her youngest is a girl, and I'm sure the next several years will be difficult for the two of them. 

						
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm more mindful this year of the meaning of this holiday than I have been in years past.  When I realize that I'm old enough to be the mother of some of the young men and women losing their lives on the other side of the world, Memorial Day hits home.  And I'm becoming more and more mindful of the freedoms our forefathers established and fought for.  I've been complacent about them, and now I want to work to ensure we keep these freedoms, when the current political climate seems to encourage the erosion of our rights.  My ex-husband fancies himself a miltary man from a military family, although no one in this immediate family ever wore a uniform.  He went to a military boarding school and flirted with going to West Point, but his whole adult life has been civilian.  He gets choked up when he talks about how he wishes he were in the military in these times, but I think that's all horsesh*t.  But I do think he is lying to himself about this as well.  My ex took our son to the Memorial Day parade yesterday.  I hope my son has some sense of the meaning of the holiday, and not just an excuse for barbecues and excessive drinking and white sales.  Of course he's only six, but he seems wiser than his years.  I feel very selfish in knowing that it would be hard for me to make the sacrifices our service men and women are making, and to know that I don't want my son to be one of them.  His father would be proud to see him in uniform, but I would be terrified.  

						
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This weekend seems to me to be like New Year's--I'm wanting to turn over a new leaf.  I haven't exercised in nearly a month, and as I plan to get back to an workable regiment after the holiday weekend, I also want to make many other changes for the better.  Forced to clean up my act at work due to an ISO audit, I need to clean up my personal space as well.  I also want to work harder at being a more involved parent.  My son takes my breath away sometimes with his six-year-old questions.  On the car radio news, he hears something about Iraq, and he says, exasperatedly, "Are we attacking   again  ?"  He's been asking me what "we" (meaning he and I) believe about different political issues.  The temptation to brainwash is strong, but I really want him to make up his own mind as he matures.  (Really, I do.  I think I do.  I hope I do!)  I want to work to make the world a better place, and a way I see to do that is by becoming politically active.  Mostly right now that just means getting educated.  I'm reading several books and listening to the radio more and more, specifically Air America and NPR.  I listen to Hannity and Limbaugh in short bursts, but I find them so hateful that my stomach turns.  I don't even know where to locate O'Reilly on the dial, but I find him so masterful of spin, I don't believe he knows his own truth anymore.  Through Air America I've become familiar with a man named Jim Wallis, who believes you can be progressive and politically active, something the Christian right views as oxymoronic.  He has a couple of websites, including Sojourners, and I plan to learn more about his ideas.  The current climate in the U.S. and the world frightens me.  I'm more afraid than I was post-9/11.  Granted, I live in the Midwest and can feel pretty safe, but now I'm ashamed of myself for being complacent.  I need to work to make this world safer and freer for my son.  More to say, but I'll save it for another time.  I just need to remember that loneliness is not an option. 

						
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is my attempt to be upbeat and positive on the topic of my choosing.  Well, come January, Bush will be heading to Crawford, Texas to begin his well-deserved retirement.  I’ve been thinking about some wonderful ways he can spend his golden years.   At first I thought he could coach a T-ball team, seeing his love of the game, even hosting games on the White House lawn.  But I realized that’s thinking too small.  He’s probably one of the most physical fit presidents we’ve had; he could take Ah-nold’s mantle and be the spokesperson for physical fitness.  He could also do a lot of good by promoting sobriety.  He could get across the message that it’s never too late to get sober and change your life.  He didn’t sober up until he was forty—and he achieved some pretty impressive goals after that!  Or he could put his compasisonate conservatism to work and help not-for-profit organizations use faith-based initiatives to help the less afluent among us.  Dick Cheney—well, I’m sure he’s nicely feathered his retirement nest with war profits, so he should do just fine duck hunting with Supreme Court justices, whose favor he could continue to curry.  John Kerry, meanwhile, will start to implement his bold plans to restore America’s reputation and heal a divided nation.  His action plan—a list of actionable items, to quote Condi—includes a new national education trust fund, a new era of naitonal service, the end of the age of Ashcroft (thunderous applause), the end of the assault on the environment, a plan to make U. S. Energy independent, the rejoining the community of nations, universal affordable health care, rewarding companies that create jobs and not phony corporate profit, restoring the middle class, cutting the deficit and ending influence peddling.  Ambitious?  Very!  But Kerry is a man of vision.  He is a man who has devoted his life to public service.  He was privileged enough to graduate from Yale, as was our current Commander-in-Chief, but Kerry chose to put himself in harm’s way and serve in Vietnam as an officer in the Navy.  He was decorated for his service with a Silver Star, a Bronze Star and three Purple Hearts.  He came back from his service, went to Boston Law School and became a top prosecutor, taking on organized crime.  As the Kerry campaign notes, “Kerry came to the Senate with a reputation for independence -- and reinforced it by making tough choices on difficult issues: breaking with many  in his own Party to support Gramm-Rudman Deficit Reduction; taking on corporate welfare and government waste; pushing for campaign finance reform; holding Oliver North accountable and exposing the fraud and abuse at the heart of the BCCI scandal; working with John McCain in the search for the truth about Vietnam veterans declared POW/MIA; and insisting on accountability, investment, and excellence in public education.”  Although Bush and Kerry are contemporaries, Kerry’s path avoided the pitfalls of hard drinking and the frivolity of owning a major league baseball team. Kerry, I believe, is more qualified for the job of President, because he has spent his life in public service, working to keep America great.  Surely he believes the old adage, “To whom much is given, much is expected.”  Kerry offers his nation so much hope.  Meanwhile, Fahrenheit 9/11 is setting box office records for a documentary.  It seems that the film may be prompting voter registration drives and imbuing those who previously felt disenfranchised with an optimism that sparks action to right wrongs done in America’s name and to regain those rights that make us uniquely American—freedom of speech, freedom of assembly, freedom of the press—and to abolish the sinister Orwellian double-speak of government which makes every day in America Opposite Day.  I do get angry when I think about the lies upon lies that have resulted in the deaths of hundreds of American soldiers and thousands of Iraqi civilians.  Yes, Saddam Hussein was an unspeakably brutal dictator, but his viciousness was at its peak at about the time photos were taken of him shaking hands with a smiling Rumsfeld and a cheerful Cheney.  But I feel great pride that we have soldiers like Paul Rieckhoff.  Like Kerry, Rieckhoff graduated from a prestigious school (Amherst) and had the choice to pursue a cushy life.  However, like Kerry, he felt a need to serve his country, and his father did before him (in Vietnam) and his grandfather in WWII.  In Iraq, he did not feel total confidence in the policies of his Commander-in-Chief, but rather than turning to despair, he and his compadres worked to bring hope to the Iraqi people.  He befriended his translator, a local artist, and immersed himself in Iraqi culture.  He worked to bring joy to Iraqi children, and when he and his fellow soldiers learned that the local school had been closed for three months due to lack of funds, they pooled their resources and presented the school’s teacher with $300 so the children could resume their education.  He learned of the plight of Big Foot, an Iraqi civilian of giant proportions who had never worn shoes to fit his size 19 feet, simply because shoes that fit were an unattainable luxury.  Rieckhoff contacted his girlfriend stateside and she purchased a pair of gym shoes on Ebay and got them to Big Foot.  The American spirit is indomitable and we are capable of great things.  I believe our future is bright.  That’s why I’m wearing shades.    

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I especially enjoyed the comments I got on my last entry, so I thought if I responded more promptly, it would encourage more of the same.  I did not set out to blog daily, which is but one reason why I don't.  I decided against creating a daily journal; what I want to do here is not document my life story but rather my thoughts and philosophy.  I often need to let those perculate, and I don't have a block of time every day to record my ideas.  So I do what I can when I can.  (Having something specific to respond to from someone else helps provide structure, which streamines the process.)  That said, my blog is pretty much stream of consciousness; I write quickly, do not take time to organize my thoughts, and seldom edit.  (But you already knew that didn't you?)  Regarding the assignment of the nickname, The White Muse, it doesn't bother me, but it doesn't quite fit, either.  I started working at this job as an ESL teacher, and my students--the factory workers--and I became very fond of each other.  So one of them came up with a nickname for me.  (Now I have had more than my share of nicknames in my life, most courtesy of my dad, so I associate nicknames with affection.)  They call me Guera, which translates more to fair-skinned than white--more of type of Caucasian than simply generic Caucasian.  My son's babysitter calls him Guero and he and I are referred to as Los Gueros. . . .and their yellow labrador is also called Guero.  But I've come to not even think about the meaning of the word, and just think of it as me.  So I use Guera as my handle in a variety of settings.  So the name of my blog, in my mind, is "Lori Muses," as in pondering the imponderables.  I was not proclaiming myself to be a muse, that is, a being who inspires others creatively.  It's an interesting thought, though. . . .  On to the next set of interrogatories--  The Daily Show is not daily at all, but on Monday through Thursday on Comedy Central.  It is a parody of a news show, but it is very witty and very rarely sophomoric.  Jon Stewart is the host and head writer, and the show has won Emmy's and the Peabody award.  I look forward to it every day.  Jon gets accused of having a liberal bias, but when I've seen him interviewed on other shows, he comes across even more as a bemused objective observer.  Besides, the Daily Show is followed by Tough Crowd, which is much more conservative (five comedians discussing the day's news, very boisterously).  The pundit who made the crude analogy was Al Franken.  Liberal, Harvard-educated, Al Franken.  His books are very funny and very well-researched, as is his show on Air America.  My news sources are a bit varied.  I get the headlines from AOL, and I get breaking news from CBS, ABC and CNN.  I subscribe to Newsweek and I get articles from the New York Times and the Washington Post emailed to me.  I occasionally will glance at Time or the Wall Street Journal, both of which my company subscribes to.  Otherwise my news sources are from the radio, primarily Air America, NPR and WGN, and occassionally from WBBM, and if I'm desperate, from WLS.  If I hear something that I want to verify, I try to research it from mainstream sources, such as U. S. News and World Report, the Chicago Tribune, etc.  I get daily email from a think-tank called the Center for American Progress.  Their information is well-documented, and beyond pointing out problems in current policies, they suggest coherent, sophisticated solutions.  I don't have the specifics on the cuts in veteran's benefits and police officers on patrol; I will research that and 'fess up if I am in error.  The after-school program in particular which has been cut is really not an after school program.  Head Start has been drastically cut, and that is a federal program.  But I will look into this more.  I won't deny that previous Democratic administrations have sought to reduce the military.  But I believe (and will have to research) that much of these cuts were related to hardware and not to cutting military pay or benefits.  I believe that the Democrats have tried to cut funding for obsolete military equipment and fairy-tale systems like SDI.  I do know that military retirement benefits and health care have been cut; National Guard soldiers are not eligible for government health insurance, for example.  Hazardous duty pay was cut, I believe from $125 to $75 dollars a month.  (I have to check those figures.)    Meanwhile, soldiers of fortune in Iraq are paid six figures.  Soldiers like Paul Rieckhoff find this inequity demoralizing.  (But he had some wonderful memories of his time in Iraq, too; I'll share those in a future entry.)  I find it very difficult to accept that Halliburton is the only corporation qualified to rebuild Iraq.  It seems to me perhaps several corporations, with many different specialties, could rebuild Iraq.  It seems to me that the whole endeavor should have been much more international, if it were justified, and we would be sharing this enormous undertaking with many nations, instead of relying on one corporation with uncomfortable ties to the current administration.  Yes, Rush did compare the prison abuse to frat boy shennagins.  To be fair, this was in the first few days of the scandal, before many of the more brutal pictures were released.  But he continued to defend the actions of the soldiers.  "Come on, people," he said, "these people are the Enemy!"  But actually they were the people we were supposed to be liberating.  70 to 90% of the detainees were wrongfully imprisoned.  I will try to document this in a future entry.  I define "knee-jerk" as a quick unthinking response; it can apply to any political persuasion.  I have not looked at Christianity Today much, but I do run across quotes from it very often.  It has always struck me as a very objective source.  I think one reson I started writing this blog is an uneasiness I have with the Right co-opting the label Christian, as if one cannot be Christian and liberal.  But I think Christ himself was pretty radical, and aren't we supposed to be striving to be more Christ-like?     

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Last night, at the end of another long work day, I had an interesting conversation with one of my bosses.  I stopped in his office to ask whether he wanted me to lock the door.  He was checking the headlines online, and he mentioned to me that Jack Ryan had dropped out of the race.  We embarked on a discussion of politics that made me experience a heavy heart—an expression that I didn’t really understand until last night.  My boss is what I would call a knee-jerk Republican.  I don’t think he ponders the issues much; he decided a long time ago that Democrats are bad, and Republicans may be bad, too, but at least they won’t ruin the economy.  So we chatted about the current global climate.  I learned he thinks the Abu Gharib scandal is much as Rush painted it—just some frat boys blowing off steam.  When I pointed out that people had  been killed, he was surprised, but it didn’t seem to affect him too much.  He said that we had to torture those people.  In fact, he said, we were right to round up and incarcerate Japanese people during WWII.  I would have been dumbfounded if I weren’t so opinionated and ready to speak my mind.    He asked me how many people had been killed, and I didn’t have the stats at my fingertips, but I knew it was more than twenty.  I did the research and found out 25 detainees had died.  The article I read (from the New Yorker) dated May 3, 12 deaths had been determined to be either from natural or undetermined causes, 1 death occurred when a fleeing detainee was shot, 10 more were still under investigation and 2 were determined to be homicides.  What I hunger for is a conservative with whom I can have a reasonable discussion who can clarify and support that point of view.  I’m getting bits and pieces of this type of dialogue from my sister and little tidbits from my brother, but being geographically apart (as well as idealogically) makes such conversations difficult.  But my boss is not the man to have the conversation with either, although we both certainly are respectful of our differing opinions.  He admits that he is not particularly informed about poliitics, not being especially interested in it unless he knows the players personally.  He surprised me by saying he thinks Clinton could have been a great president, but was unwilling to concede that Clinton did anything good during his administration. I understand being extremely disappointed with the tawdriness Clinton’s immoral and unwise behavior brought to the presidency.  Yet despite this scandal dominating the second term of his presidency, his administration thwarted at least three or four terrorist attacks on our soil, his economic policy was so much more responsible than the current administration’s, and America’s reputation in the world was not tainted by the man’s deep flaws and foolish mistakes.  I plan to see the movie Fahrenheit 9/11.  I am not an enormous fan of Michael Moore’s; he uses theatrically tactics that are manipulative and as such, lessens the impact of his argument.  For example, he takes a mother who lost her son to the war in Iraq to Washington and films her emotional breakdown in front of the White House.  That is shameful, I believe.  He can make his point without intruding on this woman’s grief.  This mother, apparently, gave Moore permission to use the footage, but the argument against the war must be made intellectually, not emotionally.  On the radio I heard an Iraq War veteran, Paul Rieckhoff, speaking about his experience in Iraq.  His grandfather had served in WWII, and his father in Viet Nam.  Rieckhoff himself had gone to school at Amherst, and as such, was privleged enough not to need to go into the military.  He joined the Army in 1998 because he felt he needed to give back to the country that had done so much for him.    He speaks without anger but pointedly about how the military was and is let down by this Commander-in-Chief.  Supplies were scarce, from ammunition to body armor to vehicles.  He says soldiers were on patrol in 120 degree heat with only one water bottle apiece.  His unit, he said, did not have Humvees, but when the time came for them to need such vehicles, they stripped down SUV’s they could find but could not properly armor.  (I have heard but have not verified independently that several of our war dead have resulted from injuries that would be preventable if our troops were sufficiently armored.  I have heard that families of our troops have bake sales to raise money for Kevlar.)  Meanwhile veterans’ benefits are being cut, hazardous pay for the military is being scaled back dramatically, and solidiers’ tours of duty are being extended indefinitely.  All so the President’s wealthy friends can buy a new yacht with their tax cuts.  There are fewer police on our streets, after-school programs are being cut, and “tax cuts, corporate interests and union-bashing. . .come first.” Jack Huberman, A Guide to the Most Appalling Presidency of the Past 100 Years.  Halliburton, with its extremely unethical ties to the President of Vice, Dick Cheney, gets no-bid contracts to rebuild Iraq and charges our government for a bag of dirty laundry and $80M to purchase a new truck to replace a slightly less-new truck which is marred by a flat tire.  Meanwhile, Halliburton executives stay in luxury suites at luxury hotels at the taxpayers’ expense.    Cheney is proving himself to be a pathological liar.  I saw a delicious bit of tape about Cheney on the Daily Show.  After the 9/11 commission released its report stating there was no operational link between Al Quaeda and Iraq, Cheney gets on TV to do his spin control.  He points to a alleged meeting between terrorist Atta and Iraqi intelligence officers in Prague in April.  He vehemently claims such a meeting has neither been proved nor disproved.  The Daily Show cuts to a quote from the commission report:  “We believe such a meeting in Prague did not occur.”  [Cell phone and ATM records determined that such a meeting at that time was impossible.]  The same female interviewer pointed out that Cheney had said in the past that there was no Iraq-Al Quaeda link, and Cheney angrily, vehemently denies saying that.  Cut to Meet the Press tape, where Cheney used the exact words the female interviewer had just quoted.    So pathological is he, that Cheney’s latest mendacity is denying on Fox News (with the ironic slogan, Fair and Balanced) the foul language he used when speaking with Patrick Leahy on the floor of the Senate, in front of witnesses.  When asked if he did indeed “drop the F-bomb,” Cheney shook his head demurely and said, “It’s not the kind of language I usually use.”  (A non-denial denial, if ever I heard one.)  Meanwhile, hilariously, Cheney’s aides are saying Leahy was deservedly cursed out!  Thank goodness this administration is bringing decency and civility back to the government!!!  Another way the administration is trying to link Iraq to Al Quaeda,  the administration points to a 1994 meeting between Bin Laden and Iraqi intelligence.  One of my favorite pundits cleverly yet crudely put it this way, “If I gave Britney Spears my phone number and she wiped her butt with it, does that mean we dated?”  Back to Fox News, for a moment.  Their news is so absurdly biased that it would be laughable, if it weren’t duping so many into believing that the war in Iraq is justified.  So I’m not laughing; I’m trying to find a remedy for the queasiness I feel.  To return to where I’d begun. . . I have tremendous respect and admiration for my boss because he is a very ethical businessman.  Making opportunities for his employees to provide for their families is a very important part of his work to him—a moral responsibility.  He has made many sacrifices for his workers—one year giving employees an energy bonus in a year where energy prices spiked, eating the increases in medical insurance premiums for several years, and giving all his employees a raise when the business relocated to a facility much further from where most of the workers live.  So to hear such an ethical man defend torture was disheartening at best and devastating at worst.  He scoffed at the Geneva Conventions as being irrelevant.  Even setting aside the huge moral questions, torture can never be effective when the detainee has no useful information.  I have been trying to educate myself more and more on the Bush administration, and I’m finding so many reasons to want them out of the White House.  I’ve been discussing this with my ex, and he has been trying to dissuade his mom from voting for Bush.  (She is nominally a Democrat, but the story is that if you don’t register as a Democrat in the city, your garbage doesn’t get picked up.)  He has offered her several factual arguments against voting for Bush, but she remained unconvinced.  Then I told him something I thought was amusing, but not the least bit provable or even believable.  I heard a psychologist on the radio speculate, based on partly on the pretzel-choking episode and the bicycle mishap, that Bush is drinking again.  This was enough for the mother of a newly-recovering alcoholic to want the man out of the White House.  Yet again my thoughts are jumbled as I can’t type as fast as the ideas come to me.  But the demand for my musings is there, so here is my offering.  

						
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My sister pointed something out to me that dilutes my previous rant, and I looked into it, and she was right.  The vast majority of presidents did not attend funerals of the fallen.  I distinctly remember Reagan attending such funerals, reinforced by many of the images over the last week, and Clinton and Bush the Elder attended a few, but these were rare exceptions.  That said, this administration is trying to infringe on freedom of the press in many ways, including not allowing flag-drapped coffins of fallen soldiers to be broadcast.  My sage sister also provided me with a quote that I found quite poignant.  "I do not know what the heart of a bad man is like.  But I do know what the heart of a good man in like.  And it is terrible."  Ivan Turgenev. 

						
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have a huge jumble of thoughts, so please forgive me if this is somewhat disjointed.  My wise and well-respected sister*** forwarded me an email from a soldier stationed in Iraq, wherein he enumerated many successes in our campaign in Iraq and expressed frustration at the negative American media coverage.  I was so self-satisfied with my response to my sister that I decided to post an edited version on my blog.  (Ouch--I sprained my arm patting myself on the back.)  I think it’s unfortunate that most of our media outlets have the philosophy “If It Bleeds, It Leads” guiding what stories get prominence.  I’m delighted and   not   surprised to learn that things have improved in Iraq on so many different fronts.  But I believe it would be foolhardy to ignore the problems; they can’t be corrected if we refuse to address them.  None of the wonderful things in the email contradicts the fact that there are horrible things happening in Iraq as well.  It’s interesting that the soldier in the email makes a remark about Kerry.  Kerry voted for the war, and is not in favor of suddenly pulling out.  He is upset about being misled about reasons for the war, and does not agree with how the president is managing the war.  I find it very disturbing that Wolfowitz could not accurately come up with the number of dead American soldiers when asked recently (he was off by 1/3!).  I find it appalling that the majority of American dead have lost their lives since our Cowboy-in-Chief announced “Mission Accomplished” in that spiffy jumpsuit.  The Abu Ghraib scandal is very real, not a media fabrication.  And the abuses are much worse than what Rush Limbaugh characterized as fraternity pranks.  People died as a result of some of these abuses.  Rush likes to remind us that these people are our enemies.  But we’re supposed to be the liberators.  Imagine if in WWII we went into the  concentration camps and had attack dogs intimidate the prisoners.  Yes, these people were being detained, but at least 70% were being wrongfully detained.  Innocent until proven guilty—isn’t that part of our great democracy that we would like to see the Iraqi people enjoy? At the very least, the sophomoric “pranks” the prisoners endured are culturally insensitive.  And I think that’s a problem.  I am ashamed to learn that my government has decided not to abide by the Geneva Conventions, not the Torture Treaty signed in 1994.  This sends the message that while we are not as bad as the likes of Saddam Hussein, we seem to be cut from the same cloth.  This makes it so much easier for others to hate us, and has made recruitment in Al Quaeda soar.  Now, I don’t think we should pander and try to be loved the world over, but I find it troubling that we willingly scamper away from the moral high ground.  Meanwhile. . . .Al Quaeda was no friend of Saddam, and Iraq was not involved in 9/11.  (That was our good friends, the Saudis.)  But now with the instability of Iraq, Iraq is a training center for terrorists.  Okay.  A year and a half ago, there weren’t terrorists in Iraq.  There weren’t WMD’s.  Bush has been taking resources away from the war on terror to fight his personal vendetta.  He is sacrificing the lives of our soldiers in an unjustified war—at least not justified by the reasons we were given in 2003—and he does not even have the decency to honor the fallen by attending funerals of those who have made the ultimate sacrifice.  Reprehensible.  A while ago, I pushed my dad to make a criticism of President Bush.  All he would say is that he didn’t agree with the president’s plan to go to Mars, as our children and grandchildren would be paying off the debt of such exploration for decades.  Meanwhile, Bush is the only president to cut taxes during wartime.  Thank goodness, he’s not a tax-and-spend liberal.  He’s a   cut  -tax-and-spend compassionate conservative.  And our soldiers don’t even have what they need.  Families of soldiers are spending their own money to provide kevlar to protect their loved ones.  Humvees are not properly armored, which has led to avoidable casualties.  But Rummy wants to do this on the cheap.  I guess that’s easy to do when you’re sending other people’s children into harm’s way.  Bush has cut hazardous pay significantly and is cutting back on veteran’s benefits so his billionaire friends can have some walking-around money in their pockets.  Is that supporting the troops?  Furthermore, I’m revolted by the war profiteering going on.  Why is Halliburton getting no-bid contracts in Iraq?  Honestly, I don’t know how Dick Cheney sleeps at night.  Vote for Bush--why change Horsemen mid-Apocalypse?  ****My other sister is equally wise and well-respected, even if she is the one who outed me.  

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've been outed as a blogger by my own sister!  Well, since my family can now find me, I'm very curious to hear reactions to this editorial:  http://www.sojo.net/index.cfm?action=sojomail.display&issue=040512#3.  (I don't know how to do a hyperlink, but you can cut and paste to your browser.)  I've been thinking a lot of the Christian Right's disagreements with the Christian Left, and since I'm the lone heretic in the family, I'm interested to hear opinions from people who I know have love in their hearts.  (I'm not so sure about Tim LaHayne (sp?), Pat Robertson, Jerry Falwell, et. al.) 

						
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I just heard the news of Reagan's death.  The cable news networks seemed ghoulish this morning pondering the eventuality after quoting Nancy saying something to the effect that Ronnie had gone somewhere where she could no longer reach him.  I assume that meant he was comatose.  But I don't get why the news media needed to report on that.  While Reagan seemed perfectly likable to me, I never understood how he got to be so deified.  I don't think it's entirely accurate to attribute the fall of communism to Ronald Reagan.  As far as his approach to governing, I think he basically let his staff do that.  I never felt he had the smarts to really be in charge.  I feel that is even more the case with George W.  The problem here is that Bush has surrounded himself with self-serving, war-profiteering, middle-class destroying, lying megalomaniacs.  I know, I shouldn't hold back like that. 

						
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Apparently you have to become a dittohead to gain access to archives of Rush’s show, for which I do not have the stomach.  (And up with which, I will not put.)      I did find many of his comments quoted in an editorial.  I’m cutting out the editorializing to present Rush’s own words, which I did hear come out of his mouth in several re-broadcasts.  "I'm talking about people having a good time, these people [CIA agents and MPs at Abu Ghraib], you ever heard of emotional release? You heard of need to blow some steam off?" Limbaugh asked a caller. "This is no different than what happens at the Skull and Bones initiation and we're going to ruin people's lives over it and we're going to hamper our military effort, and then we are going to really hammer them because they had a good time."  On his May 3 show, [Limbaugh] said "have you people noticed who the torturers are? Women! The babes! The babes are meting out the torture."   The photographic evidence of the more sexually graphic abuse was the same as "good old American pornography," as Limbaugh said on May 6.   "I think a lot of the American culture is being feminized. I think the reaction to the stupid torture is an example of the feminization of this country," he told his audience.   "It could well be that the whole purpose here, which has been said, was to humiliate these prisoners. And there's no better way of doing it than what was done. These are Arab males -- what better way to humiliate them than to have a woman have authority over them? What's the purpose here? What's the objective of this? The objective is to soften them up for interrogation later, later on. As I said, there was no horror, there was no terror there was no death, there was no injuries, nothing." [Twemty-five people died, as of early May, while detained in Abu Gharib.  One was shot while fleeing.  Ten deaths were determined to be from natural or undisclosed causes.  Ten more deaths were still under investigation as of early May, and two were ruled homicides.]    I heard some excerpts from Rush’s show yesterday.  He was talking to a caller, a self-described Christian, who was expressing concern that Rush’s viewpoints were often not very Christian.  Rush disconnected the caller to respond.  He said he was not a preacher and never claimed to put out the Christian viewpoint, only the conservative viewpoint, and that he never quoted the Bible.  Then he proceeded to say that Jesus never said that wealth should be taken from those that earned it and given to those who didn’t.  Rush went on to explain that Jesus said that if you give a man a fish, he eats for one day, but if you teach a man how to fish, he eats for a lifetime. (!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!)  I do believe there are a few fish stories in the Bible, but this sure isn’t one of them!  I’ve been studying a bit of Methodist theology, and the concept of grace is central to Wesley’s philosophy.  The idea of earned and unearned (implying deserved and undeserved) does not feel very compassionate to me.  And certainly the ideas of manifest destiny and entitlement are very troubling to me.  Rush boasts that his talent is on loan from God. . . .well, that is true of all of us.  Just because some among us haven’t had the best opportunities or the best education doesn’t mean we aren’t all deserving.  

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Let’s revisit the Ten Commandments issue. This was an issue several months ago when a judge in Alabama refused to remove a monument in the courthouse which had the Ten Commandments on it. I believe that this is a violation of church and state. The counterargument is that our country was based on Christian-Judeo traditions. But that’s not really the case. 
</post>


</Blog>