<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was 4++am, when mark walked to his friend's house. He was supposed to take his bike, which he left it at his friend's house and drove to work on the very same morning.  Suddenly a shadow dashed to his front, and the next thing he knew, his head suffer a heavy blow that the pain was immense...   2 malays stroked him v "parang" and punched and kicked him... He was badly hurt. 12 stiches on his head, not to mention a broken bone on his index finger and bruises all around. Drenched with blood, he managed to walked to his friend's house, which thank god he did it, or else I might lose a good friend, a sincere friend.  Life here is not easy, or may I say life is difficult. Even in this quite peaceful land of Malaysia (compared to those suffering as a consequence of war) still people with greed, always thinking of ways to rob, snatch, or even kill for more and more money. Should they have their own hands, why not seek a job and earn some sinless money. To them, all other people are working in order to fulfill their desire, to let them rob and kill?? If I were a superhero, say spiderman... These will be the first people I will reek their face and chop of their ****.    Now I just hope that mark can resume his life well. I pray for my family members well being every now and then. To me if the authority are not concern about peace, sometime we really have to take it into our own hands, one way or another. Protect ourselves and our love ones.   Peace...Peace...
     
    
</post>


<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      我们会有未来吗？天晓得。。。曾经。。。曾经。。。过去的总得过去。 我只可以等。。等你觉悟，让你我走自己的路。彼此的伤害还不够吗？这样下去我们会有结果吗？如果他没离开你，你会回来我身边吗？为何要在决定放弃后回来；为什么要在爱淡了以后；他放弃你以后，又回到我身边。两年了，我怕了；真的怕了！再照顾你到你毕业，我就可以放心了。再见了，我的 First Love...
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Till this day, I am not able to forget how we broke up 2 years ago, yup 2 years... We were on our long vacation back then. We were far aparted.  Days pass by and I was surprised suddenly she seemed to change. Fewer and fewer call, not even a sms in days. Then came complaints, blames ... Until I couldn't bear. We spilt. I was curios how a gal so into u a month ago could turned into such cruelty when she decided to end the relationship.   I rushed to her hometown, just to find that she's then in love v another guy... Great! The way they hold their hands, sweet talk v each other... all being done in front of my own eyes! I was greeted v coldness from her, even reprimended by her for trying to mend our relationship.  I stayed for a night, yup couldnt bear stayin for too long. I was nothin compared to her new lover, actually her best friend's bf or ex-bf should I say...  By the next day, I told myself I might have a chance still, I want her back..badly. But how? Al I could do is to go back and clear my mind. Really... fear reaks my bones, my flesh, especially my heart. I shall remember this day. We have been together since freshmen, almost 2 years. What is in that guy whom she knew for just 2 weeks could make her decide to leave me...Why... I admit mistakes I made, but not like this one she did. I will never betray her. When I was v her, every other gals seemed to be normal, no one can ever replace her...yah, I wonder did she ever felt that way... The way ur lover is the only one u wanna love and care for. The day I left, the guy and her sent me to the station. All I can do is just pretend to be normal, cool... till the bus drove far, then only I allow my tears to fall. But u know wat? Till this day we r still "together". I sent her to uni still coz in the place we study, she has no one to turn to. Soon after uni reopens, her new bf went back to her best friend. She was in deep sore. Came to me and I comforted her. I still want her back. But she didnt give any promises, instead try to mend her relationship v the guy... I was thinkin omg, what is wrong v her, v me?? 2 years passed by just like that, I am not goin to wait no more. Though I was v her all the tim, my feelings for her faded as days pass by. Till recently she wants a commitment from me... I cant really cant... I dont feel the love in her, or even in me... Just another joke she's playin v me, that's the impression she gave me. Just 3 more months b4 she graduates, all I can do is wait, wait till she goes back to her home in far distance, where she will find her happiness... she sure will. Then I can have my own life back. For now, I can just wait...
     

    
</post>


</Blog>