<Blog>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hola. first time to post. i dunno what to talk about. i'm not even sure people are gonna read this but thats okay, i still got xanga. its o-so-much cooler than this. umm...all i have to say is that boys are dumb. bye bye  love...dork
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    alex...what a hottie...love that kid...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>


<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and she does it again! damnit, i'm never introducing a guy to my friends ever again. ima de-friend myself or i don't know. but i'm soOoo SICK of guys that i have a chance with and that we like each other going for my friends i'm like, WHAT THE HELL?!  HELLO?! I'M HERE! REMEMBER ME?! gawd.     DAMNIT.  yeah, i think im just gonna get rid of muh friends and just be lonely.  i'd rather be lonely than "heartbroken". ya know that saying "its better to have love and lost than to have never loved at all." well thats CRAP!  its more like, "its better to have love and lost than to have gotten fucked up the ass with a cactus."  haha, i like i like. alrighty...bye bye  yo te amo con todo mi corazon...gina 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      gah... so hannah came over tonight. k don't get me wrong, i love the gal but shes like one of my best friends little sisters so its kinda weird ya know? and ria didn't even come. so yeah. and then brian and jermaine come over un-invited and jermaine kept huggin on me and shit and i kept pushin him off cause gah i mean like literally 5 seconds before he was like, i met the love of my life...at the hodeo, i was like, what tha fuck?! and yeah...and then brian taught me how to 2-step which was kinda cool but then he kept givin' me hugs and he tried to kiss me like twice and i pushed him off and he just kinda smiled like it was all cool, but i don't get him!! i mean i'm getting on to him for messin' around with Ria's sister and he thinks I'M gonna do shit with him? come on now. but hey, it showed that i had self-control, i think this is a first...go me! yay! but ummm...anywho*hah...i was just thinkin, isn't it funny that for once i'm showing self-control...hmm...  yo te amo con todo me corazon...gina
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      man...lap dances are *great*!   haha. i'm just gonna spill cause ria doesn't know 'bout this place. Brian is soOo hott and he gave me a "lap dance" he wasn't serious about it...i think. and it was great fun but he kept tryin to kiss me. for one ria was around so i'm not kissing him. and for two shes like madly in love with him and so i'm not doin the shit she did to me cause we're over that. and three even tho she did do that to me she at least did it behind my back so i didn't have to see it, haha. I sound awful...gah.  i just love that kid to death...already. he probably feels like a pimp. him and ria aren't goin' out but they act like it alot and him and her sister are messin around and i tried to talk to him 'bout it but stupid hannah came in.  but i think he understands that i won't hesitate to kick his ass if he doesn't drop one of them, cause its bad because hannah doesn't have the balls to tell her sister. I think if shes gonna do it she should tell her. i love this thing cause i know no one will read this...or no one that knows any of these people so its nice just to vent. yay. i dunno. and then brian's stupid friend jermain...pisses me off. he'll be all sweet to me and then he does the same thing to hannah and then he comes back to me and i'm like, uhh...do i look like sloppy seconds?   well...i do look like sloppy seconds...or maybe sixteenths...hah. but thats not the point.  so yeah...he was like, i love you. i was like, really? thanks! haha.  it made me giggle.  he thinks hes a damn pimp...fuck that.  and then him and brian are always out at the hoedeo (rodeo).  that place is so scuzzy. i wouldn't go in there to save my *LYFE* aha.  even tho i bytch about all this stuff i still have alot of fun when i hang out with these kids. but brian. i dunno about that kid...he plays around too much to not be serious sometimes, ya know. but dayum it was nice..he kissed me on the cheek and i was tryin to play it off like i didn't lyke it and he started kissin my back n shyt and i was like, DAYUM!  what the hell happend to my spelling? o well.  hah. and yeah...it was quite...nice. but shhh...thats our secret.  but i don't think i would like...wanna be with him cause hes a 'player' and plus ria likes him and so does hannah so i'm not gettin my ass stuck in between there...its just a guy, i'm sure i can find better. but anyone looks better compared to brandon...what a dick. everytime brandon's name comes in my head i get dizzy. weird? i think so. o well...fuck him...hes an ass. never again...never again. okay well i don't have much  more to rant and bitch about and i really have to PEEEEEEE. bye bye fer rizzles muh nizzles....oh scratch that.  yo te amo con todo me corazon...gina
     

    
</post>


</Blog>