<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I just received this message in my email......Hello Lovers Unite Member Just to let you all know that Sarah gave birth to another lovely baby boy last Thursday. Hes called Sam. They are all very well but resting up for a few weeks.  Which means your membership cards may take a bit longer as Martin is also taking some time off! love Sarah, Bob and Pete xxxx so this would be her second child...now I eagerly await her 2nd solo album. Saint Etienne have also compiled this groovy sounding collection......Songs For Mario's Cafe We've put together a compilation of music which kind of goes hand in glove with Caff the movie. It's music suitable for playing in a cafe - one not unlike Mario's Cafe in Kelly Street, NW5. So it is called Saint Etienne Present Songs For Mario's Cafe and it's coming out on Sanctuary very soon, we'll let you know when there's a definite release date but I reckon it's the last week in June. It errs on the side of sixties beat, sixties girls, and seventies soul, with a healthy serving of melancholy Look out for that one Giddy London!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hey Giddy London!  Looks like this could be worth checking out in Sept!  I wish I could see it!........... Pet Shop Boys plan free film gig  The Pet Shop Boys will unveil their latest project - a soundtrack to the 1925 film Battleship Potemkin - at a free show in London's Trafalgar Square.  The film, an account of a sailors' revolt in 1904, has been a major influence on film-makers and artists.  The show, which will take place on 12 September, is part of a season of events taking place in the square.  In a statement, Neil Tennant and Chris Lowe said the soundtrack would include three new songs.  However, it will mainly be a instrumental score.  "It's wonderful to be given the opportunity to write a complete soundtrack to this classic film and then to perform it as a free concert in the heart of London," he said.  The soundtrack will be orchestrated by German composer Torsten Rasch, who recently launched his live work, Mein Herz Bernnt, based on the music of hard rock band Rammstein.  It will be performed by the 26-strong Dresden Sinfoniker.  Political dissent  Trafalgar Square was chosen because of its long history as the focus for political dissent in the UK.  The show is part of Trafalgar Square Summer 2004, a programme of free events organised by Mayor Ken Livingstone.  Philip Dodd, director of the nearby Institute of Contemporary Arts, which is producing the show, said: "I'm deeply grateful to the Pet Shop Boys and all the events collaborators for their immediate recognition that Trafalgar Square is the place for re-imagining the past in terms of the needs of the present."  The film, directed by Sergei Eisenstein, tells the story of a mutiny on board a Russian battleship, sparked by the crew being given rotten meat to eat. The revolt leads to a riot, which leads to a fleet of battleships being drafted in to destroy the Potemkin.  Artists influenced by the film include Francis Bacon, who said he was haunted by the screaming mouth in the film and was inspired to use it in his own work.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Yay! This is good news I read on a Canadian website. After the stinker that was "Big Fish" I can't wait for this return to "Nightmare Before Xmas" territory.....From Variety..... Johnny Depp and director Tim Burton are teaming up once again on the stop-motion animated film "Corpse Bride," Variety reports.   Depp will provide the lead voice, and Burton will share directing duties with Michael Johnson.   Other actors contributing character voices include Helena Bonham Carter, Emily Watson, Albert Finney, Richard Grant, Joanna Lumley and Christopher Lee.   "Corpse Bride" is scheduled for release in October of 2005.   Depp recently signed on to play Willy Wonka in the Burton-directed "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory," which will hit theatres on July 15, 2005 &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Chris and I both had the day off so off we pedalled to Clifton Hill for lunch. It was a very sunny but windy day and we dined on a disappointing pastie at Deganni's (is that what they're called?).  After that we rode home via Fitzroy to sample some gelati from a new icecream cafe that had opened. It all looked yummy but in actuality tasted so bland and dare I say, not sweet enough. Probably too many natural ingredients.  Across the road was this giant cupie doll that Mr Saliba dubbed "Big Baby" which caught my eye. How do I win one of these?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Graffiti in Brunswick street Fitzroy where we tethered our bikes.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Just finished reading "Lulu In Hollywood" which is a collection of essays written by the iconic Louise Brooks. What a smart cookie she was. Her astute observations of life in tinsel town during the silent era thru to the talkies is both fascinating and somewhat sad. No wonder she gave it all up in the end. The final chapter she wrote is called "Why I will never write my memoirs" which like her relatively brief film career leaves the viewer/reader wanting so much more.  Dear Giddy London, if you are reading this  have you ever seen "Pandora's Box" or "Diary of a Lost Girl"?  These are defining Brooksian moments that will haunt you forever. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Atom Ant Crayons&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hands up who remembers Atom Ant? I was a huge fan of this miniscule yet mighty cartoon insect. I just loved the cute helmet and the way he hurled all those supercrooks into the air. "Up and at'em, Atom Ant!!!!" These snaps are the front and back of a crayon pack...the sort of thing I would have nagged my poor mother to buy while shopping at the supermarket on a Friday nite after school &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    At last! Thanks to the new city library I was able to view my first Preston Sturges film. Having read so much about him (and his influence on the Coen brothers) I was thrilled to discover that his reputation as a comic genius was well deserved. What a premise! Hollywood director Joel McCrea hits the road disguised as a tramp in order to gain first hand experience of human suffering for his upcoming flick "Oh Brother Where Art Thou" (see the Coen connection?). On the way he meets up with aspiring actress Veronica Lake (dressed by Edith Head and looking totally amazing!) and the two hit the road with hilarious results. What makes this film even more remarkable is the way in which  Sturge's social concerns are so perfectly  intertwined with the slapstick comedy.  This film charters darker waters as it progresses but ultimately it becomes a filmic ode to the ability of humour overcoming depressing odds.  A scene involving a church filled with chaingang prisoners howling with laughter at a Mickey Mouse cartoon is priceless.  Can't wait to get my hands on "The Lady Eve" - another Sturges comedy of the sexes starring Barbara Stanwyck.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I was awoken today by the sound of the postie dropping a parcel thru my letterbox. Hmm..what could it be this time?  To my surprise it was a cd I purchased thru Amazon from one of their secondhand sellers. So, for the low low price of 10.90 aust I received this fabulous Gloria Estefan nonstop party cd in less than 7 days from the US plus it wasn't even used...shrinkwrapped and fresh!  So I eagerly popped her on the cdplayer and it was as if the Miami Sound Machine days were back again.  This is a great dance album. Wow!  Get that conga line going now!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I was in JB Hifi today and was pleasantly surprised to pick up a copy of EBTG's second album "Love not Money" for only $9.99!  How ironic!  It's a catchy collection of poppy/folky/jazzy songs....very similar to their first album which Chris Saliba and I both adore.  Also includes a cover of The Pretenders' "Kid".   Interesting fact  - the name EVERYTHING BUT THE GIRL was taken from a shop in Hull, East Yorkshire, UK, where Ben and Tracey lived during the early 80's. The shop, which stood on the Beverley Road, sold brand new but dated household furniture to newly married couples. Stuck in a retro timewarp, the shop closed and was knocked down during the late 80's &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    How sweet!  Madonna and her new pal Michael Moore met up backstage to plan the overthrow of George "Papa dont Preach" Bush after her concert last week.  Look out George....looks like your "Lucky Star" could be sooo "Borderline"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Check out this amazing photo.  A very young Dave Letterman and a gorgeous looking Divine. What an episode that must have been. &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    He's back!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Newsflash!!  This rare sighting of Dribbles took place today. I was pegging out the washing when I felt a furry presence behind me. Imagine my shock when I turned around to see the original cat inhabitant of Arden street.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I came across this exciting news today...mecca lecca hi!  Time to turf those dusty vhs copies....Image Entertainment and Herman World Announce Agreement to Bring Classic Television Favorite ``Pee-Wee's Playhouse'' to DVD   CHATSWORTH, Calif.--(BUSINESS WIRE)--June 8, 2004--Image Entertainment, Inc. (NASDAQ: DISK):   -- Complete 45-Episode Series (Including Six Episodes Never Before Released) in Two Individually Priced Collections and "Pee-Wee's Playhouse Christmas Special" DVD Releases Planned for Fall  -- A Definitive, Specially Packaged Limited Edition Containing All 45 Episodes and Commentary by Paul Reubens to Be Released in 2005  Image Entertainment, Inc. (NASDAQ: DISK) today announced the signing of an exclusive license agreement with Herman World, Inc., which will see the Company release the complete 45-episode (including 6 "lost" episodes never before released to home video) classic television series "Pee-wee's Playhouse," split between two box set collections, and also "Pee-wee's Playhouse Christmas Special," on DVD this fall.  Paul Reubens, star and creator of the series, commenting on the deal, stated, "I am extremely pleased that `Pee-wee's Playhouse' will be available on DVD. The digital medium affords the shows a look that was not possible when they were originally broadcast or made available on VHS in the 1980s and '90s. I look forward to working with Image's creative, sales and marketing teams to make this series truly special."  Image, with the full cooperation and participation of "Playhouse" creator and star Paul Reubens, also plans to release in 2005 a definitive, specially packaged limited edition containing all 45 episodes with commentary by Paul Reubens and additional bonus material culled from Reubens' vast show archives &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Yes folks...only a matter of days till Chris' first lemon is ready to be squeezed.  After 1 year and 2 months of waiting patiently the sour fruit of one's labour has finally arrived. Taste test results to follow. Stay tuned.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Upon arriving home after my 2 hr bike ride from Nth Melbourne to the Docklands and onto Southbank I was greeted by this lovely sight. "Oh Blackie...you shouldn't have!  Such lovely flowers!"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    More bridges for riding under. The river is home to a large amount of birdlife...esp ducks.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is the entrance to the new bridge crossing the Yarra.  It's fun to ride on and I was amazed at seeing all the new construction going on.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Here's the entrance to a new bridge  near the waterfront/docklands precinct.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Yo ho ho and a bottle of pepsimax!  Here's the jolly Pollywoodside which I was able to ride past via the yarra bike path.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Just moments away from the big march!  Mum and Dad had travelled down from Geelong to protest against the logging of Tasmanian forest. I had no intention of joining them but was soon swept up in their treehugging politics.  Chain me to a tree now!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Here's Mum adding her signed leaf  to the protest banner. She's a dab hand at this.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Mum and Dad watch as the Chainsaw Cabaret performs for the crowd. I'm having a good 'ol chuckle.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Here's Chris Saliba and  my mum hamming it up for the camera.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    What a surprise!  Robert Franklyn joined us during the march.  It was a lot of fun. Who would've thought?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I found this at my fave tabloid scandal website......................................................TROUBLED Britney Spears sinks to a new low swigging whisky and Red Bull and scoffing junk food in the street with her love-rat fiancé.  The once-glamorous pop princess, 22, looked a slob as she drifted from one low-budget store to another for lunch with jobless dancer Kevin Federline.  First the pair  who have just flown home from a beach holiday in Hawaii  picked up French fries at Neptunes Net on the Pacific Coast Highway in Malibu.      Then 15 minutes later, they stopped at sandwich shop Subway for filled rolls and fizzy orange. They left munching bags of cheese and onion Wheatos crisps and salt and vinegar Lays.  Finally, came their third stop in 30 minutes at a liquor store to buy Britney a miniature of Glenlivet whisky. She gulped it down in one, followed by a chaser of caffeine drink Red Bull.  Kevin, 26  who has dumped his seven-months pregnant lover to woo Britney  clutched a bottle of cola and a stuffed grocery bag with a packet of cigs balancing on the top.  An onlooker said: I had to look twice it didn't even look like Britney. Her hair was a mess and she looked like she was wearing his jeans, they were so long.  The only giveaway was her bling-bling engagement ring. Britney who six months ago wed pal Jason Alexander for 55 hours has known Kev three months. She proposed to him with a £25,000 ring.  The singer has been riding high at No1 with Everytime but has cancelled a world tour because of a knee injury. She was recently pictured looking bloated, spotty and puffing a ciggy.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I was in JB today in search of Kylie's "Chocolate" single on cd (she really should have marketed a limited edition edible version) after having previously purchased the vinyl picturedisc. Anyway, I was browsing thru the Duran Duran section and found this, the remastered version of their debut album. I first owned this on cassette which was probably played to stretching point... then a couple of decades pass and whaddya know,  I possess it once more. Forget about the obvious singles....what I love are the lesser known gems such as "Anyone out there" and "Sound of Thunder".  And what a relief  to find no unnecessary "bonus" tracks, just a lovely cardboard digipak cover. The 80's never looked so good!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    From Yahoo news....(trust the Japanese to come up with this doozy..looks like Furby has bitten the dust!!)       TOKYO (AFP) - Fans of Hello Kitty will get a chance to realise their dream of chatting with the hugely popular cartoon character later this year with the launch of a hi-tech robot of the feline.  The 52-centimetre-high (20.8-inch) robot will be able to recognise 10 people, greeting them and having chats, using phrases such as "It's already lunch time. Have you eaten yet?", according to manufacturer Business Design Laboratory Co. Ltd.  Equipped with an ultra-sound sensor and camera, the mechanical Kitty can tell if anybody is approaching.  It can call a playmate's name and start chatting by sorting 20,000 patterns of pre-registered conversations and picking phrases it feels are best suited to the occasion.  Hello Kitty was created by Tokyo-based firm Sanrio Co. Ltd. According to Sanrio's "biography" of Kitty, the feline was born in London on November 1, 1974.  Hello Kitty products are sold in 60 nations and some 50,000 different types of Kitty character goods were sold worldwide during the previous fiscal year to March 2004 alone.  Business Design hopes to sell 2,000 robot cats this year, priced at around 400,000 yen (3,710 dollars), by mainly targeting women in their 30s who are among the cat's biggest fans.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    All rise...his majesty has arrived. Notice the damaged crown...this is a common problem Crater Critter Collectors have to contend with. It is almost impossible to find a mint Kingly.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The official govt sanctioned Crater Critters identification guide.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well almost. I've started reading a book called "Searching for Kingly Critter" which is all about the history and collectability of those wonderful moulded plastic toys we found lurking within cereal boxes back in the late 60s / early 70s. My heart skipped a beat when I saw the cover of the book featuring the regal Kingly Critter himself. I was obsessed with collecting the Crater Critters, Tooly Birds and the Camel Trains but I actually found King Neptune and his underwater orchestra to be the most fascinating and dreamy.  What is more amazing was discovering that these toys were created and manufactured in Richmond Victoria Aust....just across the way!!   Click on this  urlLink link  to discover a wacky world that I had previously thought long forgotten except in my crazy frOOt-Loop fueled dreams.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The two Chris' decided to have a little picnic down by the Yarra on what was a perfect Winters Sunday. No rain, plenty of sunshine and no wind....well not till Chris consumed this can of baked beans.  Heaps better than the UK product.  Nice spread on bread for a sandwich sensation. Beanz meanz Heinz!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Mmmm. Nothing like the taste of a Mocha Blast 98% fat free milk drink.  Chris and Chris found this drink at the local city Safeway and took it on their picnic. Chug-a-lug!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>