<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I found this website that when you push the button you can name your emo band that. I love the site. There are some great names. Its good fun.  http://members.aol.com/Valdes379/EmoGame.html  Anyways...I have to go to bed soon so I can be rested for my BIG day. I have to figure out how to do photos for my blog but yeah. Night Night. jeno
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Like I said yesterday I went to a Party. I DRANK a LOT! Too much, so this morning I had to go and sit on the bathroom floor for like an hour. I had to wait 45 mins to puke because I knew I was going to so might as well get it over. I only Puked once at that party. In my whole drinking career which was just started when I was 15, I've only puked 3 times counting the one last night. And the last two times I puked for hours on end. But other than puking I had fun. Everyone is usually irritated because they are drunk sept me, but this time only one kid was. He said the reason for his assholeness was because he hadn't seen me in a while so he wanted to make sure to make up for it. The FUCKER! Well now I'm home and bored to death and I have school tomorrow that I don't want to go to. I want to because I ran for Student council Prez and I think I am the only one that ran which in away is good but I didn't want it just handed over to me. Well whatever happens happens. I'm going to go and fulfill being border. Bye bye  jeno
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey hey! Last night was Prom and it was okay. It wasn't the best dance I've ever been to, but it was better than some. Well like every dance for high school there is always drama. I had a share of my own but I don't express it in a situation like that. All of my "friends" had there own drama and I had to listen to them Bitch. Not fun. I did still bust out with my cool moves. My drama, if you wanna hear me bitch. My drama was that I met this guy at a writing Conference but he lives in another state about 5 hours away. I really like him and he really likes me but the distance is really screwing us over. So he couldn't come to my prom and plus he didn't go to his prom because he doesn't do the whole high school dance scene, he would rather go off and get high. Which is another reason that it just wouldn't work between us, I'm not straight edge but I'm not a complete pothead either. Anyways so he couldn't come up for prom, so I asked one of my friends to prom and I asked her because she was the only one with a dress. She was pretty much chill through the whole thing but the guy she likes and I guess likes her wasn't talking to her so she was all sad and depressed. For me this guy I liked all my high school career but I got over him a couple months ago. He was there with his girlfriend, which she hates me. They had a fight there and I couldn't do anything and I tried to get him to talk to me about what happened but he didn't say anything. I was happy that they had a fight which sounds bad but then I was really hurt that he was sad and he wasn't with me. After they kinda made up and they were all kissy infront of me and my heart just shattered and my stomach knotted. I felt so bad. I was about to cry. I didn't, I went on with my life. Today I'm going to a party. I cant wait its been since Feb. since I've done anything. I'm jonesing for something. I should stop bitching. Have fun. Jeno
     

    
</post>


</Blog>