<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is Memorial Day and while we attended the requisite party at our good friends Jeff and Kathi's house, I had to think about the deeper meaning of Memorial Day. Although I have always known the true meaning, before now it has just been a day for fun, cooking out, and entertaining.  Now I realize that it is about remembering those who have died both in wars and not.  I spent a lot of the day talking to my neighbor about what a brewmiester my cousin was.  Then a new neighbor arrived.  He has to be in his late 80's and is a WWII veteran.  He ate with us, talked to the kids and even shared a beer with the guys.  I was in awe of him because he is just a neat old man and he had so much fun just talking and watching the kids swim.  He just lost his wife of many years in January and yet here he was still seeking out friendships with his neighbors who are young enough to be his grandchildren. What a cool guy!  And we did have a nice day just relaxing by the pool, eating and watching our kids play.  It is great to have good friends!  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it was bound to happen, I guess.  Last summer I was told that my cousin had a "blog"....not quite knowing what that was, I wasn't sure if I should be concerned or not!  After logging on to his blog and seeing what a really cool thing it is, I thought I might one day try it and never gave it another thought. My cousin was a total computer freak.  He knew everything there was to know.  While I like to think I am pretty good, I had no clue how to do this.....  Life gets to us sometimes, you know?  We all get busy and times just flies by and of course, I never did get around to trying to figure out how to be a "blogger".   Now we fast forward to April of this year when this same dear cousin of mine suddenly passed away at age 35.  Now I was forced to stop and think about some things. I realized  that life is just way too short.  And, yes, I had read his blog, but had I called my cousin?  Had I sent a card or an e-mail?  No....and now I can't. And yet, even with that kind of wake up call I find myself still being too busy to stay in close contact with those who are the most important to me.  I vow to do better.  Not a day has passed since that April morning when we lost my cousin that I have not cried for him, his little girl, his wife and his parents and brother.  Our family will never be the same again.  But I do know that we must take time to connect with others, even though we are too busy and life is crazy most of the time.  Because, I have sadly learned, when they are gone, it is too late. So, for you Jeremy, I too, will be a blogger!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, we survived our vacation.  It was cold and rained a lot but still beats the heat of Texas in June.  Spending time with 35 relatives is quite an undertaking....and then there are those who come home with you for another week!    Got a call today that my dear friend lost her baby boy at 22 weeks gestation.  How can that be fair when that baby was wanted so much?   It is hard to understand sometimes.  The summer is passing quickly.....maybe we can get some things accomplished before school starts back up.... Why is it time goes so fast when you need it to go slowly???? 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We are officially on a much needed vacation.  It is so cold here and only going to get colder.  We are in northern Wisconsin and from Fort Worth, Texas, it is a world away.  Riding so far in the car with two teen and pre-teen boys plus a grown man is almost more than any woman should have to bear.  Between the farting and burping, there isn't much room for conversation.  It should prove to be a nice week away from the rat race that our lives have become.  My parents will be flying in to join us tomorrow and I really should be getting some sleep now.  I had good luck with scratch cards today, which I really never buy when at home, but on vacation, it seems that anything goes.  I won a total of 145.00 and spent only 22.00.   Not a bad profit.  Kind of makes up for having to sit with kids who burp and fart all day.....
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night the metro area was hit by huge storms and we were without power for about 3 hours.  It got pretty creepy, just me, the kids, the dog and a bunch of candles burning.  They say it is headed our way again right now.  It made me realize that we depend on electricity and our TV's, Computers, etc. WAY too much!  My kids and I sat there in the dark and didn't quite know what to do......sad, huh?    We are supposed to be heading up to Tulsa tonight, but will have to wait until we see what the weather is going to do.   I hate this...I am ready to get on with my vacation and head north where it is cool!    
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight I met one of my new students.  Yes he has some brain damage, but he understands right and wrong and knows what is expected of him.  He came into my class, rolled around on the floor, screamed at his parents, hit his baby sister, threw cars, etc....This is not the first child I have taught who was like this.  Do you think 4 minutes of time out will do this one any good?  Nope!  It sets him off more.  When my boys were little I never would have put up with rude, disrespectful behavior and yet these days it seems to be the norm.  The kids I teach are special ed, however, we have MANY who are very bright children who know how to manipulate better than any adult.  I am just thankful I don't have to LIVE with those kids!
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I can hardly believe it.&nbsp; Today was my last day of "freedom" before returning to work after summer vacation.&nbsp; Our summers in Keller are so short...we are only out about seven weeks and I am not quite finished recovering from last semester yet.&nbsp; Tomorrow it is back to the salt mines as they say.&nbsp; I'll have a few weeks to get used to my new kids and new schedules and then my graduate school will begin again!&nbsp; Why am I doing this to myself??&nbsp;&nbsp; I have to work, so that one is a no-brainer, but the grad school thing is just a personal achievement I really want to have.&nbsp; If I didn't have to drive all the way to Denton to attend classes it would not be so bad.&nbsp; Oh well, I guess I will just suck it up and do it anyway!   Scott and David are not at all happy either.  They go back next Tuesday...what I would give for one more week...... 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow!&nbsp; Today was quite a day!  While trying to be a good mom and take my boys for one last outing to Six Flags before school starts I was involved in the scare of my life!  Scott, David, and Scott's friend Jeff, and I had been at Six Flags all day and had a ton of fun even though it was very hot and humid today.&nbsp; We had to leave at 3:30 due to Scott and Jeff being due at a party (that's a blog for another time....not quite ready for these high school parties), so we decided to ride just one more ride and then go.&nbsp; Jeff and David opted for bumper cars while Scott and I just wanted one more roller coaster ride.&nbsp; We hopped on the Flashback as Jeff and David went to the bumper cars right next to our ride.&nbsp; The first part of our ride was fine, but then, as we were totally on the top, almost flat on our backs, VERY HIGH IN THE AIR, the thing jolted to a stop!&nbsp; At first I thought it was just going to stop for a second and then go, but as the seconds became a minute, I realized that we were stuck!&nbsp; And as I looked down below, there stood David and Jeff and all I could think about was that I was going to die on that thing and my little son was going to see the whole thing!&nbsp;&nbsp; Bearing in mind it was 101 degrees and I suddenly had to go to the bathroom, I began to panic just a bit.&nbsp; Scott, on the other hand, was having a ball.&nbsp; He said it was the best part of his day.&nbsp; Finally, after about 15 minutes (which is a LONG time when you are stuck on a roller coaster) they got it going again and all I could do was pray that this time when it stopped, we would be on the ground!&nbsp;   Thank you, Lord for getting us off there safely!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      These last few weeks have been crazy.&nbsp; I suppose that time really does go faster when you get older, but it is hard to get anything accomplished when time is zooming by!   School starts back for me next week and the boys the week after that.&nbsp; My niece, Susan moved in with us two weeks ago after accepting a job in Human Resources at the Albertson's Division Office here.&nbsp; It has been lovely having her and not as much of an adjustment (at least for us) as I thought it would be.&nbsp; It is nice to not be the only woman in the house!&nbsp; She will be getting her apartment next month but for now I am trying to spoil her a bit.&nbsp;   My graduate courses will resume the end of August and while I dread the drive to Denton, I really want this degree badly.   I have been working out regularly lately.&nbsp; Dixie, Susan and I are attending Jazzercize four to five times a week and working out in the gym on other nights.&nbsp; I have never worked out so much and I hope it helps.   Our family is still reeling in the loss of my cousin and I still haven't been able to be much comfort to his parents.&nbsp; Of that, I am ashamed.&nbsp; I wish so much that I could reach out to them, but I am so aware that both my sons are alive and healthy and how is that fair?&nbsp;&nbsp;   On a lighter note, I have been able to spend some much needed time with a dear friend whom I had not seen in a year and that was lovely.&nbsp; My closets are cleaned out, my laundry is done and so I guess I can go back to work.......   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Night before last I had the strangest dream and it really has me a little freaked out.  I dreamed that the whole family, Linda & Louis included were at this restaurant for someone's birthday celebration.  We were talking and suddenly the door opened and in walked Jeremy.   We all just were shocked and stared at him and didn't know what to think or how to behave because we all knew he had passed away in April, yet there he was, just like always, healthy as could be.....He smiled at us and said, "Just joking guys!  I didn't really die!"   And then everyone was angry at him for the horrible joke, but so glad to see him too.....And when I woke up I felt so strange because I can't figure out what that all means.  I don't know if it means anything at all, but it was so real and yet so strange.   I wish he could come back.......it sure would make so many of us happy again.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>