<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    a closer look&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Dictonaries have for years attempted to define handsome. We now have the answer.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello there all you fair folk of the world who choose to partake in this new adventure of mine. Bombastic blogging has arrived, and apparently this is where it is at. In our 'advanced', 'progressive state' of being, the computer-age is a defining element of modern culture. It shows us how far we have come, how progressive we are, the efficiency and economy of the times, it also upholds the notion of change, giving credibility to the idea of evolution. We are going places! The technocrat places his faith in the ability of machinery to save humanity from their plight. The tidal wave of technology has come crashing upon us, sweeping us off our feet, and into the unknown. The rip curl off that tidal wave, has hit me for behind, and I also have succumb to the overtures of the computer-age.  The 'impersonal unknown' is what I'm engaged with, it may become known, if you learn its language and spend countless hours in communication. I do not speak the language of computers. I do not know why they do certain things. I was told in school that computer illiteracy would be my ruin, if you did not move with the times your existence was rendered meaningless, a spare part in the relentless machine of advancement. Abandoned and obsolete like old hardware in the skip at the science-park. Of no use, expired and out-of date like Windows 95. The education system dreamed up a future of dependence, dependence to the computer. Those in the know would be employable, those who didn't know their @ from their tab and their Java from their F12 would be unemployable. I am unemployable.   I'm illiterate, I cannot communicate with the computer. I do not understand it, it does not understand me. I do not want to understand the computer. It is a functional tool. I use and abuse it, when the abuse is too severe it crashes, when it crashes I become irate. It often crashes. I'm often irate. The printer cable from the PC does not fit into my MAC. It confuses me. I save essays that I have worked on for hours. There is no record of my essay, all files have been wiped. The MAC even talks to me. I'll tell it to hop it, but it remains resolutely on my desk. It is big, ugly and grey weighs like an unforgivable sin and disturbs the calm with the whirring of the fan. I understand hammers. They hammer in nails. Some hammers have a claw end, this is useful for pulling out old nails. I like the hammer. I know what it does and why it does it. Hammer in the morning... Hammer in the evening...  The web. The net. Abstract entities. Fisherman and his friend, the Fisherman's friend, use their net for a purpose. They catch fish for consumption. That is what fishermen and their friends do. Their net serves a purpose, it is real, when you pull it out of the sea it is dripping wet, the rope scores your hands. I understand nets. They receive the football, contain beautiful legs, and are an integral part of Wimbledon. I confess to not understanding net-curtains. Burning books is considered anti-intellectual, but I cannot find anything anti-intellectual with burning net-curtains. Amnesty international is pleading with house owners to release their net-curtains without further delay. Reason being, their horrendous capacity to block light, create exclusion and hide the private. Say NO to drugs! Say NO to net-curtains!  The purpose of my blog? It is a diary. Bringing the private into the public. Recording that which is often left unsaid, publishing those thoughts that Political correctness labels as non-thoughts. Confront the taboo. Look at the controversial. Speak the mind. APS is crap. Food is over prized. Celebrities poo. Bureaucrats are a hinderence. Life is full of contradictions. I ramble.  Blogging off.  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You may not know me, but I know everything about you...  Psalm 139:1  I know when you sit down, and when you rise up...  Psalm 139:2  I am familiar with all your ways...  Psalm 139:3  Even the very hairs on your head are numbered...  Matthew 10:29-31  For you were made in my image...  Genesis 1:27  In Me you live and move and have your being...  Acts 17:28  For you are my offspring...  Acts 17:28  I knew you even before you were conceived...  Jeremiah 1:4-5  I chose you when I planned creation...  Ephesians 1:11-12  You were not a mistake for all your days are written in my book..  Psalm 139:15-16  I determined the exact time of your birth and where you would live...  Acts 17:26  You are fearfully and wonderfully made...  Psalm 139:14  I knit you together in your mother's womb...  Psalm 139:13  And brought you forth on the day you were born...  Psalm 71:16  I have been misrepresented by those who don't know me...  John 8:41-44  I am not distant and angry, but am the complete expression of love...  1 John 4:16  And it is My desire to lavish My love on you simply because you are My child, and I am your Father...  1 John 3:1  I offer you more than your earthly father ever could...  Matthew 7:11  For I am the perfect Father...  Matthew 5:48  Every good gift that you receive comes from My hand...  James 1:17  For I am your provider, and I meet all your needs...  Matthew 6:31-33  My plan for your future has always been filled with hope...  Jeremiah 29:11  Because I love you with an everlasting love...  Jeremiah 31:3  My thoughts toward you are as countless as the sand on the seashore...  Psalm 139:17-18  And I rejoice over you with singing...  Zephaniah 3:17  I will never stop doing good to you...  Jeremiah 32:40  For you are My treasured possession...  Exodus 19:5  I desire to establish you with all My heart and all My soul...  Jeremiah 32:41  And I want to show you great and marvelous things...  Jeremiah 33:3  If you seek Me with all your heart, you will find Me...  Deuteromony 4:29  Delight in Me, and I will give you the desires of your heart...  Psalm 37:4  For it is I who gave you those desires...  Philippians 37:4  I am able to do more for you than you could possibly imagine...  Ephesians 3:20  For I am your greatest encourager...  II Thessalonians 2:16-17  I am also the Father who comforts you in all your troubles...  II Corinthians 1:3-4  When you are brokenhearted, I am close to you...  Psalm 34:18  As a shepherd carries a lamb, I have carried you close to My heart...  Isaiah 40:11  One day I will wipe away every tear from your eyes and will take away all the pain you have suffered on this earth...  Revelation 21:3-4  I am your Father, and I love you even as I love My son, Jesus...  John 17:23  For in Jesus, My love for you is revealed...  John 17:26  He has exact representation of My being...  Hebrews 1:3  He came to demonstrate that I am for you, not against you...  Romans 8:31  And to tell you that I am not counting your sins...  II Corinthians 5:18-19  Jesus died so that you and I could be reconciled...  II Corinthians 5:18-19  His death was the ultimate expression of My love for you...  I John 4:10  I gave up everything that I loved that I might gain your love...  Romans 8:31-32  If you receive the gift of My son Jesus, you receive Me...  I John 2:23  And nothing will ever separate you from My love again...  Romans 8:38-39  Come Home, and I'll throw the biggest party Heaven has ever seen...  Luke 15:7  I have always been Father, and will always be Father...  Ephesians3:14-15  My question is...Will you be My child?...  John 1:12-13  I am waiting for you...  Luke 15:11-32   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You can. You really can. If anyone can, it's you that can. To reach a weight of perfection. The ideal weight, a smaller size, less on your plate, sleeker thighs. You've heard it all before. The stream-lined you donning a catsuit will purr and woo, persuading men that slender chicks no longer poo. Someone in the desert once, promised the earth, and all within, only if you bowed to him. When Mrs. Melton Mowbray releases her latest info pack on dieting will you die trying to achieve a new look? On her video, your own eyes will see, that watching your weight will keep you lean. No fuss to be honest, only a few minor alterations. To 'feel great', there is no need to emigrate, just calculate your fat burning rate. Your room by now, a science lab, walls cluttered with graphs, instructing you how, pointing the way. Eyes fixed on your weight, constantly watching, all you begin seeing is weight. Wait a minute! You're telling me, I'll 'feel great', when all I'm doing is focusing on my weight. How many points can I have to keep me on track? A muffin here, a Donut there, eat these and I'm falling back. You can enter the calorie count, but be sure, that this is the steed you wish to mount. A clapped out mere, blinkered and blind, trotting behind the roulette ball, to spin in the merry-go-round, round until your head is spinning with points and pounds. Is it worth believing that weight loss is achieving? 3 pounds down, thundering applause!! They pat you on your back, say your doing great, 'fat camp' coaches lifting you up with praise. When all the while, a pie chart recording the calorie count, sends signals to your brain; 'Mouth. Begin. To. Salivate.'.  Slim fast, quick as you like, instant success with a few shakes. Hocus pocus, no effort at all, rabbit out the hat, check it out; 'I'm no longer Fat!' Hey presto, before and after, now my life is smiles and laughter. They told me it would be fast, overnight transformation, back to size 10 at last. Itching to appear in front of the mirror. It will finally tell me what I want to hear. 'Mirror Mirror, Does my Bum look BIG in this?' 'Tiny, stay here a while longer, minescule, look how pretty you are, infinitesimal, the world around you is big, microscopic, meet with me, I'll testify to your beauty. I'll be slimming fast, into my ideal past. Shedding pounds, before your eyes, losing excess, gaining ground. No time to wait, or a second to delay, instant remedies will save the day.  You on the diet bandwagon? Did a dietician in his guru form promise you the earth? Did the nutritionist sell you a piece of earthly wisdom? Sell you the dream ticket, only to be seated behind a pillar. Do we not adhere to wisdom, because in our folly we reckon that wisdom is held by experts. The sole property of people in the know. "We did not follow cleverly invented stories." If they did not follow, I shall not follow either, whether celebrities do or don't. Goodbye to 'Hello', thumbs down to 'OK', farewell to the Glitz, nothing but the superficiality of the rich. Fantastic fad diets to seduce the weak, proposed for financial gain, can you smell? This plot reeks. Your experts are "Experts in Greed", fulfilling their need by supplying you a supplement feed.                           Metabo Ultra Max  HOT PRODUCT!              a natural dietary supplement to help your body speed up  your           metabolism and burn fat safely - lose upto 10 pounds in a week...                             1 month supply Only £19.50   "What is the Hollywood Diet? The Hollywood 48 Hour Miracle Diet® is allegedly a special "Miracle Juice" (can you really say that and keep a straight face) that has been scientifically formulated (oh boy, should sarcasm mode be turned off or on), and designed so that in just 48 hours you will cleanse your body (of what) and lose up to 10 pounds (of muscle, I guarantee it)! This mad as a hatter plan is said to have been created to give your internal body a vacation, wash away unhealthy toxins and fat, and give your digestive system a much needed break."  What would Fatboy Slim see into the situation? He would lament at the schizophrenic nature of our society, the double standards, and willful hoodwinking of one's self. Dieting we should hope, would lead to some improvements, maybe some weight loss. More and more people are sucked in by the popularity of dieting, while all the time the rates of obesity are soaring. An interesting correlation. Is it about health, or purely image? Because some image freaks out there on 'healthy' diets rationalise their way into the battle cruiser, to partake in a night of intoxicating over consumption. Who are you kidding? Slightly ironic you may find, that on an amble down the Asda aisle, you may find a whole range of 'Weight Watchers' cakes. A 12-pack of mini muffins, with a negligible amount of calories in each cake. (Fat Free, so insignificant and small, low calories, in fact great for you). 'I'll take 6 multi-packs!' My face can have a feast, down the hatch in one, the jaw work and remote fiddling will burn away the flab. Negative calories, an excuse to eat, you will be controlled by the master who you decide to meet. Still dying to diet with Mrs. Melton Mowbray?  "For a man is a SLAVE to whatever has MASTERED him."   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Skepticism. That slightly uneasy feeling that makes you question. To ask the why, carrying a healthy line of inquiry into the axiomatic territory of accepted norms. Not so much, to unpack and unravel, but to understand who dictates the course we travel. Every year, without fail, certain dates set in stone, crop up on the calendar pages, inviting us into action, prompting us to conjure up a certain feeling. The effort of the earmarked day is to manipulate the condition of your heart into a position where it beats in rhythm with the consensus. That 'special day' requires of you very little, just to feel a 'special way'. I've never really been too hot on the idea of imposed days of pre-determined feeling. I ask myself. Is love dynamic, or purely mechanical? A love comprised of a few token gestures at strategic points in the year. An intermittent love that appears back from exile, only to make a fleeting cameo. Hello and Goodbye love. Staying over just for the night, fleeing in the morning, to be seen again at a pre-arranged moment. A moment of mechanical love that seems to appease, never quite accomplishing a fuller release.  Dead Saints, the servants of the Holy God. Can they, pray as you may, be the ones to impart a glowing sensation of warmness, formerly known as gay. That dead saint deity, bringing you bags of gayety! Saint. Valentine, I presume, a lovely kind of chap. Never to meet him, I do sometimes sincerely doubt. On the 'day of love' I traipse home in the rain, wondering whether St Valentine is away from his office. Did he ever receive my fax? I did so plead for a share of love to fulfill my need. He surely is a lovely kind of chap, I will undoubtedly receive my portion, that 'love feeling' to halt my heart from reeling. That saintly dude, a devoted chap, never did hear my plea. The elusive glow for that 'special day' again keeps well away. For a manufactured day, custom made to exhibit our unending capacity to produce feeling, we opt to live in make believe, feeling because we ought to feel, disregarding the sadness our eyes can see.  In Simpsons, we have a scenario, where due to the dearth of meaningful days of celebration, there is an acute need to create something new. A new day, worthy of celebrating with all your might. 'Love Day' something warm and fuzzy, something pink and cuddly, something happy and joyful, full of heart and good-will to mankind. A love that is nice, so cute, happy to hug you for hours on end. Universal 'love day' would probably be a huge commercial success, competing to knock off ST.Valentine from his pedestal of love. The feast at the love festival would be brought to an abrupt halt. A juddering halt, when the realisation dawns on us, that we have begun loving love. To love love is to miss the point, to ignore the people, and ultimately fail to ever meet love. In loving love you never begin loving people, but a fading glow that is passing away. God is love. Therefore his words are in love. Obedience to his words keeps you in his love. When in God, then in love. When in love, then bearing fruit. Not just on the day of harvest, but continually into eternity. Who is satisfied with love days, often empty, always temporary.  I failed to ring my Dad on Father's Day. No shame in that, it was not a blip. I got me thinking though. A blessed boy I am, to have a Father in my life. So many without, and without memory. Memories aplenty, stories of old, insights into love and life, who I am and where I'm from. His eyes would crease up at the corners, in readiness to shed a tear, moved by something unknown, yet beginning to move you also. I'd keep checking his face to gain clues on his emotions, inside I would react in tandem, wanting to share his sensitive heart. Now here, away from home, the simple strumming of the guitar takes me back. It's a clear signal. Father is home. You are secure. Be still and know that your Father is in the house. If our new spirit cries out Abba Father, then let this heavenly call, be also to our earthly Father's. In the present climate, social policy and the welfare state make the Father redundant. Independent women, single parents and the paternal state are trying to replace the irreplaceable.  Happy Love Day
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My days of football fanaticism are over. I have mellowed out. My character has a rounder look to it, the rounded look of a man who walks around the circumference of the stadium with deep-rooted circumspection. 'It doesn't matter' or does it?  EURO 2004 is finally upon us, after much hype, and no end of talking, the ball is now rolling, rolling towards a swift conclusion, after which the ST.George's flags will be buried away, with it the nationalistic pride of a once great empire that now only unites in the name of football. It is astonishing to see how much passion is involved with the game, and how great an emphasis placed on fleeting sporting success. I can see the dynamics behind falling in love with the 'King game', declaring your devotion to the cause of the country by adorning everything in red and white. People for once can rightfully feel proud, share a common vision, know that there is a definite objective, and begin forming bonds of solidarity that espouse togetherness. That togetherness is nonetheless nothing short of a mirage. A togetherness of pipe-dreams dreamed up by utopians on opium. In a society that is fragmented and broken, where people run after their own desires, the figment of unity is perceptible when a setback arrives and defeat is experienced. Idolisation turns to blame and slander. Hope and Optimism gives way to deflated depression and emptiness. The hero's only remain so, if they are heroic in victory.  The deep cry of the fervent football fan is to belong, to be a part of something, to play a role in a success story, sharing in the glory of victory. You often hear a football fan say: 'We beat the Irish Today', and that 'we' most certainly includes 'you', 'you' are in the 'we' that beat the Irish, and so you have access to the taste of victory. You are in a position where you are able to credit yourself with honour for an achievement accomplished by others. In a state of passivity, sat on the couch, with beer in hand, your 'extended family', the 'water-carriers' and work-horses are the propellers who possess the capacity to take your ego to dizzy new heights. Postmodern football fanaticism serves only one purpose. An opportunity to exhibit your winning credentials, partaking in success regardless of your inertia, an inertia that renders your support meaningless. Winning has to come instantly, defeat is not tolerated. The football fan grumbles and moans in defeat, no longer identifying with their team. When victory comes, they are happy once more to bite into their prawn sandwich and bask in the glory of victory, recognizing that a part of the success should be attributed to them. The football fan sees himself as the yeast that makes the dough rise.  It has passed into footballing folklore that the invisible 12th man has an uncanny ability to influence games. The illegal 12th man is made up of turnstile fodder who come to be entertained, masses of people who only 'sing when their winning'. Commentators often remark on the added bonus of the 12th man factor, eulogising about the 'Hell's Kitchen' atmosphere in Turkey. The 12th man theory may be compelling to some, but it has its shortcomings. Due to security reasons the fans of the away team in a keenly contested local derby have not been permitted access into the stadium. The atmosphere is one of hostility, the away team are reduced in numbers when Russian import Kickalumpakov is dismissed for an innocuous looking incident involving Gucci handbags at no more than 4 paces. The home fans are going beserk, their rhythmic chanting and thumping drumming is incessant. In fear, the referee buckles beneath the pressure created by the 12th man, deciding the become the 13th man. With no vocal support, apart from the booing ringing in the ears, the away team with 10 men, escape from the fire-bowl of hatred with a victory. May we lay to rest the myth of the 12th man.  England versus France. When the titanic battle of nations unfolded before us, it wasn't merely a question of footballing supremacy. In international football when rivals lock horns the cold war climate returns, people begin reminiscing about former glories, reflecting on their political ideals, wishing to stand in the gap for the nation state to uphold their sovereignty. Football is politics. Football provides the perfect arena for the warriors of the land to assemble, uniting to defend the common ideals of the land, fighting to preserve their own order, establishing earthly Kingdoms that will vanish. The English plead for God to save their Queen, wanting to retain their monarchy, being set apart as a nation with a heritage. The Brits also want to rule the waves, to have the power of former days, building an empire founded on a lust to master and control. The stench of pride lingers in the air when supposedly 'great nations' engage in combat.  Liberty, Equality, Fraternity! The French Revolution was a rebellion. Liberalism brought freedom to be enslaved to your own selfish desires. An unconstrained freedom that deceitfully calls itself freedom, never telling you whether a boundary line exists, pretending that 'wrong' can be 'right' if only the 'wrong' feels 'right'. The French fought for principles that already existed, being practiced in the Kingdom of God. In our pride, we begin looking for answers through our own intellect, because we wish to be the problem-solvers, the great-minds who remedy the ills of the world. An over arching desire for equality, its endless pursuit, blinkers you from the effects of the means used to achieve the end result. Equality is the dream, or sameness you may say, of freedom, who can say. So, a violent extermination of those who resist equality, will herald a new era of equality? When you kill somebody, the exact message given out is this; 'you are not equal', your subhumanity and difference warrants death. The French wanted a brotherhood who would create their own heaven on earth. A heaven void of God, ruled by essentially 'good' people who knew how to achieve equality.  The French Revolution did not deliver. Its promises failed. Its protagonists are dead. Its philosophies empty. Its legacy crumbling. Why? There is no life in the message, no future, no hope. The French Revolution did not realise, that what it aimed to achieve, had already been achieved. It tried to repeat the impossible and failed. The Cross of Calvary speaks of a monumental achievement, an act of obedience, which brought a mission to its conclusion. 'It is finished', and all was accomplished, there was no need for the futile attempts of the French Revolution to usher in a kingdom founded on rationality, the deadly enemy of faith. When faith is replaced with rationality, hope disappears, the vanishing hope leaving a vacuum to be inhabited by a voice of reason that proclaims man-made prophesies about a glorious future of progression.  It is a truly wonderful desire to belong, to be set free, to know true equality, to boast about the achievements of another. But have we access to the promises through the French Revolution or the revolution of the heart. The revolution of the heart turning your focus to Jesus Christ by Whom all has been accomplished. "It is for freedom that Christ has set us free" Dynamite! "Don't show favouritism. Suppose a man comes into your meeting wearing a gold ring and fine clothes, and a poor man in shabby clothes also comes in. If you show special attention to the man wearing fine clothes, have you not discriminated among yourselves and become judges with evil thoughts." Equality par excellence! As for the brotherhood, it is from everlasting to everlasting, a bond of true unity, united in Christ, to share in his riches, and finally know that you belong.  From football to here. A meandering road. Well, when ZZ next strikes a double against your beloved country in the dying minutes of the most important game in history. Remember. Perspective. Leave the sofa behind, smile to yourself, open a tin of pineapple chunks, and eat. Saying to yourself; 'It's a funny old game!'    "What was ideology? It was and remains a system of ideas that are usually goal- directed. Thus, it is a theoretical explanation of the world's situation and a prescription for improvement or radical change of that situation. In this sense, ideology is rooted in historical consciousness, in an awareness of mankind's progress through time and how that progress might be redirected toward an alternate objective. Most ideologies are, therefore, fundamentally political, bright descriptions of the means and methods by which the instruments of revolution, party, or government ought be used for the purpose of social change.  Ideology is, in a way, the secular equivalent of theology. It directs the believer's attention to a perfected future when present woes will have dissipated and social harmony will reign. The future, therefore, holds the promise for the ideologue that heaven holds for the devout, religious-minded individual.  The introduction of ideology into the modern world was one major effect of the new secular spirit of the eighteenth century. Once society was deemed to be man- made--and here the influence of the Enlightenment is noticeable--then it could be changed. Ideology was the prescription for that change. And the force of ideology was felt throughout the modern era.  In sum, the French Revolution did many things, unleashed new forces, destroyed old ideas, offered new promises. Not the Revolution itself, of course, but the people who made it.  It was during the Reign of Terror, 1793-1794, that revolutionary tribunals meted out hasty justice. Opponents of the regime, revolutionaries themselves, fell beneath the blade of the guillotine. This was the awful period in which "the Revolution devoured its own." Some eleven thousand individuals died as enemies of the state, and their deaths added up to a new, horrendous activity of modern Western civilization: institutionalized violence, the harsh elimination of political opposition by the state. Later, Stalinist Russia and Nazi Germany would cause the figures of the French Revolution to seem small. Unfortunately, the mass age would also mean mass annihilation."    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have you not heard? Do you not know? The trolley-pushing position at your local Supermarket is one of prestige, a celebrated mantle only entrusted to those with finely tuned personalities, capable of seeing beyond the monotony, being able to rise above mediocrity. I have now joined this elite band of people. Infiltrated their ranks, carrying out the most sophisticated piece of ethnographic research on the psyche of the lowly trolley-boy. I'm only serving my apprenticeship, gingerly stepping onto the first rung of the career ladder, knowing that many intensive months of rigorous tuition is to follow. There are mentors, role-models, masters, and surrogate Father's aplenty. All eager to impart some knowledge, knowledge of worth, of worth in my steep ascent into the higher reaches of portering fame. You may have to ask your misconceptions to leave politely, after I reveal to you how the work of a trolley-boy is not for the Simpleton. Years of bad-mouthing, negative stereotyping, and wild generalizations, have left this earnest servant of the community, buried underneath the rubble of shame to suffer in anonymity. Let's reveal the true beauty, and silent wisdom of the trolley-boy trade.  Glenn is no mug. At 37, he is pushing trolleys for a living at Asda, he does it part-time, earning enough to maintain his rotting holiday home that he bought for £7000 some 7 years ago. His passion is script-writing, he is a real film buff, knowing absolutely everything about films, apart from those awkward first questions that you fail at because of stage-fright and performance pressure. "Go on, ask me anything about films, I now the lot." "Who won the male Oscar in 1979?" "Ahh, well, let me think..." Sadly, Glenn faltered a little, unable to answer the question, his face-saving mechanism kicked in and he reeled off numerous amazing impersonations. De Niro, Eastwood, The slithering tongue Hopkins from Silence of the Lambs. I knew the lines, but all I could hear was Glenn. For Glenn, Asda is the soap, the ongoing drama in his life. He loves to talk, he'll gossip all day. About short Scott who superglued the green cupboard shut, yet protesting his innocence while holding the tube of superglue in his hand standing right beside that very same green cupboard. About the workman who was sick in the bin. About affairs and real life, interests peculiar, fishing tales, and cinematic fables. Glenn is not mad about trolleys, he has things in perspective.  Gerald the greeter, a retired engineer, is nifty with his hands. He blessed me with my most important tool as trolley-boy, the key. He fiddled away with old discount cards, the aforementioned superglue, and a sharp pair of scissors, and in no time I was the proud owner of my very own trolley release key. He proceeded to take me through a crash course in releasing techniques, or should I say technique. "You put the key in the hole, like so, and there we have it. Now you try!" In, Out. "Could you just run that through with me one more time?" After watching the training video in class for the fourth time, Gerald finally let me loose on the trolleys. I tell you how it works. You know the light switch...  Brian 'keep on the move or management will spot you', shows me the places where to pick litter from, by knowing which way the wind blows, he finds me some great spots. The most frequently picked up piece of litter is the fag butt, this saddens me. Wealth gone wrong. Brian tells me the legal requirements for trolley-pushing. Only allowed to push up to eight at a time. I obey. He abhors talking, only respecting the real workers. He keeps on warning me about the management Sharks who monitor your movements. "They're watching! "Up on the gangway, in the office, cigarette room, and on camera, keep moving boy!" I assure him that I have the capacity to work, but he shrughs at my suggestions of improving team morale by getting to know each other. "I never talk about my family." Brian came out of retirement to be active. He hates standing still, his knees ache, so he keeps on the move, for the sake of exercise and the fear of exposure. I want to share the gospel, so I have to talk, It's my duty, a duty of love, I speak words that are not mine, the most life transforming words in the world, they cut into you like a sword, sometimes the sword hits granite and bounces back, other times it reaches flesh, and the love of Jesus moves in.  Glenn, Gerald, Brian and I agree on some things. It is detestable to see anybody try to nick a trolley, however fun they are down the high street, however many barbecue grills you can get out of one, and however aesthetically pleasing they are to the eye. The caster-lock, super-clamp, electronic gizmo wizardry, halts any scoundrel as they reach the magnetic boundary lines that activate the yellow lock that encircles the wheels. The brakes are on, and thou shall turns into thou shall not. We rejoice! I ask of you. See in the next trolley boy you meet: A humble servant.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Student accommodation is notorious for poor interior design, on arrival to our current house we wandered whether there had been any design to begin with. When you cast your eyes upon shabby workmanship and botch-jobs 'par-excellence' the creative juices within you begin flowing. Several mis-placed, badly managed oddities strike you as being somewhat alien in your surroundings. The eye-sore aliens created such anguish, we had to proceed in extraditing them to pastures new. The large bush down the bottom of our alley. The local dump. And into the fire, banished from existence, neutralized from being. What went? The green fairy-lights pinned to a central beam in the living room, celebrating the arrival of Christmas, yet still in place come June. Destination; unknown. 2 brown armchairs that were dismantled with great care on our patio in the back garden. Excellent firewood. Having heaved around 2 tons of pure junk from behind our rotting shed, I was kindly informed by the Landlords, not to go near the white sheets, not of innocent lasagne, but deadly Asbestos. Our removal mission had come to a premature end.  Apart from all the throwing away and burning, there has been several other battles to be engaged in. If you have ever attempted to remove three layers of wallpaper, from a room the size France, with old knives and wooden spatulas, then my friend, you earn the utmost respect of your fellow worker for clean walls. The principle at work in applying several layers of wallpaper,one on top of the next, is the principle of haste. Everybody knows that removing wall paper is most pain-stakingly slow work on the planet. So, in an effort to save time, you paste new onto old and do a runner. It grieves me.  I can vouch for the fact that removing wall-paper will induce a cathartic sensation if approached in the right frame of mind. Purpose driven endevour, that takes a task to its completion will reveal the glorious transformation that has occurred. Showing what is, for what it is, without hiding defects under a facade of luxury. When the wall-paper peels of in enormous sections, coming clean off the wall, leaving but an echo of the ripping sound hanging in the air, you begin to fathom the simplicity of pleasure. A pleasure that does not let you down, sting like a viper, leave you empty, and linger as a temporary happiness. When I subdue myself, stop the chase, and end the pursuit for gratification. Something wonderful happens. I find joy. In being, using my hands, and labouring for a cause.  What I see, if I see correctly, is days where people expect much pleasure, loving pleasure for the feeling it creates, chasing it to avoid stripping wall-paper. Stripping wall-paper is boring, rarely does it excite or raise the adrenaline levels, slowing you down in your search for the instantaneous amusement. Postmodern culture has an engine room that generates powerful messages as to how in effect enjoyment is played out. The over-riding value is fun, inviting us on the roller-coaster of playfulness, trivialising anything serious as nonsense. Anything you do can be laughed off, the gravity of your actions minimized, in the name of 'Having a laugh' or participating in a bit of 'Piss taking'. Everybody has to play the game, the rules are known, and nobody is allowed to be offended or get hurt. The instrument for the postmodern message of deception, takes pride of place in most living rooms, spewing out endless images of counterfeit happiness, and shallow materialism propagating the urgency to accumulate.  Alcohol is fun. The telly told me so. WKD or wicked is skillfully advertised, pitched on the market to satisfy your average fun-fiend. Getting your friends trousers wet around the crotch area, in the toilet of a club, while he is having a date is amusing. It sells wicked. Better still, the real practical joker, prankster of the highest order, should be caught cleaning in the buff, when his friend brings his lady around for the first time. Priceless. Then there is the Bacardi cat. Who hits the boulevard and is an instant success with the most gorgeous women in town. The Bacardi you see, makes you irresistible to the opposite sex. Bacardi increases sexual prowess, therefore, the more I drink, the more cat like I become, all the while the women find me harder to resist. Fun is it not? Headaches, hangovers, hangings, fights, date-raping, liver disease, obesity, sexually transmitted diseases, abortion, drink-driving, red-noses. Not so fun any more. But hey, who would like to curtail your freedom. Turin Brakes: 'Have another drink my friend, smoke another cigarette'.  In the age of playfulness, when public discourse turns into a joke, where everything becomes blurred and loses meaning, we can be liberated by driving a Peugeot 306 chabriolet. Apparently it releases the hero inside yourself. Whereas, women are set free by 'Body Form For You', by simply positioning a slim-line panty-liner in place, period troubles are over. They leap on bear horse-back and ride into the distance in a cloud of dust, returning for a Judo bout followed by skipping along in a field of yellow tulips. Products have become our salvation. Materialism our freedom. To make a statement, be sure to wear a communist red USSR T-shirt, without knowing Stalin or the essence of communism. Postmodernity allows offence while advocating an individual freedom to chase the tail of pleasure. Never to catch it. Always eluding. We keep on chasing.  Chasing pleasure is futile! Neurologically it overloads the brain's pleasure centres and depletes your feel-good neurotransmitters, serotonin and dopamine. Psychologically it creates unrealistic expectations and boredom. Physiologically, over-indulgence in anything creates tolerance, addiction, and health problems.  There is still a few tough spots upstairs. I wander whether I should use the chisel? If I leave it rough, I won't have to sand, to have it smooth, It will take another 2 hours. Pure Hessian or Golden Blossom? Why is wall-paper so difficult to remove? Maybe I'll get Britney and Christina round, fill the Jacuzi with Krystal and throw a wall-paper stripping party? The Bacardi cat could do portering. Hanging up coats, washing dishes, parking cars... Can't let him on the dance-floor!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      3 Bawden Close, hidden away on the outskirts of Canterbury, next to vast expanses of grazing fields, inhabited by peculiar cows. Idyllic. They are the oddest of cows.   Students over the years have built up a reputation for being relentless party animals, engaging in bizarre nocturnal rituals to the detriment of community spirit. Mrs.Fields at number 4 has suffered during the past decade, she exhibits all the abnormal symptoms of a woman driven to the brink by countless irresponsible students frolicking in her neighborhood. The curtains twitch. I now understand why she wears her wrist supports. The decibel meter tells a sad tale, a tale of noise pollution. Mrs.Fields holds the patent for the world's first mouth catalyst, not unlike a doggy muzzle, to reduce pollution and return peace. Mrs.Fields is a campaign activist, a fervent lobby-group protestor, she demands action, and her voice is heard. Her hard-nosed, steely-eyed silence loving friends have established a revolutionary group to bring about change. The noise politics of 'noise ban' action group is to introduce a noise tax, charged to you by fax, since most telephones make a right old racket. 'Noise ban' action group have adopted sign language as their official form of communication, re-soled their shoes with rubber, banned angry outbursts, confiscated musical instruments, taking a dim view of mothers in labour, and frowning upon child-like exuberance. But a cow toleration policy has slipped into their manifesto unnoticed.  The students in 3 Bawden Close are an unusual bunch. We are mild mannered and quiet. We fall in line with noise party politics, keeping the regulations, thus avoiding unnecessary taxation. But of late we have begun a silent uprising, a protest in the heart. We have whispered about the cows at lunch. How they keep us awake with their incessant MOOING. Our heads hit the pillow before twelve, our eyelids shut at 3. Jim has resorted to sleeping pills, Becca opting for the double whammy of ear-plugs capped off with ear-muffs, Phil prays, and I suffer. A chorus of MOOING cows and the humidity of summer keep me awake in my green-house, tossing and turning, sweating and fidgeting the conscious nightmare of animals gone wrong drags through the night. I plot my revenge as I walk to uni the next morning, weary and bleary eyed, I catch glimpses of the multitude through the hedgerow. They cover the entire hill, some sauntering around in the sun, others chewing grass on the embankment. They seem happy, even though they have 5 bellies, weird digestion systems, awful problems with regurgitating, and mean methane. They are oblivious to my troubles. I was once informed by 'Patsy the Panther', an ardent green, who carried the spirituality of the animal kingdom, that all animals, even the ordinary cow, shared in our understanding of the world, and empathise with us in our sufferings. The hollowness of her demented green philosophies had struck me some 2 weeks earlier after spending 3 hours pleading and begging the cows to be quiet. The voice of reason, coupled with a bribe, a bag of freshly mown grass, brought with it a crescendo of MOOING and a highly unsatisfactory conclusion. Sleepless in Bawden.  So it's mainly cows, not a nagging conscience that keeps me awake. Our estate is mainly plastic, brick-work finished off with yards upon yards of glossy plastic. Our estate is called Hales Place. Many a taxi driver has refused to drive there after slurred pronounciations of the destination by prospective customers. The roads are full of pot holes, and the street lighting is always KAPUT. There are notices on every building; 'NO BALL GAMES', the kids play football, and run on top of garages. They peer through our patio window while we are having dinner, they scarper before we have the chance to invite them for afters. Mrs.Fields is fiction, and number 4 is occupied by a lovely lady. She commends us for our hard work in the garden and awaits the day we topple over the huge fir-tree that leaves her garden in the shade. Jean is at number 2. She is tanned throughout the year, a brilliant orange tan, covering her form head to toe. She loves a good gnome surrounded by pansies of all colours. She sings along to Whitney Houston love songs, and we all stop to listen. I don't think she can sing, but I like to hear her sign, I enjoy her singing. It is heartfelt, full of meaning, exploding with life.  Canterbury is amazingly peaceful, the cows eventually fall asleep, Jean finishes her singing, the TV lies dead in the cupboard, traffic comes to a standstill, and you are left with time. Time to be still, time to be quiet. Those moments when you ask tough questions, wait for answers, and meditate on the goodness of God.      
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You’re with me on this hilltop We look at the spires toward heaven You’re with me beside the fire We burn the earth beneath our feet  You’re with me in the shed We fear not dark, the wasp’s sting You’re with me in my room We laugh at the coldness in Britain  You’re with me in my sleep We dream of all the wandering sheep You’re with me when I stand We rise together, to a free land  You’re with me on this hilltop I see the far I see the near You’re with me on this hilltop 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rather. In all honesty; completely. I raised my fingers in the aftermath, and only two remained upright. A score of two from a perfect ten may entice you to sit down, watch and find out; what warranted even those two fingers to stay up. It may misleadingly convey that there is some merits to the movie. The ‘five shining stars’ scoring system, may be more effective in communication the abject failure of the entire movie. There would be four dull stars, and the fifth only partially illuminated, just enough to make you laugh at it for trying to be a star.  Bill Murray starred, very faintly, a bushel obstructing any light that would normally radiate from his stage presence. The bushel in this instance being a weak script and amateurish directing by Sophie Coppola. Her father’s advice about skilful movie making was obviously left spinning at the airport carrousel in Tokyo, leaving her with a lost cast, hopelessly attempting to salvage something of worth from a project doomed for failure.  Was it really that bad? The movie begins with an elongated still shot of a woman wearing underpants, lying in bed, motionless. The next couple of scenes also feature the underpants, or a woman cavorting in these underpants. The subliminal message of these early scenes becomes apparent when the finishing credits begin to roll, and you realise that punch line would never be delivered.  Bill Murray, a struggling Hollywood movie star, goes to Japan for an easy payday. While out there, he works on a few commercials, sipping on Ice-T, while a crazy Japanese cameraman snaps away, all the while, making sure that Bill’s facial expressions speak of the luxury of the ‘whiskey’ he’s enjoying. He also appears on a talk-show with Japan’s equivalent of Graham Norton –suited in garish pink. Murray comes to a point of career break-down ushered in by his mid-life crisis involving nights out dressed in orange shirts.  Bill can’t sleep at night; he roams the hotel at 3a.m in the morning, meets a red-head in the bar, or a woman by the pool. He rings his wife back in America, assuring her everything is fine, proceeding to have two casual relationships with women of the night. That is the whole plot in its entirety. No message of hope. The movie insinuates that during mid-life crisis when your career is experiencing a dip, you can travel abroad, and engage in some harmless fun. The movie positively encourages it, while trying to disguise it with airy-fairy philosophies, exotic romance, and the artiness of a smoky jazz-bar.  Verdict: Underpants.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was walking back from the shop yesterday, in the surprising evening heat. The short-cut route takes you into a park, a brown path snakes diagonally across the expanse of grass standing out from the green, there is a play-pen where kids are swinging. In the middle, there stands a solitary goal, posts and bar.  A tanned English boy, bare chested and thin, approaches me with a ball at his feet to ask whether I'd like to join in. I hesitate a while, thinking I'm too busy. I'm about to carry on through, only to be apprehended by the whisper of a gloat. 'We're winning 8-2.' I have to step in and join the losers.  My team mates are on holiday from Spain, a boy of about 4, a boy of about 6, not a word of English between them. Their dad is the big guy, reading a newspaper, lounging on the mattress next to the picnic hamper. Mum is with the others, amusing them with the swings.  I try to orchestrate proceedings to haul us back into the game. I feed them the ball in good positions, wishing for them to score, and when they do, they make sure dad has taken note. Their red ball says Espana on it, it's a little flat, probably a precaution for their delicate feet.  After conceding another goal, we re-group at the solitary goal to talk tactics. I say 'benga', and the boys smile, I say 'ole', and the boys smile. We kick-off, generally aiming for the direction in between the bike and the jumper. We notch one, it goes in off the handle-bar.  Before the inevitable come back is accomplished, the other goal vanishes. The tanned boy hops on one post, and his accomplice wearing the other gets a ride on his saddle. The game finishes before it has even started. We all feel glad though, knowing that we were onto something good.  I pick up my shopping and start for home again. I congratulate the boys on their performance. One of the boys runs up to me with a can of diet-coke, offering it as a thank you. I look at my watch, realize it's not 11.30 and wave the Spanish family goodbye.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Said a prayer for you tonight, A prayer never said before Asked for joy for you today, Deep that has no feeling after  Cried a tear for you tonight, A tear never seen before Pleaded for peace to flow, A heart that you didn’t know  Sang at your wedding today, Words, you couldn’t understand Beseeched, bring it in the wind, It would reach even your kind  Told a tale to you tonight, Fantastic; with an uplifting twist Again; who’s the battling prince, He’s been a hero ever since  Gave life for you that day, A life never lived before Summer sun, rainbow ends A promise to heal and mend 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      She must have dined with angels  I sat in the car park of the drive-through  Her silver fork dangling back and forth  Remains of the ketchup marking my sleeve  Her hunger never shouted, living in obedience  Fast food told me; ‘fasting is the onset of death’.   She must have walked on water  I cried at nursery, could not tie my laces  Watched her glide across the room with poise  My dance instructor used me for a doormat  Her elegance was mindful, never forgetting her  Sat out the waltz, hampered by the hernia in the ball-room   She must be the sister of music  I nearly drowned in the shower singing  Melodies of her laughter ringing true  Tied tongue, a sly cat trips out with a devilish purr  Her harmonies quell violence, claiming you captive  Joined the sing-along, soul hollering a dyslexic song   She must be the definition of beauty  Consoled by comments of inner grandeur  Honest eyes penetrating, piercing the frail façade  Journeying in the arid places, observing sad faces  Her still splendour, faithfully sculpting its own art  Masterpiece I may be, broad strokes you see   She is the loveliest maiden by far  Born to be forlorn, etched by a scar  Fair mermaid on land, sustained with a kiss  Invitation to intimacy, closeness is bliss  Her warmth nurtures life, fostering peace  May the cold rebellion be shattered in defeat?   She is the loveliest maiden by far!               
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've noticed two distinct types of shopper, there are probably more, but these are the most striking, from either extreme. There is the 'receipt saving penny-pincher' who is sure to know the exact time when the reducing labels appear on the shop floor. And in the blue corner we have the 'willy-nilly plastic swipers' who love to spend just because they have credit.  My observations are completely in line with ethnographical research methods, and therefore scientifically valid. If you would like to dispute any of my findings, which are rooted in relation to a specific time-context in an actual geographic location, you'll have to immerse yourself into my body; viewing the world through my eyes, and feeling the heat I feel in my arteries.  'Mad-Derek-On-The-Mike', was formerly the town crier, but now he spends his evenings at Asda engaged in pro-active selling. The radio cuts out, you hear the crackle of the microphone as it's switched on, a momentary silence now pervading the steel hut that many call Adsa; and before you know it, the familiar cackle of 'Mad-Derek' fills the air-waves, calling out to all bargain-hunters to come and snap up the irresistible Sushi, that is now knocked down to a remarkable ten pence.  This is when the penny-pinchers rush forth to grab their prize, the commotion builds, and the melee around Derek is about to swallow him up. An over eager middle-aged Japanese man is dumped on his backside in his efforts to beat 'Big Steve' to the last bag of toffee donuts. The penny-pinchers always deal in hard cash, mostly coins, rarely notes. They carefully count the loose change into your hand, making sure their not paying over the odds for their basket full of ten pence bargains. Their shopping bill varies from 50 pence on a quiet night, to £1.50 at harvest time.  Their haggard wallet holds an inch thick pile of the most inconsequential receipts, which they retain in the fear that something they have purchased may be defective. After slipping through the checkouts, they pause at the front door of the store, to carefully study the receipt, just in case they have been ripped off.  The willy-nilly people resent this kind of behaviour. Their avarice is well known, and they love to hear their platinum account cards swish through the cash register, loving it even more if other people hear it also. It's sweet music to their ears. They have no regard for receipts, abandoning them at the till as they leave. You see; there is no room for receipts in the Loui Vutton, it's too glamorous for that, not an ordinary wallet like the others, carrying only plastic and pictures of loved ones. They indulge in the 'Special' range, making them that extra little bit more special, trembling at the thought of a day when an economy product lands in their servant pushed trolley.  The willy-nillys' and penny-pinchers park in the same car-park, drive home in similar cars to the same neighbourhood. Who spends according to need? Who spends according to resources? Who spends according to fancy? I just can't work it out; social science, not really a science.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Your surprised heroes are Gods, Legends that will never fall. The shirt now symbolic of triumph, Reinstating the once lost pomp.  Your crackling Alba stereo remains, The bad air from your rotting meat is still around.  Travelling 1st class, when others walk, You despise the rain and how they talk. Friends only to friends, the elect trend, Send from abroad the eclectic blend.  Your unpaid electric bill remains, The phone-cards litter your floor still.  Stick with like, eat what is familiar, It’s like an adventure in your wardrobe. Import your flavour, ignore our presence, Can we be open and mix, integrate even an ounce.  Your debts are real; do you ever plan to pay? Came back to reclaim; would defend it as a right?  We know what is ours, how to treat our own. Could it be; what is mine is not really so. What can I lose when I own nothing? Possessed by what you have, which is never enough?  You can rob me blind, strip me clean, walk away With my nest, leave me empty handed; but what Have I lost and what have you gained?  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Vasilii Andreich was stiff, like a frozen carcase of meat, and when he was pulled off Nikita his legs were stuck awkwardly apart just as he had placed them. His bulging hawk-like eyes were iced over and under the trimmed moustache his open mouth was packed with snow. Nikita, however, was still alive, though frost-bitten all over. When they woke him up Nikita was convinced that he was dead and that what was happening to him now was not in this world but in the next. When he heard the shouts of the peasants who were digging him out after heaving aside the stiffened body of Vasilii Andreich he was at first surprised that in the next world peasants shouted just as on earth, and that Vasilii Andreich's body was there too; but when he realized that he was still here in this world he was more sorry than pleased, especially when he became aware that the toes of both his feet were frost-bitten."  Tolstoy; Master and Man.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On June 23rd, Dad blogged about the misery of Saddam, after his imprisonment. Having to reside in a small cell, after living in majestic palaces. Not being able to choose his breakfast, and having no freedom to decide whether to eat pineapple or not. Poor Saddam. Here is an update; quirky to be fair, full of contradictions, but amazingly with a touch of grace.  "Saddam is being held in a white-walled air-conditioned cell, three metres wide and four metres long, Mr Amin said. He is kept apart from the other prisoners, who can mix freely with each other during the daily three-hour exercise periods."  "Since appearing in court, Saddam had taken to reading the Qur'an and writing poetry, Mr Amin said. "One of the poems is about George Bush, but I had no time to read it."  "Like the other high-value detainees, Saddam's day begins with a substantial breakfast, an MRE (meal ready to eat), which provides 1,300 calories. He also gets hot food twice a day, which could consist of rice or potato and broccoli, along with either fish, beef or chicken. For dessert, there might be oranges, apples, pears or plums,  but the former leader has developed a penchant for American snacks such as muffins and cookies ."   "He is looking after a few bushes and shrubs and has even placed a circle of white stones around a small palm tree," said Mr Amin, a Kurd from Kirkuk, who is the first member of Iraq's new interim government to visit Saddam. " His apparent care for his surroundings is ironic when you think he was responsible for one of the biggest ecocides when he drained the southern marshes ."   Even Saddam cares for morality, plant-life, and choice foods.       
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Not being too hot on the current popular music scene, I may be drifting a little on my following point, to a degree where erroneous stereotypical anomalies creep in, but bare with me if you may. Blazing squad trail-blazed their way into the charts as a fresh-faced pop phenomenon, with such heart rending songs as crossroads and other unremarkable attempts that appear frequently in compilation albums aimed at a sophisticated niche market: Mega bombastic summer hits from the craziest garage garages 2004 volume 5 Extreme Double-Bass, attracts a certain following, a following that drive funny looking cars, who gather in cow fields with glow sticks, and most habitually meet, throwing their hands in the air, making you think; these people just don’t care.  To me, Da Blazing Squad are note-worthy for their unwitting discovery of a secret message, they latched onto a gem of an idea, a piece of heavenly logic, streets ahead of the Streets, communicating to the heart of our youth culture. To flip reverse, is to turn upside down inside, abandoning old thinking patterns, reversing into a state of unlearning, while having the ‘odd’ new logic revealed to us, which will take us forward. I certainly need flip reversing, often, in most areas of my life, from one form of thinking to another. Even the people who profess ‘not to care’, aren’t convincing in not caring, when they shout to you about the irrelevance of the issue that is ‘nothing’, sticking steadfastly to their ‘not caring’ attitude. Have you noticed that people who ‘don’t care’, mention their non caring with flamboyant feeling and gusto, they begin gesticulating with their arms (the thing that Italian football players do when pleading with the referee), they launch into a tirade about the ‘nothing’ issue, spittle flies out, angry words spew out, their face begins contorting, and they conclude defiantly: ‘I just couldn’t care less.’ I wonder.  I believe that many want to flip reverse it, because they do care. Starting to consider whether they should whack on the hand-brake, performing an extravagant U-turn, leaving behind the race designed for rats, to exercise their freedom in initiating change; walking away from the consensus, ignoring the status quo. What occurs when we flip reverse it? Rationality becomes irrational, logic-illogical, reason-unreasonable, thinking-unthinkable, ordinary-extraordinary; the tread-mill process of our mind reduces in activity, so we may have the opportunity to question why it rotates in a certain direction and not the other. People will be able to tell when you have flip reversed it. They’ll remark on the change. How effective the unexplained unseen has been in transforming your life, dragging you away from mundane conformity.  “As in this case of the wind, the effects were seen, the sound was heard, important changes were produced by it, trees and clouds were moved, yet the wind is not seen, nor do we know whence it comes, nor by what laws it is governed; so it is with the operations of the Spirit.”  ‘Get a life’, ‘You haven’t got much of a life’, ‘You’re so boring’. Ever heard it before? Others extolling you to get a life, as if it was something that you could obtain, something you could shop for at the supermarket, something which you received after much trying. “He that finds his life will lose it; and he that loses his life for my sake will find it”. To find life: flip reverse it, lose it.  Success in life will be your making, at least so I’m told. You have to be the best, in the highest position, with authority over others, money for luxuries, straight A’s in your studies, a complete winner in every situation. ‘If you don’t become something, all you’ll do is serve others and miss out on your lot, the portion which you deserve because of your greatness.’ “But many who are first will be last, and many who are last will be first.” A paradoxical enigma about the ranking in the kingdom. Flip reverse it; become nothing, be happy to be considered last.  Ever seen a travelling throng of girls heading for a week in the Spanish sun? They most definitely haven’t forgotten the toothbrush, or anything else for that matter. Loaded up with enough outfits to set up a small fashion boutique, and never understanding the wisdom of ‘travelling light’. We hoard, own much, possess mountains, and gather like a magpie, being engulfed by materials, keeping for the sake of sentimentality, holding for the need of comfort. “Take nothing for the journey except a staff – no bread, no bag, no money.” Flip reverse it; travel light, offload the burden, become a stream-lined racing horse.  Unashamedly there are people who admit that money is the real door opener. That all they desire is riches. They are engrossed in the endless pursuit of wealth. People consider money as the chief good, something that brings an answer to each and every problem. The new album of 50 cent is titled ‘Get rich or die trying’; wealth has become the ultimate goal, our release from misery, our opportunity to live opulent lives. Poverty is a disgusting word, a condition to avoid like the plague. The welfare state offers a cure, money; politics has become economy management, and your salary indicates your status. Watching ‘Cribs’ on MTV shows us what the depraved human heart desires, excess at the detriment of others. “It is easier for a camel to go through the eye of a needle than for a rich man to enter the Kingdom of God”. Flip reverse it; give generously, seek the kingdom of God, and desire true riches stored in heaven.  Don’t fool yourself into thinking that you are intelligent. I am stupid if I think that I’m intelligent because I have a degree. My wisdom is foolishness, I know nothing, and cannot boast about my cleverness. All wisdom is found in Christ, therefore, I cannot find it in me, but I can find it in Christ who lives in me. Without Christ our intelligence amounts to nothing. And we honour ourselves with scrolls, wear funny hats at may-day, take up important seats of learning, give ourselves fancy titles, and pride ourselves at being educated, a cut above the rest, in a league of Doctors and Masters. “But God chose the foolish things of the world to shame the wise; God chose the weak things of the world to shame the strong.” Flip reverse it; boast about your weakness, acknowledge where wisdom and truth come from, and know that all our knees will bow.  Our standards can be flip reversed at the drop of a hat; and they will be. Death can be good. Poverty equally so, also weakness, add to that forgiveness and a portion of humble pie. Lord, da Blazing Squad hit the nail on the head, now flip reverse me.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Generous hand, From the deep pocket of a philanthropist. Good causes, Your righteous hobby. Animal rights, For the anti-natalist green. A helping hand, Shoving you closer to the brink.  Anti-war, Not having won the battle in our own heart. For tolerance, Hating our neighbours, divorcing our wives. All this charity, Never restoring parity. A guest of mine, That is; if your shoes shine.  Caring for others, Could you move on tommorrow, another needs your bed? Mercy-killing, The 'merciful' mercenaries are willing. Giving of you, Not even that, the Gucci wallet remains shut too. Equality, What a lonesome idea when detached from the truth.   Could you love another day, If all that you had was taken away?           
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The women had become too powerful, a wily posse of highly intelligent pioneers; challenging the status quo, throwing away the rule-book, becoming independent, with a hint  of zig-a-zig-zaa and bootylicious razz-matazz to shake off their tainted role. They had grown less feminine, somehow harder to reach, easier to miss; wonderfully paradoxical in their new found power.  Revolutionary pockets of resistance sprung up amongst the famous O.G.R.E movement, whose members feared an androgynous coup was about to take place. The Old Geezers Rejecting Erasure had to concoct a cunning plan to re-establish stability into society. After all, maybe their ploy smacked of simplicity rather than fox like cunning. It introduced fear back into the lives of ‘independent women’.  It was 3a.m in a quiet suburb of London. West Hampstead had been sleeping peacefully for some time, but unrest was brewing at an address in Mill road. The vilest of all living creatures had camped itself on the kitchen floor, waiting to fright, sending the unwary entrée into flight. Its telescopic legs, forming into glasses before those horrendous red eyes, that glistening under-belly enveloped in slime; it truly was a knee shaking sight, a dark form in the dark of night.  Ceci, troubled in her restless sleep, could no longer flit from dream there and in between. She slipped on her ironed power bath-robe that spoke of high class city living and stumbled downstairs in her slumber. Not for a second, to anticipate what was about to confront her in her own kitchen (not to be confused with chicken).  The power drained from her, she developed ‘wet legs’, her posture slumped, and the fear seized her eyes. Powerless in her own chicken, without corner to hide, or hutch to run into. With her bottom lip quivering, and the top one pretending to be stiff, she mustered a feeble scream that made the bug expand two-fold, appearing ever more menacing. Paralyzed with fear she continued to wheeze her lonely cry for help, and out of the shadows came Christina dressed in her cat-suit. Ready to scratch Ceci out of trouble, and into a realm of safety.  The united front of the sister act began to crumble when they realised the laser beams zooming in on them. The piercing rays mechanically zoning themselves in on the whimpering targets. An executive decision had to be reached quickly. ‘Run, Run, Run; Run for the end is nigh.’ The girls bolted back upstairs, swiftly as a nandrolone fuelled gazelle, leaving behind the monstrous beast, to cower behind a locked door for the rest of the night.  Ben, a third house-mate, having slept through the terrors of the night, awoke refreshed and full of bounce. After pulling the remains of a mango fruit from between his teeth; which he had devoured for breakfast, downing a Tequila suicide to remove the sleep from his eyes, and playing a few Chas&Dave numbers in D-minor on a mandolin given to him by a Mexican refugee, he strode into the kitchen, picked up his car keys and drove to work.  A short story based on real events.   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When you've been broken, broken to pieces And your heart begins to faint 'cause you don't understand  When there is nothing to rake from the ashes And you can't even walk onto the fields of praise  But I bow down and kiss the Son  When the Rock falls, falls upon you And you get ground to dust, no music for the pain You opened the windows, the windows of heaven And then you opened me and crushed me like a rose  But I bow down and kiss the Son  Let the praise of the Lord be in my mouth  Though you slay me, I will trust you Lord  Kevin Prosch 1996
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Two of Ilona's friends arrived back in England after spending a week in Finland. The Finnish people had been amazed why somebody would ever want to come and visit Finland. An inferiority complex in the mind, dictating that everything about our beautiful country is more beautiful somewhere else. 'You have mistakenly stepped onto the plane heading for Tampere, there is nothing for you in Finland, it's full of cold people and angry bears.' The flight announcer is doing his utmost to go in for the big sell.  Let the truth be known. Finland is a jewel, for whoever finds it, will be astounded by its beauty. There is no clever marketing gimmicks that can ever attract the commercial crowd of Lunn-Polly to sacrifice their stint in the Spanish sun for the simplicity of Finland. For the large majority, Sun, Sea, Sangria... is all they want. Fair enough. A holiday of excess tires the body, working in opposition to the promise of a holiday. The girls; Victoria and Claire, came back smiling, having been nourished by the 'soul-food' that Riina said was to be found in the Finnish forest. It was a delight to hear them say that they would return, despite the lack of night life, despite the several mosquito bites, and despite being nearly killed by carbon monoxide poisoning in the Sauna.  If you ever do go to Finland, be very wary of the offer of an authentic Sauna. You'll be stripped naked, beaten with tree branches, made to swim in the freezing lake, and on a good day inhale a little too much carbon monoxide, making your knees knock to the tune of Finlandia by Sibelius.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    When the joy of salvation enters your heart, you'll no longer feel lucky, but loved.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    God can turn high money-spinning fashion to his advantage. He can also turn a breadcrum and a fish into a meal for 5000.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    When you happen to present a view that falls in line with God's thinking, his morality, and his overall plan for the human race; you are branded narrow-minded, intolerant, an extremely fundamental christian who offends and cannot therefore even begin speaking of love. Do I serve a God of absolutes?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When I left Canterbury after work on saturday, I stuck on LW3rd on the portable and was humoured by a song about old men missing the jewels in their life. Behaving crappy after no nap, bolting out of bed like a farmer at the crack of dawn, losing your hair and teeth, not glancing at the clock as their routine is carved in rock. Don't fear that routine will be your destiny; you are unique. Get well soon.  Let this cheer your heart:  Suddenly it's Christmas, Right after Hallowe'en. Forget about Thanksgiving; It's just a buffet in between. There's lights and tinsel in the windows; They're stocking up the shelves; Santa's slaving at the North Pole In his sweatshop full of elves.  There's got to be a build-up To the day that Christ was born: The halls are decked with pumpkins And the ears of Indian corn. Dragging through the falling leaves In a one-horse open sleigh, Suddenly it's Christmas, Seven weeks before the day.  Suddenly it's Christmas, The longest holiday. When they say "Season's Greetings" They mean just what they say: It's a season, it's a marathon, Retail eternity. It's not over till it's over And you throw away the tree.  Outside it's positively balmy, In the air nary a nip; Suddenly it's Christmas, Unbuttoned and unzipped. Yes, they're working overtime, Santa's little runts; Christmas comes but once a year And goes on for two months.  Christmas carols in December And November, too; It's no wonder we're depressed When the whole thing is through. Finally it's January; Let's sing "Auld Lang Syne"; But here comes another heartache, Shaped like a Valentine.  Suddenly it's Christmas, The longest holiday. The season is upon us; A pox, it won't go away. It's a season, it's a marathon, Retail eternity. It's not over till it's over And you throw away the tree.  No, it's not over till it's over And you throw away the tree; It's still not over till it's over And you throw away the tree.  LW3rd 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    There is another life, one we never see.  The human eye loves the surface. In a sense, the surface is all it ever sees. The eye loves the countenances of fields and mountains, the coloured shell of stone, the fluent mirror of the ocean, the speckled canopy of night and the human face which veils a life. Perhaps the eye loves to linger on the mystery of the surface in order to imagine what lies beneath and beyond.   The great happenings of our lives arise from this unseen world. Unexpected, they surprise us with urgent visitation. Yet all the while, without our knowing, change is secretly at work beneath. True change is never abrupt or forced or temporary, it arises naturally from a long, secret gestation behind the outer visage. Even in the most fixated situations, in the most paralyzed mentalities and in the most repetitive postures, the pulse of change is quietly at work.   Winter is a grey season of cold and wet. Fields lie bleak and stuck, all colour bleached from them. Trees have become gaunt black skeletons. On its first sighting of Winter, how could the human eye ever imagine the change that is about to break forth? First through myriad arrivals, buds and shoots begin to thrust forth into the air and soon the unimaginable symphony of leaf, flower and colour delight us. The deepest secret of Winter is its verdant treasure of buried Spring. As light deepens and days lengthen, sacred Spring arises to transfigure dead landscapes with beauty.   There is an unseen life that dreams us; it knows our true direction and destiny. We can trust ourselves more than we realize and we need have no fear of change. We can risk everything for growth and we will never be disappointed. We have no need to remain prisoners of the surface. Within each clay heart is the Spring that never dies - the soul.  John O'Donohue&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Winds of change, blowing down from above.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    And he complains of continuous nose bleeds.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    A generational gap may exist, but beauty persists throughout Harperdom.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    They battled intensely for 12 rounds, but the judges could not decide which 'hair-do' was the eventual winner. The contestants shared the top prize; a humble slice of cardboard Ryvita.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Is it time yet, are we there soon, how much longer, we getting closer right, is it far, the relentlessness of this line of questioning makes minutes dissipate agonisingly slowly. It gets you clock watching, checking whether the inevitable deadline would approach any quicker if you somehow monitored the situation, keeping a close eye on the movements of time. The 'here and now' is displaced into a future 'there' that has to happen now. However you act, whatever you do in the 'now', it cannot remove the present 'now' in by-passing swiftly to an anticipated 'there'. For some to wait is a deadly bore, others may count it as a daily pain, few run off, snoring still. Heard of stories, of mountain gorillas, irksomely ill-behaved creatures who leap years, remove themselves from the body, and chase fire-breathing dragons.   Having been unable to discover a port through which we can usher in the moment of life completing fulfillment that we believe to exist in the 'there', we have thrust ourselves into a time-warp ignoring eternity. We are efficient at consuming time efficiently, inefficiently, and before doing this, we plan to do it. Thus, we devise plans for our time, time-management if you like; the alien nature of the new managerial position you hold, leading to half-baked ideas about what would be time well spent as a future investment, or what is utter uselessness, nothing but a lost cause. It is a precious commodity, our time; we have only a fixed number of days to roam the planet earth, before the gates of eternity fling open, admitting us in one by one.  So we find ourselves in this slightly uncomfortable position of: time-management-co-ordinator in charge of allotted gifts of life. We can procrastinate and delay; chase and speed-up, all the while, wishing to move things forward, or clambering back in reverse, digging our heels into the turf of today. Young people always want things now, for things to move forward, are we there yet? Are we there yet? Are we there yet... On the whole, the older generation, longingly reminisce about the former glories, looking back on the 'good old days', talking of a past that is irretrievably lost; gone, never to be regained, locked away in the dungeons of history makers.  When did time seize to be an issue with a 6-year-old boy. When the present presented him with the opportunity to forget that which was coming. A good distraction, that locked his thoughts on the enjoyment of the present. A bag of Minstrels, now that sometimes does the trick, although anything less than four at a time in a smallish mouth, does not impair his speech enough to stop him asking for the time. A jaw- dropping, mouth-filling, baby-suffocating, ball-bearing, drool-inducing, teeth-breaking, gum-splitting GobStopper is what you want for complete success. It's sweet enough, last for minutes even hours, fills the entire mouth, and reduces any audible time request into a hotch-potch goboldi-gook. You're onto a winner.  The youth expect to move quickly to times when they have more freedom; the old want to prolong their stay, in whichever faddish way. They control and manipulate time for their own desire. When does time no longer matter; when you realise in the 'here and now' that eternity shall be and death will come.  "Surely goodness and love will follow me all the days of my life and I will dwell in the house of the LORD  for ever ."     
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       "Researchers last night suggested children should watch no more than an hour's television a day after finding that those who watched the box for long periods showed signs of poor health by their mid-20s.   The study followed about 1,000 people from the age of three into adulthood, and found that those who had consistently spent more than two hours a day watching TV between the ages of five and 15 were at increased risk of being overweight, having high cholesterol, and poor cardiovascular fitness.   British children watch an average two and a half hours of television a day, with many watching more."  &nbsp;  Funny what entertainment can do to us. Showbusiness may be glitzy for the people appearing in front of the camera, but what about the children who have been indoctrinated into thinking that TV is fun. Who does the parenting these days? Where do we get our values from? Is it really that fun, knowing that you could not miss an episode of Friends, would love to marry a character from Eastenders, would shriek with delight if you laid hands on a TV star?  &nbsp;  We were OK without a TV once you know. Tell me; how does the TV enhance your life, what does it bring to the plate that you so cherish? Having been conditioned to operate as if something was fun for so long, we unswervingly hold onto this fun idea and carry on laughing regardless of how empty we feel. Do we hate silence; surrounding ourselves with noise. Do we hate reality; craving for a slice of fantasy. Do we hate problems; looking for unproblematic solutions. Do we like canned laughter; the hollowness of its ring.  &nbsp;  I remember one especially awful Christmas in my life. It was a Christmas without mum, as she had flown to Finland for some work. It was me, Ilona, and Daddy O deceiving ourselves that Christmas telly was Oh so fun. I remember breaking down in tears one night, because the marathon telly-thon was leaving me soulless, without nourishment, void of goodness, and completely dry.  &nbsp;  We exclaim to ourselves, why are we lonely, depressed, and suicidal, now more than ever before! The wells we drink from serve up poison, our cisterns are empty. If TV is fun then let us conclude on an interrobang!?     
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      повна форма ти заходити за обід&nbsp;&nbsp;вказує на: від I ?   Somewhere in the upper atmosphere things are happening that man cannot comprehend. A whole host of scientists, star-gazers, meteorologists&nbsp;and Ulrika Johnson look-a-likes have tried in vain to explain the weather. It' s a&nbsp;commonly peculiar phenomenon amongst Brits to begin discussing the high science of weather whenever confronted by the cul-de-sac of an awkward silence. To stumble into a conversation about whether comes as naturally to a Brit as sporting failure. The discussion also tending to be as bitter as sporting failure; bitterness about the rain, dissatisfaction about the heat, not to mention the horrors of the 'green-house-effect' that most men point to when their marriage fails&nbsp;or car breaks down.  &nbsp;  Remember Michael Fish before the Great Storm of '87 assuring the public that everything was fine. 'Remain calm people of England, this thing is passing over us, hold onto your hats and say your hail Mary's. For all you windsurfers and cloudwalkers out there, this could be your once-in -a-lifetime opportunity to catch a good wave, or the passing dark cloud, but be quick remember, it's only passing. Famously, as we all well know, Mr.Fish was made the national scapegoat for his erroneous reporting. Poor Mr.Fish had to bear the brunt of the publics wrath, carrying the sins of a nation single-handedly, that is, if we look into the term 'scapegoat' literally.  "Bible: A live goat over whose head Aaron confessed all the sins of the children of Israel on the Day of Atonement. The goat, symbolically bearing their sins, was then sent into the wilderness."   &nbsp;     "In a broadcast prior to the storm Michael Fish, responding to a viewers query, assured viewers that a hurricane which had just affected parts of the USA would not affect Britain (it didn't). He then added, but having said that, actually the weather will become rather windy. Which, of course, it did."      &nbsp;"15 million trees were felled and whole forests decimated. Buildings suffered severe damage and ships were driven on to shore. 16 people died as a direct result of the storm damage"      So when the weather turned a bit sour and events started to look pretty pear-shaped, people began projecting their ill-feeling towards none other than our humble weather-man Mr.Fish. As a consequence, he turned into the sacrificial goat who was destined to roam in the wilderness with the burden of wrecked homes and lost lives. England needed somebody to blame. By escaping from reason they were able to avoid a sense of sorrow, transmitting their anger to the wandering goat; Mr.Fish.  I don't know much about astrology, don't know much about economy, don't know much about the rainy season, but I do know; that blessed be the one who sent the weather. They say that something in the troposhere is affecting your day down here. Whether in the sun due to the Azores High, caught in the chill of the polar jet stream, walking on moon-lit streets, holding a torch in the dark, seeking answers from the sky; hold true, never being dragged down by SAD.               
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      An authentic spit-roast is a rarity these days. We have grown accustomed to buying the disposable, self-lighting miniature grill, that is hot in an instant, and colder even quicker. To go with our throw-away barbecue, we buy throw-away plastic sausages, politely labelled 'economy', but scientifically known as reconstituted animal meat from the floors of several second grade abattoirs. The promise goes: '45% of your sausage could be meat, the rest is definitely not.' And we love it, every last morsel, especially the carcinogenic ones; the ones that have slipped into kiss the embers when our tong grip gives way in the intensity of the flames, coated in a hard casing of utter blackness, decorated with a few flakes of ash, and so appealing to the eye.  So, over time, generations grow up thinking that this black stick, cleverly imitating a sausage, is the barbecue norm, and a delicacy to savour. We are doing our children a great disservice. They should be let in on a secret. Slow roasting pork tastes much nicer. You're very own spit-roast is easier to organise than you think. The raw materials for the feasting on a loin of pork festival are within touching distance. Do not throw away the sling-shots, that your children have been using to shoot you with, they will be the pillars that support your spit. The spit itself, a long skewer like object, could be anything, but I recommend a broom-stick stolen from your local witch; having of course beaten her with it first. Alternatively annoy your super clean granny by pilfering her Dustbuster Mark4 brush, utilising it to good effect as your spit.  We are nearly up and running. All you need now is a pig. Forget the Asterix like marauding in the forests. Forget the shop shelf. Forget becoming a farmer. All you need is love, you got it, love of kids. You'll ring up old friends, because you love baby-sitting their children. This couple you know, in addition to their charming children, also own a pet. A Pot Belly pig. They are delighted to have you over once more, as they can once again go to a quaint pub down the road. They leave you to your own devices, the children are well behaved and lovely, the night is progressing like a dream, but the pig upsets the apple-cart, setting in motion your cunning plan. The rampaging pig who has attacked you relentlessly, leaving ghastly bruises on your newly Immacced shins, has to pay. The pig violence justifies your actions, with clinical precision and the coldness of a calculated vetenary surgeon, you clobber the pig, bundling it into a sack. You smile to yourself, reflecting on the fate of the pig who upset the apple-cart, knocking dozens of perfectly good apples to the floor: the final destiny of the pig, being roasted with an apple in its mouth.  Sika ja se paistetaan... Sika ja me sita maistetaan...  Whatever you do kids, never play with fire or violent pigs, unless you want to have a spit-roast of course.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Is it upsetting when your middle finger is no longer in the middle? A little disturbing when the sun no longer shines into your room? A screw loose in your saddle, a temperature failure in your freezer.  Does it grate you, knowing that things will change? Does it tear inside, when I tell you how weak you are?  Are you happy to be missing the last train, night after night? Do you carry on cycling with a punctured inner tube? An unforeseen break-down, alarms ringing in the melt-down, an inconvenient blip.  Does it grate you, knowing that things will change? Does it throw you, when your agenda is subject to approval?  Does the light remain in your eyes when you hear NO too often? Would there be hope in your life if you could no longer party? Ripping through the darkness, disturbing your scene, arriving unannounced.  Does it grate you, knowing that things will change? Does it annoy you, not having it your own way?      
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       "We have painted the door-frames blue for the invisibly impaired, to help them around the store"  (A notice at Asda after weeks of renovation work)  I work for a great company, they really care about people, they are always 'happy to help'; busting Q's when your child grows restless, offering 'miles of smiles' with 'smiley squad vouchers' when the kipper looks a bit green, the 'brolly patrol' escorting you to your car in the downpour, but more to the point, they are performing essential care in the community, by looking after the 'invisibly impaired'.  You really know that love has reached town when local supermarkets start providing for the needs of the invisible masses. It feels amazing to be a part of such a ground-breaking project as this. The next recruitment fair to be organised at Asda is specifically designed to attract a more varied application response from the community. In an effort to be at the cutting edge of Equal Opportunities policies, Asda are pushing to employ more friendly ghosts, ephemeral fairies, indiscernible toads and fictitious fiddlers.  "Never stare at the invisible, give them the eye, or exchange evils"
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The political movers and shakers, liberal think-tanks, and ‘well intentioned’ reformists are slowly moving towards a complete prohibition of child chastisement. The Queen’s Counsel, a litany of supreme Over-Lords, and The Children Are Unbeatable Alliance have joined forces to remove what Lord Lester “described as ‘the serious social evil’ of child punishment.”  The ‘anti-smacking’ lobby group deem reasonable chastisement to be outrageous, an offence to the rights of children. Lord Laming said: “the defence of ‘reasonable chastisement’ – the loophole which effectively legalises smacking – had ‘no place in our society’. The moral entrepreneurs of this age have united in an effort to distort a message of discipline rooted in love, turning it into crusade against wicked parents who ‘violently abuse their children’. The worrying aspect about the impending legislation reform is the emergence of an outright ban. Assuming that a bill is passed in government enforcing an entire ban on chastisement, followed by the formal implementation of such a bill, a frightening scenario of prison could become a reality for many loving parents who take their parenting instruction from the Word of God. “Under the measure, parents could be prosecuted for actual bodily harm, which carries a jail sentence of up to five years if their smacks lead to grazes, scratches, minor swelling, cuts, abrasions or bruises. Reddening of the skin would be permitted only if it were transitory.”  Under a complete ban on chastisement, genuine love could land you a 5-year stretch inside, serving time for correcting your child’s behaviour for their future well-being.  From a worldly perspective, ‘discipline’ and ‘correction’ are nothing but dirty words from a by-gone era; designed to impinge our individual freedom, and make our lives a living misery. Chastisement is soon spoken of as smacking, and smacking has soon turned into fully-fledged violence. Everybody has their own individual right to behave as they wish according to their subjective morality, without fear of consequence, or risk of punishment. It is amazing to witness the moral outrage that is set ablaze when a child leaves the womb and is then mistreated. When the paradox of abortion and ‘smacking children’ stares you in the face with a dumbfounded expression. We should all be in agreement that violence towards children is absolutely abhorrent. The humanist revolution has nonetheless attempted to attach the label ‘violence’ to chastisement. Chastisement being pure and good, divine wisdom from God; violence being contrary to this, aiming to destroy and demean. How can our society and politicians pretend to care about the well-being of children when the unrighteous slaughter of thousands of children is happening up and down the country in ‘respectable’ abortion clinics? “The low priority the Government has given this issue (chastisement) reflects badly on its commitment to our children’s well-being, and its decision to allow Labour peers a conscience vote on a partial ban, but whip them to reject a total one, shows moral cowardice.” The only cowardice that exists in our current government, is the fear of speaking truth, the back-bone to stand up for what is right, and the political will to stick with good policies regardless of their popularity.  What was once unthinkable has now become thinkable, the unacceptable has become acceptable. We have tried to move ancient boundary lines, to suit our own selfish needs, re-working them to accommodate for the fads and trends of today. The Hippocratic Oath, which goes back more than 2,000 years, was tampered with in the seventies and eventually replaced by the Declaration of Geneva. Medical students upon their graduation used to take the Hippocratic Oath, swearing to: “maintain the utmost respect for human life from the time of conception.”  The sanctity of human life was once important. The preservation of human life was the very basic, founding principle of the medical profession. Conveniently, for some, it was decided in 1971 to drop the last five words of the oath, making abortion a justifiable practise. So doctors could now show utmost respect for human life, albeit not the unborn life. Chastisement is oppressive – Abortion is liberty. Our society is severely schizophrenic. “The schizophrenic nature our society became further evident as it became common practice for paediatricians to provide the maximum of resuscitative and supportive care in newborn intensive-care nurseries where premature infants were under their care – while obstetricians in the same medical centres were routinely destroying enormous numbers of unborn babies who were normal and frequently of larger size.”  If you do not introduce the abortion debate, alongside the furore surrounding chastisement, then you are missing the point. Both issues deal with the capacity of our society to care for those who are weak and have no political voice. Real child abuse, this ‘violent’ smacking of children is directly caused by our willingness to allow abortion. If you fail to see the correlation let Francis Schaeffer shed light on the situation. “Is it not logical, after all, that if one can legally kill a child a few months before birth, one should not feel too bad about roughing him up a little bit (without killing him) after he is born? Parents who are apprehended for child abuse must feel that the system is somewhat unfair in that they can be arrested for beating their child, whereas people who kill their infant before birth (at an “earlier age”) go scot-free – in fact, have society’s approval.”  There would be plenty of other disturbing instances to showcase the selective tendency of administering live-saving healthcare, juxtaposed with the complete disregard for human life, shown by proabortion doctors. Whether we genuinely care for people is highlighted in how we treat the weakest in society; the unborn, a gift from God. They have no say, yet we choose death, allaying our guilt by saying it was only: ‘Foetal tissue’. “Viable or not, the single-celled fertilized egg will develop into a human being unless some force destroys its life. We should add that biologists take the uniform position that life begins at conception; there is no logical reason why the proabortionist should try to arrive at a different definition when he is talking about people, the highest form of all biological creatures.” The chastisement debate is another effort to move away from Biblical principles, a ridiculously superficial argument dwarfed by the continuous murder of children in the name of women’s rights. Things have become so utterly twisted, it is frightening to imagine what other evil practises men can conjure up and call them ‘good’.  I was chastised as a child. I deserved it. It was just punishment for a naughty act. My parents had nothing hefty in the armoury, but it would hurt nonetheless. I would be spanked for my disobedience and ill-behaviour, twelve times with a wooden spoon spoke a language that I understood. Red skin, Oh yes! No bike rides for a few days, extra cushioning on seats, sleeping on your side, and some stiff walking. Ouch! Five times NO to a child of two can sound like YES in their ears. If a simple NO is not sufficient, other tactics are required. I love my parents. I love them because they smacked me in love, knowing what was best for me. “He who spares the rod hates his son, but he who loves him is careful to discipline him.” Chastisement is about love, careful and considerate love. “Whoever loves discipline loves knowledge, but he who hates correction is stupid.”  Chastisement is wisdom; lack of correction the fall-down of a fool. Discipline which momentarily stings produces good fruit in the end. I know that my God loves me deeply when he disciplines me. Disciplining me so stay on the path of life. Maybe the No Pain – No Gain situation is true after all. Whatever happened to the human race?  Resources: The Independent 6th of July 2004 The Guardian 6th of July 2004 Whatever Happened To The Human Race? Francis A. Schaeffer   “If a mother can kill her own children, then what can be next?”  Mother Teresa  “I've noticed that everybody who is for abortion has already been born.”  Ronald Reagan  “If people are not made in the image of God, the pessimistic, realistic humanist is right: the human race is indeed an abnormal wart on the smooth face of a silent and meaningless universe. In this setting, abortion, infanticide, and euthanasia (including the killing of mentally deranged criminals, the severely handicapped, or the elderly who are an economic burden) are completely logical. Any person can be obliterated for what society at one moment thinks of as its own social or economic good.” Francis Schaeffer  “We should avoid weasel words like ‘smacking’ and ‘tapping on the leg’. Hitting is hitting.” Salman Rushdie  “We should avoid weasel words like ‘foetal tissue’ and ‘genetic matter’. A baby is a baby.” Patrik Harper 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Spotty face, oily skin. 'White heads' sprout in and out of season, they do not respect faces or fear your image. They come as they please, camping where they like, often leaving behind a crater or mountain to hike. Mushrooms in the rain, grenades during war, mosquitoes in the quiet of night; so they come, ganged up in clusters or sitting pretty on the end of your nose. Sometimes with unnerving stealth, camouflaged as a boil, they creep upon you, tip-toeing their way past your elaborate defenses.  Clearasil; is an ambiguous product to say the least. It is a confused misnomer, told what it is, yet behaving schizophrenically. Clerasil, or Clearasil; even if I was clearly to know which, I'd still be unsure as to the why. Zit away, we swat away with this medicated pad. This most invigorating lotion works you deep, penetrating, exfoliating, removing all undesirable impurities. We follow the course of treatment with religious devotion, counting the clock to this hour, setting the alarm for that, applying the cream before sun-down, consuming the pill cleverly hidden in a banana. It comforts our minds to know that we are being pro-active in dealing with our 'issues'. 'I'm on the Clearasil, simply because, clear it will, leaving my face smooth as silk.' Cut out the choccies, drink plenty of water, lay outdoors being roasted by the sun, slap on that burning chemical in the yellow bottle just for fun.  Finally, spot free after solution number 10. Tis been a long haul, an arduous trek, to save face from ridicule from them. The furrows in my brow now bother me, I wonder whether I should worry less. The bags beneath my eyes, they belong to someone else, 'Excuse me Sir would you mind carrying these for me.' Wrinkles beginning to amass, I contort my face in front of the mirror, making it stretch with the strength of my palms, I look hideous; but at last I'm wrinkle free. This double-chin gets me down, it wobbles when I speak, can't I just have one, one just like Jimmy Hill's.  You can become the project if you so wish. A grand project who needs a new design. To be revamped and reconfigured, worked on as a hobby on the side. Pursuing promised perfection on your own, adding glamour to your mundane role. But there is always that spot that you cannot control, a blemish that no foundation will hide, the rough face on your wedding day and the man at the mortuary who spruces you up for the final viewing. The memory of your beauty is already passing away, the photos capturing that exquisite look are fading fast, to be buried in the depths along with the anchor and mast.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Heavy northern autumn sky Mist-hung forest - Dark spruce, Bright maple - And the great lake rolling For- Ever to the narrow grey beach  I look west along the red road Of the frail sun To where it hovers between Shelf of cloud and spiky trees, Receding Shore;   The world is full of seasons; of Anguish, of Laughter,  And it comes to mind to write You this:  Nothing is sure Nothing is pure And no matter who we think we Are Everybody gets a chance to be Nothing  Love's supposed to heal, but it Breaks my heart to feel The pain in your voice -  But you know, it's all going somewhere And I would crush my heart and Throw it in the street If I could pay for your choice   Isn't that what friends are for? Isn't that what friends are for?  We're the insect life of Paradise: Crawl across leaf or among Towering blades of grass -  Glimpse only sometimes the Amazing breadth of heaven    You're as loved as you were Before the strangeness swept Through our bodies, Our Houses, Our streets - When we could speak without Codes  And light swirled around, like Wind blown petals, Our feet   I've been scraping Little shavings off my Ration of light And I formed it into a Ball, and each time I Pack a bit more on To it I make a bowl of my hands and I Scoop it from its secret cache Under a loose board in the Floor And I blow across it and I send It to you Against those moments when The darkness blows under your Door   Isn't that what friends are for? Isn't that what friends are for? Isn't that what friends are for?   BRUCE COCKBURN     "A man has been charged with wildlife cruelty after police in Edinburgh discovered an alligator in the boot of a car, officers confirmed today.   'Serg, look here, there is a coat in this boot to match your shoes.'  The 3.5ft spectacled cayman was found yesterday afternoon after it had allegedly been offered for sale in a specialist publication.    'CROCS 4 SALE, Bargain Buys to suit all needs.'  The beast was said to be "probably quite traumatised" by the journey cooped up in the back of the vehicle and is being cared for at a sanctuary.   'Probably - Probably Not: Who knows? Quite - Tell me, on a scale from 1 to ten. Trauma specialist are working around the clock to restore stability into the shocked beast.  SSPCA spokeswoman Mairi Ball said: "These alligators will attack anyone, they have big teeth and can grow up to three metres long."    'They have BIG TEETH! Stop the Press. What else? They eat babies, if dangled above their mouths. NO. Possibly, quite probably, maybe, if only by chance, perhaps perhaps perhaps...   Tinkered with an article from the Guardian.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I couldn't quite make out through the vending machine glass, whether I was paying for Starburst, Opal Fruits or Chewits. The blighter was facing away, all I recognized was a fruity colour. Down it went. Down to the hatch it went. Your hand prods through and grapples away. I snatch at my treat and pull it away.  Cherry Chewits. You get a dozen or so little squares, all individually wrapped, all annoyingly well wrapped. I was dithering away, unsuccessfully unwrapping, trying my utmost to unravel the treat. Scrape I did, scratch I did. To no avail. With the clock ticking and brake time ending, desperation struck. The irremovable became the resident coating. Have you ever eaten cherry-paper goo?  Not only had I consumed a fraction of the coniferous Nordic forest, but to add a stinging insult to the grievous injury, I was left sticky fingered in Asda, without sink or soap.  No use pretending to be a kid. Boycott Chewits.     
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Cats and Dogs; I didn't see them. Supposedly, so said a tale of old, They'd pour down in the wind and cold.  The furry ones first, Followed by the barking mad. Wasting time chasing storms, Bide my time, wait here for them to fall.  A cascade of Cats A deluge of Dogs  Tormented by the torrents of pets Hey Rolf, Do you know any vets?    
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Received my essay back after the Easter holidays and was left a little perplexed by a few things. I wonder whether you would be able to enlighten me on the following points.  1.The marking grid on the cover sheet has been left untouched. I have no way of telling what factors attributed to my low mark.  2. You seem to insinuate that only academic knowledge is worthy knowledge, down-playing the significant contribution of journalism as a valid source for information. It is absurd to suggest that academics is the only avenue of securing sound knowledge. By questioning the credentials of Melanie Phillips, you effectively disregard her view-point and hold your own knowledge as superior. She has been the lead social policy writer for the Guardian and surely has an understanding of Social Policy? If my milkman has pearls of wisdom, do I reject his pearls for not being an academic?  "Awarded the Orwell Prize for journalism in 1996. Her ideas have influenced politicians in both government and opposition. Styled a conservative by her opponents, she prefers to think of herself as defending authentic liberal values against the attempt to destroy western culture from within. Melanie read English at St Anne's College, Oxford before training as a journalist on the Evening Echo, Hemel Hempstead. After a short period on New Society magazine, she joined the Guardian in 1977 and soon became its social services correspondent and social policy leader writer. After a stint as the paper's news editor, she started writing her column in 1987, taking it to the Observer and then the Sunday Times before starting to write for the Daily Mail in December 2001."   3.An opinion poll, as I understand it reflects public opinion, not newspaper opinion. You have instructed me not to quote public opinion.  4.'You don't engage with the complexity of feminist views'. With a restrictive word limit of 1800 words, you can only comment on certain facets of feminism.  5. It is always a delight to receive constructive instruction. My essay is described as a 'rant', 'hyperbolic', full of 'animosity' towards the 'wicked feminists'. There is not a shred of animosity within me against any feminist, but do I have a right to question their cause? The irony of the 'rant' comment does not escape me. I have browsed through a few feminist titles, and that very same word has sprung to mind on a number of occasions. Double-standards?  I do have to admit that I was rather disappointed with the mark, but not unsurprised considering how the world of social science works. I thought the whole idea of coming to university was to be able to debate, argue, offer opposing view-points, respect other perspectives, and be rewarded for hard work. Obviously I have missed the point somewhere, forgetting to win points according to the rules of the system.  Would it be possible for my essay to be reviewed in light of some of these misgivings. I fully respect your position of authority and am happy in any circumstance. Look forward to a reply.  Patrik "Learning without thought is labour lost; thought without learning is perilous" (Confucius) Harper 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If I were to say to you, or even sing: 'I don't want to know about evil, all I want to know about is love.' You may think to yourself; 'Golly gosh, what a fine man, pursuing goodness and desiring love.' After this, I'd ask you to review the defining moments of my life, and conclude whether I had lived the lyric in action or wished for it on a ganja cloud.  Esteemed musician, fine artist, lyricist beyond compare; woven together sounds to delight the soul, full of sensual smoothness to get you walking on 'solid air'. An alluring kind of quality permeates throughout his work. The lyrics dance lazily, oozing with an upward vibe, a zestful call-out to run from the evil in the world.  Hoodwinked. By the winker in da hood. Contrived. A carefully engineered mask. The man of peace came forth, declaring the virtue of war. Try as you may, to reach that elusive standard, the true ideal; your graciousness has not the elegance to conceal from where you came. A troubadour from the saloon, with a voice of silk, fist cold as stone; singing of love, while the truth unfolds. We men, know the art of mis-communication, of mixed messages, delivered from a podium on high.  It took him time, 40 years to be precise, to understand that thumping another isn't so nice. From a position of violence to begrudging passivity. Transformation, a turn in the heart. How did he finally come to know? To discover a capacity within him to refrain and say 'NO'. Would a clear recipe suffice? Just quickly. Wham bam, that's how it all began, to remain in the flow start with a bang. Bang; in goes the Yin&Yang into the Magimix, something from both polars, a little white, a little black. Bang; throw in some Zen Buddhism, to show you the way. Bang; a smidgen of da herb, to polish off the concoction.  Would it be safe to assume, for arguments sake, that the green-fingered herbalist would never strike. He is now a conscious objector practicing pacifism, a man of peace, with a heart full of anger. When the ganja no longer grows and the resistance turns brittle, where do you turn? Who would you throttle?  Contradictions leave you a little puzzled, scratching your head for answers. No, not a nit fest scratch, but a poised scratch of puzzlement. I sing about love and practise evil. Am I a liar, or am I weak?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     Technique technique technique. Remember the speech? Since that momentous day, I've been mentally rehearsing all my movements, refining them in my minds eye, so that when it comes to the crunch, my action will remain efficient; a deft swinging motion that divides between bark and wood. A crash course in wood chopping would rattle through the absolute necessities required of an axe-wielding woodman. Apart from the obvious advantage of owning a sharp axe; there is a host of individual points of technique that will compensate if you lack a precision axe head.     Be on the attack. Growl like a cornered wolf. Charge into the wood with a dynamic thrust, letting out a blood curdling war-cry. Intimidate the wood into submission, making it clear that you'll be at it with your bare teeth if the axe head flies into the lake. Keep hitting the same spot until you have a breakthrough. Don't smile. Keep it simple. Unleash the power.     It's all in the stance. Maintain a 'frog-like' bounce, keeping flexible at the joints. The body shape is similar to the 'sissi-paska' position adopted in the Finnish Army. So, you're only allowed to feel tense for the fear of bears and the rising tide. Loosen up Woodcutter's Son. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fishing expeditions end with tall tales about the 'one that got away', exaggerations, fleshed out facts and preposterous twists in the plot. I'll leave much elaboration aside, and let the pictures communicate the truth. Christopher and I did a few leisurely laps of the lake, once in the mid-day heat, when we had a little squirt tentatively nibble at our lure, the under length pike stole away when he discovered that novice fishermen from England give slack enough to make a get away. We returned empty handed.   urlLink     Christopher had a rough idea where the 'McDaddy' of the lake would be at, having caught an enormous beast of 79cm the previous day. Apparently they all hang out at the same bars. We rode gently along, basking in the sun, inching our way forward; bang, the line went tight, Christopher adopted the frog stance to give himself a fighting chance. We saw it jumping out of the lake, some 50 meters from the boat, livened up by the sting of the lure. Reeled it in, snatched it into the boat, and took the knife to its spine. I was pretty made up. It was my first time in a boat during Pike wrestling.        Self sufficient living as encouraged by the sixties generation of flower sniffers arrived in style this weekend. On Saturday we had new potatoes from Dad's plot, accompanied with pike from the lake caught by Christopher. It was my best meal of the year. Fully organic, eaten on nature's doorstep, with a knob of shop bought butter. What an experience.     Painted toe nails may look fancy when you have your new flip-flops, the summer winds dislodging sock fluff from in between the digits. Red Red Toes are lovely on the Spanish sands. But beware, the insatiable appetite of the predator pike, combined with its poor eye sight, makes your painted nails an attractive snack. Good looks under water is like dancing in front of the mirror. Wasted.     We used a red bin for the excess bits and off-cuts, we lost about a 3rd of the fish. The head in itself weighed about a kilo. Captain Birds Eye uses the contents of the off-cut bucket for his choicest crispy fish fingers. It is good to know what enters your mouth, and where it came from. I'll let you in on a little secret.      Fish Fingers. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Violent men with all their might A stirring of heart; passion's call Swords unsheathed; ready to fight Forcefully advancing, till they fall In arms, in arrows path for freedom Charming, that your prince is peace In wars, at death's gate for thy Kingdom Fitting, death will be your release Even to the point of death means dying Double edged sword of sharpest truth Pacifist cowardice or holy crying Slayer, robe dipped in blood; uncouth    Vengeance, you think it won't come   Paradise, for warriors who overcome       
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Life is a journey. Some like to go from A to B, straight from A to B. I'm working through the alphabet. Skipping from letter to letter, trying to spell a word that makes sense, to know a direction that is sure. What would I like to take on this journey of mine? Not a lot. A happy heart, good memories, and a knowledge of my destiny. It began in Kontula; the Chicago of Finland, with burning cars and drunken maniacs. The ghetto has received a face-lift, our former block of flats has experienced the process of re-generation, now offering luxury accommodation to the Kontula gangsters.   urlLink     From deepest darkest Kontula we fled like a bullet out of an AK-47 into the peace of Kauklahti. I'd skate on the river in the winter, float my way down stream on a polystyrene raft during summer. We'd snap up tired fish from the river banks, when they stopped to rest from their struggle up river. We lived next door to stable. I rode a horse, a clapped out mare. Touched the fence, that electric fence. Note of caution: never wee on an orange fence at the perimeter of a field.      A move on foot to next door. A massive garden, fit for a football pitch. Unfortunately, Dad made me join Kakka-Pyllyt to play football on the nasty gravel with other hyperactive little boys, leaving him a huge patch of ground for potato cultivation. I understand though, the potatoes were far more likely to feed the family than any future income from my footballing talents. Wise move Dad. Go for potatoes over football any day.     The river that runneth through Kauklahti. Our beloved Suikero made its maiden voyage along here some 10 years ago. We spent hours after school painting our canoe; it was red and yellow, named Suikero, after a cheesy crisp very similar to a Wotsit. To our horror, the river also ended up being Suikero's grave; I found it half sub-merged on my way back home from school. I was distraught.     Kuusakoski. Our favourite play-ground, full of interesting scrap, most of which was crap. We'd hide underneath a huge tarpaulin covering the remains of a jet engine. We'd sneak our way inside the warehouse, riffling through piles of junk, carrying off with us computer components that we believed to be coated in gold. Fools gold.     Burning down the house. Not my handy work. I was rather shocked to find this old house in this state. A school friend of mine used to live here, maybe he still does; the basement could be OK still. Who knows? I wouldn't be surprised if Tillin Toni had something to do with it. He once had a vendetta against the school, and like any angry young Finnish boy, he traipsed to the school with a match box in his hands. School is out for summer, school is out forever! God Bless you Toni, where-ever you may be, hope the fire has reached your heart by now.      I loved this house. We met the Simpsons here, the seventy proof rum, a box of nuuska, to name but a few of the interesting additions into the world of an innocent teenager. Skate-boards, which stayed under my bed. Rap music, that I did not understand. Baggy trousers, for both you and me. Home brewed apple wine in an alley way up the street. Never again. Apples=Cider, Grapes=Wine, apples do not equal wine. Our third and best Sauna, Terva drops, sizzling beer, clean behind the ears, exhausted from the heat. Lovely.     You know when you are in a Finnish Metro. Inconspicuous it is not. Impossible to fall asleep. Hard seats that numb your back-side, the orange so loud it screams in your ears. Fast though, without the hindrance of those white gloved chaps who shove you in, or the 'skin closeness' of the tube.     Bigger feet, more energy, different perspective, small world. It's all home. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Helsingin Sanomat ran a story in their Sunday paper about an active river in Vantaa. Days of relentless rain had swelled up the river, it's volume expanding over night, rising menacingly up the banks to wipe out much of the early summer 'greenness'. Vantaankoski pulled in the crowds. A natural phenomena to behold.  We sniggered in the morning, laughing at the trivial nature of the news; only to find ourselves at the cordoned off bridge, staring at the amazing rapidity of the river. It makes you think. What is a news worthy story? Are we genuinely interested in what happens in the Oval Office; what is said in the Commons; how many are killed in the latest bomb blast in Iraq; who is winning the presidential race for the White House?  When a river swells in the neighbourhood. It's news. It's exciting news. Do you need to know about death and power-politics. To be convinced how important powerful people are -those who make all the important decisions-, when all the while, a river thunders a profound wisdom. The staple media feed is death, suffering and fear. Happy families, successful marriages, and boisterous rivers rarely make the news. It's no coincidence that people are increasingly stressed, staring at hopeless situations; when the only wisdom they receive is filtered through the 'official channels', leaving a void without God, filling it with fear and uncertainty.  Concentrate on what is good. Contemplate goodness. For, if we believe what our eyes see, all will seem negative and life but a war.   We can stand on the bridge, looking at the water, nodding our head in approval, or stand in the crowd during the coronation, looking on the might of man, nodding our head in approval.  "So we fix our eyes not on what is seen, but on what is unseen. For what is seen is temporary, but what is unseen is eternal."
     

    
</post>


</Blog>