<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       HOW TO BE THE BOSS   When the Lord made man, all the parts of the body argued over who would be boss.   The brain explained, "Since I control everything and do all the thinking, I should be the boss."  The feet suggested, "Since I carry man wherever he wants to go and get him in position to do what the brain wants, then I should be the boss."  The hands argued, "Since I must do all the work and earn all the money to keep the rest of you going, I should be the boss."  And so it went with the eyes, the heart, the lungs, and all the other parts of the body, each giving the reason why they should be the boss.  Finally, the asshole spoke up and said it was going to be the boss.  All the other parts laughed and laughed at the idea of the asshole being the boss. The asshole got so mad that he closed up and refused to function.  After a few days, the brain grew feverish and could barely think, the feet felt like lead weights and were too weak to drag the body anywhere, the eyes got crossed and couldn't see, and the hands hung useless at the sides. They all conceded and made the asshole boss  And so it happened; all the other parts did all the work and the asshole just bossed and passed out a lot of crap.  THE MORAL: You don't have to be a brain to be a boss, just an asshole.  Alternate moral: No matter how well things are going, it can all be shut down by a single asshole.   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fair weather but Feverish me. Darn...the flu virus is attacking me. Hopefully Paracetamol will do the job.   What causes Fever?  Fever is a symptom, not disease. Fever is the body’s normal response to infections and plays a role in fighting them. Fever turns on the body’s immune system. The usual fever (37.8ºC to 40ºC) that all children gets are not harmful. Most are caused by viral illnesses. Some are caused by bacterial illnesses. Teething does not cause fever normally.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fair weather. Just found out the Germans nearly claim a famous victory in the Euro 2004 Group D crunch match against Holland...Hard luck. Hopefully the weather will remain like now for the rest of the day,becourse I have to go out for some meetings later in the day. Keeping my fingers cross. Hmmm....What's that fragrant aroma??haha....Mother is making "Popiah"(Chinese finger food delicacy) today yummy...... 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "You must learn day by day, year by year to broaden your horizon. The more things you love, the more you are interested in, the more you enjoy, the more you are indignant about, the more you have left when anything happens." -- Ethel Barrymore (1879-1959), 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Never continue in a job you don't enjoy. If you're happy in what you're doing, you'll like yourself, you'll have inner peace. And if you have that, along with physical health, you will have had more success than you could possibly have imagined." -- Rodan of Alexandria
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Accept the things to which fate binds you, and love the people with whom fate brings you together, but do so with all your heart." -- Marcus Aelius Aurelius (121-180 AD), Roman emperor, philosopher
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Three grand essentials to happiness in this life are something to do, something to love, and something to hope for." extracted from -- Joseph Addison (1672-1719), English essayist, poet, statesman 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       True facts about females????  FEMALE STAGES IN LIFE    AGE DRINK   17 - Wine Coolers 25 - White wine 35 - Red wine 48 - Dom Perignon 66 - Shot of Jack with an Ensure chaser  EXCUSES FOR REFUSING DATES  17 - Need to wash my hair 25 - Need to wash and condition my hair 35 - Need to colour my hair 48 - Need to have Francois colour my hair 66 - Need to have Francois colour my wig  FAVORITE SPORT  17 - shopping 25 - shopping 35 - shopping 48 - shopping 66 - shopping  DEFINITION OF A SUCCESSFUL DATE  17 - "Burger King" 25 - "Free meal" 35 - "A diamond" 48 - "A bigger diamond" 66 - "Home Alone"  FAVORITE FANTASY  17 - tall, dark and handsome 25 - tall, dark and handsome with money 35 - tall, dark and handsome with money and a brain 48 - a man with hair 66 - a man  HOUSE PET  17 - Muffy the cat 25 - Unemployed boyfriend and Muffy the Cat 35 - German Shepherd and Muffy the Cat 48 - Children from his first marriage and Muffy the Cat 66 - Retired husband dabbles in taxidermy, stuffs Muff the Cat  WHAT'S THE IDEAL AGE TO GET MARRIED?  17 - 17 25 - 25 35 - 35 48 - 48 66 - 66  IDEAL DATE  17 - He offers to pay 25 - He pays 35 - He cooks breakfast the next morning 48 - He cooks breakfast the next morning for the kids 66 - He can chew his breakfast 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Below quote is extracted from&nbsp;&nbsp;Marcus Aurelius Antoninus(121-180), Roman Emperor    Happines............    "The happiness and unhappiness of the rational, social animal depends not on what he feels but on what he does; just as his virtue and vice consist not in feeling but in doing."  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ex IO outing outside Indonchine  urlLink     urlLink     Was an ex Narco IO gathering and a farewell thingy for Gavin, who is leaving for australia for his studies. A VIP turn up for this gathering as well, Francis, still the same freaking self. Had a wonderful dinner at Seoul Gardern and ended the night at Bar Opiume Indonchine at ACM. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Daddy" and Belle fooling around around....tsk tsk........  urlLink     urlLink     Caught Belle and Daryl "fooling" around in China Bar. :P 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Taken at China Bar  urlLink     urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nic and Belle...........  urlLink     urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The 3 Bitches regulars at Chinabar  urlLink     urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Team Alpha  urlLink     urlLink     Well this is the Alpha team IOs batchboys consisting of Gavin, Zhongwei aka "jian ren", Terence and myself. Gavin right now is studying in Australia bah doing some bio-medical degrees, as for "JIAN REN"  oso back to his student status studying some degree in SIM and Terence is currently teaching IT in some sec school....   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Team Bravo  urlLink     urlLink    Team Bravo- Daryl aka daddy, Kelvin aka kinky yeo, Audi and Abdul Can see how "cock" is daryl hairstyle??hahaha.....he's the one who always handling those complicated cases....its not he's good its becourse he's always so "suay"!! As for Abdul ,"looks like osama?", he's the lucky one...handle so few cases....god damm it.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Narco Team  urlLink     urlLink     Taken before or after our lunch.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Narcotics Team  urlLink     urlLink    I  wish to state that the above pictures were taken during 2002..... :P   These are the bitches that are posted to the Narco team as IO....miss those times even there's lots of shit that we've went thru 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>