<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      All right, guys. After hours (and when I say hours I mean minutes) of scheming, Dakota and I came up with a plan!     :::a little man runs in with a trumpet and plays three notes: dun dun dun!:::  Y'all can POST YOUR STORIES HERE!!!                                       :::dun dun dun!:::     :::Takes out dagger and hurls it, instantly killing the little trumpeter:::  Anyway, you can POST YOUR STORIES HERE and I will critique them!   You may see a critique or two by someone named Agent9 or something similar. If so, don't be alarmed. It's just Dakota. I admit, he is a pretty scary guy, but I'm sure his critiques are something you can all handle. ANYWAY, that said, POST, GOSHDARNIT!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hello, everyone. I am Kathleen, known as the Hell Giver on the Suggestions for Book Topics message board at AOL. Sadly, AOL is gay and decided that I was not worthy of its approval. Thus, I now cannot log on or check my email account (which is probably chock-full of advertisements for "Hot Russian Brides")and, even sadder, I cannot visit my board. Grrruf!! That makes me  very  angry. Very angry indeed. And so I will be here...floating around on the Internet, waiting for someone to find me. Oh well. That's my swan song. :::takes a melancholy bow::: Thank you, thank you. I'll be here all week. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      K. If y'all want to see any of my other writings, go to  urlLink www.tensen.net/read .  All right! Now go!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If any of you remember Bruce Coville and his Unicorn Chronicles, here's the prologue of his third book in the series (which is unpublished and unfinished as of late). And now, Brucie, my good friend, I shall critique it. My comments, by the way are the  italicized  bits.  Prologue:  The Dimblethum stopped, looked around, sniffed the air.  For a moment the huge creature thought he had caught the scent of something unpleasant . . . something dangerous.   This is trite, or at least the way it's written is trite. And the use of "huge" is...eh...okay, but the Dimblethum can definitely de described in a better way. But I do like how you start with the Dimblethum here, as the Dimblethum is generally a supporting character in the previous books.     Holding himself as unmoving and silent as the silvery-blue trunks of the eldrim trees that surrounded him, he stood and listened intently.    Better!      Nothing. After a moment he moved on. He had parted from the gryphon, Medafil, two days earlier and now was making his way back to his own territory. Though he had never crossed this particular stretch of Luster before, the manbeast was guided by powerful instincts that pointed him back to his home ground. After his long journey to help his friend Cara rescue her grandmother, the Dimblethum was eager for the comfort and familiarity of his own cave.  An hour or so later he stopped again, this time to gather sunberries from a low-growing bush. Savoring the sticky- sweetness of the bright yellow fruit, he remembered how much Cara had liked these berries. How was she faring with the unicorns?    I like this. Nothing really outstanding, but the story is moving along nicely.    Without realizing it, he curled his upper lip in something between a sneer and a snarl. Save for Lightfoot, he had little use for unicorns. Nor they for him.   Eh...I don't care for "without realizing it". I'd probably say something like, "His lip curled in an unintentional grimace that was someething between a sneer and a snarl."   The Dimblethum put the thought aside. He would have no more cause to deal with unicorns for now. Trying to think of more pleasant things, he decided he would try to catch a fish for dinner that evening, maybe one of the silvery ones with blue stripes that he liked so much.    Again, I like the Dimblethum's thought patterns. Very bear/manlike indeed. Good job, Mr. Coville.    The sun, hot against his shaggy hide, was making the Dimblethum drowsy. He yawned, opening his great muzzle so widely that the ferocious teeth were on clear display, then shook his head and rubbed his paws over his odd face, which looked like nothing so much as that of a bear who had begun to turn into a man and stopped halfway in the process.    This second sentence is FAR too long. Chop it up a bit.    Insects droned in the trees above him, their slow hum contributing to his drowsiness.    Like it!     He considered taking a nap, but decided to press on. He was eager to get home; he had been away for far too long.  The Dimblethum was passing under a quilpum tree when a low voice whispered, "I know what you want."  The Dimblethum stopped, looked up. There was no one in sight. Even so, the voice spoke again. "I know what you want."   "Go away!" growled the Dimblethum. He shook his head and started forward.  "I can go a world away and I'll still be close by," whispered the voice. "And no matter where I go, I'll always know what you want. The question is, do you know what you would give to have it?"  "Go away!" roared the Dimblethum.  "As you wisssssh," sighed the voice.  The Dimblethum heard a rustling sound, then nothing. He waited in the silence for a long moment, then leaned against the tree, covered his face with his paws, and began to weep.    Lovely ending! Fabulous indeed. And thank you for using "weep" instead of "cry". Many children's authors seem to think that, though children are dear and wonderful, their\ emotions are not as developed nor as deep as those of an adult. This is quite to the contrary. And this exhibition of familiar emotion is exactly how to entice children to read on. Great job, Bruce! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Recently I got a German Shepherd puppy named Annabel (aka "Anna", "Anna Danna", "Annie", "Quick! Catch Her Before She Poops Again!" and etc.)  Since I got her four days ago she has done four things: sleep, eat, drink, and poop. She is definitely the most prolific pooper I've ever seen. I had to get up no less than seven times in one night to take her outside. And then it wasn't even solid stool. It's watery, runny, yucky stuff that stains carpet horribly.    ...I'm sure this is horribly disgusting, and I apologize...                          ...sorry...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Recently Dakota and I saw  Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban . While it was much, much better than the previous movies (thank you, new director and new Dubledore!) it was still far from perfect.   For one thing, Aunt Marge flew out the door and into England's skies. This never happened in the book.   Harry was simply standing on a street corner when the Knight Bus approached, rather than summoning it with a  Lumos  spell.  Who  was  that creepy guy who follwed Cornelius Fudge around? I don't remember him from the books...  Ron and Hermione flirted quite a bit more than is in the books. In fact, Ron isn't really interested in Hermione until the fourth book.   I don't recall Harry taking a long, drawn-out (though theatrically fantastic) flight on Buckbeak. Also, I remember there being several other hippogriffs rather than just Buckbeak.  In the book, it wasn't Harry who saw Peter Pettigrew on the Marauder's Map; it was Professor Lupin. But in the movie it was the other way around.  What was with that whole "Harry in the Sky With Dementors" thing? That never happened!  Where was Cho Chang?   Where was Cedric Diggory?  Why did the dementors suck a little bit of something out of Harry and Sirius when they were lying in the mud at the edge of the lake? They don't do that.   Why didn't anyone tell Harry what the Dementor's Kiss was before the end of the movie?  Why was it that when Sirius's soul was sucked out into the air (which never happened, by the way)he acted as though he were dead. I thought I remembered someone saying that "one can live without a soul" and "to live without a soul is far worse than death itself".    These were a few of the things I saw. There were more, but I'll spare you. In any case, this  Harry Potter  was far,  far  better than the previous two. But as LeVarr Burton of  Reading Rainbow  used to say, "you don't have to take my word for it".
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Pretty soon I'll be going to a leadership seminar sponsored by my electric co-op. I can get up to $7,500 in scholarship money, so this is a good thing. However, I will not be able to critique stuff. That'll be next week, by the way. But no one has been posting much anyway (except Brandon. Thanks, Brandon!).   Recently, I went to an ETWA meeting (East Texas Writers Association) at Casa Ole. There were a bunch of old people there. The youngest person besides myself was thirty-four! There was only one published author in the room: Tom McFarland, whom none of you have heard of, I'm sure.   At the end of a really long discussion about cruises, these people decided to read their manuscripts. A very fat man (with embarrassingly low pants) named Gordon read a story called "Charlie the Nose", which was a relatively good story about a man who mowed the grass on a golf course. Sadly, this was a rather uneventful story. He didn't ask for a critique. And good for him, because I probably would've burst his fat little bubble of security.   Then the thirty-four-year-old read a few poems. He was pretty good. Very good, in fact. He was my favorite.   I read my "Jonathan Rigby and the Man Behind the Screen" and the first two chapters of  Panola . Though I asked for critiques, no one had anything to say, other than Mr. Tom McFarland. He said, "you need more setting. Other than that, it's great!"  I considered this, and decided I couldn't use his critique. I want to introduce descriptions of the setting when the main character sees it for the first time (she is a child, after all). It would be more powerful that way.  Shortly after, he read a story he'd written. OH MY GOSH! I'd expected much better. It started off pretty well, but then fell into complete mediocrity. And as we all know, mediocrity = bad.     So if you meet a published author, don't assume that everything they write is good. I think that this guy just got lucky. Oh well. I hope we all have such luck in the future!   Cheerio! And good luck to Mara in England! 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      All right, you heard me! Teen and Adult Fiction here!    Gabby!  Your critique is a comment on this post!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok. I think I'm going to go by genre now. Everyone writing a Sci-Fi/fantasy story, post it here! In this post, I will critique it, and other people can read it by clicking on "comments". Well, here we go!    Brandon!  Your critique is a comment on this post!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp;Now let's get something straight: I am officially in love with the   Zelda   games. I've been on my GameCube all night and all day in a vain and ill-conceived attempt to finish all the miniquests in&nbsp;    M  a  j  o  r  a ' s   M  a  s  k   .   &nbsp;(I like these colors!)
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Well, I'm in Waco today to watch my little brother play baseball in the World Series. It's only 2 and a half hours away, but it took us a little over six hours to get there, because a) my mother gave us the wrong directions b) we went to College Station, and c) We ran into construction...a lot of construction.   So now I'm here in this hotel, eating fried fish and cheesecake and listening to Mr. Tom ask why I haven't done any drugs or drank any alchoholic beverages before and why I don't plan to...ever.  Here's a bit of the conversation.   Mr. Tom: Well, if you don't do drugs or alchohol, your shirts sure are fooling everyone else.  Me: Why do you say that?  Mr. Tom: Well, the last time I saw Kermit The Frog playing the guitar, I was drunk as hell at a Motley Cr&uuml;e concert.  On a lighter note, I read and critiqued Mara's "Reflections" recently. Very interesting. You should read it.  Dakota's sitting here, watching everything I type, so I'd better watch myself. I shant be too mean or...well...critical in this post. Darn it. Of course, Brandon is the only person who ever comes to this blog, anyway (Hi, Brandon!), so I suppose it doesn't matter that much anyway.   Did anyone take the AP tests this year? If so, did any of you make a 5? I made two 4s, and I want to know how I can improve. I suppose it's silly of me, as I should be glad I passed the things in the first place (3 was the passing mark). Oh well. I'm P.O. ed and I have no idea why. Maybe I'm lonely. I miss my friends. I mean, I love being around Dakota every day, but I've just gone a long time without really talking to my friends in person. This doesn't include my Internet friends, by the way. I can talk to you guys anytime I want.  Except Shane, who's off showing his Pony Of America, Oatie. (Go, Oatie!)   Why do I feel like this? Am I just bored or what? Do I need to rest? Is my tongue coated? Do I have a fever? What is going on? Do any of you get depressed every now and then? If so, what do you do?  Hmmmm...maybe I just need to curl up with a good book and a cup of Earl Grey in my very own corner of the Rusk County Mental Institution. A whole branch of my family tree is there anyway.    I guess I'm just suffering from Kindred-Spirit-Withdrawl. I haven't really spoken to some of my friends in a long time. Even my best (girl) friend, Lauren. She was hosting a party at her house the other day, and we had to leave early to get home on time. I did talk to her, but not a really good, in-depth conversation. I've always thought that I didn't really need people, other than Dakota, but I guess I do. Weird, for a somewhat antisocial person.   Oh well. I'm fine, I think. I'll just go to sleep. I'm probably just tired and grouchy from riding in the car all day. Nobody put me on the prayer list or anything (well, you can if you want). Well, I'm going to go sulk somewhere.   Send me a story or something, someone. Keep me sane in this baseball-studded world!                                                              :::ducks flying baseballs:::    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Well, I think it is. Ever since the eighth grade, a girl named Laura (whom I like to refer to as "Arula")  has been in loathe with me. And the weird thing is, I didn't do anything. You see, it all started off like this...  Long ago, we were in the same kindergarten class. And we'd have singing contests and that sort of thing. Well, when it came time for the "Talent Show", we both sang. I, however, got the most applause. She cried. And I suppose that's where this whole cycle started.  We didn't have the same classes for years until I was in seventh grade and took drama. I went to One-Act that year and got All-Star Cast. The very next year, she auditioned for the One-Act and made it. Now, I'm trying to write this in a neutral POV, but she was horrible. Again, I got All-Star Cast, and she got nothing. Now, this never really bothered me. I tried to be nice to her. I stood up for her when people called her a b!tch. Now, I'm not trying to be conceited, so if I'm coming off that way, slap me. I know I'm not the best actress in the world, but I also know I'm not the worst. And Arula's definitely more toward the worst. I knew she'd taken all this poorly, so I didn't (and haven't) brought it up in her presence. There's nothign more annoying than someone rattling on about how great she is. Believe me, I know.  But then I started to notice a pattern. Everything I did, she'd attempt to do. And she'd fail miserably. I mean, after I'd written  The Princess and the Dragonslayer,  our conversation went exactly like this:      Kathleen  : Hey, Laura. And how are you on this fine day?    Arula  : Oh, I'm fine. But I've been thinking lately.     Kathleen  : ...okay...(withholds urge to say "a dangerous pasttime" like Lafou in  Beauty and the Beast ). What about?    Arula  : I think I want to write a book. You know, about how Christian parents can raise good kids.     Kathleen  : And you would know about raising children how?    Arula  : It's obvious, really. I don't see why parents get all confused and then make...(with a glance at my combat boots) ...mistakes...with their kids.    Kathleen  : Okay. Go for it, I guess.    (KATHLEEN starts to walk away)    Arula  : It should be easy. I mean, if  you  can write a book anyone can.                                        (Now here's what should've happened)     Kathleen  : You talkin' to me? You talkin' to ME?! ARE YOU TALKIN' TO  ME ?!?!?!?!?! AAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!                                     (KATHLEEN bodyslams ARULA)   (What really happened)       Kathleen  : Um...okay. Right...uh...bye.       Later on that year, I found that she'd been talking to my best friend behind my back, and had told her that she was "worried about me, and thought Lauren (my best friend) ought to leave me alone," because I was being "slowly posessed by the Devil" because I read books with dragons in them. I talked to her, and she denied it wholeheartedly, so I let that one slide. Then, in my Freshman year of high school, she, Lauren and I had been put into a group to do a project over  Treasure Island  (horribel book!). It had been weeks and I was starting to wonder when we were going to work on our project, when Lauren said something like, "Now, make SURE you can come to work on it tonight. It's almost done."   "What?" I said. "How can it be almost done? We haven't even started working on it yet!"  Here she gave me a funny look and said, "Laura and I've been working on it every Tuesday and Thursday for two weeks now. She always told me you'd said you couldn't come."   Needless to say, I confronted Arula. In a nice sort of way, of course. I merely said, "All right, let's get this straight: I don't like you, and you don't like me. All I want to know is why." She responded by saying that it was my whole personality that she detested. And then I left her alone, thinking she'd get over it.    But she didn't. When I started dating Dakota, she started saying things about how lascivious  (i.e.- a dirty slut) I was for dating a boy four years older than me (and, girls, they're not ALL lying pigs!). And Dakota and I are anything but lascivious. We're nerds, for crying out loud! Christian nerds, at that.    Anwyay, and she still does very rude and immature thing to this day. For example, I was giving a report on AIDS, and she was sitting in the back of the room making faces as though someone had shoved a skunk up her nose. When she started distracting people, I said, "Laura, are you all right back there? Because if you're making faces that hideous, you must be in incredible pain. Why don't you go to the nurse and let me finish my report?" Everyone laughed, thinking it was a joke (which it sort of was, in a serious sort of way). I probably should've just ignored her, but AIDS awareness is something I'm very passionate about, and when someone's keeping me from telling people about it, I tend to get a little miffed.    Do any of you have an arch-nemesis? If so, how do you handle him/her?  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>