<Blog>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Finally, i have finish reading my pocket book, Artemis Fowl.. about the story, ok lang.. full of aventures and magic! Father & son relationship, di tuloy ako maka-relate.. The author was an irish man who was a teacher in elementary before. My favorite part there is when Artemis rescued his dad of course with the help of the fairy,Holly & his butler..!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have you heard the new song of Rivermaya?! Its called the "Balisong". Its kinda weird nga eh.. cause the song is not about the title but againts it.. hehe.. cute noh..?!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      guyz.. did you saw the match of Chris b. & Shawn?? Ang tagal!! They bought wanna win.. cause Chris wanna retain the hevy weight campion belt.. but Shawn want the title so badly, muntik na nga siya manalo eh.. all he had to the is cover chris for the count, kaya lang Triple H showed up & did something to shawn (dunno what move was that eh) if it wasn't for Triple H, maybe shawn is already our new WWE Heavy weight champion.. di ko nga lam kung sino kakampihan kon eh..oo nga pala, hehe.. something showed up from shawn michaels (kita nyo ba un?! hehe). Anyway, can anybody tell me when the judgement day is?! im so exited to see John Cena kick Rene Dupree's ass..!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my favoriTe barkada..! Too bad tapos na show nila.. :(  i've been watching their episodes since they were still teens..! cute ng kwento nila!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    sana i-replay..! hehe..
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      dream,believe,survive!!.. That's their motto..! hehe..! guess who's my crush on those six guys..! hmm.. &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      cLick barkada..! i always watch their show..!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      my favoriTe band..! i love this guyz! They have the best opm songs! duncan--> cutie..!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      oh yes! i feel the sting baby!  one of my favorite wrestler superstar!! isn't he cute..?!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    hope na lumipat ka sa smackdown..  para sama kayo ni john cena..!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      jonaThan feLix anThony cena.. my ultimate idoL..! he's the reason why i love watching wwe..! & of course HBK,rei mysterio & Y2J..&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink     JOHN CENA RULEZZ..! weLL, he's reaL name is.. jonaThan feLix anThony cena.. he sTands 6'1 and weighs 248 pounds (kinda heavy..ryT..?!) he's eyes are coLor bLue and hair is brown..! He jusT Turned 27 This LasT apriL 23.. He grew up in WesT Newbury, Massachusettes. John Cena was caLLed "The ProToType" (UPW,OVW years..) know why i Love This guy so much..? hehe.. He was good in kicking oTher peopLe's ass and do his cooL moves inside The ring.. whaT moves..? i'LL give yah some.. 5 knuckLe shuffLe, FU, kiLL swiTch & Throwback.. And now he is our WWE U.S. champ..! Torie wilson is so lucky to have john cena as her hero..!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      yuuhi--> japanese word for "red sunset" cool huh?!? haha.. new word! &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What can i say?! butterflies are so cute! &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    "Love is like a butterfly; if you hold it too close, you might kill it,  but if you won't hold it close enough, it can fly ayaw"
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      haha.. know i found a long lost friend! she's now in Singapore.. huhuhu, i already miss her! She's my former classmate at csa, we two are close! as in! we two eat together tuwing lunch, we share food (kasi we both love tempura!) & sabay kami lumabas ng school.. The sad part is, she need to go to Singapore due to her parent's business thingy..argh! But know.. mag-ka chat na kami sa ym.. And im so happy na! kasi nalaman kong uuwi sya here! now, all i have to do is wait for her to arrive!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i dont wanna be rude or anything but.. MARKET STINKS!!!--> wet market ah! i almost wanna throw up.. And it even got worst! A big man just stood up in front of us that's why we can't make it through the exit of the market..aarrggh.. i was holding my breath for 10 sec. already!! And from the market we just walk going to the Meralco building. Good thing they have an aircondition room. Then, after that trip..(at home) mama got angry at us.. we were like "huh??" kasi naman mali daw..blah! blah! blah!.. Bad Trip!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i Love my boy bud because..  »he LeTs me know on whaT guys Like & don'T Like bouT girLs »he never says no when i ask favor »he TreaTs me Like his younger sis..! »he makes me Laugh (aLL The Time..!) »he can proTecT me.. »he can be as sweeT as a..umm.. niLaLanggam na..Lansones..! :P  i Love my gaL paL because..  »she never faiLs To make me Laugh »she aLways make me happy! »i can TeLL her my probLems (speciaLLy when iT comes w/ famiLy) »she aLways give me advice (& iT aLways works..!) »she hands me a handkerchief whenever i cry »she aLways Laugh on my corny jokes!                                                      --> & ThaT gaL paL is aiko..! ;)                                                                                      *miss yah gaL..!* 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      --> kelan ba talaga pasukan..? First, june 7, then the next ting i know my classmates are sayin' na june 14 daw ang start ng classes.. Then, the radio said that the H.S. department's classes start on june 24..so, i guess i'll just call my friends & ask them..well, majority wins nalang..! hehe.. baka mamaya pupunta me ng school with my complete uniform, la pa pala..! But, know what?! im already exited na pumasok sa aming all new renovated school!! hehe..!  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      huhuhu.. i think you already know what my emotion is huh?! The reason behind that is.. Because, i wont go to school (Colegio San Agustin) cause ill be leaving this July and move to Canada. And i dont know what to do without my friends..huhuhu!! And you all know that im not quiet comfy at our house cause its BORING! And when i say boring it means nakakapatay na boring! It's like im a hell in a.. cell?? or house! Mas gusto ko pang sa mall nalang matulog eh! huhuhu.. :c
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday,we took a bus from my mom's office going to Metropolis & when i was about to go down the bus just move! i was still on the stairs going down & dunno what to do.. Then i jump. When i was already on the ground my body was shaking & guess what?! it happened to me 3 times that day!
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A while ago,we watch Harry Potter (Prisoner of Azkaban) at Festival mall.. Im with kuya Miggy, ate Kate & Milo. But we didnt had a chance to walk around..huhu.. cause Tita Jovy called up & told kuya Miggy & Milo to go home na! That's why after the movie we walked strait to the parking lot & ride in the car & drop kuya Miggy & Milo in their house.. Then, aTe Kate will have her sleep over at our house.. Well, at least im ganna have a reason not to get bored whole evening!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      3rd release of the movie of Harry Potter! it was cool & full of magical expirience!--> Better than before! My favorite part there is when Harry figured out that Serious Black wasn't the man who traidored his father, cause it was Peter (The mouse of Ron) So, he decided to free Serious from the jail.. And save him from the penalty that the councilor gave him! So, at the end Harry found the answers to his question!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      cute huh?!?&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    This is a butterfy fish.. La lang.. i just think that its kinda interesting!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Im going now at my school.. Wish i could see my friends! huhu.. i miss them so much.. Sana we could talk 'till 5:00! & sana i will see people na i really wanna see & talk to!!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      haha! its me.. im at the garden of our house! i think im 2 yrs. old that time!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
          U  CAUTION       IN THE INTEREST OF SAFETY IT IS ADVISABLE TO KEEP AIKHO AWAY FROM FIRE AND FLAMES.     Username:     From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      add nyo ko ah?!?  crazy_21_alison@yahoo.com --> friendster,myspace,hipster,friendzy & hi5  pillow_angel_06@hotmail.com --> friendster..  black_butterfly21@yahoo.com --> friendster din.. :::hehe.. dami noh?!?::: 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Your are the most beautiful thing I've ever seen You shine just like sunlight rays On a winter snow I just had to tell you so  Your eyes sparkle as the stars Like the moon they glow Your smile could light the world on fire Or did you know?  Your minds full of everything That I want to know I just had to let you know I just had to tell you so Your're my butterfly Fly high..
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     urlLink    we were in school.. sa harap ng classroom namin nung first year.. miss kho na school!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Can't wait na makabili!! huhu.. i wanna have one.. i mean.. three pala! Kasi bibilhan kho rin sila Donnalie & Jay-R eh.. Don't worry guyz.. i'll try to buy! pwomise!!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
          A     Awkward       I     Innocent       K     Kinky       H     Hot       O     Overwhelming       Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wow.. friday na! And one week na me here sa house, while my classmates at the school and having fun! huhu.. Later i'm ganna go to school, kasi favor sakin un ng bestfriend ko..makaka-hindi pa ba me?! Love ko un eh! Di ko kasi sya nakita nung i went to school last tuesday.. Anyway, have you watch the episode of raw?! It was awsome! I totally love the "Steel cage match" of Y2J & Christian.. Christian was a total jerk! As well as Tomco & Trish Stratus! But on the other side, Edge didnt won the Intercontinental Champion from Randy Orton.. Im ganna wait for smackdown!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Burn"-usher  [Intro] Girl, understand why See it's burning me to hold onto this I know this is something I gotta do But that don't mean I want to What I'm trying to say is that I-love-you I just I feel like this is coming to an end And its better for me to let it go now than hold on and hurt you I gotta let it burn  [Verse 1] It's gonna burn for me to say this But it's comin from my heart It's been a long time coming But we done been fell apart Really wanna work this out But I don't think ya gonna change ya I do but you don't Think it's best we go our separate ways Tell me why I should stay in this relationship When I'm hurting baby, I ain't happy baby Plus theres so many other things I gotta deal with I think that you should let it burn  [Chorus] When your feeling ain't the same and your body don't want to But you know gotta let it go cuz the party ain't jumpin' like it used to Even though this might bruise you Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn  Deep down you know it's best for yourself but you Hate the thought of her being with someone else But you know that it's over You know that it was through Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn  [Verse 2] Sendin' pages I ain't supposed to Got somebody here but I want you Cause the feelin ain't the same find myself Callin' her your name Ladies tell me do you understand? Now all my fellas do you feel my pain? It's the way I feel I know I made a mistake Now it's too late I know she ain't comin back What I gotta do now To get my shorty back Ooo ooo ooo ooooh Man I don't know what I'm gonna do Without my booo You've been gone for too long It's been fifty-eleven days, um-teen hours Imma be burnin' till you return (let it burn)  [Chorus] When your feeling ain't the same and your body don't want to But you know gotta let it go cuz the party ain't jumpin' like it used to Even though this might bruise you Let it burn (let it burn, let it burn, you gon'learn) Let it burn (gotta let it burn) Gotta let it burn  Deep down you know it's best for yourself but you Hate the thought of her being with someone else But you know that it's over you know that it was through Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn  [Bridge] I'm twisted cuz one side of me is tellin' me that I need to move on On the other side I wanna break down and cry (ooooh) I'm twisted cuz one side of me is tellin' me that I need to move on On the other side I wanna break down and cry (yeah)  [Breakdown] Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh oooh Ooh ooh oooh (can ya feel me burnin'?) Ooh ooh ooh oooh ooh oooh  So many days, so many hours I'm still burnin' till you return  [Chorus] When your feeling ain't the same and your body don't want to But you know gotta let it go cuz the party ain't jumpin' like it used to Even though this might bruise you Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn  Deep down you know it's best for yourself but you Hate the thought of her being with someone else But you know that it's over You know that it was through Let it burn Let it burn Gotta let it burn 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, maghapon na wala si mom..hmm.. haha! solo kho ang computer! joke.. All i know is she's waiting for Tita Ciony at the airport. & like yesterday i am BORED to death. That's why i cant tell anything bout something today!!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, this day is not like yesterday or like any other day that is "boring"!! Cause i just attended my voice lesson &.. i dont know how to say this but.. it was.. (i cant believe i am saying this..) cool..! Teacher Dianne changed a lot..cause before she was a little strict but now..hmm.. Anyway.. WWE judgement day was cool!! hehe.. John Cena,Undertaker.. RVD & Rey.. Torrie Wilson.. Specially Eddie Gurrero rocks!!!!!! Yeah.. But, another wait will happen.. "bad blood"!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, mom just arrive a little late than expected.. But she told me to attend a mass, so i dress up & so did mom. We tought that we're ganna be late but when we arrived at the church..the priest is not yet there. It took us about 20 mins. for waiting the priest then.. When the mass is over we cant go home..why?! Cause the rain was pretty strong & we have no umbrella & even though we have one we still cant go home..asking why again?! There's no freakin' jeep.. So, we decided to ride a trycicle instead.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I didnt had a chance to see Lp live.. arrgg.. bummer!!  The reason is.. The person who will ganna give us ticket was not around so.. umuwi akong luhaan!  All day, i thought i could attend the "my most awaited" concert.. Kainis talaga..
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      di pa kumpleto yan!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So here i am..(again!) Sitting in front of the monitor of my p.c & letting the time pass by me.. ano ba hinihintay ko?! The day of our flight in Canada? Or the day before it?! It's like im holding a rope that i can't let go, cause i know that the other end of  it are my friends,relative & "special" someone of mine that i'll surely ganna miss..*sigh* what a life..
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hmm.. i really don't know what to type.. So, i'll just tell yah all what just happened at 'raw'.. They we're in Canada! it was damn weird!! awww.. La Resistance just won the Tag team Champions from Edge & Chris Benoit..oh yeah! That two idiotic freaks just won.. & i just can't believe it! But in the other side.. Shelton Benjamin got the Intercontinental Champ from one of my crush, Randy.. i was suppose to be dissapointed cause Randy loose & i don't even like Shelton, but i was shocked & a bit..happy?! hehe.. Know what?! i like Matt Hardy & Lita together! (don't know why!) maybe they really do fit together! i just hope Kaene don't get in the way! I just simply don't like Tayson Tomco.. he sucks!! He just broke Y2J's ribs..huhu.. He's bad!! He will pay on bad blood!! And the past episode of 'raw' was so exciting! Specially the part when Y2J & Shelton teamed up againts Randy & Ric Flair.. i also loved when Shawn attacked Triple H.. They didn't stop! hehe.. They just did when Eric told them that they'll have a Hell in a cell match! wooaahh! Can't wait for bad blood! Ok, so.. i haven't control myself from lookig for the results of Badblood.. but damn! Triple H defeated Shawn! i am so distraught!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just attended a seminar about emigrants (check out the spelling!.. its because the man said, we spell it in 'e' when the person still don't arrive in their designated place & when they do.. we can already spell it w/ an 'i'! uyy.. nakinig!! hehehehe..) Anyway, it took the seminar for about 2 hours or less.. the office was so cold & very quiet.. Then, after the session me & my mom went in Glorietta and ate at Kenny Roger's.. Bad trip lang yung pag-uwi, cause the rain was so strong..
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Me &amp; my mom went to Tita Ciony's place. We had pancake for breakfast, Then we went downtown. We went to a mall, &amp; it was cool.. After that, we went billards &amp; swimming! Then dad picked us up &amp; on the way home we saw a huge ship, dad said it was a ship of the celebrities! awesome!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hehehe.. im not really good at that sport! i just scored 75! (hey! that's still a passing grade!) Mom didnt played with us cause.. she said her arm is aching.. next time!! ok, i enjoyed that! After that, we ordered at the mcdonalds cause were really hungry!  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>