<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im here.finally. im bored already how sad is that? but maybe cuz ive been sleeping all day and need some excitement. like wild sex. DAVEY I NEED YOU NOW!!!! well tomorrow i have no clue what we're doing. ill probably clean out the pool and such and get ahold of my cousin so i can hang out with her. i miss davey.i miss angela.and kt.and bryce. i want to call all of you right now. this leaving thing sucks.  ive been thinking alot about my future and college and stuff (it happens when ur bored as hell) but ive always wanted to go to florida. no matter what. but now, its easy to see how priorities can change. i never thought about staying for something. i would stay for davey. i hate this place but i love him so much i would do anything for him. i hope he knows this. i wish there was some way i could tell him this without sounding all emotional and mushy gushy. i have been thinking about this and him all day.  but anyways my eyes hurt and my neck aches. my heart aches.so i must go soon. but not now....im not through...hmmmm? oh yes kt and angela and bryce and everyone write a comment! i miss u guys so much!!!! what did u guys do today? kt dont forget to come to my house and be careful when u and bryce are there alone, because my uncle is going to go over to my house once or twice to fix our computer so dont freak out or anything just pretend like your doing what ur suppose to or watev. hehehehe write to me peopel!!!!
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i cant sleep. 6 hours and 55 minute left to sleep. there goes another minute. shit im gone dude ill blog it up when i get to chicago baby yeay!!!!!!!! haha jk...no, but seriously i will.
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just realized now how much i am in love with davey. its kind of scary actually. i hope he doesnt see this because he would tease me and call me emo (awh the things we do) but i am emotional in life tho. i am soooo emotional. im only going to be gone for a week and i started crying when he said he was gonna get off the phone. he thinks i lie too much to my mom too. that really upsets me. i HATE when people lie. but i lie to my mom so much. he doesnt know when im lying to him he says. i want him to know i love him and i would do anything for him. when u think about someone so much that they just are in your mind all the time, that u can picture their face at any time, or when u realize ur not thinking about them, it hurts your stomach? i think im a freak. but it feels so good. i am going to miss everyone so much. i want to come back already and i ahvent even gone. i suck. 
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so im sitting here.in my underwear. drinking a cold mountain dew and a pop tart i almost burnt. this is the earliest ive woken up all summer naturally. usually if i wake up this early i have to set my alarm clock and press the sleep button a dozen times. but no. i guess its because i have to get up at 6 tomorrow morning and get on a plane for chicago. then take a shuttle down to bloomington. yup. im not too excited. but watever. i like airports though. new people and sites i guess. theres such diversity in international airports. those ones are the best.  i wish i could sound smart. seriously i read other blogs and they sound so intelligent and shit. and it hurts. no not really i just typed that without realizing it. im fucking bored!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey hole of the ass yeah thats right biatch u hit me in the head with a pop can and slapped my leg! ow!(im screaming  ow  in the naughtiest kinkiest way possible, mind u)so um yeah i guess the plan is for u to take jason to bryces house at 4 or whenever. or actually call kt's cell phone at lunch and she'll hopefully know the dealio. good night sweetie and everyone.  p.s. write me a comment ho! the red mark on my head makes me think of u. mahahahha
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      poor angela is in weiser.sniffle. i miss u!!!! she left today and is coming back tomorrow..thank goodness..i cant spend another night alone! :D ha well today i went to daveys and hung out with him and jason. we walked to albertsons in 97 degree weather and we all had black clothes on and pants. we were like baking in the sun i was soooooo hot. ekk. the only cool thing about hot sunny weather is when theres a beach. and guess what? theres no fucking beach!!!!! anywhoooo we walked down there and got SLC punk ~best movie EVER! i would die for heroin bob. oh yeh and we got mountain dews they save my life i swear. so yep. we just basically chilled. and there was a thunderstorm about 8 or so, so i opened his window & davey kept telling me not to pull up the blinds because they wood break and i was like "nah dude im not stupid".. boom. they broke. and fell on his bunny's cage. oops. sorry nibbles. but i fixed it and we all watched the lightningthunder storm. mmmmmm yep.yep yep yep. if i was RusSian i would use the word yep so much cuz it means sex. yep yep yep. what a great language.
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was an ok day i guess. in the morning i went to the greenbelt and bicycled like 15 miles.hot hot hot.and then um i painted our bathrooms & the kitchen: took off the hinges and put the new ones on-really boring shit. then i went to toris house and me and kentucky dreaded his hair damn it looks so hott! yay tori! then we all went to smokeys and kt couldnt stop looking at the door everytime it opened for brycey. i swear ur obsessed but hey i cant really talk..im pussywipped.its rad. mahahaha but anywhop uhh o yeah then i got locked out of my house for an hour or so. that sucked. daveys at the amp(another mans poison) show. i wanted to go again, but i was doing toris hair and i had to do crappy work. but uhh hopefully i can see davey tomrrow before we leave tuesday or ill cry :(  oh yeah ok get this....u can say "in my pants" at the end of  ANYTHING  and it will make sense. try it. like... i like cheese...in my pants kayla...in my pants im having fun...in my pants.ooh that sounded kinda dirty anywho all u have to do is say something and add "in my pants" at the end.genius   
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      BEAT YOUR HEART OUT Baby, you make my heart beat faster. Baby, you make my heart beat faster. I know.  Let alone to rest alone, Yeah you’re making me. I had to run the damage is done, I give it up, I give it up. There’s nothing left so take the rest, Yeah you’re draining me. I set it alight it burns so bright, Stab it out, stab it out.  Baby, you make my heart beat faster. Baby, you make my heart beat faster. I know. Yeah I know. I know.  I had to run the damage is done,  I give it up, I give it up. I had to go it got control, Yeah you’re breaking me. There’s nothing left so take the rest, Stab it out, stab it out. I set it alight it burns so bright, Yeah you’re draining me.  You make my heart beat faster. Baby, you make my heart beat faster. I know. Yeah I know that it’s true.  Let alone to rest alone. Let alone to rest alone. Let alone to rest alone.  Baby, you make my heart beat faster.  There’s nothing left so take the rest.  Baby, you make my heart beat faster.  Let alone... 
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, maybe that’s the problem with punk, and the root of its hypocritical nature. The fact that it is no longer a statement at all. It is a deviation from the mainstream, but by deviating it only becomes it’s own separate mainstream. Punks no longer shock people.                            -The Creeps    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ^^^^MAHAHAH thats a quote from angelas pool that shall never be forgotten.... so i just got home from hanging out with the gang. i had so much fun davey was talking so much and cracking jokes we all felt high it was awesome  angela ditched skool today it was sweet!!!!! yay go angela! so we went to her house and swam in her pool and played around an electric fence :) then we went downtown for bryce's "better than sex" pita. and walked around during a thunderstorm. then went back to bryces and anthony joined us and we watched (well, kinda)kill bill & a bunch of shizazz. i really hope angela and anthony work out they seem cute together. today was radd so i dont want the day to end cuz tomorrow i have to paint our kitchen cabinets and doors in the house and put new locks on em and shit so its gonna be lame-o. watev. so nightey night davey kt angela bryce angelas new lover anthony & bobby and bryces cute doggy brooke.mahaha 
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i smell like chlorine and mango.:+
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hum de dum daddys in san fransisco im listening to pretty girls make graves and drinking mountain dew. awh this is the life. now if only bryce and kt would get back from the mall so we could go swimming! okay so on the mountain dew cup from arbys it says  "what are you eating today?" hmm? um well i had a peice of toast in the morning and the mountain dew that im reading from for lunch. my mum volunteered me to babysit this evening at 630. thanks mom. psh i hate when they do that. o well least i can get some $$ cha ching. now im listening to drain the blood. devil music. wat can i say? i want angela to ditch skool right now!!!! okay angela? good girl, now u can tell me ALL about your new infatuation, dearest anthony. MAHA im talking weird. its not everyday u hear me say dearest. so treasure it.  oh yeh this guy pissed me off this morning i was walking from moxie java this morning ( i had to stay there and wait for my classroom to open for drivers ed and then walked there) so about 830 i walked down about a block on a busy street to my class and i had on my lazy ripped up black sweatpants my sex pistols shirt and the black painted jacket that davey made me. so this ass hole decided to stick his whole upper body out the window and scream "ooohh sexy punks!!" and hollered and shit and did that little thing where u make a V with your fingers and stick your tongue out like ur eating a girl out. it PISSED me off. i dont really know why either. maybe just the way he did it. it made me feel easy. so basically a slut. but hey, watcha gonna do eh? i am #2 of the skank trio after all. ooh phones ringing. its kt gotta go
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      happy birthday davey!muuuuuuah  yeppy it was my lovers b day and it was really fun. it was weird hanging out with his family but i had fun i actually didnt feel so out of place. plus jason was there too so that helped.  oh yeah and we had a water balloon fight. wow i got soakkkked im tired and bored. blah. davey painted my jacket it looks soooooooo hot i love it. just tanned yesterday with my girls and slept. ill write more exciting stories tomorrow! i know i cant wait either!!!!!!
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im freaking out about this ring thing. cant believe i lost it. one minute it was on my finger and the next it was gone. god im so stupid. but watev. i dont really have much to say except that i hope tomorrow is better than today was. i was bored out of my mind. i think i might go to roaring springs with bryce and kt and tori but im not sure. hope i do. daveys at another show right now. damnit beevis  
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I HAVE PURPLE IN MY HAIR NOW!!!!!!! I SWEAR ITS GOTTA BE THE RADDDEST COLOR IN THE UNIVERSE!!!
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      jeez the warped tour bands are gonna suck compared to last year. the bands were so much harder last summer and i missed it. ggrrrr the only bands i really want to see that bad are the sounds the casualties and the eyeliners.eeeeeeekkkk and the eyeliners arent even coming here now!!!!!stupid sell outs.i cant believe such talented bands are sellouts 
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      TODAy i hung out at daveys with davey jason kt angela bryce and royce. it was hardcore. and i dont say that word lightly. hmm there was lesbian comic porn (almost kt!) haha and jason made a pipe put of wood, davey blew up fireworks and crap in the backyard and more sex in the city. plus royce & davey wouldnt stop playing their bass and guitars. those dirty punks davey loved the cd i got him. and the Buzzcocks pin:) i had to get it for him.i couldnt resist. davey and jason and royce are at the defiance show right now. i wanted to go soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo bad but i couldnt. im piassed! no not really. i got to put eyeliner on jason so it all evens out in the end.    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so yesterday had to have been the greatest day in the entire history of the skank trio. okay, it wasnt  that  orgasmic but it was so much fun. *k yesterday was girls day for the skank trio (kT, me, and angela) so there wasnt aloud to be any boys. but me and kt ended up talking to our guys on kt's cell for awhile anyways. yes we're rebels. but anyways we went to the record exchange so i could get davey his birthday present. everytime i go there they are ALWAYS out of oxymoron. im serious i have been there a trillion times and i look every time for it and its out. but when i went to go look, i saw the last one. the LAST FRICKEN ONE!!! i was soooo happy. and not only that, but it was the one he asked for "fuck the ninetys" one. it was fate i swear. jizzus i was happy. then we went and walked around town holding hands and getting whistled at. holler! jk im not a wanker.  *then we went back to kts to get her stuff and off to angelas blah blah blah. then to smokey mountain (oh yeah we went to taco bell again and got the biggest fucking mountain dews and shit but angela didnt finger her burrito. purr.why'd i just purr?) anywho! so we went to visit bryce at work at smokeys and he wasnt there but chilled with this guy that was like on crack. he dove into a dumpster full of pizza boxes. CARDBOARD ONLY DUMBASS. pffsh. doodle oodle oooh. my dog is snoring mahahha. oh yeh then we went back to angelas and did our nails radd colors and watched 4 hours of sex and the city. its the bible i tell you!!& we went to bed at about 4 and woke up at 930 and then tanned blah blah blah
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nighttime! i love it! except for the fact that you're suppose to sleep or something like that shizazz. you know. well instead of going to the shows this weekend im gonna go to daveys. i love the band kittie now. listening to their song "paperdoll" ooh talk about voodoo creEp shit. eeek. BUT i have a mountain dew here with me & me and angela threw bean burrito crap at a jeep mwahahha. angela we are sOOOO FRICKEN RADD! i swear!no seriously.you think im joking. but im not. thats the rad thing. yes! wait haha i dont know why i said yes i am just in a good mood for some reason even though i spent all my money today. dumb kayla! bad! on t shirts too, how sad. there was nothing i could do i swear officer!! awh okay im sorry im done. actually im probably not.  oh jizzus angela and i went to taco bell and they gave us so many fricken burrtos( thats why we threw it at the jeep and dropped it on the road in albertsons parking lot. tehe. we had plenty to spare. AND THEN! angela fingered the burrito! sick shit! mwahahaha love it. wellllllllllllllll i think im gonna go. but maybe not im not sure yet.  mmmmm nope...... hope tomorrow goes all good and funn and all with angela and kt. i hope kt is still coming. i havent talked her really since she has been back. well i tried to but then the whole thing about her getting in trouble happened and everything so yep yep. lalala night everyone. i l0ve u xoxoxoox  OFF TO BED
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       haha that was for u angela^ since i am NOT racist!  yay a new clean blank post. booya bitches. thats right. so i just got a call from katie. not even a hi or anything she just started yelling at me. "kayla dont call my house! why did you call my house? now im in trouble!" and i just sat there again. i just wanted to call her to say hi and i missed her and to see if she was back from being with bryce. but i guess i was wrong. my bad? she didnt tell me so there was no way i would have known but she apologized for yelling at me so its cool. i went the whole day without another headache.and now i have one. im going to the mall with angela now and get some fresh air. later dogs
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wednesday was a really busy day so i had 0 time to write here and i was really upset last night too. i went to daveys school and saw angela jake justin jason and people and stuff and it was cool going to see em at aschool .haha suckers. jk. um and so then i went to daveys and then went out with angela my slutty buddy. tehe. we are twin skanks. i love it!! but yeah then i got home and i was on the phone with davey. ya see while we were at his house we had been talking (me jason and him) about how its dumb when girls are like "ehh im sooo fat" and then they are so skinny. so i was liek eyah thats dumb. and they started yelling at me that i do that. so i was like eh watever.and davey said "if you think ur so fat why dont you just work out?!" and for some reason that pissed me off. and he said it again on the phone and i started to get defensive and everything and he told me "well what if i told u the truth about it u would slap me watever it was that i said" and i was "no i wouldnt. go ahead and tell me the truth i dare u." so he goes..." alright you're soo fat. in the sides and everything." god i was so quiet i wanted to hang up and never talk to him again. he was like "im just kidding hunny dont ever take me seriously like that. you are so skinny you are perfect in every way." by this time i was trying not to cry and shit so i was pissed. i know he was joking to see what i would do but i was BEYOND PISSEDand he knew it. so i guess we fixed it and everything but i was all sad and quiet and everything when we were getting off the phone. i was like well im going on a jog ill talk to you tomorrow. love you bye. and i heard him say i love u too  really quiet and sadly and i said bye and hung up. 
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey missy midg i thot u couldnt call yoyo!!!!humph. i feel.........pretty? no.nopey. i feel like being mad at someone and yelling at them on this thing. hmm who shal be the lucky winner?!!!!! not my brian(haha last post i spelt brain wrong.idiot.) anywho ummm i choose u picachoo!.nooooooooo.now im mad at myself.for not being mad at anyone. so much anger.grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr ----------------------- yoyo brycey!!homie g dog fer shizzle i didnt know u wanted me to call ya man, i thot u were spose to call me ice-tea. hehe i made a rhyme yay. i love u!!!!!
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ekk today was the first day of drivers ed at 9. i thought i was going to die. my head still hurt and it was absolutely KILLING me. i hvae taken 7 IB profin today and took 4 last night.i think im am becoming an addict. that is my prediction. and my class is filled with little preppy girls and jocks and and all. the only girl i really clicked with was this girl cierra. i think that was her name. but yeh we got along pretty well. shittles my head  STILL  hurts!!!!!!!!maybe i have a brain tumor or something. it kept me up until 3:30 last night. ughhhh      this is nifty ^ or "neat" as kentucky would put it. i miss my kt 
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my day didnt start out so well but it got sooooooo much better.i did a bunch of work in the morning and was crabby but then i hung out with angela and i had SOOOOOOOO much fun. i swear u can do the most boringest things with that girl and it will be a blast. so we were at her families barbecue thingy and me and ang were all making inside jokes and crap and her little step sister was like "are u guys high?!" hahaha man i wish!!!!!and then there was the squished spider, and the scary ketchup, that im deathly afraid of, and the purple hair dye all over the bathroom floor.YAY.we did angelas hair darkishpurpleblack on the bottom layers and it looks wayyyyyyyyyy hottness. were gonna do mine tomorrow and then blue purplish streaks in our hair and then go downtown again i think. im tired and my head STILL hurts so im gonna go before it explodes. and gets all over the keyboard. ewe.
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i hung out with davey jason kentucky bryce angela tori yesterday. we put like a purple-ish/red streak in my hair. it looks way rad. but i was gonna dye my hair darker today like a darkashblonde so then ill have dark blonde with purpleish red chunk.yey. DE starts tomorrow. i have to get up way too early. ekk ----------------- kentucky, who is suppose to be an alcoholic, didnt have anything to drink yesterday. i was really suprised, but proud of her. aww my lil slut, you're really not an alcoholic!!! jkjk  oh yes, jason passed out like 3 times yesterday. he had drank the night before and then did again in the morning and then in the afternoon with all of us. first he passed out on the front lawn, proli just for fun. but then he came inside on the couch and feel asleep. so angela drew on his face while he was asleeep with marker. that was sooooo fuckin funny. he had little whiskers and monstrous side burns. awh it was grand. 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, stan, the plan didnt work out or anyhting cuz well it just didnt. so i didnt get so sleep over at daveys. but sall good cuz i thot davey would be mad that i pussied out, but he wasnt at all. so maybe i will go see him tomorrow, cuz brycey said he could take me if i want. AND I WILL PAY HIM THE $$$ BLING BLING!!! oh yeah i had a convo with him today like he said that he doesnt want me to think that the only reason he drives me is cuz of money, and i know thats totally not it, but i dont want him to think im using him or anyhting to get rides. thats bullshit and i would NEVER EVER do that to anyone. except rose because she was a bitch. to me and deserved it. aww that was mean now i feel bad.poopsies.write more later maybe. in a bit. maybe. im not sure. -------------------------- okay i love angela i hope she is ok. i was on the phone with midg and she said that travis came by to angelas house and angela needed to talk to kt so she went over there. god i lov her i hope she is ok. if that devil boy hurt her little fragile woman heart i'll...i'll...i'll take away his manhood!!! (if angela aproves a course) well im outtie like a belly button mwahahahahhaa
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im mad at travis. i am almost as mad at him as i hate TOM. i just dont think its fair at all how he treats her. she is one of my best friends and if i ever met him and i saw him treating her like this i would give him a peice of my mind. and a peice of my fist in his fuckin face. grrrrrr no one treats my hos like that.no one. eh hem...brb gotta get a dew.:) so ANYWAYS i am better now. not so angry. wooooooooo. today has been a weird emotional day. i kinda had a fight with davey about friday. and we NEVER fight. we have been together for like 7 months and never really fought. so anyways we got in an argument about friday b/c his family is leaving this weekend and he wants me to spend the night. and if i get caught i will never be able to see him again. and he kept telling me to do watever makes me happy. but then he said he knew i wouldnt spend the night because im pussywipped by my parents. so what am i suppose to think? either way im in trouble. if i go and get caught, im fucked for life. and if i dont, he'll be upset and get mad at me for not taking a risk. damnit. kt and brycey came over and saw us later on after we made up.that made me feel better. i love them. and midg looked so cute. all prettied up. i hate daveys parents. they are so rude and hypocritical. they dont even let him eat.so i am having to force him to eat. he finally eats and they yell at him about paying for it. fuck! what kind of parents make their kids pay for their own dinner? isnt their some kind of law about feeding your own kids? finally he ate tho. but hes getting so skinny. he's just bones.i practically had to bribe him to eat macaroni for dinner. i hope this weekend goes good. me and kt and bryce spending the night, just chillin havin fun and relaxing. it'll be perfect. please let it be perfect. 
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had to go to the DMV thingy today for drivers ed and that was a pain in the rectum i tell you. we waited an hour to get in and then i had to take this eye test and then fill out a bunch of crappy papers. drivers ed starts next monday. cant wait to finally have my license. i feel like such a prick always asking for rides. then i went to davey's band practice. i cant wait to go to one of their shows.yay for punk rock!!haha the guitarist/singer guy eric is such a dick he thinks hes such a badass and that hes the leader. screw that. then there's dustin the bassist. hes a dumbass, thats all there is to it. pure dumbass. ...and justin... hmmm justin. he's the drummer so that explains a little.;)jk we always used to bug him about his girlfriend and how he never got any and should dump her and she finally dumped him. so the whole time he was talking about how he needs his dick sucked.ha great fun. but he is a pretty cool kid hes like the funniest and hes always screwing around.and davey is the quietest out of the band. he just plays what he's suppose to and doesnt argue with anyone. altho, on thursday he's gonna tell eric for me that i say hes a real bitch and fuck off. aw gotta love my davey. we just chilled after practice and came back to my house and went on a walk to the playground and the slides and swingset were being torn up. i guess they're fixing em and putting in new ones.cheap shit. so i just climbed a tree.:)yay hum de dum de dum oh yeah, bryce, you got silly davey addicted to that punk-0-rama game where u make songs and hes crazy about it.he was playing it at my house & he made me call u like 4 times to get u and katie to come over and he wanted u to hear his song on there. tehehehhehe 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah TOM is here. hes the biggest f*ing ass hole in the WHOLE WIDE WORLD. think of the person you hate the most, like, in the world, your worst enemy,the person you want to kill and inflict so much pain on their lives that they scream because they soooo freaking deserve it and TOM is worse. he is worse than the bully in kindergarten that used to take your crayons and ate your pudding. TOM is a bitch!!!
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      now im feelin better cuz im on a midol overdose. things are going kinda slow up there now. its hard to type. but um now my tumy doesnt hurt. i took 4 midol and 5 IB Profin. yum.and im eating cheetos. i wish i still had an orange streak in my hair. i was so rad in those days. now im just a lil cheeto. that was my name at school cuz i had orange hair. yep. did u know yep means sex in russian? wat a great language.i wish i was russian. or asian. they are real pretty.wow i feel fucked up ------------------- so bryce wrote a comment on my last post saying that if i ever said i was in the way again he wood chop off my legs and eat them. that made me feel purdy special cuz i feel cared for now. im sorry brycey i was just really depressed when i wrote that and i felt bad that saturday didnt go the way u had planned. but i am so thankful that u love me! u love me u really do! ahhhhhhhhh thats from some movie. hmmm.wat was i saying? oh yes well thank you for always going to get my hunnie so we can both have our hunnies. you rule!!!!!! ------------------------ i am listening to all that glitters by le tigre. cant really undertsand what they are saying. lets look up the lyrics shall we?..... The stars are getting in and out of automobiles  And we keep wondering when we're gonna feel something real  Keep waiting for a Santa that'll never come  A real party not just people who're faking fun  But everything gets erased before it's even said  And all that glitters isn't gold when inside it's dead  All that glitters is not gold  All that glitters is not gold   I went to yr concert and I didn't feel anything  I went to yr concert and I didn't hear anything   (oh baby) why won't you talk to me?  (oh baby) you just want me empty!  (oh baby) you don't say anything!  (oh baby) why won't you answer me?   All that glitters is not gold  All that glitters is not gold    I sat thru yr movie but I didn't see anything  I went to yr comedy club and didn't laugh at all  I went to yr movie and I didn't hear anything  I went to yr concert and there was nothing was going on   You don't say, you don't say,  you don't say anything........  YAY :)
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yesterday went to roaring springs with midg and bryce again and then picked up davey and went to bryces house. alot of the times, even tho i am best friends with both kt and bryce, i feel like i shouldnt be there. like all bryce wants to do is get alone time with kt so im in the way. and i  hate  being in the way. it drives me absolutely insane. so yeah we are suppose to go to roaring springs again tomorrow but since sat didnt work out for bryce maybe we'll just go another time so they can have some fun
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the raddest kid ever you ask? well yep that would have to be brycey. he is the most generous fellow in the whole world. he will do something for you even if he has to go the hell out of his way and it doesnt benefit him at all. plus he makes you giggle so hard u cant breath and usually does it when u just took a drink of m dew... oh shit now ur trying not to spit it out on everyone and explode with laughter and m dew like mt. st. helens  but anywho. yep. u should meet this kid. hes my bestest buddy.
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so yesterday i "supposedly" went to roaring springs. but no! something majorly more fun~i went to bryces with kt and davey and brycey we did stuff and i havent been sober since.we ate all of kt's munchy food and watched blues clues and took pictures of all the fucked up things. it gave me much pleasure.not that kind of pleasure u sicko!!!!!!!!!!!! HAHA now im gonna write a whole new post about someone way cool. dog.
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its early for me but i cant sleep anymore and im deciding wat i should do today. my dad stayed home sick which he never does so that kinda messes up my plans for going out. but oh well ill leave anyways. --------------- while i was in bed i thought of things i want to do before skool starts again: 1. lose weight 2. grow out my hair longer 3. get my root color ash blonde back 4. get tan 5. hmmm basically i wanna be perfect.god.i hate life
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       last day of skool today but it didnt feel like it was over at all. and i believe i passed all my classes but im not sure. my legs hurt from having sex in bryces car. jk we crammed in the back cuz he's the nicest fellow in the world and he took me kt davey jason micheal and angela to the record exchange and to simplots hill.o yeah and i warned micheal and jason and davey not to steal from the record exchange cuz they have a new cam system but NOOOOOOOOO micheal didnt listen the little dirty shit he just pulled out his pocket knife and was like hmm im gonna be a dumbass and steal!!! so i was like yoyo im outta here and me and davey went outside and waddya know? like 5 seconds later. 5 seconds i tell you!the group comes outside and tell us he was busted. fuck yeah! i love being right. im glad it was micheal and not anyone else too cuz he is a bitch in the ass hole i kid u not.so we left the exchange and went to simplots hill and it was sooooooooo hot so we threw pinecones at bryce and kt and it made it all better:) i love bryce and kt so much. they are so good to me.jason and daves cheap asses only gave him 5 buckaroos for gas money so im gonna try to be extra nice and also pay him some big bucks tomorrow. seriously they dont have to ever let me see davey, but they do. god i love them. they are the shiznits and my bestest buddies. ya i hope this saturday works out with going to bryces cuz that would be so much fun. i thot about chickening out  but if the plan sounds good after i work it out with bryce and them im gonna go for it. wat the hell wat is there to lose when you're nothing? 
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay fine! so im writing my third post today...shut up im bored!!!!!!!!!! i am bored putting off studying for my bio final. wat is there to lose when im already screwed. hahaha the funniest thing today-brycey was at my house with kt and i was like dude dont cuss my bro is here k?and later on he was like (i dont remember wat we were talking about at first, but...) he was like "dude thats fucked!" and i shot him a look and he was like "...i mean screwed i mean..oh shit!" and and we all just started cracking up laughing. they are my bestest buddies. i love u brycey and kentucky hehehe jk jk.jizzus! haha member that kt? that was great fun. can u tell i have no life..you're probably thinking..wat kind of loser is this girl? she writes 3 long posts a day and is mega lonely. actually i have a life its just the parental guidance that stop me from having one at the moment. and im waiting for kt and davey to call back. calllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well i just got back from getting davey at his practice and i was mad that i didnt get to hang out with him and then he acted all madtoo. so now im mad that he's mad that im mad. get it?so we called the place he was practicing like 5 times because me and brycey couldn't find it. so we finally get there and his friend cums outside and is all like "finally found it?" in a smart ass way and i just think oh fuck off im not in the mood. and THEN his little cousin comes outside and is like "davey,its your ugly blonde" so then i wasnt just pissed ...i was beyond pissed. davey comes outside and we pile in the car and the whole way home i wanted to kiss him, but never got one and we joked with bryce and everything with everyone but davey still knew i was pissed so when we go to his house he looked sad and i felt really bad. im waiting for him to call now so i can tell him i love him. but at least now i know it wasnt his fault that he couldnt see me. i love u davey
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i realize today i am infatuated(coolbig word) with lesbians.even tho im not one they're still so f*ing cool & i bought a lesbian pin at spencers YAY! and we looked at kamasutra booklets OH LORDY WAS THAT FUN.but well im frustrated with a boy who will remain nameless. he will remain nameless because i love him but yes i am just frustrated cuz we were all suppose to go on a picnic and go to simplots hill BBUTTTTTTTTTTTTT when i went to go pick him up he wasnt there.kt and brycey poo just asked me why we're going to pick him up from his band practice tho and i said this..... cuz i want him to know exactly HOW PISSED i am. he will pay....dun  dun dun but he really wont tho. wow cool my thing is like disco mania. kt and bryce are K-I-S-S-I-N-G but not in a tree, on my futon. and im listening to The Sounds so im cherryi miss davey i wanna see him ppppppppppllllllllleeeeeeeeeeeeaaaaaaaaaaaaaaassssssssssssssssssee!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     Which 1990's Subculture Do You Belong To?    &nbsp;  &nbsp;  thats funny. ive never considered myself indie. or watever the hell they're talking about. so...........i have come to the realization that davey and i are the new sid and nancy. only i will probably end up killing him. bahaha.ANYWHO i havent had the urge to write on this like i used to. quite crazy i believe. maybe too busy. or maybe because my life just seems bleh and i dont want to complain about blehness to everyone else. i really want to hang out with angela tomorrow i hope she doesnt go off to mccall alone. please angelina.    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i havent written on this&nbsp;in so long but no one seems to have missed me &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; EVERYONE STOP FIGHTING!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well im officially drunk.no just kinda now.im fading. oh yeah and theres no such thing as being too drunk to fuck. well not to me. just so you know. in case you need to know that anytime soon. it may cum in handy. i mean come. oops. my bad. im putting alot of periods. heres one.two.three. anyyyways um lets see i drove today then went to daveys and then hung out & had wild crazy......uh nevermind. HA jk. umm? oh yes we watched south park and had some nasty tasting beer which i drank faster than davey-i am proud. and then jason came over but i had to leave. so i was in the car with my mom on the way home and my mom was like wats wrong with you. i told her it was allergies cuz my eyes were watering and they were drowsy and i was spacing out and i couldnt hear wat she was saying. she totally wouldnt have believed me but that minute i sneezed. thank god.i was like YES! FUCK YES!SHE WILL ACTUALLY BELIEVE ME!!  so i was home and i ate and ate and ate. cuz i do that. specially when im drunk. bagels are good.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      listening to sex and violence by exploited. thats basically what i got bitched at about last night for 2 hours. sex drugs religion friends punk curfews phones all the shit you can think of. all i was thinking about was how i wanted to call davey and say goodnight to him. this is the second night in a row i havent gotten to talk to him and say goodnite, i love you.   damnitT i am so emo  so anyways i kind of ignored the screaming and crying from them. my dad bitched about how i dont love or respect him and that i take advantage of my mother. NO SHIT SHERLOCK!! wat a dumbass. blah blah blah. so THEY came up to the settlement of i respect them and be home when i say im going to and spend more FUCKING QUALITY TIME with them blahdee blahdee blah and then i can have a later curfew if i call or what not i dunno i really wasnt paying too much attention. before this, my mom found a picture from soccer that i had stabbed with jasons pocket knife because i was bored. OH WATCH OUT IM SUICIDAL IM GOING TO STAB MY FACE!!!! wat a loser she thought i was like insane or something and that i was going to kill myself because i stabbed a picture. parents these days, i tell you. we should just lock them up. thats what they deserve.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this may never start we could fall apart and i'd be your memory  lost your sense of fear feelings insincere can i be your memory  so get back to where we lasted just like i imagine  i could never feel this way So get back to the disaster  my heart's beating faster holding on to feel the same  this may never start i'll tear us apart can i be your enemy  losing half a year waiting for you here i'd be your anything  so get back to where we lasted just like i imagine  i could never feel this way so get back to the disaster  my heart's beating faster holding on to feel the same  this may never start tearing out my heart i'd be your memory  lost your sense of fear feelings disappear can i be your memory  so get back to where we lasted just like i imagine  i could never feel this way so get back to the disaster  my heart's beating faster holding on to feel the same  this may never start we could fall apart and i'd be your memory  lost your sense of fear feelings insincere can i be your memory  can I be your memory 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what if i disapeared from existance? what if one day i woke up and i wasnt in my own bed. i was no where. what if i was just..gone. would you look for me? would you care that i was lost. would you go on without me? would you still think about me? and dream about our future together. would you give up and start over. would you find someone new. would you replace me? or would you give up? would you become lost too. in a pool of emptyness i feel like all the emptiness in my life is eating away at me. like i am such a horrible person to everyone. i dont deserve to be so lucky. to have a wonderful boyfriend and such great friends. i dont even feel like i deserve to live. to think about all the horrible things i have done in life, i literally make myself sick. if i was someone else, i would hate me. i couldnt stand myself. i always mess everything up. im sorry.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              urlLink   What Is Your Best Sexual Skill?        Name:         Age:         Sex:     Male  Female       Sexuality:     Straight  Gay  Bisexual       Flirting Skill Level -  61%                                                                            Kissing Skill Level -  67%                                                                            Cudding Skill Level -  90%                                                                            Sex Skill Level -  82%                                                                             Why They Love You      You are too sexy for words.        Why They Hate You      You take more than you give.              This   Quiz   by  urlLink  lady_wintermoon   - Taken 229958 Times.          New - COOL  Dating Tips and Romance Advice ! 
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ignore that last post. i was ordered to write it against my will, but i put sexy instead of stupid so eat that bitches. sooooooooooo.....last night after all the camotion of warped tour and angela's x-boyfriend at tcby, we went downtown to the big easy to meet eric, but he never showed. so to cheer her up a litle we just walked around the cruise and all around and got hollered at. i really dont like when guys do that. not only because i have davey, but it makes me feel like a slut. ecspecially when they stop and pull over and start talking to ya. then i wanna smack em.i feel like a fucking prostitute!! so first these guys pulled over and were like "ladies, looking fine tonite, wanna go for a ride?" and i was like "no, sorry, shes MY BITCH" and grabbed one of her dreads and pulled her off with me in the other direction. so we kept walking and they came back and asked us if we were sure, and angela said something like "maybe if it wasnt stock" referring to their car. that made em go away. HA BITCHES.  but i guess we both had too much to smoke and loud music and dust and jumping and crowds and shit because we both had KILLER headaches that night and we went right to sleep. i felt bad because i just crashed right there. but the drugs helped the next morning. :D yay for drugs!!!!!!!!!haha  later on today after i came home i slept for awhile and just sat around cuz i felt like shit. but then jason called me and told me to come over to daveys because he was bored and davey was having practice with some other kid i forget his name. but i couldnt so they came over to mine. jasons drunk ass just plopped on the floor the minute he walked into my room but david only had  none and a half beers... ha!right! hmm lets see we walked to justos and got soda and then went to the park and played on the weird fucked up playground and we came back to my house and just talked while i tore up my shoes.  im suppose to be doing the dishes right now. shit, i dont think so!! im not your bitch. thats what id like to say to my mom..... EAT SHIT YOU STUPID CUNT MORMON YOU'RE RUINING MY LIFE SO FUCK OFF BITCH!!!!  but dont forget peace and love and to be gentle but firm. lol
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im sexy i gave half of a half of a box of pizza pockets to jason but hes drunk so fuck off. 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i love mosh pits. but one thing that really makes me wanna vomit is when shirtless sweaty nasty guys are in the mosh pit.i mean who wants to rub up against a slimy hairy back!? so that was warped tour and it was alright for my first one. angela and davey came by and picked me up. we went to tcby to get our tickets and angela went into a political talk again with these two punkers.i love when she does that.then angela did her hair in way rad dreads while me and davey watched monster-scary ass movie- so then we were off to the concert and met up with katie and bryce and went off yonder to watch some shows.  first i saw casualties who are really sexy & they are pretty good live. the dust was flying into my eyes and i could smell weed everyonce in awhile. i coulda cried then i saw random shows like the sounds, nofx, story of the year, coheed and cambria, new found glory, and bad religion. i used to like the sounds alot because they sounded like blondie, but i realized the only thing good about them live is maja is really hot. and so are the other band members in it. they are all hot. but thats all. no one was into it and i think the band knew it. the bad religion one was my favorite cuz me and davey were really close and the moshing was pretty good. like 4 girls were thrown close to me and fell trying to crowd surf cuz this anal guy wouldnt help. so mean.  later angela and i went downtown to see her eric man from nevada but he never showed. i told her it was because he had a small penis. i have a sense about these things. and katie couldnt spend the night we were both really bummed about that. it seems like something is on her mind and something is really bugging her lately. but she wont let it out. angela and me and davey have all noticed it. probably just thinking about bryce alot, maybe shes worried about him. he looked sooo happy in the crowd at coheed. it was good to see him smile. 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i drove for the first time today for drivers ed and i did pretty good for my first drive. my driving partner is really cool i like her. she may be going to warped tour tomorrow too so that'll be neat. and i got these killer shorts from zumiez and these guys were talking to me there it was strange stuff.  then i wanted to talk to bryce because i ahdnt talked to him all day and i guess all he thought i wanted to talk about was a ride. i mean common, i just wanted to talk to him and see what was up. but he was eating dinner so i get it. but i was wondering what shows he wanted to see for tomorrow and so i said "so whats going on with tomorrow?" he was "just like get a ride with angela". thats not even what i meant. o well. maybe he just has alot on his mind. tell him i luv him for me k? im really tired and im just rambling so im gonna go to bed. ill write tomrrow maybe if i have time but i probably wont. so dont miss me
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im sucking on a watermelon tootsie roll pop. its new, i think. maybe not tho. i got it in chicago. maybe its just a chicago thing. but anyways its good. and thats kinda how my days was. actually some parts were absolutely grrrrrreat..like tony the tiger great. and other parts were just okay. so i went to my driving thing and my partner never showed up so i have to go back tomorrow and drive cuz she forgot. what a ho.  and i got to see davey and katie and bryce and jason and angela all today. brycey was feeling sad and so then everyone was feeling sad because we all love brycey. he is the best bryce in the world. i heart him lots. then we went to the movies and saw spider man 2. man i cant go to the movies anymore. all i do is make fun of em and giggle the whole time. well i do when im with davey. we were screwing around the whole time it was great.like making fun of their faces and i dropped a couple of things and yeah. then we went to the park and frollicked and...is that how u spell frollicked? anyways uh...oh yeah i had a really cute conversation with david about our first date and red sharpies and how they connect uu. it was deep. i had a good day mr rogers.  p.s. katie, ...(kayla singing)  " its gonna be okay " 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so im trying to figure out how i can tell you all about my trip efficiently. i dont usually do things efficiently but i give this one a try. nope. jk thats gonna take up alot of time so no. basically i visited with my relatives and i saw my cousins and went to six flags and this really boring musueum and rode a train and saw the siers tower and yeah.i think thats about all. now i need a mountain dew brb................ok. mmmmmmmmm sooooo refreshing. in illinois its like coke country so its really hard to find pepsi products which blows ass. so i was deprived for awhile but then my aunt bought me a 24 pack. yum. i think it lasted me 2 days.  i have to drive at noon today. dad took me driving to practice last weekend there so i guess i kinda have the hang of it.  i only have to drive an hour but then i have to sit in the car for another hour watching my partner drive. that'll be lame. all i wanna do is see my posse. hahha i have a posse!!!
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its almost 2 am and im sooooooo tired. we just got back from chicago and im so happy to be back. but i need to hear daveys voice. and i want to see katie and angela and bryce and jason and everyone because i have missed them so much. i feel so left out since i have been gone for so long ya know? so i have to catch up with everyone when i see em tomorrow. but ill write more about the last couple of days tomrrow. i mean today, in the morning. er..later, in the morning.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its seems so long since i have written. i actually miss writing in here. scary. i know. but anyways i rode a train from bloomington to antiock today. its a little over an hour away from chicago. we just got back from watching fireworks. i can still hear some outside. i cant wait to get back home and be with my skanks and my buddy bryce and my love davey. cosmopolitan and music are the only things getting me by when i travel. but i got the book "go ask alice". so depressing. she screws up her life with acid and shit. i would never do acid. that shit stays in your system forever.  we might be going to six flags tomorrow. or swimming if its nice out i think. either way watever. thanks for writing me an email bryce i didnt know if u were still alive out there.
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      holla! im at my favoritest cousins house hillary and we are chillin drinking beers. no. jk. anywho! we went on a walk and good ol kayla had to pee pee so there was a skool nearby and i went under the bus and peed!!! awwhhh!!! so refreshing! so um then i went into this uh,? dumpster thingy(empty!) and a couple of cars came by and it was late and dark and hicks here will tattle on you, so i  had to hide an climb out when they were gone. hmm later i think we're gonna watch movies and hang out and stuff maybe watch breakfast club which i havent seen yet. any wise words you'd like to share hill??? I eat poop.love hillary. mmmkay?! drugs are bad mmkay? ummmm its friggin 80 degrees out here and its 10:25 pm. yo thats hott. and not hott like johnny depp hot, like sizzling sausage hott!!!! bamm!!!ok im done.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am filled with sadness now because no one wrote me a comment. even in my time of need!!! you dirty sluts! jk anywho ummmmm i am in the library and its wayyy to quiet. i should start making bird calls. pakaw!! yesterday i laid out in the sun and got a pretty good tan and then i went swimming and went to my cousin's softball game, where i got eaten alive by mosquitos. poo. hum de dum im gonna go now because no one loves me...im talking to skank trio here for not writing to me!!!! jk i love u guys i miss u so much please write me back
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im in illinois still and i walked down to the library to write on here and write emails because the computer crashed where im staying. i was pissed. so here i am at the library. its kinda creepy. eeewweeee.  um....i had alot to say, but now i dont. maybe ill write more when i walk back tomorrow. oh yeah, jason do u have a blog or something? how'd you get my thing u dirty mexican? davey if u r reading this i love you i love you guys angela and kt and everyone write more comments. dude.
    
</post>


</Blog>