<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
              Ahoy mates! sianz just finish my maths revision having maths papers tml..much thx to henry lee and Rovin ahaz had a enriching lesson at my place today! And rovin hahaz didnt know we could mug until just now hahaz! okei anyway, this few daes been hell busy with studies and stuff hoping thaty the term paper be over soon so i can go back to my life! hahaz        Oh yeah went for Khelsa Hockey team trials with the hockey team last fri man it was total disappointment fer me....got lost on the field but the guys tried consolling me saying that its my first time playing a real game and stuff but that didnt quite work either...worst i got so many injuries man! The damn old singh player from khelsa wif the hockey stick wah total agony! but i was determine enuff to play the whole game even though i was quite bothered by the big super bump on my head that kinda bleed abit...had to end up icing the bump fer the next 3daes...then if you tot thats over..NO! got hit by fast ball on the ankle when blocking the D...man ended up like lobin tan liaoz laming on one leg...damn! ahaz..but good thg bout khelsa is i got lotsa experience from the game hope i can improve fast man!! kinda suck being so lousy! haaz..oh yeah also gotta know some J2 hockey peeps like yongming the keeper and faizal the ex-capt, pravin super dude too hahaz all of them are super zhai and rox totally man! hahaz wad i can sae PJC HOCKEY ROX BIGTIME MAN! SATAY GUYS!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                 Ahoy Mates! hahahaz been missing saying that for a long time..didnt manage to find time to blog ever since my last entry...been super busy wif mid yr preperations and not to sae hockey and other stuff! ahahz...oh yeah went fer my first hockey trainig last week...it was a blast man haha didnt believe that i will get accepted by the hockey people so ez all thx to keat, kai kampong kid etc hahaz...brudders thx alot man if not fer u guys i don tink i will be where i am ! hahaz..okei that sounds kinda cheesy...aniwae the person i tok bout fer changing cca and hockey full cap thg..didnt knoe that he was daph's ex..hahaz from MI too...wat a small world huh..but aniwae got support from sis to change cca too so i am rejuvinated to go to cee kwok fer the last time! so pray hard its successful! hahaz            okei other than bz wif hockey and mugging this few daes, been rethinking of my options...most of the time she pops up in my mind but thats kinda annoying fer me cant seems to do thgs rite after that...damn...so i am set out to forget bout everithg on this kinda foolish infactuation hahaz...supersan if u read this don u dare sae i am in self denial hahaz and don lauff! hahaz...okei..cheesy...yeah but mb god trying to set me up or sumthg trying to make thgs harder fer me..obstacles...got to cee her acting imtimate wif her current bf in shopping malls and stuff..but i guess i am somewhat bothered by that hahaz...bah whatever...must be strong! hahaz           Oh yeah just got shocked by phyllis and her frend(my sis frend too!)...got a call from them in the middle of the night man jumped when the phone ring..satay man...must be too much of all those supernatural talks we had in the lib ytd wif kai keat and rovin hahaz....aniwae kinda sleepy now so go hit the sacks le...nite to all stay tune fer my next blog..as u all know boring hahaz....chao!~~
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Southernmost pt of Asia!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    spooky pic...look at the blur head in the centre...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    come challenge us man! &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Fun time at Sentosa! 04S08!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
            Ahoy Mates! man feeling super rotten and terrible dawg.....got attacked by flu the day back from sentosa wif the class...been a hell of a fun trip and stuff man hahaz hope we can do it more often hahaz...man got back that day mum's down wif a flu i guess caught in from her then went to cee the doc that night...high fever and stuff feeling exceptionally rotten cant eat sleep or do anythg...hope this go away fast man yearnig to go sch tomorrow got lots of stuff to settle.....           herm monday's trip to sentosa was great..the weather good sun everythg and although the class wasent full but those present party hard hahaz...08' peeps fret not man going to send the pixs to ya all soon hahaz..herm the night there was one word: Unpredictable! hahaz tot its going to be dead cold in the night but wrong only got freaking freezing when it was like two or three in the morning hahaz ricky, phyllis, supersan and me didnt went wif the other guys fer their night trek so stayed at the tower fer the night...man we got freezed to the core i guess hahaz and THX san fer the windbreaker or i will turn ice that night hahaz! tot thats the worst? No soon the Mosquitoes came and stung us like there no tomorrow...all four of us were practically feeding them and they don seems to be full! But anyway its an experience too...coz most of the time i get such stuff in camp wif my brothers hahaz not wif class and stuff...And haha we had a blast cycling too hahz...sorry fer my grp hahaz had a hard time finding rovin and his grp...that kampong boy told us to follow the monorial tracks..did it and ending ujp cycling up-slopes and down hills...man its super adraline rush when we go down but the sucky part is going back up..anyway manage to find rovin and his homies at last at some "haunted" mansion looks more to me like a broken shack hahaz and it smells like rotting wood too....So sorry to my grp took you guys cycle the hard way and make u all so damn shagged after that...Sumimaseh!          herm got to go man....take pills and catch winks headaches killing me...ceeya all! Chao!~~  Yours Seascoutingly, Kenneth aka. Medicdog
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
               Ahoy Mates!Just got back from training 15min ago...damn tired but quite fun todae get to crap wif my godbro(thomas) hahaz...been a long time since i go down for training so had a nice chat wif him at our usual spot near dojang..Well just now fer training haha Larry came down so its super fun too hahaz...last saw this dude was at tenderfoot camp in march hahaz...but anyway todae help coach the white belts chonji pattern and stuff then after that did self defence haha good learn alot of stuff todae..how to counter a back grapple and how to prevent getting throw by pplz ahaz...did that wif thomas but most of the time didnt control well hahaz jab him in the stomach or face hahaz! Sorry Bro! ahaz...            Haiz but today also didnt go well either...suffering from the post symdrome of getting rejected from hockey had a moody day thru chem tutorial..ended up sleeping at the back coz my contacts hurting my eyes..donno wad happen to them...MOREOVER, was anticipating her to come today but was wrong she wasent there haiz...so sad another dae goes by without ceeing her hahaz kinda miss her sight hahaz but its allrite lahz still passable...ended up slacking wif weiming and Phyllis at coffeebean CCK for hours before heading home hahaz...tok bout everything too..thx to them kinda help me lifty up my mood..so THX PHYLLIS AND WEIMING!(even i knoe they most probably not read this!) And weiming if you are reading this, man i cannot stand those two S animore kinda irritated and pissed by their attitude hahaz no wonder they sae birds of the same feather flocked together huh hahaz! okei enough dizzing le...kinda SEHHHHHH hahaz signing off here....Nitez!   Yours Seascoutingly, Kenneth aka. Medicdog 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                Ahoy mates! Yeah finally get over with Tution wif Henry Lee aka.Chicken haha hope he dont cee this...man SEHHH arz do trigo stuff kinda in a daze now everythgs' blur and god knoes have to memorise so mani darned formulae for just 1 stupid idiotic topic...I guess i am dead fer the comming mid term papers man...basket shldnt have slack so much....             But then again, this june hols like no hols have to mug like siaos and speaking of which i still got tons of camps and activities for scouts to attend man this is tiring....wad to do not EZ being a scout man hahahaz...guess my mum going to blast my ears telling me i been spending too much time on cca blah blah blah....ZZZZzzz....Anyway look on the bright side hehe i gotta go  fer "CAMP AHOY" yeah! first ever national seascout camp wah zhai rite? ahahz....yeah going to enjoy myself flat out fer full four days out sea and stuff from 23-26 haha rest 1 dae then nxt dae MT paper wah song bo hahaz...at least i get a taste of the sea b4 exam hahaz...I miss my sea life man....itching to kayak and touch the sea water hahaz, but most of all miss my scouter bros and stuff man....hope to get back to sea training with those dudes asap kinda sick of my currrent tasteless life man!}(coz life always taste better wif salt! hahaz i can help RSN do advertisments already hahaz!)..haiz enuff crapping already nothing to write on aniway hahaz...signing off...  Yours Seascoutingly, Kenneth aka. Medicdog
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Yeah Guest MC fer tsunami First Campfire! hahaz had no idead wad i am doing hahaz&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Zid and spastic me again :(...Going home from Thailand&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Maddies on Bus! (bobian too excited to go to the caves!)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Tsunami wif Malaysian Scouters&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Bubble boy on bus(bus-lagged from Singapore to Thialand :( )&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Big Guy and Skinny me!! hhaz&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Ah Bing..Me...Wanying(taken after the buffet looks so contented)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Bala and me acting muddish hahaz....cool huh?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Daph and Spastic me...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Bala JinzHou and ME at...MI!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
                Ahoy Mates!Came to blog again...duh...anyway todays just like any normal school day lohz, went to sch in the morning wif san phyllis and wanyi fer Chinese Oral..kinda sucks didnt do veri well but oh well its over so wads the pt hahaz....hermz nothin' much after that oh yeah went to find Kwok bout hockey transfer again....          That didnt went out as perfectly either...turns out the guy that went fer SC didnt went to find Kwok fer his transfer outta hockey so i went there like some stupid ass asking if he have see n the SC guy..got kinda screwed by Kwok but nahz not his fault that man doing wad he have to...toldd me that even if i wanna go to hockey i can't leave tkd now coz he uploaded the infos to MOE..so if i realli persist on going to hockey i have to take 3ccas and tkd takes piority over hockey..man i am totalli screwed...veri disappointed...and if that SC guy suddenly don wanna leave hockey i cannot go onver still arrgh! this is sickening man.....but nobody to blame just me and my stupidity......got tkd outside still join sch 1 wanna get shot man haiz....            Herm kinda in a dilemma now..wanna go hockey coz veri enthu and intrested bout it besides all my dudes are in that cca...so fun and stuff on the other hand kinda feel like i am betraying PJ tkd....moreover tink Kwok got a bad impression of me le...just hope he don't find out he knoes my Sis or i am realli realli super dupy screwed...Really don hold anything against him though he rejected me so many times, have ta do that if not everi1 start changing ccas and stuff..but anyway i still can play the sport even though i am not in the cca hope the guys allow me too or i will be dead sianz...moreover all the hockey j1 guys and gals also treat me not bad hahaz more feel like going over but wat the heck man hahaz....guess look on the bright side le at least i can excel in tkd and hope i can make it to nationals by this end of yr haha(This is a FAT hope!)...Herm...after session wif kwok its normal slacking at the study corner crapping bout stuff wif san and phyllis hhaahz that kinda put my mind off hockey stuff....After that saw Wen Kai have a nice chat wif that cool dude haha then found out from him that TKD federation kana kicked out of merit sport of Singapore sad even more...nationals seems to be further then ever noe coz trhe govt no longer support tkd fed..basket fed up wif the system...they want good fighters but all they do is whine bout stuff and change the fighting rules to outta point of coz we will get trashed by other competitors...and Singapore just don see the fact that some tkd academy fighters stand better chance in the SEA games than Feds....there goes my chance to get the sports scholarship fer tkd in the nationals.....further depressed now......after that went home...        Reach the letterbox of my blk look in woo got my letter don know wads it about went up to take the keys..open the box haha finally a good moment of the dae..my results for my Black Senior Dan 2 results are out...hahaz didnt realli dare to open it so bring it up to my room and settle down(come on gib mi a break if i fail this grading i waste my 200bucks man!)...finally open it haha yeah i passed! hahazz A OFFICIAL SENIOR DAN2 BLACK holder now! hahaz now my hopes are higher and thgs seems slightly better but then went to switch on the tube switch to ESPN was eager to see if there is highlights on the MBL but wad the heck it was a ice HOCKEY match made me think of hockewy again and yesh kwok....bring my mood back to ground zero again then poof went online to blab about stuff here...hahaz              Herm, kind of a bad day fer me today i shld say having tution some more in the evenings and there is chem tutorial tomorrow basket no good rest! arrgh but anw get to cee the class mb i will be feeling better by then after the usual crappings and stuff hahaz...Ha hope to get a glimse of her tml coz didnt saw her todae but again on the other hand don realli wanna cee her too...don wanna gib myself false hopes you cee hahaz....donno lahz so cee how thgs goes tml lohz...MB better mb worse but wad to do life goes on...hope she is realli njoying herself wif her other half and stuff and also njoying the hols even though i knoe its been a total crap all the way till now...kinda also looking forward to Camp Ahoy and the class outing but seems like all not going weiming my twin etc etc...haiz so kinda demoralised ZZZzzzZZ...haiz mb come back and crap more ltr after my tution so cee ya guys after that....Chao!~~~  Yours Seascoutingly, Kenneth aka. Medicdog
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Campfire burning, Campfire burning. Draw nearer, Draw nearer..haha Tsunami SeaScouts first Campfire Zhai bo??&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Ernest, yiqi and Me!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
               Ahoy Mates!Today's Vesak Day although not a buddhist but parents kinda physcho mi to go out to pray with them...so bobian act guai guai go with them but turn out to be an enriching and memorable day fer mi too!!         Okei let me go back in time to this morning..hahaz...woke up by my dad around 9am then prepare to go to the temple(s)..first temple nothing much at Bukit Batok area...hehhe told my parents some excuse then went to the main canteen to enjoy some vegetarian morning breakfast..tot its going to suck but turns out its damn nice man!! hahaz make me change my perspection on vegeterian hahaz....aniway second temple at Joo Chiat Tembling Rd...so farrrr....hhaz MORE FOOD!! took my lunch here and did i mention the vegetarian curry was WOW!! man make me Orgas_...hahaz (S08 pplz you guys will knoe wad the heck i am toking bout!)After that listern to the Monk say his prayers to the crowd and then just slack around the place abit when my parents entertain themselves wif the guests...then saw some flag stuffs went forward to take a look and found out that its meant fer students to write their name so the monk can help ya chant fer better results hahahaz..tinking it wont hurt and my grades are already that bad i wrote my name on it(hehe! asking fer a miracle to come true huh?!)but then i also helped her to write her name on the flag too..just hope she could feel the result hahaz...After that tot its going to be home sweet home but my DAD said he wanna vist the temple featured on TV ytd...you guys knoe the five story buddha thg yada yada yada....          Went all the way from Joo Chiat to Sarangoon area...get off rthe car wow shocked of my life the temple ground is damn damn big man! Went to the new building that hse the 5story buddha wow its damn Big lohz! hahaz kinda belittled ahaz...then yes! saw this banner that NUH is having a blood donation Drive on the third level! hahaz finally can donate blood went up wif my dad to lvl3 and went fer the donation...kinda long the que but its worthwhile la...go in str8 got pplz gib us the forms to filled in..kinda sappy and corny forms la ask you qns like do you have sex with multiple partners and do you have sex with another man(for male donors) hahaz!...wanted to SABO my dad 1...coz he push the forms to me so i was tempted to tick the yes box fer Qn no2. Do you have Sex with another MAN? hahaz...imagine wads the expression on the receptionist when SHE saw this hahahaz!! but end up didnt lah kinda bad hahaz....aniwae waited and waited and waited until my turn for the ccheckup...kinda cool took my blood sample put into some red colour machine then out comes my blood grp and haemogobin lvl hhahaz...guess i am hyper todae lahz blood got so much the person pass me 3unfilled baggy fer my blood wow another shock hahaz....            After the tests came the real thing....Grin...sat down at hte chair-bed thingy annd here comes a nurse finding my vein to poke the needle in to numb me hahaz(tot of linkin park numb fer no reason so started to hymn the tune...hehe)tot the next needle fer the blood bag not going to be ani bigger lahz..WRONG! its damn thivk lohz hahaz but lucvky no pain just went in then blood start comming out..nurse pass me a orange sponge fish and ask me to squeese hahaz kinda played wif the thing instead hahaz...loser i knoe...Soon filled up the bag alreadi hahaz touch it ohh its warm hahaz....okei enuff lameing...then the nurse came again took out the needle, bag and stuff(actualli its kinda cool man..the way they poke the people and take out blood and stuff hahaz)after that ask me to stay there fer 10mins then can go le...came up walkked away then got some people offer MILO and crackers to me hahaz...good sat down and sip my wonderful milo and feel less "floaty" hahaz....here i am finally fufil my wish of donating blood hahaz ghoing to do that every mth now hahaz...kinda meaningful dont you tink?...then after my dad's done we walked out of the place...okei start of part2 of my story haha          When we walked out, saw a lady who just came out from donating too..kinda got the SEH feelin lohz can she going to PENG liaoz...and thhere suddenly she flopped on the floor FAINTED!! hahaz all i tink was to go over and help so i did...help the poor lady to lie on the floor and lifted her legs up to let the...blah blah blah(lets not go to the technical parts lahz you guys will bore to death wif the first aid thingums)after that the doctors came out and assisted her haha END of story! aha              Other than all these stuff..today is kinda fun man..did a few good deeds like a scout shld hehe and yeah feel good bout them! okei talked too much le going off fer dinner now catch my next exciting episode tml! same time same place! Tata!  Ps. Oh hahaz just to add a line more Wish My Eye-candy all the best in everithg she does and be happy always! God bless ya gal!  Yours Seascoutingly, Kenneth aka. Medicdog
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
            yeah yeah yeah this blog is crappy down to the last bit..hahaz but this is the best i can forge out for the fact that i am a html I-D-I-O-T...anyway just finish trying to make out all those html commands on the template thingy then realise that my blog so empty decided to write another "exciting" log of myself(Hope you guys don't bore yourselves to death)...anyway its 10.32pm now all thx to this blog thingy i miss my smallville2 also i am lazy to on the tube to catch it lahz hahaz..        More or less a usual tuesday nite wif my dad using my room as his gym and my mom hustling round the hse donno wad the heck for..hahaz...at leasdt one good thg my "Evil" sis is not home to snatch cilvilization from mi!!(haha TV, Comp, the toilet etc..).Chattin to "Supersan" now but mostly all crap lahz wad zai or not zai stuff and the usual "SEH" that i have copyright over..hahaz donno wad the heck i am toking bout huh? nvm keep it there coz its too lame you guys might as well eat ice rather than hear these lame cold jokes hahaz...         Don't seems to have ani good stuff to write on to make this entry intresting too....okei let mi tok bout my phathatic life in PJ now then...herm well landed my self into quite an intresting class wif intresting people(herm lets cee wad we have..Kampong Boy..Ba ding...juice...lao da Ben and Ashlesha and my twin bro! hah)teachers are quite okei lahz ..apart from halal pork which everi1 HATE! hehe.. work wise piling up day by day and dont seems to be able to clear test haiz dont mention failing everi1 of them...dont even tink i am going to be promoted man...CCAs..hahaz abit in a mess now..got caught btw TKD and hockey hahaz...since kwok dont wanna let mi into hockey man how sad can it be? the big block of meat just wanna deprive me of two years of fame and joy hahaz! coz PJ hockey is going to be legend man! don pray pray! hahaz somemore all my dudes are in hockey come to tink of it why did i choose tkd in pj in the first place when i already have it as a external thg?? ironic....              herm ccas....gals hahaz good stuff...gals in pj arz not too bad got quite a number of fine babes on campus hahaz..J2 and J1...haha but the best still come from 04S__ hahaz(for me to knoe for u to find out!) hahaz...man she is a super hottie and hell of a cutie man hahaz...tink guys drool over her hahaz...but too bad she's attached to some guy outta campus(this guy must be such a lucky dude huh?)..herm other than this eye candy didnt take much notice of other gals on campus..got a few good looking 1 but just cee cee forget forget hahaz...wad can i sae my eye-candy rox hahz....but got a few close calls too...when i am stealing some glances at her through her class and she look out and stuff hahaz...hahaz kinda act oblivious though to cover up...but come to tink of it i have spoken to her too hahaz..yeah that faithful day on sports day trainin hahaz she was runnin the same event as me hahaz manage to knoe her more and stuff thru another frend ha....then after than there were occasional waves and hi-byes and make my dae and stuff hahaz....but thgs got better on PPDay, hahaz went to support her class stall and stuff hahaz have a nice chat wif her too hahaz that was the dae man! hahaz           After that thgs more of less become normal...mb becoz it was here when i realise that she have a strong relationship wif her other half and come to be enlightened that its usless to bum around her or wad so i drop it hahaz...but easy said than done hehe come on can't blame it man she's some hot stuff hahaz!             Okei i guess thats enough crap fer the night hahaz seems to be drained of ani thoughts already..so signing off here! Free Gangway! Secure!  YOurs Seascoutingly, Kenneth aka. Medicdog
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
           AHOY MATES!haha kinda got inspired to blog after readin' other peeps blog hahaz...so end myself at blogspot.com hahaz...kinda lame for an answer but aniwae today been quite enjoyable other than attending some PW lecture tat bored me ending up ponning the lecture hehe...Oh yeah got all the way to Plaza Singapura wif some peeps from the class had lunch at Bk..all routinal stuff i guess then got tired and then back home...          Herm now slacking in front of the comp typing stuff bout myself and tinking of how "clever" i am to just fall down from the tupid chair a while ago..totally loser...waiting fer time to slip so i can watch smallville2 and ogle at kristen kurk aha...other than that its another normal tues i guess :)          Nothing much to say fer now so stick around fer more "exciting" episodes to come! Signing out!  Yours In scoutin', Kenneth aka. Medicdog :P          
     
    
</post>


</Blog>