<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hola... ok right now, it's 1215 am on wednesday the 30th of june. i'm totally pathetic because i can't sleep and i snuck out of bed to use the net so yeah, i'm crazy too....( the drama-mama is so going to get eyebags soon!) anyway, yesterday, the 29th of june, the queen went to school for drama rehearsal.( i mean, me )ms has busted me. when i reached school, she sms-ed to say that she's on MC. eddee, the usual bloke, went MIA. couldn't find him. stupid you-know-who went off without telling me with her pscyho-sttalker boyfriend!!! (B****) ( hee....)so there were only amirah, donna, charmer and myself. it was quite fun actually. we went to the AVA room where we practised singing. ( hell, we practised using songs NOT related to our musical! i'm going to be so screwed!) charmer and i had a ball of a time! (ball??!!!) ha ha ha! he sang several songs to me though.( ok, actually he sang several songs and looked  at me all the time. ) man! he's a BOY! a BOY!!! damn it.... he got kind of 'pissed' when he overheard me telling my donna that i met this cute leon. (????) then, for no rhyme or reason, he called keith something which i can't remember.( apparently, i only understand english...) ha ha ha! the funny thing is, i immediately laughed when he dedicated his next song to keith as a form of apology cause he thought i was pissed! so funny! he and i got into several mini 'verbal warfare' with one another and the wierd thing was, he wanted me to be there and listen to him sing hoobastank's "the reason". i couldn't ,of course, because  it was keith's theme song. (!!!) when i went outside, charmer didn't sing it.... that's really wierd.... i mean i'm not saying he likes me or anything! (oh please, i may be thick-skinned and dramatic but i'm not THAT thick or anything...) plus, i don't think we complement each other. there's no....chemistry. it's just a form of crazy, childish infatuation on my part.....(see, keith? now, you know how lonely i really am...) besides, my bestfriends know that i don't fall for boys! i'm crazy for intellectual and artistic men! (can't seem to find them, except keith....)  man, i better keep my hormones in check....the trouble with being born with oestrogen and progesterone...sigh.......... the good thing is, the male species can be so easily  manipulated and freaked out with them....hee hee.... all hail MOTHER NATURE!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, the drama-mama went for her poly orientation at nyp today. i met up with jia yi at the mrt station and went to school together. (okay, i misjudged the time and ended up an hour early.) we went to this extremely cold theatre of the arts for several boring talks. the only thing i enjoyed was the emcee who is a cute eurasian hottie named leon from molecular biotechnology... hee hee hee! the drama-mama went havoc with infactuations today!!! anyway, i got into the first class , CP0401, which is like a prison number!! grrr.... so low-class! i met my classmates for the first time today. out of 26 people, there are only 5 malay-muslims including myself. of these 5, 3 are malay boys and the other 2 consists of myself and this very religious girl named TRINAS. she's really sweet and sporty. we hit it off immediately. the three boys and i didn't start talking until we all went for lunch as a class at the north canteen. there,they finally plucked up enough courage to ask for my name and then,( gasp!) ask how i did my hair! (???) i mean, it seems the drama-queen's hair of many bundles has become a kind of conversational piece of sorts. when i said it's natural,they kind of like gasp and then some of the jap-inspired chinese girls in  my class who i didn't talk to previously, started making conversation with me....(see the power of food??) so, yeah, i enjoyed myself with my new classmates. but the one thing i can't stand were the same questions many people asked me: "are you singaporean?", "are you malay?","are you a eurasian?".... etc... i was posed these questions even in the toilets!! grr.... when i got home, i went online and saw liam. he's finally back from his hollywood sexually-provocative holiday! JERK!!! i chatted with him for a while before he passed the conversation to keith. keith asked about my orientation even though i didn't really remind him about it. he said he remembered it from the first time i told him about it. so sweet..... i told him about everything and also stupidly about the hottie, leon. stupid me!!!! he got really quiet and i could sense that he was unhappy and disappointed. i immediately regretted it and apologized. he accepted my apologies but i know him too well.... he is still feeling sore about it. he said he will try to come down after his musical. somehow, i have the feeling that he wants to come down to nyp and see for himself how i am doing in poly...(gasp) i can't make him do that. sometimes, the things he doesn't know about will really help to shield him from a lot of pain.... it's not that i will cheat on him or anything. i mean, he means a lot to me and i love him so much. i rather be hurt by him than to hurt him..... oh woe is me...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, the drama-mama haven't been able to write in for quite some time because APPARENTLY i was banned from the computer due to the fact that i was hooked for long periods of time. but never mind, all is well and the drama queen is back in full force today... yesterday, saturday june 26th, i went out with my mom and younger bro to parkway where they got pissed with me because they said that i took them on a long shopping trip without buying anything...grrr....it's not that i don't want to get anything, i just couldn't find anything i like! anyway, would you rather the queen get something she doesn't like and then get mad with the whole world?? grrr....(i can't get mad with them because i'm going out with them again today to get something...heeeeheeee) and on friday, the 25th of june, i had drama rehearsal at school at 10am. we had so much fun! unfortunately,charmer couldn't make it.(jeremy wen dropped by by the way and nobody cared...hee hee hee)then, at around 5 pm, we decided to go to the beach and film some shots of the characters. then charmer called me as we were making our way out of school and asked me to wait for him at the bus-stop because he was on his way...sigh.... so sweet....anyway, i did and when he came, charmer, donna, amirah and i took a cab to east coast beach... it was so sweet! i sat at the back with the girls and we were playing around....amirah was so cute! we reached the mcdonalds and met up with ms haslynda and eddee and yani. we went to get food and then had a picnic near the rocks... it was awesome! we didn't do much filming because APPARENTLY, it was getting too dark so we mainly lazed around on our picnic mat and watch the sun set. i spent some "QUALITY TIME ALONE" with eddee on the rocks. we chatted until about 830 before we joined the rest on the mat. so fun! we left the area at around 1015 and decided to get some ice-cream at mcdonalds. i sat near charmer and he got a sundae for me...:) we shared my sundae...(actually, all of us were helping ourselves to each other's ice-cream) his mom called to say she'll be picking him and amirah up. he asked me if i want a lift home and i stupidly said no. so in the end, i shared a cab with ms has... you should see that you-know-who's face. she got her psychotic stalker other-half with her anyway. overall, i had a great deal of fun with them although when i looked at the sea, i thought of sarah and sam and i guess, i miss them a lot. i wonder what they are doing now... hopefully sam's leg is getting better.... sarah should have stopped working at the hospital by now... bet she's enjoying the fact that she won't see sister yong by now!!! :) peace out!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, the drama-mama is a little sad today because firstly, my mom confiscated my credit card!!! she said i've spent farrrrrrr tooooooo muuuuuuuch!!! why??! sigh, now i'm at the mercy of my saving box which is,honestly, not very promising in weight.... secondly, i got a mail from keith and reading it makes me a victim of melancholy... (boo hooo hooooooo) sometimes, i really pity that poor boy. it's not fair that he has to feel so much pain and sadness being so far away from me. i mean,here i am in singapore laughing my pants off and there he is in SF all teary everytime he listens to Hoobastank's "the reason". (i should have never talked on and on about them...) honestly, i am very disappointed and sad that he can't be with me physically here. i mean, everytime i go and take a walk at the beach by myself, i will always find myself crying because i miss him and the walks we used to take. knowing from him and my friends that he's feeling shitty practically every day really eats at my heart. he wrote in his mail that "I drove to a lake a few days ago. It was beautiful with the calm waters and I even saw several ducks!!! Nearby there was this little kid,about 5, and he was playing with this model yacth...It was very scenic and I could imagine you and me with our little children living near the lake and playing with model toys and having so much fun.... Do you like my dream for the both of us? I believe if we hold on strong to this dream, we can make it come true for the both of us.... When everything is right, will you be willing to marry me, have our children and live together with me near a lake?" to tell the truth, i love this dream that he has conjured but i'm really scared i might not be able to be the one who will marry him, have his kids (???) and live with him by the lake.i know many people think it's still very early because we are both very young and such but somehow, it feels right and it feels perfect. no one knows this but if he were to propose to me now...(i mean NOW)...i will say "i do" without any hesitation. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i'm in so much deep shit now!! my drama folks are back from the uk and the charmer and i have not really completed our stuff!!! arrrrrgh! (this is what happens when you let hormones got to your head...) haslynda called and asked to meet me on monday.( i suppose she wants to check on the things i was supposed to do... wonder if i can fly off tmw and escape from confirmed hell??? ) charmer called to say "not to worry" because "i make sure you won't get scolded". what the hell??? he's a BOY! a BOY!!! men! where are you??? hee hee... come to think of it, men do come to my life at my worst times! keith sms-ed and we sent like about 48 sms-es to each other over a period of 1 hour!!! i'm so screwed... my mom will definitely flip if she sees my phone bill! (i really wonder if i can get an air ticket now...) in actuality, i didn't really regret the whole sms thing because i miss keith so much! (i'm not really into the mushy things other people like to share via sms-es) keith and i chatted about the usual life going-ons, our new friends and also about the latest things we've done. man, there are so many things i want to do with him... i miss the times we danced at his house,the reservoir and the botanical gardens... i really miss the times we sat at the beach and at the sides of that river outside the Esplanade, just holding hands and looking at each other... sigh... i really miss his smile! of course the only thing i hated about the 'conversation' i had with keith is when he kept asking whether i've been going out with ryan! what the hell??!! i know he hates ryan because ryan screwed tiffany but why can't he have confidence in me with this one? (i mean, honestly man, i can't imagine myself holding hands with ryan let alone doing it with him! yucks!) but it's just that ryan and i are friends and i can't possibly stop being friends with him just because he screwed (and dumped) my boyfriend's ex-girlfriend! come to think of it, i've never really like tiffany anyway. besides, everyone knows that tiffany agreed to do it with him. she only went bawling her eyes out to keith when ryan dumped her... BAH!!! (besides,who told her to be so clingy??) i don't understand why keith has to believe her! she must be a damn good actress...should have given her an oscar... ryan and i are just good friends and whenever we meet, we just talk and talk the whole time. no biggie. keith kept telling me to 'be careful'. i know he cares about me deeply but it's pretty irritating and when i called him (keith) "irritating", he gets all quiet and sad and moody. he may be taller,bigger and stronger than me but he can be quiet a baby sometimes... is it true that guys in love simply love to be mothered?? sigh...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yo! i'm a little jumpy today. my mom said i've caught the 'irritating virus' because i simply can't keep quiet and she was so pissed at me for singing in her face! ha ha! (when i'm happy, the whole world always want me to shut up...grrrrrr!) anyway, i was painting last night. couldn't sleep for nuts so i painted. the drama-mama is VEEEERRRRY versatile you know? heez...anyway, before that, i chatted with lord avon via sms till pretty late at night. (hope my mom won't see my bill!)  anyway, today just before i wrote in this blog thing, i read my e-mail and got a mail from liam. that KAMQUAT!! he's in hollywood now for his summer break! damn it, he's there enjoying his pants off while i'm stuck here.... plab... liam is enjoying himself there with his new girlfriend, rachel, from keith's class. idiot! he actually brought his new girlfriend to hollywood??!!!! (he's been in SF for only 6 months and rachel is already his 8th girlfriend! i'm betting $100 that he'll get a 9th one before school re-opens...)hee hee...anyway, they went to stay in a hotel there... in the same room... except that he stupidly agreed to her request for 2 single beds! i was laughing when i read his e-mail! ( bet he's kicking himself in the butt now. ) but i'm glad he had fun there with her although i wonder why he has to tell me about the christian dior bikini set she wore at the pool.... dude, he wrote like 3 paragraphs about it!!! that's what happens when you have horny friends like liam...grrr...)  p/s did he just said 'christian dior'??!!! crap! i've always wanted to get a Christian Dior bag...but mom thinks i have more bags and shoes than clothes...she won't allow me to get one!!! why???!!!! maybe i might sound my royal family....(hee hee...afterall my birthday is very near...)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, i'n back for 2nd post in a day. i did wrote in my profile that i simply luuuuuurve to talk...( for those who have been living under a rock all this while, please refer you rock-head to my profile...hee hee... it SO doesn't make sense!!) anyway, i simply have to write in the second time because i have so many things to talk about... ( the drama queen's life is never dull...trust me... it's so hard to breathe you know??) two people talked to me today. two cute people. one of them was keith and the was the one who always makes me smile... sigh.... let's call him the charmer shall we? ok, the charmer called me and we chatted for like 30 minutes before i had to hang up because APPARENTLY, my bladder refused to co-operate... grrrr....why did i use the toilet?? we talked about drama and joked a lot, so much in fact that my bro thought i was going cooookoooo...( that's how he spell cuckoo by the way.) charmer was really funny!!! he rapped on the phone for me too...basically eminem's song... i wasn't listening to the lyrics but rather his voice!! hee hee... i was swooning i tell you... anyway, when we hung up (and after i co-operated with my bladder) keith sms-ed and asked me to meet him online. he was using liam's account. that stooooopiddd liam left his password with keith so yeah, keith made FULL use of it... we chatted online and yes, i was so full of regret realizing that i've just allowed myself to be swept away by a boy... grrr.... i go for men... keith sent me a picture of a ring. he saw it at a jewelry shop in town. it was so damn pretty!!!! it was a white-gold ring with a pink diamond... something like a wedding ring... he asked if i liked it and when i said yes, he told me this : "i'd guessed you'll love it. i bought it for you by the way. " i tell you, i was so glad he couldn't see me because i was like a monkey behind the computer screen, jumping and squealing with joy! he said that when he can make it to singapore, he hope that he can put it on for me... sigh... i was a little worried about the commitment factor because i didn't want him to think that i've agreed to marry him. ( he proposed to me before he left... actually it's rather an engagement than a marriage but it's the same to the drama-mama....) i was smiling to myself when i went offline and come to think of it... i'm still smiling now.... :)
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok,ok... today, i might( i did say MIGHT ) be including two blogs because APPARENTLY, i've forgotten to  write in yesterday when there were so many actions!!!! grrrrrr......... firstly, yesterday the 13th, i went out with my royal family minus lord avon... (lord avon, don't forget our movie!) i mean, i went out with my queen-mother and my princess... princess and i had something to tell the QM. i guess perhaps, we shouldn't have told her becuase poor QM! she was pretty distraught... :( i really wanted to cry when i saw her cry because she doesn't deserve to be hurt by some low-class, butt-sniffing, d**k-headed person!!! GRRRRRR!!!!! but princess and i decided the night before that we should tell the QM because it concerned her and we shouldn't keep things from our bestfriends.... after that whole unhappiness thing, we went for lunch at Delifrance... as usual, i made a mess of my crab croissant... after that whole messy lunch, we went to princess' castle where we watched 'into the mirror'. to tell the truth, i was so freaked out that i was reading the magazines throughout the movie. i only looked up at the part where that bloke got sliced into half by the mirror and his eye got pierced by that mirror ( again ). well i did say in my profile that i love gory and morbid stuff..... i hope QM had a mirror of a time yesterday.(hee hee! no pun intended) i really hope she won't ever take into consideraton what those brain-less people have to say about her...IT'S SO BENEATH OUR DIGNITY,GIRLFRIEND... by the way, in the morning, which is on the 14th, i watched the match between england and france with my dad and two bros... (apparently mom was not interested after protugal got trashed.... by GREECE!!!) Viva Les Bleus and all hail Zinedine Zidane!!! woooo hooooo!!!! ha ha ha...the london eye got trashed by the eiffel tower 2-1!!!!! ha ha ha ha!!! the french were so smooth as usual...now it's really true that french guys are so sexy and smoooooooth..... yummy!!! dad became the drama-papa that morning...kept grumbling about england's performance....like helloooo..... I'M THE DRAMA-MAMA in the house...gonna bring the house down by rubbing the 2-0 victory in his face....life's awesome... p/s that mirror movie made me lose sleep last night... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yo wassup?? ok, just 15 minutes ago, when i checked my e-mail, i found that my ex, shoninura yokonamatisuka just e-mailed me!!!! (i now know why he hates his name...if i have to type it in full again, i swear i might throw my keyboard out the window...) that bloke! i didn't know he still remembers me!! kamquat! he e-mailed a new pic of him and his family living the cold 'wretched' life in london...you gotta admit man, the weather in london can piss you off in the long run...yeah, he became whiter but hee hee, more buffed up!!! yes....to those who knows how woozy i can get....yes, HE'S DAMN HOT!!! damn! almost all my exes become cuter after that...(wonder why...) hey, i did say ALMOST...well, there are two people who look even worse now...ok, i'll change that...3 of them took it pretty badly after i left...ha ha ha! i can be so evil at times... i like... the whole family is making progress with the 'i'm miserably sick' bug. mom and dad are almost back to their normal body temp but i realize they are purposely trying to sound sick so that i will be their 'slave' for another day...grrr...  i got a mail from kieran today. i know he reads my blog so i'm not going to cover up whatever i'm going to say. i don't know whether i'm avoiding him. (thank god, i didn't tell keith about my blog!)i guess, i'm just not ready to face him yet. i know how much keith means to him and i know that keith means a great deal to me too...i guess, i'm really uncomfortable keeping my secret with kieran from keith...kie, youshould understand that i'm not doing this on purpose...i don't even know what i'm doing now or whether, i really am doing something... i'm sorry but you and keith are very important to me,just the way liam,my bestfriends and family are to me... i'm stuck in a rut now...i cannot hurt any of you but then again, to free myself of this pain, i might have to hurt either one of you, which i'll never... please promise this kie, promise that you'll never mention this to keith!! PLEASE!!! let me be the one to hold on to this secret! you guys have always been the ones to keep all bad news from me... please let me be the one to shield you guys from the pain just this once!!! it hurts a lot when secrets burden but if to keep your loved ones safe and happy, it's worth going through the pain...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok, first of all, i don't know why i DIDN'T include my blog for yesterday!!! why in the name of oily fries did i forget??? grrr...anyway, the drama-mama went to my class' barbecue organized by my princess, sarah. i went early because APPARENTLY, i'd realized that i would choke if i were to meet the rest. anyway, met a couple of people whom i'm KINDA okay with so yeah, no biggie... on my way home, i HAPPENED to meet some people and i swear man, i almost puked on my way to the bus!!! yucks!!! hate my life then...but again, i boarded a bus and at the tanah-merah bus-stop,(again) a cute guy boarded the bus and sat beside me.... hee hee hee.... riding on the bus never felt so damn good.... secondly, i've talked to keith and yeah, we're over the whole sharon-the-bitch-just-cannot-keep-her-clothes-on-and-stop-herself-from-attacking-people's-boyfriends thing. i mean, i have to  chill you know? there's no point getting all pissed over these kind of people... it's so beneath-my-dignity...plab... thirdly, i became my family's chaperone to the doctor's today.APPARENTLY, the entire family went down the sick tube and i had to be the unlucky one to take care of them. trust me, they are all over the age of 15 and can be such a pain when they are sick!! they owe me big time.... hee hee... oh yes, the particlar someone called me many times today and we chatted a lot about drama and such.... oh life!!! you're so unfair! why must you tempt me with boys??? i go for men, not boys!!! breathe....breathe....breathe.... i'm so in love with hoobastank's "the reason".... the song is so sexy!!! uh huh...yummy.... ok,ok...i have to control the whole writing thing...cannot type so much. my fingers hurt from all the housework i had to do just because my whole family WENT SICK AT THE SAME TIME!!!grr....it's a mess by the way. i mean, asking the QUEEN to do house work??? i don't even wash my plates man.... the world's gone crazy... peace ...V
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Being a drama-mama sucks at times. you see, drama-mamas are kinda expected to be on the 'crazy' and 'pathetic' mood almost all the time.( please ah... we're no dumb blondes... to all my blonde friends,no pun intended.) drama-mamas have mood swings too. i had drama rehearsal today. after today, i have a 9-day break while some of my drama folks enjoy their pants off in the UK!! KAMQUATS!!! apparently, there's this girl (let's call her you-know-who) who is APPARENTLY a permanent resident under a rock. she is like so fucking proud of the fact that she's going!! what the hell??? dude, i've been there man... big deal!! anyway, a certain someone had mood-swings today... he might have a girlfriend apparently.... tooooooooooopiddddddddddddd.....  got to find a lot of bad news today. APPARENTLY, today is called 'DOWN WITH THE DRAMA-MAMA'. keith won't be coming down to singapore until christmas!!! WHY???!!!! sometimes, i really feel like i have no boyfriend at all... it seems like i'm only attached by name. i haven't seen him in months!!! i miss him so damn much... you know, i really trust him but i'm scared that i might let him down... help the DRAMA-MAMA please....   p/s i think i will start the " Save the Drama-mama " Foundation soon...  i must be crazy... see what all those crappy music have done to me??? 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today, the Queen got to know something really sad today. during drama, (as usual) keith called . i picked his call and what he said to me was so depressing that i had to will myself not to cry in front of my drama folks. he went to a classmate's party. they had booze but he didn't drink anything other than soda. he stayed mostly in a bedroom where he spent the time surfing the net on his pal's com instead of partying with the rest downstairs. he said half-way, he heard the door being opened and when he turned to see, his other classmate, a bitch named Sharon, entered the room. he realized that she had had a couple of drinks. before he knew it, she closed the door, removed her top, pushed him to the bed and began kissing him and touching him! fucking bitch!! she wasn't wearing any top other than her bra!! FUCKING BITCH, WHORE, ASSHOLE!!!!!! he told me that he pushed her away and went out of the room. he then went home and called me from his car.he cried and said that he misses me so much. i love him very much but somehow,i feel like we've been apart for so long, i don't know whether i can trust him. this bitch is shapely and very hot 'cause i saw her picture before.HOW DARE SHE!! HOPE SHE WILL FUCKING GO TO HELL!!! i mean, how can a normal guy not get turned on by her? Fuck man!! Fuck the fact that i can't be with him physically. Fuck the fact that I can't punch the bloody bitch in the face and Fuck the fact that i actually am beginning to have doubts about my own boyfriend... the whole world is so screwed! i miss him so much... i don't know what to do. liam told me to trust keith because he said that keith loves me very much and that he will never hurt me. kieran said that the fact that keith actually called and told me showed just how much i mean to him and how much he loves me... i don't know... i'm so FUCKING TIRED... SCREW IT.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today, i went out with the queen-mother. she came for my drama rehearsal and it was really cool 'cause the drama-mama really misses her a lot!! we lunched at parkway (again) and after that took the bus 14 home. apparently, when the bus reached that ARMY BUS-STOP, three army guys boarded the bus. trust me, they are SO NOT CUTE and one of them, apparently the obvious loser actually had the gall to sound so cool!!! WHAT THE?? and trust me when i say that he's NOT THAT INTELLIGENT. he had this squeaky voice and a sonofabitch character and he actually talked to his dude/loser friends about his girlfriend whom he SUPPOSEDLY dumped... come on man, once a loser, always a loser. nothing's gonna change...   anyway, drama rehearsal was cool. yeah, the queen's hormones went havoc again and just knowing that i will be hanging out with that person over the holidays makes me all woozy with excitement!! trust me...he's THAT CUTE AND CHARMING!! true, even though the drama queen does not date boys, only men, sometimes, we have to make exceptions in life, you know...hee hee...  okay, now here comes the sad part... keith won't be able to come down to singapore anytime soon. he's busy in college and besides, i think that to make him fly down here to see me will be a great injustice to him... shit man!   by the way, ronnie will be leaving singapore soon! will miss him so much. after his NS, he will be going overseas... oh man! i'll miss him... he's still the best bro i can ever ask for , with the exception of kyle ,of course!  by the way, it seems that i really have to control what i say in public because apparently, my mom once said that i can get killed in public whenever i speak! hahaha! it was so funny looking at how PATHETIC singaporeans can get. i mean i'm REALLY PROUD to be singaporean but i really have been swallowed into the world of FREEDOM OF SPEECH, EXPRESSION AND THINKING.(freedom of SET.)i think it's important to let our ideas through without buttering up our words just because we are afraid to offend ppl. please man, have a backbone! thank god i've been telling all my drama ppl about the importance of freedom of SET. the only setback is that after that, all the profanities and gestures starts to fly.. then again, that's what makes drama DRAMA... hee hee! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today, the drama-mama learnt how to use this blog thing for the first time from my best friend, sam... apparently, i am completely lost in the " wonderful world " of the internet... all this because i have two brothers who chased me away from the computer every time i wanted to learn the way to the hi-tech and savvy nirvana... KAMQUATS TO THE BROTHERS!!! they are so genetically irritating i have to salute the fact that they actually have girls asking for their numbers... just WHERE is the love man??  the drama-mama went for drama rehearsal today.( of course!! where else can she go??)it was awesome but apparently i got so pissed with a particular someone who sometimes sent my hormones raging with the smile... aarrgh!!! no, the drama queen goes for real men NOT boys... yes lilah, breathe.... good girl!! anyway, today was wonderful and come to think of it... why in the world am i typing so much in this thing??? i think i can talk even more about today... man! i really ought to shut up for at least 5 minutes... sometimes i talk too much, i don't even know whether i make sense! RELAX, GIRLFRIEND... breathe... yeah! and by the way, the weather's gone crazy.....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      the drama-mama woke up this morning in cold sweat. so un-glam! i had a terrible nightmare. i saw myself in a crash-racing circuit. i was in the stands with keith and liam kong. halfway, i said that i need to use the bathroom. keith offered to take me there. we were walking for like a good 2 hours before we reached the bathroom.we had so much fun talking on our way there and coupled with all the hand-holding we did, it felt like floating on pink clouds!! (ok babe, you have to breathe... this is serious stuff... breathe in...breathe out...) upon entering the bathroom i was shocked to find it wasn't a bathroom but rather the ROM!!! ( for the love of wonder, i've never been to the ACTUAL ROM but in my dream, the ambiguous letters were there, smacked in front of my face.)before i knew it, keith had already slipped a ring on my finger( a big rock i tell you.) and then i don't know where it came from, we kissed and walked out...then when i realized that we were married, i threw the ring at keith(can you believe i actually threw a rock-sized ring away??) and pushed him away before running off.  now, i believe many ppl wouldn't understand what was so scary about the dream. yes,honestly, the throwing away of the ring was SCARY but the scariest thing was the fact that i actually married keith. ok, not everyone knows the real relationship i have with keith and the conflicts running through my mind so yes, i'm clarifying it. i need to lessen the burden forming within me... please tell me what to do...  i love keith. very much. and i know that keith loves me very much too, in fact i believe he loves me more than i love him. but there's no way i can be with him forever no matter how much i want to. we've gotten too close and too serious with one another that now, i find it so hard to set him free. i don't find him suffocating but it's just that i feel he deserves someone better than me. he's so perfect... he's in the states now and i have had a long time to think aboutit and everytime i do, i realize that i love him too much. he's an only child, an only son. and he's catholic. i have no qualms about different religions but it's just that i don't think i have the right to take a son away from his parents who have so much hope in him. even though his parents are awesome to me and have accepted me, even though i know keith will give up everything for me, i can't allow him to.  i really want him to be happy. now, he's all alone without me in the states. our friend, liam always tells me that keith doesn't go to college parties, he doesn't mix around with girls and every night, he will sit by his pool and cry silently as he holds our rings in his hand. he cries because he misses me. throughout out relationship, he has always been the strong one. he shouldn't be made to cry at night all alone. he shouldn't be made to isolate himself from girls. he shouldn't be made to do all this because of me because he deserves so much more than these...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       peace out, a-town!   ha ha! i'm really happy today! it's confirmed!!! (no, i'm not pregnant!) i aced my auditions! i'm now a member of my school's stagearts!!! hahaha! i have a lot of people to thank....my mom,my dad( hell, my entire family) and of course, my bestfriends, sameera and sarah! without their help and support, i know i will never be able to cope on my own....i'm very pampered you know? (see larr....my bestfriends pampered me way tooooooo much.....)   i'm having my engineering math common test next wednesday. i'm absolutely freaked out 'cause firstly, i totally suck at math. secondly, i can't fail this module or else, i'm screwed.   things with keith and me are okay. we are back again. when we fought, he hung up and refused to talk to anyone. he then went driving off to some god-forsaken place! he made everyone worried, especially me. you see, once when he went driving off alone after i fought with him, he was involved in a small accident. his car was slighlty damaged and he had to pay a fine for speeding....i was so scared it will happen again but thank god it didn't! he will be sitting for his equivalency papers soon. if he pass, he will have a confirmed scholarship to university. that means he will be the youngest kid there since he will skip 2 years of college....   i'm really happy for him!!! :)   i will be going for my ccss drama rehearsal tomorrow. can't wait! i think my drama folks are definitely DEPRIVED!! poor people man... take&nbsp;charmer and fit for example. there was this time we were all backstage and they were like 'fucking' almost all the things there! seriously!! then we have this young kid who all of a sudden, became very knowledgeable about sex.... he actually told me about the different kinds of positions!!! what the hell man....that girl-under-the-rock was initially trying to be innocent but it didn't work man!!! SUCKER!!!!   my life is actually pretty cool after all....   okay not that cool considering the fact that there's this sonofabitch in my class who piss me off simply being there....yucks man! he resemble someone from my former class in ccss....bloody hell! he goes to school in slippers, sleeveless shirts and shorts??!!! what the fuck? and he's so fucking rude! i SO can't stand him... he criticize everything and everyone straight to their faces. but wierdly he hasn't critisize me yet. i mean, he better not try to because if he does, i swear i'm going to piss the fucking pants of him!!!&nbsp; eeeeeeee.......... so low.....   peace! I AM THE DRAMA QUEEN... i will never sink to his level....   
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      okay, have you ever receive attention that you thought you never wanted before but then suddenly, you feel very flattered by it?? well i have and yes, i know i'm getting a little thick-skinned here....what's the deal? anyway, i have this friend, ryan. well...hell, from the day i met keith, my membership in the 'good friend's company' increased tremendously!  that does not include bestfriends. i mean i have bestfriends but no good friends till i met keith....(that's so beside the point.)where was i? oh yes,  today, after school, i was supposed to meet my ccss drama folk for rehearsal but apparently the fella-who-live-under-a-rock went missing...(grr) so ms has cancelled the rehearsal and scheduled it for saturday. (these drama folks of mine are so prima-dona! we have less than 3 weeks and they are still not flustered...damn! how did they do it??)so i called ryan and asked him about his life. heard he's currently on his 39th girlfriend in less than two years in singpore. (i don't know why i click with playboys...  sigh!) he asked to meet me at raffles city. he said he needed my help to buy something for a girl.i agreed and when i reached there, he saw me and gave me a hug. (i mean, it's just a greeting, no biggie) then i realized that there's this group of malay mothers and they were shooting visual daggers at me, man! what only...i don't know why, but everytime i go out with my caucasian friends, the malay community immediately look at me as if i'm hanging out with the devil! BLOODY KAMQUATS! anyway, i didn't care and ryan and i actually had a blast! he carried my notes for me, kept pulling at my hand,(??) and we had tea and cakes at the green tea tea-house there... then we came across this jewelry shop. i can't remember the name because APPARENTLY, the drama-mama only remembers the prices of jewelry....heehee! i'm such a bitch...anyway, ryan and i had this conversation:  ryan:hey, which one do you like? me:i like that ring...the design's fantastic and unique! ryan:okay.here, try it on! me:for what? i'm not buying it.... ryan:of course you're not getting it! i'm buying it. me:dude, my ring size is defintely smaller than your girlfriend's... ryan:i'm not getting the ring for her! i'm getting it for you! so, at this point, ryan and i had a slight argument. i don't like guys buying rings for me. i feel so wierd...plus the ring cost $850.90. he's such an asshole...anyway, he drove me home though...minus the whole ring disaster, everything was perfect... i don't know. i guess ryan's very charming. i mean, it's not i like him or anything! god, no! he's just such a sweet fella that it makes you want to forgive the fact that he's such a playboy. i wanted to tell keith about him but i'm kind of scared because keith hates ryan because of the bloody bitch, tiffany! keith is forever thinking that ryan will do to me what he did to tiff...what the?! for the record, everyone knows that tiffany was the one who made the move on him.she was the one who wanted to do it with ryan. and when ryan dumped her because she was too clingy, she went crying to keith that ryan used her! what an actress... i like ryan. he's a fantastic friend! so chilled out and cool! i know keith cares deeply for me but i don't want to stop being friends with ryan...now that's wierd...stuck between your boyfriend and the person he hates like hell..
       
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yo yo!! okay, the drama-queen haven't been writing for long.... it's so not my fault because firstly i'm like so busy with school right now... can you believe it?! we already have a semestral project and it's only the second week in school! grr!!! secondly, i'm so busy with ryan now. he's such an asshole but a cute and funny one at that. he's so irritating! he kept asking me out for coffee and cakes that i think i have gained weight! (gasp) oh no! the drama-queen so needs to go on a diet now.... hee hee hee....the funny thing is, my new peeps are so fascinated with my hair and my feet! so wierd... they said that my size 4 feet is so eye-catching....hmmm...whatever makes them happy! anyway, i'm finding it a little wierd being in poly right now. we have no homework. according to the lecturers, it's up to us if we want to do the tutorial questons! so wierd... no one collects the homework and nobody cares! the one thing i find so hilarious about my class is that we managed to psycho almost all our lecturers to let us off earlier than the stipulated time every day! you should see the rest of the students... they were so shocked and envious!! so fun! keith and i are having a silent war right now. okay, I'M HAVING THE SILENT WAR WITH HIM... i don't know anymore... boo hoo hoo hooo!!!! damn it!  ryan is calling again. i have the stupid feeling that he wants me to come down to his house and try his latest dishes again...oh man... i'm going to be sick! the last time i tried his 'french cuisine' i suggested eating maggie instead.... hell, no matter what, i have to admit... he's a better cook than me!i don't even cook man... the other time i wanted to boil some water using the electric kettle, i almost electrocuted myself..... and that's not a nice feeling....
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      damn! i cried a lot today. no, it wasn't because of my first day in school. my first day was cool. i hung out with the guys in my class and also with tris of course! we went all over the campus looking for a not-so-full canteen. it was fun and yeah, i had my first lessons today. first day in engineering math class and the lecturer gave us homework : 5 exercises, which is almost 20 questions....drats! the funny thing is, we don't even have the textbook!!! i met my new organic chem lecturer. he's canadian and very funny!! okay, knowing my penchant for intelligent and older man, yes, i fell so hopelessly in love!! hee hee! we were supposed to have lab work for 2 hours but he let us off after just 30 mins! you should see the looks on the faces of the other people having lab... they were like " what the fuck?? " ha ha ha! come to think of it, i might just have gotten hold to doing things independently... growing up is okay after all...  now the sad part.... :(  i don't know what happened to me today. i cried a lot, even in school. i sms-ed keith during lectures and almost cried. i called keith in the toilet and cried. i called keith on my way home and cried. i called keith at home and cried. i read his latest e-mail that he sent me and i cried too.... somehow, i miss him more today than the previous days that have passed. just before writing this blog, i called keith and i cried again... i just couldn't stop myself from feeling like that. i miss him so much! i really want to see him again... oh shit, now i'm crying again.... i don't think i'm strong enough. i guess i've fallen too deeply in love with him. all those times i told myself that i cannot love him anymore, i lied. all those times i told him i don't want to see him again, i lied. all those times i has crushes and infatuations on other guys, i lied. i lied because i was hoping i could forget him and make him forget me.... now the truth is overwhelming me.... i can no longer lie because i realize that he's always there deep in my heart... it's so painful to fall in love with someone and yet not being able to see him. i may look so happy and cheerful all the time but nobody knows of the pain and sorrow i'm carrying inside me. i feel so suffocated and i don't feel like doing anything else because all i want is to hug keith and have him hold me close to him, stroke my hair and tell me that i'm good and that i'm going to be okay... i can't stop the tears from falling... the pain is encumbering me and the smiling facade can no longer mask how i really feel inside... i'm so scared i'll let go... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      stupid liam! raised my hopes for nothing. the drama-queen is so pissed right now that i'm threatening to eat my bro's head...(calm down girlfriend, breathe...) chatted with him online and toward the end, he said this : " oh yeah, babe, keith ain't coming." i'm like "WHAT THE HELL??!!" he said that keith couldn't make it because his musical is on the same day as my birthday and that after the musical, he will have to go for his summer project at a treatment centre... keith never even went to book an air-ticket!! bloody liam! i swear, he better not come down 'cause i WILL rip his head off!! keith called to say that he's sorry he can't be there for my birthday. i said i didn't mind though i know my lie sucked because he saw through it. he sang me a birthday song on the phone and we talked for almost an hour and a half before i realize that my mom is so going to kill me. i hung up and cried on my bed... it's so sad, you know.... i chatted with my queen mother online. i feel like i've not really done my duty as a bestfriend. poor sam! she went through so much and i wasn't even there to hold her hand as she related her predicament. sigh.... i feel so guilty.... she will be having her exam on my birthday. since i believe in the notion that birthday wishes do come true, (don't laugh at me...i'm just a kid) i will pray that peace and joy will come to her and that she will go through her exam with peace and love from GOD... sam, i'm so sorry i wasn't there physically there for you during your tough times, girlfriend... i chatted with sarah online too... she sounded okay though IT IS the wonderful world of the internet...you can lie your way through the net and nobody knows... okay, i've decided. from now on, i will devote more time to my girlfriends. for my family,well.... they do take up the rest of my eveing.... ugh.... i'm so hungry now.... my mom cooked seafood and i can't even eat them...! will try my patented sad look on my bro and see if he'll cook maggie for me...if nothing works, there's still the money bribes... i'm so good at this... i'm now the official TAI-TAI...be prepared everyone...
       
    
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wassup????? the drama-mama is very happy today because......... i heard from liam that keith might be coming down to singapore to surprise me for my birthday!!!! ( surprise!) okay, so it's not a surprise afterall..... STUPID LIAM!! ruin my surprise.....grrrrr...... but never mind! the drama-queen is fantastic at looking surprised and delighted.... it's my forte! hee hee hee! oh my god! i really hope he will come down! i miss him so much. i tell you, if he were to ask me if i want to go back with him, i will definitely say 'yes'! better go and pack my bags now. (i'm going crazy again.... not even sure if he's coming down anyway. but never mind. being crazy is also one of my forte!) so my school's official starting day is this monday, the 5th of july. from that day onwards, i will be a grown person. a grown woman by my own rights. i have to finally answer for my own actions and also accept the consequences. my days of heavy partying will soon be over.(WHY???!!!!) life's not fair! anyway, i have roughly 3 years to study hard, get my As and go to university. shoot! 3 years?? i have a problem actually. you see, i don't think i want to study in singapore anymore. i know my parents want me to study near home because they don't trust me if i were to go overseas and stay on my own. (grr) but i feel like i no longer want to stay here. don't get me wrong. i'm still a proud singaporean. i love my country but i just feel and know that i will be happier somewhere else..... hell.... i haven't even started poly officially yet! okay, scrap the part about me having to stop partying. there's no way in hell am i ever going to stop partying.... it's time.......to .......get the party started!!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       woohoo!! national day's tomorrow!!! ok ok... as the self-declared drama mama and fashion guru... (i love my bitchy side!) i hereby wish the best for my country forever and may that bushy&nbsp;leadership come up with something good in the future...hee hee...." and i'm proud to be a singaporean, at least i know i'm free... "   man, the drama queen simply loves national day though i hate the idea of having to go through a crowd of people wearing red and white!! grr... so suffocating! like hello??? YOU'RE LIKE INSULTING THE FASHION GURU HERE?? my goodness! i'm so irritating! i know myself, thank you very much!   ok ok... i can't really write a lot today.. no, it's not because i'm lazy...(like hello??/ me? lazy??) i have to party.....why do you think i'm the drama queen/ tai-tai/ self-declared fashion guru/ party animal???    BECAUSE.... I AM...    &nbsp;  LET'S GET THE NIGHT MOVING........    &nbsp;  PEACE OUT.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       i know... i know.... i haven't been blogging for one hell of a long time... can't help it you know? i mean, the queen's like...so busy in school. my tutorial questions from chemical engineering principles are killing me. damn... never have the queen get all loony and pissed over some physics-like questions...( mr anwar, i am so sorry for not always paying attention to you.) eeee...... boo to physics!   my life in poly is pretty cool.. i have had a lot of fun but i miss sam and sarah every day... :( hey, the queen's so lonely.... i mean i do have a lot of friends there but nothing beats having your bestfriends by your side!!   i have had lots of happy things going on for me! first of all... I GOT INTO STAGEARTS!!! i'm so happy... okay, i have to brag a little so bear with me... " HOW CAN I, THE EVER TALENTED QUEEN, NOT GET INTO THE SOCIETY?? " ha ha ha! i know i sound like a bitch but hey, everyone's a bitch at one point or another... i just let my side show pretty obviously... hee hee.... the drama -mama is back at work in full force again....   i'm still having withdrawal symptoms...no, the drama queen is not doing drugs.( what? you think i'd stoop so low?? geez...thanks a lot) no, i had the withdrawal symptoms since i left the dior boutique without buying THAT bag!!! boo hoo hoo!!! it's so adorable. when i was in there with ryan and stef, the bag was like " come, lilah, come... get me... i'm all yours..." sigh... my credit card was like lying in my hands and saying " come lilah, use me, use me, use me!!!" (man, i sound so looney and dysfunctional...eee....so scary) i nearly bought the bag when my mom's voice came to my head.." bone,(?!) if you ever use your card to get something so expensive, you can forget about having any money ever again" grr.... so yeah, she woke me up. i walked out of the boutique and since then, the symptoms never go away... oh save me! my heart is breaking....   p/s ryan and i are good friends again. we had a long (very long) talk and he talked to keith too... though keith still refers to ryan as the bastard and still cannot trust him, he has allowed me to chill with ryan as long as i tell him. cool huh??   i went back to school on the 31st of july for speech day and it was fantastic. i took like 71 pictures ( i think) and they all turned out goooooood.... i took a shot with charmer but that scrawny yi hong had to sneak into the photo as well... grr... i had shots with my drama folks too... eddee had his arms around me in every photo. ha ha ha so funny! i got a plaque for my distinctions and i was so proud when mom and dad place it in the living&nbsp;room so that everyone can see it...sigh... the whole event was very fruitful. i feel like i've finally graduated from chai chee... it's so sad... but then again, ties will never be broken as long as we persevere to preserve it... oh no... the drama-mama's eyes are wet!!! see lar.... my emotions and hormones are going haywire again....crap man.....   
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>