<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When you don't have a "Jumper-In-The-Door", it's good to have an  urlLink alternative  to immediate humor.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...it's just more funny that way. This is one crazy-ass  urlLink Kikkoman Soy Sauce  advertisement. (It is worth watching to see the hanging cat and Super-Kikkoman Soy-Sauce-Man in bed with a lovely lady.)
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As stupid as  urlLink this website  is, I understand the sentiment.   This one works on so many levels.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...FROM BEYOND THE GRAVE!!!! (OOOOOWEEEEEEEOOOOOOOOO!)  urlLink Herve Villechaize  with some up-in-your-face words for all of us to live by.   Word up, yo.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Here  you shall find an amazing bluegrass version of a medley of songs penned by "Radiohead" (performed by "Rodeohead").  What? You never heard of "Radiohead"!?! BAH!! Why do I waste my time...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I find  urlLink this  more irritating than relaxing.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seasame Street had R.E.M. but Pancake Mountain Has  urlLink Ian Mackaye  from Fugazi. I was born too soon...
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "...at mile 11 and cresting the second big hill headed for fourth place overall at the second annual San Juan Island Half Marathon, Sunday, June 6th, 2004   Nice overcast day, 62F   M ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ 13.1 miles one Hammer Gel 30 ounces of Gatorade   01:28.27 (PR)"    Show off.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went in the downstairs bar to check on The Yuri.  "G.", seated at the bar, was the only customer in the room. The report of Ronald Reagans death was on the television. G. was breaking an old bar rule by talking about one of two things you should  never  talk about in a bar: politics (religion is the other). The Yuri was standing behind the bar,  listening, every once in a while making a non-committal sound like, "Mmmm", or," Hmff", or, "Snaff". I sidled up to listen.  G. said: " Sure it came at the expense of a trillion dollars of taxpayer money but Europe would not be enjoying the freedom it has today without Reagan's brilliance in bankrupting the Soviet Union by forcing them to keep up with our own military spending ."  Oh my freaking God.  While G. yapped on, The Yuri walked down to the far end of the bar and knelt down out of G.'s line of sight. Pretending to be looking for a bottle of something, he looked up at me, moving his fist near his mouth, poking his cheek out with his tongue.   Ah...The Yuri. The Great Sage. He nailed it once again.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is the new trailer for  urlLink "Fahrenheit 9/11" .
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A noon phone call from K: "I want to go out tonight." "O.K." A quick check on-line and...shazzam!  urlLink Pedro the Lion  and  urlLink John Vanderslice  at The Bottom of the Hill. I took K. to see PTL during early courting so why not again.  At the show, Corona for me and a (strong) 'rita for K.   "At least you are not the oldest guy here tonight," she said, nodding toward J.V.s' keyboard/guitar/noise player. He was a small guy with a sailor’s beard (short and thick, nothing on the upper lip), small glasses and a black watch cap. "No way. That guy can't be over 30." "Maybe. Well...what about that guy?" She pointed out a guy who was, yes, much older than I. He looked as if he had some previously bad days. Many, in a row. "Whatever", I said.  J.V. hit the stage. He looked just like a friend I had in grade school. We drifted apart in High School but our mothers were still close. I remember the phone call a few days before Christmas one year informing us that he had accidentally killed himself by injecting lighter fluid. He was sixteen. I hadn't thought of him in quite some time but was reminded of him when I saw J.V.s' bleach blonde hair and narrow face.  J.V. was quite good. Nice songs, good breaks.   K. forgot her earplugs so we stepped back to the bar to fetch some and watch the last of his set. (Another (strong) 'rita for K.)   I went back to the restroom and when I came out, the guy with the sailor beard was standing nearby talking to someone. He was a pretty small guy and, on closer inspection, I can comfortably say that he was much younger than I. I stood by for a second to see if K. would come up. I wanted us both to approach him and have him officially settle the bet by asking him to show us some I.D. but I noticed K. across the hall so the mystery remains.  PTL started off rough with a few missed notes here and there but, overall, still a nice tight band. After about five songs, singer/songwriter David Bazan asked the audience if there were any questions. He has done that at every show I have seen. It is usually pretty funny. The questions tonight ranged from, "What are you going to do after the tour", to, "What do you think of Kierkegaard?" But my favorite:   "Are you disappointed by the news of the breakup of 'Phish', and are you concerned that their fans may overtake your future shows?"  Bazan repeated the question slowly for the audience who collectively snickered. "Um...no, and...um...I am going to have to say...um...no".  Their set was good and the familiar songs were just that with the crowd politley cheering for them when the first bars of any of them were played. The new songs were fair but not great and the poor sound on Bazans vocals didn't help much but again the fans were pleased.  At one point during PTLs' set, K. turned to me and said, "This may sound like drunk talk but...I wish they were our friends, you know?"  Yes, I do know.  We were too tired to stay for the encore. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I find motivational posters insulting. Apparently, I'm not the only one...   urlLink www.despair.com   I think  urlLink "Get To Work"  is my favorite.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Yuri has done his part by creating this great bumpersticker. I think he is selling them and if anybody needs one  urlLink let him know .     Nice job, Yuri.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a large painting that I finished right after college.    In Andy's words (via e-mail): "The shots pretty much tell all.  We were drunk and the painting was the topic."        I am sure Tequila was involved.  (Thanks Andy) 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a card sent to K. From a friend in New Zealand.   Two words: Atkins Diet.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink It's another great McSweeney's List! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Dancing boobies!!!   (WTF!?!)  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a great obit of an amazing woman (if only just for the last line).   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...How about a death metal band with a parrot for a lead vocalist? Check out  urlLink "HATEBEAK" ! As their label says, "How completely and stupidly brilliant!" I couldn't agree more.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Poor kitty. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Monkeys. Road Rage. Bribes. What more could you want?  urlLink TRUNK MONKEY! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This guy gave his (evil) cat an enema due to constipation (the cats, that is) and  urlLink wrote about it with little pictures .   Poor Fred.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This  is pretty cool. The computer is smarter than you might think. It caught me thinking of "tequila" and "Great White Sharks".  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...sneak into your friends house and   urlLink do this  to their cat. Laughs all around!   (...something they fail to mention in your Mini Cooper's driver manual.)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's play  urlLink "Hipster Bingo!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Let's play Rock, Paper, Scissors...with Saddam!!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There was an antique boat show at the club last week. K. and I walked past this one. "I like this one," I said. "It's even named after you," she said.   I told her that I didn't think that was particularly funny.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>