<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay, i have just a few minutes before morgan calls and says that they're on their way over to pick me up. the trashmen and the trashtruck are outside picking up trashcans. i never realized how noisy they were.  well, megan, i hope that you're having an excellent time at YET ANOTHER camp this summer. i tell ya, you're gonna camp ur summer away.  i'll miss you all! i'll call u when i get back, meg!   liebe, katja von detton
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why can't two people ever be having the exact same emotion at the exact same time?  so all of you out there know that i like frankie, and that frankie sometimes likes me, but always at the most inconvenient moments. well, yesterday night he told me that, had things been different at the beginning of the semester, we would probably be together now. he said "if i hadn't screwed up months ago, i might not be alone." i told him that the window of dating opportunity isn't as small as he apparently thinks and that something can still work out. he simply replied "Whatever. I suppose so."  i was like holy crap, make up your mind. i just want to go out with him so something will have happened that will be the product of MONTHS of "will they, won't they"...it's terrible, but it's what i'm really thinking, so what? and besides, everyone knows that deep down everyone prefers "they will" instead of "they won't". i should share this piece of information with frankie and see what he thinks.   well, constantly on nate patrol. that boy is gorgeous and fine. add a comment if you agree! (cough, cough, meike, cough) tomorrow i leave for kansas city. i am all packed, and though i haven't left yet, i still have that horrible feeling that i've forgotten something that if vital and terribly important to the outcome of the trip.   i'm listening to a mised CD with songs such as:  edwin mccain: i'll be  relient k: sadie hawkins dance (gag for those of you who know what went down @ sadie hawkins...hehe)  someone: building a mystery  dashboard confessional: screaming infedelities  someone: rain (the song for the integris hospital commercial about the babies or woman with cancer...sheree chamberlin sang it @ BALTO assembly)  someone: California, here we come  someone else: title unknown   sorry to be so specific and sarcastic.   VERY, VERY SAD LYRICS:   It's hard to listen to a hard, hard heart  Beating close to mine.  Pounding up against the stone and steel;  Walls that i won't climb   Sometimes the hurt is so deep, deep, deep  that you think you're gonna drown.  Sometimes all i can do is weep, weep, wepp  with all this rain pouring down.   {chorus}  And it's strange how hard it rains now,  Miles and miles of big, black clouds.  But i'm holding on underneath this shrowd.  Rain.   It's hard to know when to give up the fight,  Some things you want will just never be right,  It's never rained like it has tonight before.  now i don't want to beg you, baby, with something you cannot give,  I'm not looking for the rest of your life, i just want another chance to live.   chorus   and it's strange how hard it rains now,  miles and miles of big black clouds,  but i'm still alive underneath this shrowd.  Rain.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I AM GOING TO KANSAS WITH MORGAN! i'm leaving tuesday morning and i'll be back next wednesday! i am so excited to be going, finally!  yesterday frankie called me, told me he missed talking to me, told me that he's never known anyone like me and i deserve to know how interesting and special i am.  i've gotten into the habit of, when i clean out the lint screen in the dryer, i've thrown the little messes of lint behind the dryer even though there is a mini-trashcan on the counter by the washer. there is about a two inch gap between the dryer and the wall, and i imagine i've almost covered the floor back there. but it's okay, no one will find it til i move out and five years later they finally sell the house.  my new favorite song: (Dashboard...of course... written by the fabulous mr. carrabba. it's not out on single yet, says the cashier at sam goody, but i need to save my money anyway for the trip. the plane ticket back is fifty bucks and i imagine i'll spend about $100 just...around...)  "Vindicated"  Hope dangles on a string Like slow spinning redemption Winding in and winding out The shine of which has caught my eye  And roped me in So mesmerizing, so hypnotizing  I am captivated  [Chorus]  Vindicated I am selfish I am wrong I am right I swear I'm right I swear I knew it all along  And I am flawed  But I am cleaning up so well I am seeing in me now the things you swore you saw yourself   So clear Like the diamond in your ring Cut to mirror your intentions Oversized and overwhelmed The shine of which has caught my eye And rendered me so isoloated, so motivated I am certain now that  [Chorus]   So turn Up the corners of your lips Part them and feel my finger tips Trace the moment, fall forever Defense is paper thin Just one touch and I'd be in Too deep now to ever swim against the current So let me slip away  [3x] So let me slip against the current and let me slip away  [Chorus]  Slight hope It dangles on a string Like slow spinning redemption...    the bold parts are my favorites. i'll sign on before i leave. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just a letter-slash-joke that i hope you all enjoy!  Dear Mom: Our scout master told us all write to our parents in case you saw the flood on TV and worried. We are OK. Only 1 of our tents and 2 sleeping bags got washed away. Luckily, none of us got drowned because we were all up on the mountain looking for Chad when it happened. Oh, yes, please call Chad's mother and tell her he is OK. He can't write because of the cast. I got to ride in one of the search & rescue jeeps. It was neat. We never would have found him in the dark if it hadn't been for the lightning. Scoutmaster Webb got mad at Chad for going on a hike alone without telling anyone. Chad said he did tell him, but it was during the fire so he probably didn't hear him. Did you know that if you put gas on a fire, the gas can will blow up? The wet wood still didn't burn, but one of our tents did, also some of our clothes. John is going to look weird until his hair grows back. We will be home on Saturday if Scoutmaster Webb gets the car fixed. It wasn't his fault about the wreck. The brakes worked OK when we left. Scoutmaster Webb said that a car that old you have to expect something to break down; that's probably why he can't get insurance on it. We think it's a neat car. He doesn't care if we get it dirty, and if it's hot, sometimes he lets us ride on the tailgate. It gets pretty hot with  10 people in a car. He let us take turns riding in the trailer until the highway patrolman stopped and talked to us. Scoutmaster Webb is a neat guy. Don't worry, he is a good driver. In fact, he is teaching Terry how to drive. But he only lets him drive on the mountain roads where there isn't any traffic. All we ever see up there are logging trucks. This morning all of the guys were diving off the rocks and swimming out in the lake. Scoutmaster Webb wouldn't let me because I can't swim and Chad was afraid he would sink because of his cast, so he let us take the canoe across the lake. It was great. You can still see some of the trees under the water from the flood. Scoutmaster Webb isn't crabby like some scoutmasters. He didn't even get mad about not taking the life jackets. He has to spend a lot of time working on the car so we are working on our merit badges. When Dave dove in the lake and cut his arm, we got to see how a tourniquet works. Also Wade and I threw up. Scoutmaster Webb said it probably was just food poisoning from the leftover chicken, he said they got sick that way with the food they ate in prison. I'm so glad he got out and became our scoutmaster. He said he sure figured out how to get things done better while he was doing his time. I have to go now. We are going into town to mail our letters and buy bullets. Don't worry about anything. We are fine. Love, William
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      www.skylarth.blogspot.com/ is this guy from edmond, 15 years old, and he seems pretty cool. i wanna meet someone over the internet! i prlly go to school w/ him but u never know. this is so frustrating. leave me a comment and tell me whether or not i should leave him a comment and introduce myself! 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      www.skylarth.blogspot.com/ is this guy from edmond, 15 years old, and he seems pretty cool. i wanna meet someone over the internet! i prlly go to school w/ him but u never know. this is so frustrating. leave me a comment and tell me whether or not i should leave him a comment and introduce myself! 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Morgan's back!!! she got back at 10:14 on Tuesday night from Kansas F***ing City (KFC) and now she is here for a whole gosh darn week! I hope i hope i hope that my parents will let little mo take me home with her for the next week, but I don't think they really want me to go somewhere   all by myself   so, what are you gonna do? i saw my arch hated rival today at the mall...KYLE CARMAN I HATE YOU!!!! YOU ARE A MAN SKANK!!! he was walking that way and i was walking this way and well, we made eye contact that went something like this:   WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING HERE?!?!?!  Here's how it went down: Him:  hey me: (awkwardly and a little bee-yotchy) hi H: are you uh, still, um...swimming or... me: yeah. you? H: no, i, uh, well, i play baseball, uh, now. me: oh.  H: is that guy your, uh, boyfriend or whatever? me: who? Oh, yeah. (frankie was there so i just used him...he was out of hearing distance.) H: oh. so, uh... me: how's your summer? H: okay. your's? me: awesome. So are you coming to north next year? h: no, uh, santa fe, yeah. me: great. maybe i'll see you around sometime h: uh, yeah. okay. bye. me: bye.  HAHAHAHA! stupid 1 grade younger than me but two weeks older than me curly haired swimmer boy! he is cocky and rude and a jerk and a man skank and he thinks he's so man pretty, but really....rrrrr.... he is cute, though. :)  "Donde esta mi gato?" "Save a horse. Ride and cowboy." "Save a tree. Eat a beaver." "I heart JTT" "I love Italian Boys" "YOU are my sunshine." "VOTE" "Jesus is my homeboy." "Ewes not fat. Ewes just fluffy." "Mary is my homegirl." are all awesome shirts I saw at the mall.  today mo and i went to F.C. w/ savannah and lauren and lauren's friend and we hung out and got those awesome old timey pictures...we got to dress up like skanks at a bar! maybe I can scan it and plop it up here on the site for ya'll to see. the guy who was operating the ferris wheel was so seriously hitting on us, it was so nasty. he looked like kenan off kenan and kel. EWW!! he was like..."so how old are ya'll? wow, you young. you trippin! got a pen? i lost my phone number...what's yours? i get off in three hours, aw yall still gown be herr?" The dippin dots guy was mighty fine!!! but all i could think about was hanging out w/ meike und uli und der daniel...  BOO HOO i miss drew drew, do you miss me to? after the third round of eruption i almost threw up my funnel cake on your shoe. frontier city was coo' i really want(ed) to go out with you but you was trippin boo. What the heck is wrong with you?! you should of asked me out one day before schoo' Or in Deutsch.  word.  i'll talk to ya'all later! I hope i'm in KFC this time next week!!!  liebe, katja  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "All hail Katja von Detton, supreme ruler of the universe!!!" -all my faithful servants "JESUS! You're white! Get away from me!" -meike und katja und strongsad "If Iy had twoo desquibe mysewf in wun word it wood defnitlee haff twoo bwee...fwuffy puff mawshmeww-ohs." -HOMESTAR "Katie, I love you. marry me, please. i've loved you all along. Wanna go out? I promise it won't have anything to do with alchohol or hippity-dippity. you can trust me." -rhinehart...yesterday...right...
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!! I have concluded, after extensive research and observation, that Franko really does have the hots for me. I told all of you! MWAH-HA-HA!!! :) ...or at least he did Freitag... On Friday night at about 10:00 the phone rang and the King of Mixed Signals (HIMSELF!!!) asked what I was doing. Turns out he and his Best Friend Forever from Tay-hoss (texas) are roaming around the neighborhood and wanted to give me a ring. I didn't think that my parents would let me out of the house that late, especially to visit boys, so I was like "I'm sorry, Dan, but I can't!" (that was his friend from Texas' name...Dan. )and he's like "but Frank told me all about you and all I want to do is shake your hand, come on" so I asked my mom and she was like "just for a few minutes" and I was like "cha-ching!" So they came over. I was sitting on my mailbox when I saw Frankie walking under a streetlight next to this kid with alot of blonde hair, almost all the way down to his chin. He walked up and shook my hand and then like, looked me up and down and said"Okay, Frank, now I believe you." I was like OMG!!! you are the freaking hottest dude I've ever seen in my whole life!!! After I got over how awesomely gorgeous Texas Dan was,  we hung out in the front yard till exactly 11:08, when my little sister, for the third time, told me it was late and I should come back in. They told me to sneak out of the house at midnight and meet them by the pool to hang out with (I quote) "The hottest buckaroos in all of the Midwest".  Sadly, i did not get to meet them because it scared the pants off me just thinking about getting caught not sleeping innocently in my room.  But, yes, now I am madly-in-love-slash-hate-slash-like with Frankie again. But my new SoulMate of the Week is: DAN FROM TEXAS!!!   p.s.     why don't seagulls fly over the bay? duh; then they'd be bagels. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i know. he totally should.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And as you watch the baseball fly overhead, Sigh and look into the bright sun. Say, "Charlie Brown Nevermore."  p.s. ich liebe rinehart aschenbrenner  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i've lost nine pounds. you can't really tell, but I'm still proud of myself. no brownies for me, meike. i had a dream last night that i took a taxi to the airport and all the German club was there with their luggage. i didn't even have money with me, and savannah wouldn't bring me my money, so i had to wait for a flight two hours later than ya'll and it was also four days LONGER. i dunno... i've been thinking about eric A LOT. i like him so much, because he's not like anyone else i know. any other guy, anyways. i think i'll call him up and ask him out. it would be really forward, but i seriously doubt he'd say no.  new fave quote: "No, i was never a boy scout, but I did have a brownie once." -Dax on that movie "without a paddle"  i'm going to see The Village with melanie, and i'm scared already. i'm such a wuss---think i should ask eric to that?  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have still not given frankie The Letters, and have decided not to. But, wait?! I can't not give them to him! i wrote them to him!  No...he'll be completely thrown off and freaked out, which I have decided is an 64% chance, and I don't like those odds. I guess some optomists would say that it is also a 36% chance that he'll love them, but... i think i will just give him this one i wrote&nbsp;yesterday:  &nbsp;Just kiss me if you want to give it a try. When I think about you, I think “let’s date!” It would be hilarious, exciting, beautiful. The world would smile at us and we would be able to GET SO MUCH DONE.  what do you think? megan? tania??? (who, if you're reading this, I REALLY REALLY MISS YOU SOOOOO MUCH!!!) oh, and, by GET SO MUCH DONE, i mean in a strictly emotional sense...right... NO MORE SADIE HAWKINS DANCE MISHAPS!!! jk...i wouldn't mind. ha! take that, drew!!!  oh. eric, my eighth grader, is, sniff sniff, going to santa fe! i saw his name in the paper about a santa fe summer freshmen league baseball team. i am so upset, but i figure i can still get a bite out of him, or some weird saying like that. Love Will Find A Way.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i went and saw King Arthur yesterday. if you were contemplating whether or not to see it...don't. and that's all i have to say bout that. BUT. at the mall i looked over and saw Blake, the super cute soccer player who i like to torture because of the way he plays, runs, etc. sitting in the food court alone&nbsp;not TWO TABLES AWAY!  so i, being me, go up and plop down in the seat beside him and am like "what's up, soccer boy?" and then I notice that some very cute twelve year old is walking up to the table. he and i make eye contact and my mouth drops open. " Will?!?!"  i shout. no, no way, i am thinking, this boy with short hair could not possibly be the hottest freshmen at North, who i pine over more than any other boy at the whole school. he smiles at me and says "it's katie, right?" and i am thinking "it's whatever the hell you want it to be!" but then i'm like, yeah. he asks if i thought the oklahoma history final was hard. i said "not really; i wasted a bunch of time studying for it, though. i thought lorenz would try and put some trick questions on there." and he was like "me, too, i was really worried about it, but i came out with an A in the class." I asked him if he was playing soccer at ESC and he was like "no, i'm working at my dad's office." i told him about my making the Blue 89ers B starting team, which doesn't sound like much, but it's awesome to be starting for anyone, esp. anyone Blue. I&nbsp;talked for like, five, maybe ten minutes and&nbsp;then i was like "well, i've got to go." and blake&nbsp;told me about&nbsp;this party he was having&nbsp;for the&nbsp;end of summer at his dad's house and asked it i would want to come. will looked directly at me and i was like "yeah, that'd be awesome", and then i put my phone number into his&nbsp;cell phone and smiled at them and was like "see ya" and will said "yeah, see ya around"  or...that's what i wished would have happened. really, i didn't know it was Will&nbsp;until he walked by my table and&nbsp;looked right at me.&nbsp;i figured out it was him&nbsp;and i was like,&nbsp;flirt with him!, so i pointed at&nbsp;my hair and told him&nbsp;i liked his. he said "thanks, katie" and that was it. blake asked me what was up and i said not much, then he said&nbsp;"see you at school".  well, i know i liked the first story better... i'll&nbsp;HOPEFULLY see you later today, meike. bye!&nbsp;&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;Day One:  &nbsp;Went to Council of Elrond. Was prettiest person there. Agreed to follow some tiny little man to Mordor to throw ring into volcano. Very important mission - gold ring so tacky.  Day Four:  Boromir so irritating. Why must he wear big shield like dinner plate all the time? Climbed up Caradhras but wimpy humans who cannot walk on snow insisted we climb back down. Am definitely prettiest member of the Fellowship. Go me!  Day Six:  Far too dark in Mines of Moria to brush hair properly. Am very afraid I am developing a tangle. Orcs so silly. Still the prettiest.  Day Ten:  Gandalf fell into shadow. In other news, I think I am developing a spot on my nose. V. serious situation, as Elven spots likely to last for 500 years or more. Still prettiest, despite blasted spot. &nbsp;Day Eleven:  In Lothlorien. Suspect Galadriel may be prettier than me. Also, am quite sure she copied my hairstyle. I was wearing that same look at least 1,000 years ago. Silly bint. She was most annoyed that I used her mirrored fountain to take a nice bubble bath. I choose to ignore her claim that my hair clogged her drain. Not one strand of my hair has fallen out in 800 years, why would it start now? Still prettiest by far.  Day 30:  All this paddling about in boats is hell on my complexion. Aragorn obviously starting to find Frodo strangely attractive. Sam will kill him if he tries anything. Still the prettiest.  Day 33 :  Boromir tempted by Ring. So tedious. Cannot be tempted myself, as already have everything I want i.e. perfect hair and a butt like granite. Have been getting very strange letters from someone calling herself "Stacey" who wants to do obscene things to my elfhood. Fortunately have super-duper elf vision so can run away if I see her coming.  Day 35:  Boromir dead. Very messy death, most uncessesary. Did get kissed by Aragorn as he expired. Does a guy have to get shot full of arrows around here to get any action? Boromir definitely not prettier than me. Cannot understand it. Am feeling a pout coming on. Frodo off to Mordor with Sam. Tiny little men caring about each other, rather cute really. Am quite sure Gimli fancies me. So unfair. He is waist height, so can see advantages there, but chunky braids and big helmet most offputting. Forsee dark times ahead, very dark times.   go to  urlLink http://gohoax.com/forum/viewtopic.php?t=58 &nbsp;for all the Lord Of the Rings major character's very very secret diaries.   &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today, when I was babysitting...again...on the way back from the pool, who should drive right by but Frankie, without a license, in his super hot truck. i was all freckly from dos horas of the sun and it looked like i was about to enter myself in a wet t-shirt contest, because i was in a hurry to get back to the kids' house and hadn't commited myself to fully drying off before we got back on our bikes and rode home. i pretended not to see him but when he honked, it was hard to keep ignoring him and i was forced to&nbsp;at least wave&nbsp;to him. despite how i'm making this sound, i am really super-excited because i have had this buzz all afternoon from seeing my for-real soulmate, even if it was only for, like, twenty seconds. but, i still reserve my right to hate his guts. i think that i'll write him a note and actually give it to him. i hope, i hope, i hope that he'll call tonight because after I saw him, i called his cell phone and left a message that said, "you know, frankie, it's illegal to drive around without a license in oklahoma. i'll visit you in jail." he is either so totally into me or can't stand me or feels the exact same way that i do about him, which is a lot of the first thing and at the same time, a lot of the other, too.  &nbsp; anyway, today i tried over and over to teach the kids i babysit to swim freestyle correctly. all that was happening, though, was that they looked like they were drowning; flailing their arms around and around and bobbing up and down in the water.&nbsp; It made me want to swim circles around and around them. I guess I didn't learn to swim properly til I was about six...oh, wait. they're&nbsp;nine and eleven... &nbsp; i also saw&nbsp;daniel, who is my hot neighbor who does&nbsp;triathalons and i have been madly in love with since &nbsp;I MOVED HERE! well, i've got to go. i'm already looking up&nbsp;homecoming dresses. hopefully,&nbsp;the whole thing won't be a replay of the sadie hawkins dance...hehe...megan, u know what i mean. i just...won't&nbsp;dance with frankie...that's all. HA! like i&nbsp;could ever avoid that.&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      why can't every girl be as lucky as me to have so many boys that really like&nbsp;me and don't ever get around to asking&nbsp;me out? it's like they know i am crazy-bonkers about them and then don't feel obliged to reciprocate. i have to tell you a secret, and that is that I am terrible at letting things go.  My memory is wonderful and I can never completely stop liking boys that I am crazy-bonkers about. I hear a song on the radio and i want to call Scott, who was actually my boyfriend, so I suppose that's not a very good example, is it? I write a note and I want to hand it to Nate. I long for conversation and, in turn, Frankie. I drive by Frontier City and want to sit close to Drew. I swim and want to swim with Ken. I watch anyone making out and I want to be making out.  &nbsp; More tomorrow. My mom wants me to go to bed now. &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Harpy: Harpies are beautiful creatures with wings that are said to have terrorized sailors. You are slightly arrogant and vain but you probably deserve to be. You are confident in your abilities and know what you want to achieve in life. Similar to vampires you will use almost any means to get what you want. You have some friends but you only hang around with people who think like you do. &nbsp; or a...    &nbsp; Phoenix: Phoenixes are litterally birds of fire. They are brave and majestic and have the ability to be reborn from their own ashes. You are strog willed an confident- a true leader. Although you can get down in the dumps occasionaly you are never there for long. Many people flock around you and like you as a friend.  &nbsp; &nbsp; true enough. scary, but cool. i did it twice. go to  urlLink What Mythological Creature Are You (Many Results and Beautiful Pics) &nbsp;to get yours. they do have awesome pics. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Swing Swing" ...but tweeked a little.  All American Rejects  &nbsp;  Days swiftly come and go.  I'm dreaming of [HIM]  [HE'S] seeing other [GIRLS]  Emotions they stir  The sun is gone.  The nights are long  And I am left while the tears fall.  Did you think that I would cry,on the phone?  Do you know what it feels like,being alone?  I'll find someone new  Swing, Swing, Swing  &nbsp;from the tangles of  My heart is crushed by a former love  Can you help me find a way  To carry on again.  Wish cast into the sky  I'm moving on  Sweet beginnings do arise  [HE]&nbsp;knows&nbsp;[HE] was wrong  The notes are old,  They bend,  they fold  and so do I to a new love.  Bury me  ([I] thought&nbsp;[MY] problems were gone)  Carry me  (away. away, away...)  &nbsp;  I DON'T KNOW (FIRST, WHY I'M TYPING IN CAPS...IT'S FUN, THOUGH.) IF I TWEEKED TYSON RITTER'S WORD TO RELATE TO FRANKIE OR NATE, BUT YOU KNOW IT SOUNDS BETTER WHEN I'M SINGING OUT LOUD BECAUSE I DON'T SOUND LIKE A TOTAL LESBIAN OR ANYTHING...  SO, MEIKE, I'M SUPER GLAD THAT YOU'RE BACK.  I RECRUITED&nbsp;BRYAN TO THE BLOGGING WORLD, JUST AS U RECRUITED ME, MEIKE. I SERIOUSLY DOUBT IF HE'LL EVER GET ON IT AGAIN, THOUGH, SO I CAN STILL CALL HIM A MAN-SKANK AND NOT FEEL LIKE HE'S READING IT.  &nbsp;  OH, I BROKE DOWN LAST NIGHT AND RANG FRANKIE. WE'RE GOING...ON A WALK...AT NINE, SO I DON'T KNOW... I THINK I'M GONNA TRY TO PSYCHOANALYZE HIM AND THE HYPNOTIZE HIM AND MAKE HIM ASK ME OUT ON AN ACTUAL FACTUAL DATE. THE THINGS HE MAKES ME WANNA DO...I'D KNOCK OVER A QUICK-E-MART FOR HIM...(RANDOM TWEEKED INSERT FROM AN ATARIS SONG.)  &nbsp;  I WANT TO BE WITH HIM SO BAD. IT SEEMS LIKE HE'S BEEN A MAJOR CHARACTER IN MY DREAMS FOR THE PAST WEEK.  &nbsp;  OH, AND, NATE IS AN AWESOME GUY, BUT I'VE FINALLY REALIZED THAT THE ONLY THING THAT'LL EVER HAPPEN BETWEEN US IS GOING TO HAPPEN ON A FOLDED UP PIECE OF COLLEGE-RULED LOSE-LEAF THREE HOLE PUNCHED PIECE OF PAPER BETWEEN THE DESKS IN THE DIRTY GERMAN ROOM, AND THAT THE SEXUAL TENSION IN THOSE NOTES CAN BE CUT LIKE BUTTER...OR AT LEAST ERASED BY AN ERASER.  MAN, I AM SO DEEP.......AND HOT.  I DON'T KNOW WHY&nbsp;I DON'T HAVE GUYS THROWING THEMSELVES AT ME. DO YOU, MEIKE? HM...MAYBE I NEED A FEW MORE PARTS EGO IN MY SOCCERGODDESS77-MILKSHAKE. (SEE OLDER BLOG ENTRIES.)  YOU GUYS KNOW I'M JUST KIDDING, RIGHT? (OR AM I?)   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             urlLink  Am I cool or uncool? [CLICK]       You are  urlLink Cool !      You're pretty cool! People look at you and think.. 'wow.. that person is cool!' Congratulations. Use your position wisely and teach the dorks below you a thing or two. There's nothing like recruiting a cool person.      urlLink  Cool quizzes at Go-Quiz.com         
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last night I had the weirdest dream.  okay, so, meike, you were over at my house and we went walking around the neighborhood and went to (guess!) frankie's house. we snuck in and looked at his pool and stuff, then went in and sat in the living room. BUT, it wasn't really his house (i've gone over there b4 to see him and I used to babysit the kid who lived there before him), it was WAY bigger and super, uber pretty. it was a 2 story, too. anyway, these 2 little 10 year old kids, who claimed that they were my cousins, were with us and i asked them if anyone was home. They said, of course someone's home, and so we tried to sneak out, meike. we were halfway down the street when we heard the kids and frankie and his sister and mom and dad yelling and running after us. so, we took off at a sprint and they chased us around for, like, an hour, all around the neighborhood. finally, we thought we'd lost them, but when we were taking a breather, frankie runs up from behind me and then grabs a hold of my foot and refuses to let go. neither of us can stop laughing and finally, he pulls me close to him and hugs me then calls me "julie" which is the name of his ex-girlfriend in Texas, and when I looked at his face, it was really Colby, the (hot)guy who comes to stay with his mom and stepdad every summer across the street from me. then colby calls me "tania" which is one of my really good friends who used to live by me and moved away who had a HUGE crush on colby. i was still laughing and hugging him, though.  i don't know. what do you guys think it means?  am is super desperate to get a bf that i'll hook up with anyone and sneak into their houses?!?!   oh, and i think nate has a 'girlfriend', but when i say that, i mean that she thinks of nate as her boyfriend and nate thinks of her as an "ass to try and tap". i'm happy for...er....him, though. honestly. i don't know what came over me but when we drove by and they were hugging and kissing on eachother in the pool, I smiled, then realized what i was doing and tried to make myself stop, but i couldn't. i don't know. i've been wierd lately.  liebe, katja  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          How to make a soccergoddess77        Ingredients:   5 parts success  5 parts humour  5 parts beauty        Method:  Blend at a low speed for 30 seconds. Add a little cocktail umbrella and a dash of lovability        Username:       urlLink Personality cocktail  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      frankie? drew? nate?  how could I chose?! you have obviously never seen nate, who is GORGEOUS AND FINE! drew is a wrestler who (don't tell anyone bc we had to practically beat it out of him) is still a boyscout in his sophomore year of high school...jesus... frankie is the only one of the three who can't drive, but they all own cars. (don't ask.)    based on cars:  nate by a long shot. all three have trucks, but frankie's is a 2004 Ford F150, drew's is a 2002 Nissan (TINY), and nate's is a: 1956 classic navy blue hot-hot-hot ford truck which he redid himself. (so hot)   on looks:  Nathan again. he is so hot. drew's(6foot) really tan, but so is nate now (lifeguarding and all), and frankie's(6 foot 2) a "tall, skinny, ugly swimmer" according to my friend leeza-bee, but he isn't ugly. nate is 6 foot 6! ( :O ), he's super muscley, but not too buff, has curly blonde-brown hair, and blue-green eyes, and a really nice chin.   personality:  frankie. nate is obsessed w/ sex, booze, and chicks. drew is a little less outgoing than i usually like in my dudes, and is kinda serious. frankie is smart, sarcastic, funny, but has a really narrow minded view on some things. he can take a joke, but is really flirty, although his and my relationship is different because we hang out a lot and he talks to me way more than other chicks.  the winner is obviously Texas Dan...or Emilio Estevez.  well, i'm bored of writing now.  i'm leaving for San Antonio tomorrow. Yippee. best case scenario: i see texas dan and we fall madly in love, and become pen pals til we both go to the same college.  worst case: i am eaten by a cactus-monster and don't get to find out if frankie and i ever get together.  or i break my legs climbing on the alamo or fall off the hotel room balcony and can't renew my Kerr McGee swim contract.  liebe, katja  hey, how did you find my blog thing anyway? was i right about the swim team?   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Frankie, You're the kind of guy that makes me think that I'm better off home on a Saturday night, with all my doors locked up tight. Be sure that I won't be thinking about you, baby.  ...but... When I'm talking to myself, please note that I'd rather be talking to you. Liebe, Katie 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm so bored that i'm posting 2 blogs, one right after the other.  my bff melanie and i are doing really well right now. we're in an "up" stage. sometimes, we get into these random pits of angriness and we ignore and are super, uber beeyotchy to eachother and then we decide that we're friends again. odd, i know. i hate doing this, but i'm stealing things off of other peoples' blogs and writing them on my own. (mostly you, megan.)   "Once you can accept the universe as matter expanding into nothing that is something, wearing stripes with plaid comes easy."  "People who never get carried away should be."  "The shortest distance between two points is under construction."  "Common sense and a sense of humor are the same thing, moving at different speeds. A sense of humor is just common sense, dancing."  "Wait, I just remembered something! You're boring and my legs work."  "Time is what keeps everything from happening at once"  "Never take life seriously. Nobody gets out alive anyway."  "Procrastinate later."  "Never put off till tomorrow what you can avoid altogether"  "The mind is like a parachute; it works much better when it's open."   "One should respect public opinion in so far as is necessary to avoid starvation and to keep out of prison, but anything that goes beyond this is voluntary submission to an unnecessary tyranny."       –Russell  and here's a few that i even got myself! imagine... (all from awesome songs, by the way)  "and when i say 'let's keep in touch, i hope you know that i really mean 'i wish that you'd just grow up'." "What difference does this difference in age make? i know how it ends...so kill me quick." [ how i feel about natey-boy] "if you ever said you missed me then don't say you never lied." "this night is hell. i'm sick and sunk and i blame myself, cause i was making things hard and you were just trying to help."  all those songs came from the CD "your favorite weapon" by the awesome band "brand new".  now i'm morbidly bored and no one is home...i would call frankie, but i'm not letting myself contact him...he is going to come get me.   nate was lifeguarding today and he walked in while i was leaving. he nodded at me and asked if i'd done anything (eye brow raise) exciting yet this summer. K:"plenty, but none like you're thinking." N:"we could change that." grin. " call me if you're bored and i'll find something for you to do." K:"i'll remember that." smile. "see ya" N:"tchus." and then i let him check me out as i walked out to the parking lot and then turned my head and smiled at him. i love that kid so much. i'm thinking we'll go to prom together this year. excellent! what do you think, meike? just think, if we get married, we'll be katie & nate! sigh...okay, i promise i won't say or type any of those thoughts out loud anymore. i'll keep them to myself. but when he said "if you're bored" i doubt he meant TONIGHT.  i would call you, meike, but you're apparently in colorado or someplace that isn't oklahoma (lucky). it is going to be so freaking awesome sophomore year! you and i can reign over deutsch club and we will finally be like all the other clubs: 1. homecoming float 2. actual event turn-outs 3. FIELD TRIPS during school 4. after school 5. best trip to germany EVER 6. 2 whole pages in the freaking yearbook instead of one. i promise to try and get a picture of just the officers in there!  note to self: talk frau hill into GIVING us the positions of prez & VP because we are the only 2 (of 4...hehehe) who show up to EVERYTHING. even if frau doesn't. and besides, she adores us! but i'm thinking about putting a hit on that emily girl because she won the award and i didn't. of cours tanya did. and you. i hate you, meike von detton! jk, you're my second in command. (like hemler to hitler.)(lol, sorry! couldn't help sticking that reference in there!) (ps- kinda random, but my grandfather (the one whose belly button popped off) killed hemler when he was a sniper during WWII and it was raining so hemmy went to put the top down on his convertible and gramps shot the bastard. just so you know.) 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      franko update: i'm waiting for him to find out that i have had a cell phone for the past two weeks but haven't given him the number yet. (hey, i can give friggin mixed signals, too.)i left a message on his cell on mon. that said i was home, but that was all. he hasn't responded yet. all i said was "hey, it's me. i'm back. you're gay for not picking up your phone and if you're screening this call i'll kick ur ass."  i got back from morgan's on monday, where i had so much fun! (sorry...footloose is on in the background so this won't be my best work yet. hehe) i got to meet her boyfriend, michael, whose DADDY is the preacher-man, and who is also (cracking up) HOMESCHOOLED! them goshdarned homeschool kids are the funniest people in the whole world. OVERPROTECTIVE MOMS, JUST SEND YOUR KIDS TO PUBLIC SCHOOL. IT'S BETTER FOR THEM, ENDANGERED SPECIES, AND THE OZONE LAYER. AND THEY'LL HATE YOU WHEN THEY DON'T KNOW HOW TO INTERACT W/ THE OPPOSITE SEX UNTIL THEY'RE 26. i'll fill you in about  every last detail about the trip  later.  oh, i have an announcement to make!!! I HAVE A READER WHO IS NOT MEGAN!!! her name is caroline (hi, caroline!) and i guess that she got my blog name b/c when i went and checked out her profile, it said swim team and i think that she and i are the only bloggers that are on the swim team (or who are proud enough to claim that we are indeed, swimmers, to the internet world.)  she thinks i'm EXCITING! [i know, megan, i can't figure it out, either...little does she know!!! HAHAHAHA!]  and, answering ur question, (sie hast eine frage, meike! ha!) my life is sometimes rated Y, most of the time just PG or PG-13(language), and the notes I wrote to nate in german are...NC-17(themes may be inappropriate for viewers under the age of 17. alchohol content, severe sexual content, violence, and occasional drug references. gaw, i love that kid.). she leaves me comments, and sorry, kiddo, but i didn't read any of them til about 6 1/2 minutes ago.   oh, caroline, drew is this kid whose relationship w/ me was hot, hot, hot after we went on a trip to frontier city (an amusement park that's only interesting if boy-yoys come) and almost made out on one of the rides in the dark. after that, he and i constantly flirted/ignored eachother and have all year since. never anywhere in between, always at totally different ends of the spectrem. odd, eh? needless to say, i am still madly in love with him.    liebe, katja von detton
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Things I Hate:   uncertainty starting my period during my period Frank Louis Lezu being single having a boyfriend being 2nd best the length of my hair still being in love with my exes backing myself into a corner by liking three guys the same amount at the exact same time. swim practice ugly, small dogs   smelly people   push-mowing    babysitting for people who don't pay enough   babysitting in general   cowboy boots   ugly perverted boys who hit on you despite that terrible look you're giving them   "It's not you, it's me." when they don't mean it   "Can we still be friends?" when they do mean it   chewing tobacco or cigarettes   DRUGS   losing my keys   suicide,   murder, etc.        Things I Love:     Scott Coffey   smiling people   confident people   sandwiches   the All American Rejects   cute boys   muscley biceps   boys who play soccer   boys who play baseball   love letters   music   piano   orchestra concerts   school dances   high school, in general   MY high school   Frank Louis Lezu    very hot actors   movies   dates   friends   class   people   contact with people   gummi bears   Reeses cups   Reeses pieces   chapstick   eyeliner   art    freedom of expression   Blogs   the internet   color   sound   taste   sight   touch   cats   big dogs   did I already say Frankie?    
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      went to synagogue with misheala this morning. thankfully, they didn't ask me any questions about anything mildly Jewish because I would have been like "uh...well..." you know what i mean. i did get to wear my funeral clothes, though. i love wearing suits. now that i don't swim for UCA, the only place i can wear them is to funerals. darn.  last night frankie was JOGGING while i was RUNNING and we kind of ran/jogged right into eachother. well, it was late at night and it was very dark. it was kind of awkward but i asked him to run with me and he was like 'yeah, sure.' so we did and you know, i absolutely hate trying to keep pace with just one other person. especially someone whose legs are longer than mine. i could tell that we were kind of trying to impress eachother, you know? so we ran all the way around the lake and stopped and sat down on that bench where we proceeded to make out like crazy...no. he wishes. we did talk for a while, though. i wouldn't of minded making out so much.   Okay…silly little fantasy of me calling him up and it goes really well and I confess to writing him all these love letters and he says “Love letters?” and I say ”More like f*** letters,” (hehehe) and he says “So…no love letters?” and I say “Well, yeah, some love letters,” and he says “Good.” And I am impossibly happy, heart swelling up and bursting over.   i am so entirely desperate. maybe i should just call nate. or maybe adam saylor...no i'm kidding. i love that kid. i think he's so adorable and as soon as i can [date] i am going to ask him out. he's so sweet.  melanie thinks that the following guys had crushes on me freshmen year:  drew (well, duh.) derek (ick.) frankie (see  drew .) ben (i think i'm going to be sick.) adam (yeah, that's probably right.) will (huge gasping surprise. she did admit that he stares at me whenever i'm around, though. very nice) tyler brush (not sure. )   and i'm adding:  nate (deep down, there is something there, i swear.) denver (who i don't think you know about, megan, but i thought he has been giving me the cold shoulder since i accidentally called him dallas. oops. apparently not, seeing as he goes out of his way to talk to me.) ken (for like, all of two seconds)  can't wait to see school. can wait, however, for school to see me. haha. call me when you get back from the middle of nowhere, meike.  tchus! liebe, katja von aschenbrenner (did i type that outloud?! silly me.)      My'>http://www.readingforresults.com/rating/pg13.jpg"> My  life is rated PG-13.  urlLink What  is your life rated?   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      v. cute football playing boys just came a knocking asking us to buy a few...or eight or six Varsity Cards. One looked like Kelby Wood just not so mean and vengeful looking, and mucho mucho taller. The other one was v. tall, with curly/wavy blonde/brown hair and v. nice eyes. I think his name was...Nate.  So.  I am thinking of getting a perm just because I am so freaking tired of my hair and my big nose that I want to cut both of them right of my head. At least if I got a perm, my nose wouldn't be the first thing you gasped and shrieked at when you saw me. lol. no, just kidding. i think I am v. pretty, just maybe a littly freckly. But it's summer so it's the worst time for freckly people. It's freckle season. I just wish it was the same as hunting season and that freckles could be whacked...pardon my soprano.   I am sad that I haven't lost any sizes yet. I would love to be a size four or five next week, but you know that will take at least two weeks...For those of you who don't know me I am being completely sarcastic. I am commited to running everyday at least once and eating less calories than I burn and maintaining my diet at least until I drop 2 or 3 sizes, which my mom says will have happened by two weeks into the school year. I can dig it.  Megan, I have decided that I do not want to be in your project for the Ruff Draft because of what I read on your websites. While Thrift Stores are the coolest places ever, it's the same kind of cool as socks with designs on them; the kind of cool that you do not want every student in Edmond reading about. Especially Eric Sample, who Melanie called and he is most definetly going to Santa Fe. I think we freaked him out a little, but he said that yes, he does know a chick who is a year older than him named Katie. He said "oh, yeah, she's really hot. Does she go to Santa Fe?" Most definite NO, little man, but feel free to call me anyway. I'm dreading Back To School Shopping, seeing as how I am going to have to buy jeans that will not fit me in a few weeks. sigh. life is so unfair. oh, well. at least i'll be skinny.   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i am going to see the VILLAGE!!!! aaaaahhhhhhhhh!!! with melanie...and savannah. i told melanie that i would dedicate a whole entry to her, but i've already talked about something else! oh, by the way, did you know that on a typical "girls' night out" ladies talk about over forty subjects and guys would only talk about 4. but guys don't have a "girls' night out" so now i'm confused. i'm already off track. okay...one subject...i can do it... starting on the next line, i will only talk about melanie.  MELANIE... is my best friend in the whole state! (lol, jk mel) has red hair...just like me! and I write eachother notes! ...except when we're randomly pissed off at eachother, which happens quite a bit. and I are super competitive. pretends to not have have very high self esteem, but she should, and i think she does. isn't very good at executing punch lines. jk; she tells good jokes. has WUNDERBAR! taste in boy-yoys. plays soccer. runs four miles on the treadmill every morning.  i have to go. I HATE SABANDA! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>