<Blog>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm taking courses for completion of my Masters In Organizational Management (MAOM).  So there is a major focus on personalities and how they go (and sometimes don't go) together.  So, I decided that I had to take some for myself.  I went to google..(isn't that great?) and found some great links.  I decided to go hog wild and take a few of them....I even took a disorder one (but it said I was 56% narcissistic-so I didn't really care to read more).  A few of the sites I visited are: www.humanmetrics.com (basic personality score) www.advisorteam.com (that's were you can get your temperament score) www.similarminds.com  (that is the best one with lots o' tests)  So I guess you are dying to find out right? No, probably not!  But here it goes anyway!  Test one (from humanitarian)  ESFJ  (Extroverted Sensing Feeling Judging)  Test two (from advisorteam)  Idealist  Test three (from similarminds) ENFP (Extroverted Intuitive Feeling Perceiving)  Test four (from similarminds)  that's the one that I didn't like  Anyway, what are you going to do with this information now that you have it?  Not much really.  You have to take these tests over a period of time, because (as you can see) the results can change over time.  It is not failsafe, but can give a very good understanding of how you view the world around you, and can give you a glimpse of how you can better interact with people.  So give it a try..there is also a test for married couples.  Be careful here though, cause you can find out that you are incompatible!!  Keep Learning!  PEACE, JPB 

						
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So my partner Steve and I decided, despite the reviews, to go see the Stepford Wives.  I am glad that we did.  It was funny as hell!    The updated version of the 70's motion picture (at least I think it was done in the 70's) really went out of its way to make its own mark.    Of course, the reason I wanted to see it was because it had Bette!!!  (God I love Bette) You can have your Judy Garland, Liza, and Barbara (for all of the friends of Dorothy out there) but I prefer the more avant garde.....Bette....and the more sublime....Olivia...(that's Olivia Newton-John for those of you who might be scratching your head wondering what the hell I'm talking about.)  And another thing....don't be dissin' the ONJ.  She is a beautiful human being and my first (and possibly my only crush) on the female persuasion-so that says a lot.  I digress.  More on the ONJ later.  Back to the movie.  They have updated the premise.  Included a gay couple (a Stepford "wife" for the gay man),in fact-the actor that plays the gay, limp-wristed lover (who gets Stepfordized) was in a wonderful film (that my friend JH introduced me to) called "Best in Show"....Sorry folks can't remember his name but you can't forget his character.  So, you have Bette (God, I love Bette), Nicole Kidman (you know-once married to Tom Cruise)....(btw, has he come out yet??) Matthew Broderick (boy he was cute back in the day), Glenn Close (she's awesome), Christopher Walken (ok, I don't care what you say..This dude SCARES me), Jon Lovitz, and a special appearance by Faith Hill (isn't her husband in real life just delicious??)....  Directed by Frank Oz.  Enough said.  I have to say that there were some scenes that were awful.  The editing was terrible (I mean, for ME to notice that's saying something), and some far-fetched ideas that don't work when you see them through (such as the scene where Dave Markowe turns his wife into an ATM and money pops out of her mouth...)  I guess I could believe it if they followed that path through the entire movie (which they didn't)....The method in which they "changed" the women of Stepford, into robots, I guess, doesn't hold through the entire movie....It was like they scrapped the idea half way through the movie and changed gears, but decided not to go back and rewrite what was already filmed.  So I guess what I am saying is that there was a lot that was NOTICEABLY wrong.  But I LIKED it a lot.  It was extremely funny (unlike the original) and at times macabre.  All in all...Good fun....  And did I say-  Bette was great!  She's such a unique woman....And her transformation was stunning.......  So- go see it!    I give it 3 baseballs out of 4 (for sheer fun-forgetting all else).  JPB 

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hi everyone,  Look for excerpts from my upcoming book here!  First entry coming soon!  Peace, JPB 

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok, Ok.  I know this is going to sound completely insensitive, but it's been bothering me for a few days now.  Yes, it is sad when ANYONE passes away.  I feel for the Prez's family.  But do we have to have a "week" of mourning?  I say this because back when Reagan was President, he did not seem to give a rats ass about those people stricken with AIDS.  In fact, he NEVER MENTIONED the word AIDS during his ENTIRE presidency.  For one hailed as the "great communicator" Reagan failed to take leadership on an issue that was begginning to rear its ugly head during his watch.  Why was that?    One can assume that he just plain didn't care.  Why did we have to lose so many people to a disease whose lives could have been saved- or at least prolonged, if Reagan would have taken a few moments out of his busy life to talk frankly about what was happening.  That didn't happen.    I don't feel any need to honor him for honor is something that is deserved.  Honor is an adhereence to principles considered right. Failing to recognize a health crisis that lead to the infections and deaths of Americans (not to mention those worldwide) is something "lacking" honor.  So for all of you Honoring such a man....remember all of those that have passed away because of what he refused to do.  I'll get off my soapbox for now. Peace! JPB 

						
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Well, this is my first attempt at doing a blog.  I have a website, I belong to friendster.com and I am on the meetup website.  Geez...what else do I have to do to stay up with technology!  I will write more when I have time, but that time is not now.  JPB 

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok,  Sorry I've been away for a while, but I have been working hard on my degree (and its taking up a lot of time!)   After seeing our GREAT former President Clinton at the Democratic Convention in Boston- I longed for the days that he was in office!&nbsp; I don't condone what he did (though I gotta tell you ...who wouldn't want to get a BJ in the Oval Office-just so you can say you did???)   Anyway, I digress.&nbsp; The past four years, have been terrible.&nbsp; I am embarrassed by Bush, he's such an IDIOT.&nbsp;   ...more later....   In the meantime, check out this fun parody of both Bush and Kerry ... it's really funny!    urlLink www.jibjab.com    See you soon!  PEACE,  JPB     

						
</post>


</Blog>