<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This world is cold  But you don't you don't have to go  You're feeling sad, you're feeling lonely, and no one seems to care  This pain you cannot bear    But we all bleed the same way as you do  And we all have the same things to go through    Hold on if you feel like letting go  Hold on it gets better    Your days you say they're way too long  And your nights you can't sleep at all  Hold on  And you're not sure what you're waiting for  And you're not sure what you're looking for      Don't stop looking, you're one step closer  Don't stop searching, it's not over    What are you looking for?  What are you waiting for?  Do you know what you're doing to me?  Go ahead...What are you waiting for?    Hold on if you feel like letting go  Hold on it gets better than you know  Don't stop looking, you're one step closer  Don't stop searching, it's not over
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every time we get hurt, the goal is, obviously, to alleviate that pain. The one thought in a broken mind  is to patch it up. What isn't realized is that is all one can do -  patch.  band-aid.  duct tape.  But  there will always be a mark. There will always be a scar. There will always be a reminder of your past.  In short, pain never goes away.  And each time we're hurt, that takes from us. Our personalities are very rarely affected by the positive  in life, mostly, because humans expect it. We not only want happYness, we feel we deserve it. So when we get it, we not only don't cherish it, it barely even effects us.  Only the negative leaves a scar.  So throughout your life you have a certain amount of strength - a fixed amount. Non-renewable. A gift card of sorts with a fixed amount of it. And each time you get hurt, each time you lose in life, that amount is depleted. One, two, three, four, and your strength ebbs, and you're always  slowly losing at life. You're always being depleted. You always scar.  And so we live out lives, becoming more and more cynical, becoming more and more hurt, some retaliating  by not caring, others rejecting society, still others creating beauty to try to stop the world from scarring further. Nothing - none of it, works.  And one would hope to have nothing on the card at the moment of death, but it never works out that way. Some have something left at the moment where their soul goes to God, and they die fighting, trying to draw one more breath because there is still life within them. Life, so to say, hasn't killed them yet.  And some people lose it all before their physical deaths: their souls die. There is nothing left for them, and these are the recluses, the suicides, the cutters, the burners, the maimers, the killers, the punk revolutionaries ... those without hope.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing bad really, but compared to yesteday, today is just dull. Just music, and a good cold drink. What else does one need to be happy. (dion't bother bringing in the third itme, I know!)
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      42 - the answer to the untimae question of life, the universe, and everything. Seems unable to help me though. Maybe it is because I still do not know the ultimate question of life, the universe, and evrything. Well, we still have 11 hours and 32 minuts as of now until the Vogons come and demolish earth...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay. one sixths of summer school is done. grades were due today. As expected I got an A+ (102.1%) We took a "TEST" - 30 questions multiple choice, AND we got tpo bring in a page's worth of notes!!! easiest thing ever! Summer school is not 2 bad I have to say. It' sjust three hours a day, and we get time there to do the homework, so no homework. So the two major complains against school are eliminated. Finally all the things I ordered are coming in. This is the first time ever that I had a problem with buying electronics online. Hopefully the last too.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yet another sunday. It's too hot to do anything, so I just sit here the whole day sipping mild alcoholic beverages, and reading Steven Hawking's "A Brief History of Time". The formulas all check out so far.  I'm unbelievably bored. School tomorrow - even worse.   Song of the day:  Elvis Presley - A little less conversation   A little less conversation, a little more action please All this aggravation ain't satisfactioning me A little more bite and a little less bark A little less fight and a little more spark Close your mouth and open up your heart and baby satisfy me Satisfy me baby  Baby close your eyes and listen to the music Drifting through a summer breeze It's a groovy night and I can show you how to use it Come along with me and put your mind at ease  A little less conversation, a little more action please All this aggravation ain't satisfactioning me A little more bite and a little less bark A little less fight and a little more spark Close your mouth and open up your heart and baby satisfy me Satisfy me baby  Come on baby I'm tired of talking Grab your coat and let's start walking Come on, come on Come on, come on Come on, come on Don't procrastinate, don't articulate Girl it's getting late, gettin' upset waitin' around  A little less conversation, a little more action please All this aggravation ain't satisfactioning me A little more bite and a little less bark A little less fight and a little more spark Close your mouth and open up your heart and baby satisfy me Satisfy me baby  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm bored. I allready programmed all I can in one day. Read all I can, didi all I can. And still only 1 PM. Damn, Life sentence on earth sucks. I'll take death over it anytime.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      2 days till Tracy returns! Thats' 172800 seconds. That's 172800 times of sad realization that she's not here.  MOOD:  (*_*)  :-... 8}  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, its just 3 hours a day, with two fifteen-minute breaks. Some poeple I know are in my class, and that is good. The teacher is a n00b - just out of college - but he tries. With him its fun, and we don't even have any book-related homework. He said that he has to give them out to us becaus of department rules, but nowhere in those rules does it say that he has to make us carry them back and forth each and every day, or for that matter use them in calss. He gave them out, wrote down our book numberes, and we stached them right back in the pile in the classroom. More teachers should do this. Here it is clear that he knows the subject. If he didn't, he'd not risk by not giving us books. This is nice, as now there's no need for a backpack - just a binder and a pen. The class, "Government", seems fun, and we allready had two debates, both showing off Bush's incompetence - I could get used to this :-D. Hopefully this will continue to be this fun.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Summer school starts tomorrow. What could possible be worse? Exactly even I cannot thing of an answer to that question. I am totally out of things to do. In a way I'm content with summer school starting tomorrow - at least it's something to keep me busy. All programs are selling good, no updates needed. No ideas on what next yet. My day today was lik ethis: Wake up, dog walk, eat, slack off, eat, sleep, wake up, slack of, go 2 bed. That is it.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sundays are bad days be dafault: school closing in on you, last minute work,etc... Toda was worse than usual. Nothing at all to do. Absolute boredom. It's 4:20 and I'm allready out of I deas on what to do. I think I'll go tak a loooong nap, maybe after I'll think of something to do.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      saw the HP3 yeasterdy. My sister is a big fan, so she made me go there at midnight to see it. Well, the cast sucks - the caracters got older, and malfoy no longer fitted in as he should. Also the new Dumbledore sucks. The movie directing was somewhat good, and this accounted a bit for the bad cast, making the movie tolerable quality. Nothin amazing here. Move along. Still looking forward to Chronicles of Riddich, and Ocean's 12.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SCHOL IS OVER. FINALS ARE OVER!!!!! FREEDOM!!! What more can you ask for? Summer will still suck: summer school, but since ints just 2 hours a day, and its government and economics - I'll slack off like never before! Plus I've got real work 2 do. Programs are selling good, but market is still open - need to make more - reap the benefits of the open market.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      	Here's what I realised today. Everything in this world has a price. That is just how the world works, however unfortunate that may be. Some things are more expensive than others, but in the end - the more you have, the more you get; and then you have more, and get yet more. Leonard Cohen summarized this nicely: "The poor stay poor; the rich get rich. That's how it goes. Everybody knows" (song called "Everybody knows"). This should not be a revelation, just more of a thing that one needs to admit before attempting to understand anything.  	Another thing: never try to force people to change rapidly, this will make it even worse, and that is not something you want to do. No specifi exapmles will be given here, as that would be rude, but today, once more, I realised soemthing. People would do anything to keep their world exactly as it is. Thats' just how it is. Even if it currently suck, even if they're on the verge of death, even if it's their doing too. Just keep it as it is. It's easyer this way  	People give up too easily nowadays too. Noone is willing to put up a fight, even if it may change their life for the batter.    Lyrics of the day Keywords: Hopeless, love, suicide  Counting Crows - Black And Blue  Fading everything to black and blue You look a lot like you Shatter in the blink of an eye But you keep sailing right on through Everytime you think you’re learning You just look a lot like me Pale under the blistering sky White and red Black and blue  You’ve been waiting a long time You’ve been waiting a long time To fall down on your knees Cut your hands Cut yourself until you bleed Fall asleep next to me  Wait for everyone to go away And in a dimly lit room where you’ve got nothing to hide Say your goodbyes Tell yourself we’ll read a note that says I’m sorry everyone I’m tired of feeling nothing goodbye Wash your face Dry your eyes  You’ve been waiting a long time You’ve been waiting a long long time To fall down on your knees Cut your hands Cut yourself until you bleed But fall asleep next to me  Have a dream I’m falling down On my face Scrape my knees Scrape my hands until they bleed she's fast asleep next to me Next to me Next to me Next to me   	
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         The summer school is over! Finally. The last day was kind of cool. Vicky brought in donuts for everyone, and there were a lot. Then we did some review, and then too the final. It was 123 questions and Ii finished in 40 minutes. The next person after me was 30 minutes later. I always do scantrons that fast. The test was easy. Here's the hardest question off it "Are credit cards part of the money supply?" Anyone will tell you that the answer is no. That's how easy the test was. After we just talked. Our teacher, Mr. Campion, gave up one of those thanks-for-everything speeches, which unlike the others actually had some meaning to it. Then Dan Kurganoff, being the idiot that he is, asked Mr. Campion to arm-wrestle him. That took exactly four seconds. I'll upload the video on my website sometime soon. Then on the bus home I sat with Olya as usual, but as she was bringing a friend over 2 her house on the bus, we sat 3 to a seat, and we couldn't play chess as we usually did. That was somewhat sad. Now we wont get a chance to play till the beginning of the school year. Well if she continues practicing as much as she did this summer, and continues to improve at the same rate, she's had quite a good chance of beating me in the beginning of the year, so now I have to start practicing too, to avoid the embarrassment of being beaten in chess.  The rest of the summer will probably be work time. I've got a stack of books that I want to read; good thing that summer reading book is finally over! And we're going to Vegas and LA too. Hopefully there'll be something fun to do there. I have lots of work to do this summer. I have 3 custom program requests lying in my inbox, ranging in price from a few 100' to a few 1000's. Plus I've got to finally finish the program I've been working on for a while now:  PalmSFX, and release it.               Three weeks of summer left, and then I'm officially a senior. W00t W00t!               Well it's 1 AM here, so tome to go for a walk with the dog. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3 more days of sumemr school. just 3  more days. final project has been turned it, all the work is done, now just to live through 3 more days, and it will all bo over. I cannot wait! Taking a lot of time lately prograaming, as the more programs I have in the market, the higher the revenue. Hehe, what to do with all that money, that is the question, that I still am unable to answer. Besides that life is going ok, nothing amazing going on, but not too bad either. Mild.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well this weekend was fun.  Went canoeing in wisocnsin, stopped on a few islands, swam a lot, lots of  fun things, would take too long to describe. Then monday and tuesday were as usual - boring. Not much really going on now... 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did nothing the last three days. Same nothingness every day. And same coming up for the next 3 days.   then in 3 days we go off kayaking on some stupid river in wisconsin, cause my dad likes 2 plan surprise outings, so I willnot be back until monday... 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Summer school, home, dog walk, homework, bored to death. What to do, what to do?
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The most useless day evr was today. I did absolutely nothing. At all!!! I started abunch of things, and talked to a few people, but got nothing done at all. Summer school semester 2 starts tomorrow, and that's really depressing. Ugh, economics. Like I dont know how to count money...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What an amazing day! I cannot think of a single thing that caould be done to make it better (well besides making it longer). Havent had this much fun in years! Thanks...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well I leave to vegas today at 5pm, Well yestrday was a totoal suckage, as everyone wjo wa sin position to cause me pain did, and today, well tray finished me off.  Anand warned me this would happen, so I guess I was expection this, and however it was quote a shock. and not a pleaseant one at that. But yeah. I guess i'll survivie. I hope vegas will be interesting, and when i come back i might be able to sort all this out, or to totally forget it all! Anand was right, it seems. however I wil lrefuse to admit that until I have conclusive evidence.  If you need to contact me, use the email(which i'll try 2 check) dmitrygr@gmail.com, or call (847)537-0509, when u hear the voice, press 1, and wait. Personal msgs:       Tracy: Ouch! That was cruel! (Anand warned me this would happen - but i didn't listen) Eleonora: Your entertainment for the week:  urlLink http://dmitrygr.palmz.ru/log.php    Josh: RTFM, then Google, and only then ask!   Brett: Hell yeah!   Jackie: The conformists are attacking, run!  Raffi: The new rammstein video is worth the download   everyone else: looks like u were not worth this space. But dont take it personally! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well summer without school is supposed to be fun, but apparently summer school ruined the prospecs of a fun summer. Almost nothing to do. I've finished a few custom programs, and now I'm reading "My Life" by Bill Clinton. It is quite interesting, and I have to say that critics have been way too harsh. It's an interesting read. I've watched the democratic convention live feed, and I've head quite a lot, and the case against bush is mounting! Watch Kerry's acceptance speach here :  http://mfile.akamai.com/12294/asf/dncc.download.akamai.com/12294/07292004/john_kerry_100.asf  Lately i've been going to sleep even later then usual so I'm somewhat more tired then usual.  Bored to death. If you have any idea of wht to do, or just want to drop by, feel free to do so. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>