<Blog>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My first experience with computers started in the 7th grade. My mom was nice enough to save up all of her grocery receipts for six months so I could buy my very first computer...the Timex Sinclair 1000. The local grocery had a promotional thing going, if you turned in the receipts (six months worth) you only had to pay $50 for the whole shebang!  I was very excited about this computer! The Timex Sinclair had a 3.25 MHZ Zilog CPU, 2K of RAM, connection for a cassette back-up drive, a 16K RAM pack and a thermal printer. If you would like read more about the 1000 use the following link http://oldcomputers.net/zx81.html. As soon as I could I hooked the system up to the T.V. in the living room and off I went. I spent the next 10 hours typing in line upon line of BASIC code to produce a clock that barely kept time, AHHHH heaven.  It was not long before I found other friends and teachers at school who also had the same computer set-up. We soon started an after school computer club that met twice a week. Every thing was going very well However, little did I know that my computing days would soon be coming to an end.   After a while the others in our club started to get borded with using these tiny under powered machines and started upgrading to larger PC's. I could not, due to my parents financial situation, not to mention a lot of people were less than supportive of my new hobby. I was told by an older cousin in no uncertain terms that my lack of mathematical ability would keep me from pursuing a career in computers so I should "just give it up". So I did.  The next real contact I had with computers came shortly after I joined the United states Air Force. The Air force started buying a limited number of IBM compatible 286 machines round about 1990-91. We used them to order supplies and write performance reports. This was my first introduction to the world Microsoft products more specifically Windows 3.1.1. After messing with these machines I felt the fever coming back over me.  I was a little strapped for cash so I tried to find a used IBM compatible machine but, my efforts were unsuccessful. Not long after my search started I received my first credit card (mistake #1 but that is a whole 'nother BLOG). I had several friends that were into computing and they persuaded me to look into purchasing an Amiga 500HD, they said these units were the best out there for gaming which was what I was after at the time (this was another mistake and a whole other BLOG I could write). Needless to say in less than 2 tears Amiga folded and I was left with a lot of useless computer stuff.  Since the Amiga I have owned several machines upgrading from year to year, all of which run windows operating systems. My next project will be to build my own one of a kind system, geared mostly towards programming and web design. I start a introduction to programming course with the university of Maryland in two weeks. Well I've rambled on enough time to get work researching computer stuff for this BLOG Joe sends... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally have found the courage to start my very own Blog. I've decided that my Blog will dedicated to the passion in my life...Computing. I wish to learn all that I can about computers and computing by building this blog and eventually turning into a full blown website. Please feel free to e-mail with criticism, suggestions, links to cool sites or something you would like me to post on this Blog. Let us dive in shall we!  I guess the most logical place to start would be with a definition. Computer:An electronic device that processes data according to instructions fed into it (Geddes & Grosset English dictionary). Computer:A device that computes, especially a programmable electronic machine that performs high-speed mathematical or logical operations or that assembles, stores, correlates, or otherwise processes information (Dictionary.com). Personal computer:  general-purpose single-user microcomputer designed to be operated by one person at a time (The Free On-line Dictionary of Computing, © 1993-2003 Denis Howe). Simple enough I guess, I added the personal computer definition because that is the term I hear most often when friends of mine refer to their computers.  The preceding  definitions are very basic ones, and I've done this on purpose I do not wish to confuse anyone on this subject (especially me). If I were to use a lot complex definitions with lots of big words people would lose interest in my postings very quickly. Keep It Simple Stupid Is one of my basic rules. If anyone sees me straying from this beaten path please feel free to set me straight! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>