<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Underground sources have recently reported to me of year 8 parties at uni high with young girls getting wasted and stoned with the alchohol and marijuana being supplied by dodgy year 11's with unknown motives. More info to come.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Am happy to report that there were no major acts of discrimination at Pablo's party. If anyone disagrees say so. The usual women against me discrimination continued one older woman saying she prefeered a 13 yr old named jethro to me. Nothing else too blatant or egregious to report though.  Shalom,  Max K
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      news from the underground, missed out on Zoi's party last night. didnt score an invite possibly because am jewish. Neil didn't get an invite either. Coincidence? Zoi also has short hair. She will be placed under watch by the m3r for more possible acts of discrimination. Going to Pablo's party tonight. Will report on any descrimination that takes place there.  Most likely descrimination: women against me  Peace out
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you're a member email me and want to help run the site emaoil me and i'll put you on the staff list. If you want to become a member email me with your details and i'll see what i can do. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Inaugural posting. Member List:  Alex Turnbull Max Kaiser Rev. John Croker Neil Perlman Fregmonto Stokes Hart Ely-Faulks Alice Moyo NouChee Lee Anwar Abdullahi Jacob (the christian)  more to come... 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      m3r's Neal Pearlman has gone back to Iowa. He has promised to keep on posting and talking from there but it's still sad to see him go. He is an intelligent, perceptive and fundamentally decent person. During all the time I knew him he was open-minded and didn't let differences of opinion turn into personal dislike, unlike many people all over the world with passionate beliefs.  His time in Australia changed the way many of us thought about America and I think we have changed him as well.  As Neal said, the reason for so many global problems right now is fundamentalism of any sort, where people close their minds and resort to violence. The fact that Neal was able to reflect about his own beliefs makes me respect and admire him as much as anyone I know. He was a funny guy, a good friend to all of us, and could maintain an argument when drunk (Unlike Max, who tried to justify the Vietnam War).  I hope he enjoyed his send-off at Phillip Island, and that life treats him well back in the heartland of America.  Admin. OK APC considering you are effectively anonymous and most of your comments are offensive i'm giving you until tuesday to reveal your identity, if you do not all your posts will be deleted. And also whoever this is does not understand the purpose of this site. m3r is a forum for all different political views to be expressed, except for of course fascist ones such as yours cryptofascist however is allowed. I don't know what i'm saying but Peter has the full support of the m3r community and until you reveal your identity APC you have none.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As reported by Max I was discriminated against by Ludowyke because of my links to soviet composers (See my comment on his post) . I have since done some research and found that the school has been hijacked by young liberals who want to make us all fat with junk food.   1.Teishan's young liberals are influencing the staff and are getting media to come to the school next term.   2. Reports on the news have shown footballers have been sponsoring mcdonalds in school  3. The recent film Super size me has exposed the link between conservative governments and fastfood  4. John Howard doesn't want to do anything about junk food  Ludowyke knows that communists are all fit because otherwise Stalin and Mao would have killed them and that fatness is a symptom of capitalism. The Liberals are making us fat so that our brains will slow down and we'll vote for thwem.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok here's the deal. Fregmonto and i having been let out of italian early, ventured downstairs to see what was hapenning. And there was like this eating disorder resource manual for schools being lauched in the theatre. There were in fact two ministers attending this event,the honourable Bronwyn Pike minister for health and the  urlLink publicity hungry  Jacinta Allan the minister for Education Services and Employment & Youth Affairs. So anyway Freg and i sneak in there and check out what's going on. I grab a pamphlet type thing to see what its about. We've arrived at the end of the presentation. But there's still all these TV cameras there interviewing people, they were at that moment interviewing Bronwyn, So Freg and I walk past behind her. and lo and behold there's a split second clip of me walking behind her on the news that night. But anyway we go over and hang out with Claire and Pearl and such who were there to look pretty for pictures. Now here's the descrimination. So we're all in the theatre waiting to be interviewed for channel 7, the token male student has nicked off, so its left up to me or Freg to fill his place. Freg says this to Ludo, and hes all like 'sure just line up behind Claire and stuff'. Then i'm like, i know i'm using the word like a lot, its like totally hilar, anyway i step in but then I realise i have to go do some chem homework with Alex or i'll get killed by the crazy croatian teacher who likes to tell us that she's very disapointed with us at whatever opportunity she gets. So i say 'Hey Fregs more articulate anyway, i'll be off' So I walk  off and Freg takes my place. And at this moment unbeknownst to me Ludowyke realises that Freg is actually kind of scruffy looking, carrying round his shostakovich CD with a stale bread roll and an orange balanced on top, tearing off pieces of the roll and getting crumbs all over himself. So anyway Ludowykes like 'fuck I can't give the TV people this weirdo to interview' so he makes up this bullshit excuse that, Freg needs parental permission to be interviewed. Obviously this is a fallacy as Claire was shown on the news later that night getting interviewed and she tells me that Ludowyke just grabbed her off the stairs and told her to come and be part of it that day. Discrimination I say.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lavish me with praise.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok if any teachers are reading this site please piss off. it's none of your business so just stay out. this is our own student forum for discussing issues without descrimination. Here stuff will be spoken about such as how Ms Wright admitted to deliberately locking me and Neal in the community centre toilets for 20 mins coz we were pissing her off, and then pretending she didnt know when she let us out at the end of the lesson. We shouldn't have to stand for this kind of shit. So please let us have our say with our friends without anyone spying on us. Its not like we're plotting to overthrow the teachers or anything, starting with attaching a car bomb to mr Hatters car. So please FUK OFF. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I ask M3R members the question: Do you think M3R's morale has taken a massive blow, in that no one wishes to post for it brings up hurt from when they were five years old, or even hurt caused by the controversy last week, and because there are no posts M3R is now shit?  To what extent do you agree or disagree with this statement? discuss.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ok, jimmy, pete, neil. Here it is my first design for the team alpha T-Shirt, just tell us what u think and if u think its to complicated i can dumb it down a notice but yeah thats it till then see ya
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Terence Chesterfield and his cronies have infiltrated the school. Posters will be popping up all over the place any moment. There's a meeting this week, Neal,Max, me and any other m3r members that are interested are going to infiltrate it, report back and bring down these bastards from the inside. Only then will we know Chesterfield's TRUE identity, and the identities of our enemies inside the school. This is not to attack liberal supporters, but to ACTUALLY JOIN THE YOUNG LIBERALS REQUIRES A LEVEL OF DEPRAVITY BEYOND HUMAN UNDERSTANDING.  My grandparents are liberal voters and very nice people BUT THEY HAVE NO SOULS!!! Their eyes glaze over when you talk about politics and their forked tongues flicker in their mouths as they sliver down into their subterranean abode and do MATHS. That's right, Maths is a form of discrimination invented by LIBERALS.   A certain Maths teacher at school detains both MAX and NEAL for no reason, and when I go NUTS in class she does NOTHING.  WHY? I'LL LET YOU JOIN THE DOTS!  MATHS WAS INVENTED TO OPPRESS MINORITIES, THE LIBERAL PARTY WAS FOUNDED BY PEOPLE SCARED OF MINORITIES, SO SMELL THE MUSIC DAMN IT, DON'T LET THEM TAKE OVER THE SCHOOL!!!!!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This one goes out to Meggan
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      because of insiders from M3R we will have had to disban the old link so no one can post there anymore and it is now i woul like to get a vote going on banning clancy on ever coming to m3r, all who agree please say so in the comments and the votes shall be counted and hopefully he will leave  so id like to join hart in his call out to the snitch and i have one last message to you DO U NOT GET IT ITS OUT OF SCHOOL, ON THE INTERNET, THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE TEACHERS AND THEY CANT DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT  GOING TO THE TEACHERS IS AS DUMB AS TAKING A SHIT IN THE BOYS TOILETS AT SCHOOL. THIS IS A PLACE WERE WE CAN VOICE OUR OPINIONS SO IF U DONT LIKE IT GET THE FUCK OUT, COZ NOW MOST PEOPLE WANT YOU OUT.  and to the rest of u until we speak again, see ya :D
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok everyone this will be the new website for the m3r's but i need to ask you the members if we should delete all previous posts on the now defunct m3r.blogspot.com if i can. its fuking annoying. I'm letting john back in becoz it was aserious situation but from now on if anyone goes to the teachers about anything on this website they're immediatel;y banned from this website. I'm really not sure what to do here. If you want to keep running this site say so. but i'm fuking paranoid now. i think you can still access info on the old site, hopefully this one isnt discovered also ahhhhh. idon't even know if i can delete the posts on the old website now. damn penis farters
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The m3r website is fighting valiantly against discrimination and censorship. Recent events have put the site under threat and there have been calls to move it and delete all the previous information to protect our revolutionary motives. I urge Max not to be intimidated by the conformist educational forces. We are entitled to our opinions if they are not offensive.   Also I have inside information that a secret terrorist cell of young liberals is being set up inside the school. They are already starting to brainwash students and we must act fast to counter this threat. Stand firm Comrades!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Firstly I would like to say I approve of the new American we've got to replace Neal. She has offered to challenge him to mortal combat to win our hearts. I'm taking bets, Megan Nu-Ju (Max's title) is at $1.03 and Neal's blown out to $251. She's from San Francisco, the city of sin in the  eyes of Iowans, and is Neal's nemesis in every way. I'm glad that the school has stopped discriminating against personal hygeine by finding a replacement for Neal. (No offense Neal, but I suspect from your ruddy features and constant heammoroging that you have Ebola.)    In a related topic, this time in agreeance with Neal, I have come to the logical conclusion that the only way we can bring about a world  free of discrimination and nuclear weapons is to bomb all the countries with nuclear weapons. I vote that we start with England because it is rainy and I have relatives there who are part of the National Front. I think we have to accept that England (like Neal) is past its use-by date and for its own sake must be put down. Only then will we achieve our anarcho-syndicalist utopia. Gather your explosives comrades!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Meggan (Californian) - What is there in Iowa, there's nothing to do. (This implies that Iowa is boring and crap, which is discrimination)
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      These people who say steve Irwin goes to far with his documentry's are simply self indulgent, and have no idea about why he actually makes these documenrty's. It is discrimination against a crazy australian (maybe jewish!). If he wasnts to risk and indanger his life just to make a point about an animals habbitat and raise the much needed awareness that kids and adults wouldnt recive other wise then he bloody well should and he bloddy well does. If what he is doing is wrong and bad for these aniamls, then what the fuck are we doing for the animals? Its simply egotistical biast views from people who obviously dont relise that the reason those 10ft seals are indangered is because they drive a 10 seater family wagon for only there money hungry selves. Go Steve, have some fun and educate us all! 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://teamwin.blogspot.com/2004/06/home-group-for-11b.html  btw there is a new links section on the sidebar, please check out all of these. If any m3r member has a website to suggest for this section please say so and i'll add it.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    (i have prieviously raised this issue but thought it needed it's own space)  Recently i saw a movie called 'The Hebrew Hammer.' and i was worried about whether or not i could laugh at it seeing as i'm not jewish. is it discrimination to laugh at jewish comedies if your not jewish? similarly as it is acceptable for black people to use the N word but it's not acceptable for white people? please explain someone! also... i want a poll on who are the hottest sex bomb out of these two, i await your opinions... i think they are equal heart throbs!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Merlin has proven himself to be the only big brother contestant ever to have both a brain and a conscience. For those that didn't tune in tonight Merlin put tape over his mouth, refused to speak and held up a sign saying 'free the refugees'. the hostile reaction from the crowd to this further proves that queenslanders are a bunch of rednecks. Nice one Merlin
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was sitting back on my rocking chair slurpen on a peach, stairing at the situation, rocking back and forth when i had to ask my self. What does EMO really mean? so i started some intensive research, My first stop was Google. Nothing there except everything i didnt want to see about EMO. It claims that emo is extensivly just emo punk. This were i have to disagree, this is my purpose! EMO is a shortened term for the word emotional. Who the hell invented the word EMO for it to mean emo punk. wouldnt it its shortened term be like; EMUNK, PMO, EMK and the list goes on! I think people dont understand the meaning of EMO beacuse its actually everywhere, this piece of writting is EMO because it has emotion. This is what im trying to say, in everything there is emotion, which means all music is emo, which also means people use the wrong freaking word to describe one perticular type of music (emo punk). Bands like Tool and iron maiden are as emo as any other band beacuse they express emotion. No longer bands like simple plan and Good charlotte can simply be called EMO. All music is EMO, can you think of a song that doesnt express emotion? Even techno (my most feared music) express emotion. Jakes Gangster rap, express emotion! All music has emotion. You cant call one style simple just EMO.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not quite. But the OFLC have overturned their own ruling that Harry Potter be M rated, they've bowed to corporate pressure and its being released as a PG movie. The OFLC is a disgusting censorship institution which the m3r club is as of today launching a campaign against.  With their ruling of an M rating for this film they have proven ther irrelevancy to the people of Australia. When the age newspaper asked parents if they had any concern about taking their children to an M rated film, many parents said they didnt even know about the rating and others couldn't give a shit. This film is a childrens film and a fine one at that. Pretty much as soon as this M rating was announced the distibutors here in Australia applied to have it overturned and instead of sticking to their guns the OFLC have bowed to pressure. The OFLC is also heavily influenced by right wing censorship groups. Having given the film 'Irreversible' an R rating they're now going back after some prudes who want it banned have complained. The hearing will be held in Late June. You may remember further ridiculous acts by the OFLC including re rating Hannibal as an R after complaints while it was already showing in Cinemas. Many people between the ages of 15 and 18 having already have seen the film making the re-rating a complete farce, See Also the banning of Ken Park and the Banning of Baise Moi.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    An m3r member valiantly fighting against discrimination.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think we should have a meeting at Cafe Schevardze, or something like that, a Jewish deli somewhere in Melbourne. I can get my mom to pay for some of it, but if that would be too expensive/too much of a bitch to do, then lets go to MacDonalds or something, and then go to that movie that disses MacDonalds, or the other way around.  Also, I'm gonna quit my job as pornography minister, since nobody other than anwar has asked me for porn, and I think that was just random because I'm pretty sure he is illiterate, so wouldn't have seen this site. Plus for some reason in a club dominated by dudes, liking porn has made me enemies, which kind of disturbs me in its own way.   Admin. see comments for administration talk. btw when i talk of goos posts and bad posts i mean that alexs post on the GAT was a welcome postso was hillarys on Miriam. Peters post was agood as aone off and raised many issues concerned with discrimination. Harts wasnt that great. niether was jakes. Evans was about something but i think the type of posts that hart, jake and evan made were probably better relegated to the comments of some other posts. Please in the future. if you're unsure about whether to post or not get in contact with me through god_is_maxibonk@hotmail.com.  This post will remain open for people to have their say on administration issues.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You may vote to delete this post as it is of no importance abut I apologise to all the members for my pedophilic comments. If they offended then I am deeply sorry. I just like them young is all, not too young mind you. Legal? sometimes, but never anything younger than year 8. I've never really liked females of my age or older. Some may say that the liking of younger ones is my way of feeling superior (ie. bigger, stronger etc. than them) but this is not true. I don't know what it is... but... *shrugs* I don't know... Seeing as this is an anti-discriminatory site, I dont expect any criticism or the likes, but still... I want it. Comment.... NOW! I YEARN FOR DISCRIMINATION!!!!  - the deeply sorry and very hideous, Jake.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    So its come to this
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever since you u gave up your leader ship over this place it has gone into total chaos people posting completly random shit and then its just getting to hard to read u need to put it back to the way it was simple and easy with out all this stupid stuff
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And know this Children I am not right wing but I am not left wing, I think Hitler was a great leader but with very F***ed up ideas, I think that the war on Iraq had to be done but not by the states and not but covering it in lies, I do think refugees should be detained but not like they are and not as long as they have been, I will not protest and go to rallies about it because I think it proves nothing but stupidity if your going to protest do it silently and vote against the party dont disrupt people's lifes so you and some others and have a cry and yell insulting chants that would make your own mother think twice about saying, I hate nobody ( not even John Croaker), but gruge against those who think they are a higher being because of thier political veiw, I hold no gurdges against anybody I personaly think that life is to very short to hold fueds and that aggression only fuels high blood pressure, I may be seen as a Right wing arsehole that hates everyleft wing I come across, WRONG I dislike it when they force thier views upon others and try to recuirt the children on this wonderfull nation governed by morons, I am not for john howard or the cheating G.W.Bush jn and think that war is a wate of time but it stettles many-a-thing, I do not litter, smoke (anything), and although I drink I think that Alcohole should be banned as it rips to many familys apart, I have fired a gun but never would out of hatered. This and many more things may come as a shock to some and not to others, but I ask of you, Yes you, Every M3R member,poster,onlooker or veiwer to please let me have a fair go and not to go on what you have heard. I am not the arsehole I have been made out to be, just somebody defending themselves from a stereo type they have been handed and not earnd. Please if you think this is not true post or come and taalk to me about it, better yet do both. yours faithfully Peter Anthony O'Neill. pete Von-wolfestien. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Morning ladies. Well, it seems that the main forces behind the act of violent discrimination on the day of our english SAC have been penalised for their wrongdoings. As far as I know, jackson has been suspended for a week or, as according to Angus, until he admits what he did was wrong (and not to mention discriminatory). The fact that his fellow  'g'z'  or  'krew'  are nowhere to be seen indicates that they may have been suspended along side their companion. All I can say is this: sweet, sweet, deserving, victory. Enemy forces have been detained. God bless justice!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is quite possible that hart is the greatest. All the people who agree or have a differnt opinion feel to have your legs broken. Max is also cool. plus everyone else especially you, not you cleo. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As a shadow president and as a student I have a vested interest in education, it is an important tool in the war against discrimination. Today I, like some other m3r members participated in the GAT, a general achievement test given out by the Victorian curriculum and assessment authority (VCAA) to all students doing a year 12 subject. And lo! To my surprise it was full of discrimination.  Not only discrimination but a booklet full of contradictory confabulations of relativism and absolutism, the non maths questions are almost all perspective dependent but then they demand a single answer in the form of multiple choice questions. This idiocy is infuriating, how can there be one given answer to an opinionative question? Whatever happened to social relativism; what may be true and obvious for say someone from an Australian background may not be so true for someone from Asia or America. The questions in the afore mentioned GAT required not only a high level on English but a particular cultural outlook, something which not all the students in our diverse school have.  Some questions ask for an analysis of cartoons and texts, how can everybody agree on what they mean when even people in the same family disagree about there meanings? since by there very nature they are meant to have an infinite amount of interpretations, each person looking at it in their own valued and equally true way. And since we all have to do the GAT next year, I feel that something should be done to correct this insidious corruption and mindless stupidity in out education system.  What do fellow m3r members say? 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is from the office of pornography, and for its distribution. Or former office, depending on your vote after reading this. When I first created the ministry of pornography, I, like Max, Peter, and Anwar, chose positions that best suited their talents. I am an expert in the traditional Ralph style pornography, along with more internet age Paris Hilton sex tapes dubbed in Korean. However, certain people have misinterpreted this and view my posts as a sort of written pornography, exciting those who oppose my views. They, shall we say, intellectually masturbated to my posts, creating a fierce debate. Now, to take a bad metaphor too far, we have reached orgasm. Will the office of pornography fall? You decide.  WANKERS UNITE 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I Max K have bowed to the overwhelming pressure to unseat myself as Dictator of the m3r club and from henceforth this site will be run as a grass roots Brazilian-style participatory democracy with anarcho-syndicalist overtones and undertones in accordance with the wishes of our members. There will be no titles. I will maintain my position of Administrator but memebers may become administrators if they are elected popularly. Any other suggestions for the running of this site are welcome.I will no longer take unilateral action in deleting comments and posts.  Thank you and good morning Max K
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Controversial Reality TV star 'Miriam' (a.k.a Paulo Venegas) has left six British men emotionally wounded by her web of deception and lies. Maybe if they weren't so strongly against the idea of hooking up with a transsexual then they wouldn't be suffering the lingering after-effects of discrimination! I thought to myself, we need someone like her in this grand country of ours, uncovering the rife descrimination against transsexuals that goes on behind closed doors (and two-way glass). To my delight, my prayers have been answered! Miriam, Anti-Discrimination Goddess, is coming to Australia. Better yet, she is coming to our TV screens. Miriam in our living room!     8:30pm Friday Miriam enters the 'Big Brother' house under the guise of a sexy latin-dance teacher, codename: 'Maria'. Housemates are unaware of that little 'something' about Miriam, as they were inside the house when the Reality TV show 'There's Something About Miriam' aired in Australia. Sources say that Miriam has sensed an anti-transsexual vibe flowing from bachelor Ryan, Kane, and married-man Paul. Her particular method of investigation will certainly be effective in discovering and eliminating any transgressors. The m3r Club wishes Miriam well during her 3-day stay within the confines of the Big Brother house.  Source:  urlLink Six Sue Sky Over Sex-Change Snogger   urlLink Miriam Eyes Contenstants 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I, Queencleo of EDSC, declare that I have been discriminated against Either by PHSC as a whole, or just by Dictator Max  Whether this is because I don't attend your school, I once dated members of your strange community, I am atheist, I am a lesbian or any other random reason you have picked  I am being ignored as an individual And I am pointing out now I have my rights I will be heard
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Neal's ranking system is turning an egalitarian inclusive blog area into a GENTLEMEN'S CLUB. Look at all these titles these men are giving themselves! This kind of ranking system is discrimination and hypocritical in the extreme. Neal has exposed his TRUE AMERICAN IMPERIALISTIC COLOURS with this act. He must wean himself from his MILITARISTIC HEIRARCHICAL SOCIETAL INFLUENCES to truly prove himself anti-discriminatory. He is a nice chap but what is he playing at with these titles? Minister of Pornography?? Who does he think he is? Hugh Hefner? I can just see them smoking their cigars, oppressing the masses, laughing all the while. Down with the Gentlemen's club! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      De facto President - Max K Vice President - Anwar Minister for Finances and the Distribution of Pornography - Neal cheif of Armed forcess/terroism and international comunications - Peter  Add your position..
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      brazen discrimination against 11D was perpetrated today by none other than the antichrist herself Ms. Nolan.  The english SAC she gave us was missing vital information that all the other classes got, disadvantaging us greatly.  'Sickening! says our new vice president Anwar Abdullahi.  Post all of your exam complaints and discrimination here. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Caption competition:
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Recently, last Saturday, I went to a really shit party with crappy pizza. I stayed for only 10 minutes because I didnt know anyone except Peter, and he left too. However, we saw two impersonators of prinny hill people, one of whom is highly ranked in the M3r club. There was someone who called himself Goran, who looked exactly like Max K. If he hadnt been rapping and dancing (well) at the time, I would have thought it was him. Seeing how the guy sucked and was a dick, he must have been trying to bring down our reputation. There was also a girl who looked exactly like boof. But she doesnt really matter. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      m3r: can you tell me what that fight was about? Jake: it was about fuck all Jake: a homeboy wanted to start angus m3r: who's that jackson kid Jake: for no reason m3r: no reason? Jake: the ugly one me and angus gave a black eye when he was in year 7 m3r: how did u give him a black eye m3r: ? Jake: how else? m3r: wat year's he in now? Jake: 9 Jake: lol m3r: y did u give him ablack eye m3r: and anyway Jake: he started shit m3r: so he just waits 2 years for his revcenge? jake: lol, yeah jake: idiot   m3r concurs  m3r has got Angus' back on this one  Peace out  Max K  P.S. Leave a comment if you have any insight into what happened.  P.P.S. See comments for a more detailed analysis by jake
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Peter wants to be a member and we decided to let him in. If anyone objects, just post a response. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.smh.com.au/articles/2004/06/03/1086203546602.html?from=top5 http://www.aph.gov.au/live/webcast1.asp http://www.fahrenheit911.com/trailer/ http://clintflicks.com/musicvideos/dpl/  Choose your best thing ever
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Viv: 'They're all italians so they'll all be in the mafia" Adam: 'I don't like asian drivers" Freg's Busdriver: 'I hate punks. Get off my bus you deviant anarchist crackwhore' (whilst freg had a mohawk for the play)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hart has kindly designed this stunning logo for the m3r group. Although there's a star of david we are a strictly secular website.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For anyone wondering how the Sac experiment went. here are the results.    Neils: 25/25 Maxs:22/25  Conclusion: Ms Nolan has no personal bias towards students its just that she likes her essays boring and predictable.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not sure where the connection between oil and the war in Iraq is. I know that Iraq has a ton of oil, and that some people think that the reason we invaded Iraq was to exploit this oil, but unless I'm missing something, I think the United States is in fact losing tons of money on the war. We have spent 87 billion so far in Iraq, and it looks like we will continue to spend more. The oil in Iraq is owned by the Iraqi government, which distances itself from the US more and more. The US will have the same access to their oil as previously, and in fact it may be less because of the militants attacks on oilfields. You may say that the reason that the Bush adminstration wanted to attack Iraq was because of their connection to the oil business, and this may be true. However, the reason that 70% of Americans supported the war (not me however) was because they thought we were going to fight a dictator who committed genocide, not because they would profit more from the easier access to oil. Don't even mention Halliburton, they aren't ripping anyone off except we stupid Americans. I am genuinely not sure, but could someone please tell me what the difference between now and our access to Iraq's oil fields, and previously? Thanks. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In recent weeks there have been a few poster campaigns at school. Namely m3r campaigns and satirical Young Liberal campaigns. These have been met with nothing but disrespect and ignorance. M3r posters have reportedly been removed by Hatters as well as numerous young liberal posters going missing. This can be blamed on stupid students as well, who don't get the joke. Overall however there is a complete lack of respect for these poster campaigns and the the removal of them amounts to nothing less than a stifling of our freedom of speech.  Poster the shit out of PHSC about anything you care about or want to get across. We should not have to ask for the teachers permission. Its our fundamental right. FIGHT FOR IT ! 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The following may be of comical interest to the readers. It is an compilation of quotes that I recently received, spoken by none other than the most powerful man in the world. Enjoy....   Quotes from the first three years . . . . . > > can the English language survive? > > > >  "The vast majority of our imports come from outside the country." > > - George W. Bush  "If we don't succeed, we run the risk of failure." > > - George W. Bush > > > >  "One word sums up probably the responsibility of any Governor, and that one word is 'to be prepared'." > > - George W. Bush > > > > >  "I have made good judgments in the past. I have made good judgments in the future." > > -George W. Bush > > > >  "The future will be better tomorrow." > > - George W. Bush > > > >  "We're going to have the best educated American people in the world." > > - George W. Bush >> > > > > > >  "I stand by all the misstatements that I've made." > > - George W. Bush > > > >  "We have a firm commitment to NATO, we are a part of NATO. We have a firm commitment to Europe. We are a part of Europe." > > - George W. Bush > > > > >  "Public speaking is very easy." > > - George W. Bush > > > > >  "A low voter turnout is an indication of fewer people going to the polls." > > - George W. Bush > > > > > >  "We are ready for any unforeseen event that may or may not occur." > > - George W. Bush > > > > >  "For NASA, space is still a high priority." > > - George W. Bush > > > > > >  "Quite frankly, teachers are the only profession that teach our children." > > - George W. Bush > > > > > >  "It isn't pollution that's harming the environment. It's the impurities in our air and water that are doing it." > > - George W. Bush > > > > >  "It's time for the human race to enter the solar system." > > - George W. Bush  Also, in the true spirit of propaganda preceding election time, some pics!   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush.jpg   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush1.jpg   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush3.jpg   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush4.jpg   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush5.jpg   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush6.jpg   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush7.jpg   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush8.jpg   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush9.jpg   urlLink www.chewyshoe.com/bush10.jpg      
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm don't know nearly enough to post myself about this issue.But its a very very serious one. I'll leave it up to Mandisi Majavu, you can read his blog  urlLink here.   &nbsp; Still no peace in Sudan Posted by Mandisi Majavu at July 19, 2004 12:45 PM  Four months after the UN described the Darfur crisis as the “world’s humanitarian disaster” little has been done – what some describe as ethnic cleansing has not stopped and peace is still as elusive as before the international community started to show some interest in the region. And according to Jan Egeland, the UN coordinator of emergency relief, the UN started slowly in Darfur where aid workers say 350 000 might die of disease or malnutrition.  One would be compelled to conclude that the UN has a serious weakness of slow motion, because just ten years ago we saw the same snail pace reaction to the genocide that took place in Rwanda where about 1 million people were killed in the course of 100 days without the UN intervention.    The fighting in the Darfur region started last year, February 2003, between the allied militia groups known as Janjawid and the two Darfur rebel groups – the Justice and Equality Movement and the Sudan Liberation Movement. According to Amnesty International, the Janjawid are armed, funded and supported by the Sudanese government. Also, a report by the UN human rights found that the Janjawid have killed civilians, raped them, burnt down villages and poisoned wells. The 18 months conflict is believed to have killed about 30 000 people and has displaced more than a million people.  As things stand, it is believed that about 2 million people are in need of emergency relief in the states of Western Northern and Southern Darfur.  The peace negotiations that started last Thursday, 15 July, are reported to have ended up in a screaming match. The Darfur rebels are demanding that before any negotiations can take place the government troops and the Janjawid militias be removed from the Darfur region; a demand the government says it’s totally unrealistic, according to the UN news. The Darfur rebels are also demanding that the Janjawid be disarmed and people who are suspected of genocide and ethnic cleansing be prosecuted.  Meanwhile, on the international arena, Amnesty International has called on the UN Security Council to impose an arms embargo on the Sudanese government and militias allied to it. However, not all Security Council members, especially the members which have close economic ties with Sudan, are enthusiastic about going down that route. Revealing the hypocritical character of the international community, for while everyone seems to agree that the violence and killing must stop in Sudan, no one is prepared to make serious efforts by stopping the sales of weapons to the fighting rebels in Sudan.  And so the killing continues. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I on behalf of m3r endorse Marxof
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Is John Kerry the answer?
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Information about the up-coming melbourne Rally for Child Care and Paid maternity leave. Rally for Childcare and Paid Maternity Leave Women are saying that we want to decide when, if and how we have children. Without access to crucial supports like paid maternity leave, affordable childcare and an independent income, we don't have a real choice. All that Howard and the Labor Party offer is a narrow view of motherhood and a welfare scheme for mothers who stay home, with many strings attached. It's time to take action!   Let's put our plan: * free, quality 24-hour childcare * pay equity for all childcare workers * employer-funded paid maternity leave for all women * equal pay, equal employment opportunity and secure jobs for women * and more!   SATURDAY, 28 AUGUST, 12.00 NOON Treasury Place, Spring Street, Melbourne (outside Peter Costello's federal office) Endorsers (in progress): Australian Services Union, International Women's Day 2005 Collective, Radical Women, Socialist Alliance   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I always knew this guy was dodgy.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.alephbet.org/  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      America vs. Australia (basically, Iowa vs. Victoria) When I first got to Australia, and went to school there, I thought it was incredibaly easy, compared to my school back in Iowa. The subject material was a lot easier, as was the grading scales. The teachers, with the exception of Mr. Thompson and Ms. Plymin, were not even close the quality of Iowan teachers. In Iowa, you can choose different levels for each class. For example, you can take Basic English, English, and English Honors. Your previous teachers tell you which one would be best for you, but you don't have to follow their guidelines. The one thing I like was how in English and Literature we wrote creative pieces, which I hadn't done since the sixth grade. Although the school seemed much easier, the way to get into university seemed ridiculously hard. To have almost your entire entrance based on one test at the end of the year is absurd. Infinitely many things can happen to someone on that one day. A relative could die, their parents could get a divorce, or they just be really sick. Then they do poorly on the exam, and they basically fail life. In America, the universities look at your extracurricular activities, your grades throughout high school, your standartized test results, and many other things such as race and economic backgrounds to determine your entrance to university. Even if you do not do well throughout high school and drop out, you can take an equivalency test, which if you pass, basically means you are the same as a high school graduate. You can then go to a community college, which are somewhere between trade schools and universities in the Australian system, for two years, transfer to a university, graduate, then go to medical school and become a doctor. This would be impossible under the Australian system.&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok noone comes to m3r anymore. noone posts or comments so i'm just going to post any old shit. On Thursday we will be launching our advertising campaign to counter&nbsp; Teashan's evil Young Liberal campaign. If you have any deas on what to put on the posters say so. I'm thinking at the moment.   Stop the Young Liberals Fight Discrimination Join m3r today  something like that. Ideas? 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys. Look what Peter found.&nbsp;  urlLink www.5m3r.blogpot.com .  Also to all you people bitching and insulting eachother. Pukin stop it. This site is not for personal fights. You're welcome to come and join in the debates. But don't just come to this site to start trouble.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok this just in from our undercover Uni High correspondent. Details are sketchy at the moment but apparently a uni High tough has beaten up one of our Princes Hillians at the tram stop. Apparently it was a yr 10 that was beaten up. His identity remains a mystery. Can anyone fill us in? If it was just a Homie then Puk that . its not worth a post. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In Australia it is compulsory to vote, or at least to get your name marked off at the polling booth. I think that this is a good idea and the way it ought to be but others disagree. We are a very rare case amongst nations having this law but its&nbsp; a strength of our democracy not&nbsp; a weakness. Its a small duty to all the other Australians who vote and also those that can't yet. I personally will be relishing my chance to vote when it happens an i cannot wait to be involved in our democratic processes. Now the issue for people that disagree with mandatory voting is that people should be able to choose. And they are able to choose. They only have to spend a short time at the polling station then they get on with their lives. making it compulsory engages people with&nbsp;politics, it encourages them&nbsp;investigate policies and&nbsp;form opinions on&nbsp;issues. In America people don't vote because they don't care about certain issues its because both parties are so similar in what they stand for that it breed voter apathy and disengagement. At present it isn't cool to vote although&nbsp;it may be fashionable this year as the movement grows to get rid of the symptom of America's sick system rather than to fix the cause. Many other nations get by fine without this system and i think in a perfect world we would get by fine as well. But compulsory voting engages with the average person. And throws them into the democratic system forcefully. If we did not have compulsory voting , this nation would be a far less democratic one. And anything that could facilitate Australia being more democratic is a welcome thing indeed. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have just arrived home from a screening of famed activist Michael Moore's new film    urlLink Fahrenheit 9/11 (2004) &nbsp;, I shows the events leading to and after nine eleven, including Americas invasion of Afghanistan and Iraq, basically a story of the cheating bushes illegal rein of terror.  The film telling the other side of the story, commercial (channel 9) media wouldn’t dream of showing.  Though funny, this film presents serious and present issues, having some very disturbing scenes inappropriately followed by a hilarious George W. Bush anecdote.  Throughout this film I found&nbsp;me grinding my teeth out of pure hatred of the us government and restraining my self from charging at the silk screen, yelling abuse at the war hungry tyrant pictured before me.  There was no mention Australia's involvement in the Iraq war, which shows how little impact we had for all the trouble it caused.  The film focusing on&nbsp;exposing bush and his lies to a mindless nation&nbsp;blinded by media, government, confusion and patriotism.  This film doesn’t really have the charm and humor used in 'Bowling for Columbine', using hard facts and having a greater emotional effect.  I would definitely recommend this film to all, I think Peter and Mavericks should definitely see it just for research sake or to open your minds. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok the new m3r project is to create a list of all the teacher's home phone numbers and addresses. We can do this through the  urlLink white pages website  but we need to find out which suburbs the teachers live in to narrow it down. So your homework or rather schoolwork is to find out your teacher's suburbs as subtly as you can. Also as you can see your humble administrator has changed his display name to Nu-Ju and I would ask you all to change your display names and profiles to leave no evidence of who you are.  &nbsp;  BTW if people don't want to be involved in this say so.    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey there's some good stuff  urlLink here  I think as an m3r experiment we should try as many as we can. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey chek this out guys. If Ludowyke tries to  urlLink google himself  look what page comes up as number 1.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In the interests of keeping the site open, maintaining the excellent level of debate we've got going presently and avoiding personal misunderstandings and fights, something needs to be done.   I think Max that you should have placed prominently a list of what we believe and what our site regulations are, to avoid confusion by newcomers, as has happened with A_P_C.  Make it clear all these rules have been decided by the m3r community, and keep the list open to comment so that anyone who's interested can comment and campaign for whatever change they want. Maybe you could have it as a post which you replace and update regularly, and which people can continually vote on.  That way we can see the development of the beliefs of the group as a whole and add another area for people to argue about. It would also increase the feeling of ownership by everyone involved.  Admin.  Rules Ok here are the rules if anybody wants to add some more or challenge a rule say so. Fregmonto you've put me on the spot here. Could you help out.   1.This site is open to debate, all political views are welcome, except for blatantly fascist, racist,homophobic, sexist, basically no descriminatory views are welcome,  we all here have a good sense of humour and these things said in jest with no real feeling beneath them are acceptable. Please don't stop posting things that are un PC just exercise some good taste please. 2. The m3r community does not welcome anonymous posters if they post anything vaguely offensive. Please visitors to this site who aren't known to the m3r community you are welcome to post comments. But if you are known to us a name would be very much appreciated. Your comments will not be deleted unless they are offensive. 3.If m3r is to remain an utterly free cooperative positive forum for the reporting of injustice and for debates it requires all of you to be responsible in your posting. Stick to these guidelines but above all have fun! 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last week, the government was behind a project of slimming up children in schools. Fine, Great, any suggestions of how they could do this? Well, why not go in there and publicise McDonald's, after all, it is the healthiest food around. Celebrity footballers were paid to come to our schools and talk about ways in which to lose weight and become fit. Some of this plan led to the recommendation of McDonald's family restaurants as an aid to the fitness program. Now, I'd like to think that I'm not just having a cheap shot at McDonald's here as that would be contraindicated, but honestly, and especially after the release of Super Size Me (which im yet to see, but I understand it was scary enough for Maccas to have to release an advert campaign to protect themselves by pointing our their understanding of the misinterpretations that this doco may have conveyed). What was the real plan behind this odd occurrence? Is there any plan at all? Is this discrimination against the local businesses of Australia that also supply fast food? What does the government have to gain by backing this hodiernal recommendation. And I also would have expected more from some footballers, I hope it was genuine, and not simply for the money. Any thoughts?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A little question: why does the government encourage everyone to have lots of babies (we have a dropping birth rate) and then say we don't have enough room for refugees  (we don't want these people in our country)? How is this policy created by anything other than fear and racism?  Surely if the government was serious about battling the "ageing crisis" it would welcome newcomers to the country.    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The environment is one of biggest issues facing our world today. There are newspapers, websites, and even whole political parties dedicated to its preservation. The main threats to it are from factories dumping, governments not regulating, and logging. The first two are easily preventable, but the third, which causes a large percentage of the damage is not so easily stopped. The logging is mostly in countries like Brazil or the Congo, where the people rely on it for a living. The logging industry provides work for thousands of people there, and the land cleared provides farming land for thousands more, whose food provides sustance to millions. If the environmental activists had their way, these people would all starve, and it would severely depress the economies of these growing countries, hurting even those who arent in the logging industry.  In the first world countries like Australia, the U.S., or even Tasmania (maybe a two and a half world country), the logging should be cut down on, at least in first growth forests. Also, Uma Thurman is the hottest chick alive, and Jennifer Aniston is the best girl next door.  Admin. This just in- James is gya.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Reviewing all m3r's posts recently I have come to the same conclusion as Hart: Our greatest moment was the debate in the comments on Peter's "let us be fair on the stereotyped" post(June archives). This in turn was in response to the debate about the ranking system. This was the site's richest and most exciting period and I thought at the time m3r had a bright future.   Unfortunately since then the site has been knocked off course by the seemingly interminable bullying saga and teacher intervention.   Although their have been interesting posts since none have generated the same heated but intelligent debate. At Phillip Island I had a great discussion with Neal and Hart on a whole range of issues from America's place in the world to personal religious belief to fundametalism to Guatemalan fruit companies. This is the kind of debate we've been missing. Now that Neal is back in Iowa we have a golden opportunity to hear about the opinions of his friends back there and return to the best days of m3r. Start posting and commenting on things you feel need talking about. You don't have to be deliberately controversial, just say what you believe, and who gives a fuck what any teacher thinks about it.   Admin. If anyone is wondering why there are a few deleted comments around, its because i'm now enforcing our new policy, which is to delete all comments made anonymously. btw this does not mean if you don't have an account with blogger.com you can't post comments, just make sure you leave your name or else your comment will be deleted.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I don't clog up this site with non discrimination iowa news and stuff, we can post on my blog if you want to. www.nealisbetter.blogspot.com
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm moving my thoughts and such to  urlLink my own blog.  This site will only be used for more official things. John and I hopefully will be smacking down lots of people next week, so there will be news. Other people are free to post whatever the shit they want. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The importance of national identity is an interesting issue in its importance. In germany you will nobody expressing national pride to a far degree. If you have a german flag in your house or something like this people will think you're a Nazi. Is this reaction to patriotism to extreme. In America after 9/11 the american flag became ubiquitous.  What does a flag represent. Does the american flag represent as the song says: Compromise, Conformity, Assimilation, Submission, Ignorance, Hypocrisy, Brutality, the Elite. Or is it something else that was yearning to be expressed here. A feeling of collective sorrow, a will to overcome grief, a recognition of the freedom that was taken for granted? In Australia John Howard has tied school funding to the compulsory flying of the australian flag. I find this completely inappropiate, it is enforcing a patriotic position onthe australian student who has never been patriotic and never should be. Where is a healthy point between national pride and irrational jingoism, surely its not up  a flagpole. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Word to all kinds of stuff. Team win has been resurrected. I've been asked to recruit new members. So anyone interested leave a comment right about  urlLink here.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Random unattributed quotes:  Blank space is the transmission of information whereby the viewer has an opportunity to become involved as a participant.  I remember when I was young I would only say I was Jewish if I thought the person asking the question was anti-Semitic.  ...well the answer is that you create a myth. Something that people can play a role in, can relate to. You don't want the truth to be told? Well, I don't want to get philosophical but there is really no such animal. Especially when one talks of creating a myth. How can you have a true myth?... Distortion is essential to myth-making.  Nobody understood it. That is nobody could understand what it all meant yet everyone was fascinated. It was pure information, pure imagery, which in the end is truth.  Actually, all uniforms are enemies. Just another extension of machine living.  Catch-22 says they have a right to do anything we can't stop them from doing.  You don't use a gun on a computer, you pull the plug out.  My girl and I went up to the U.N. today to watch the debate. After a while it seemed so ridiculous and disgusting, my girl and I began to make love in the gallery. They threw us out but I still think what we were doing was more valid than what those clowns were into.  It is up to us to create God. He is not the creator. That is the whole history of Christianity. For we have but one way of creating God, which is to become Him.  As long as there are no myths accepted by the masses, one may go on talking of revolts indefinitely, without ever provoking any revolutionary movement.  - Revolution for the hell of it 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi all, i've just gotten off the phone from my Greek auntie who is in Athens at the moment. She is staying at my grandparents apartment in Kalethea-where the two ararchist bombs went off a few months ago- and had some interesting stories to tell me about the olympic city.  Firstly the airport. She arrived last week. She got through immigration eaysally, collected her bags, then was on her way out to meet our relatives that live in Athens when a police officer approched her. This is a rough transcript of what happened: Police officer(in broken english):" Where are you from?" Auntie:"Australia" Police:"Where have you come from?" Auntie:"Australia" Police:"So, err, do you have anything in your bag?" Auntie:"..........well" Police:"Anything I would be interested in?" Auntie:"No" Police:"Move on".  As for everyday life in Athens, apart from an increase in tourists, things remain the same. My Aunties cousin, who is an olympic voulenteer, is in the opening ceremony on the weekend. She was talking to my Auntie, and invited, in an offhanded way, for her to come to the opening ceremony practice run today!!!!!!!!!! FULLY SIK!!!!!!!!  My Auntie asked her what security passes or precautions she needed to do to go, and was told she can't bring 1-cameras, 2-mobile phones, 3-coins. Apart from that, she is fine to visit. Coins? Aparently the organisers are worried people will throw the coins at the peformers.  She will be ringing me tomorrow, i'll tell you what is in the opening ceromony.   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What say you to the suggestion that Latham is Australia's saviour? What say you to the suggestion the Kerry in America and the world's saviour? Are there any major differences? Is Latham advocating democratising further Australia? Is he suggesting more public control over industry and resources? Is he suggesting a process of reinvigoration? Are his policies going to make a major change in Australia. Or will it be as Naomi Klein has said. Latham in Kerry in, the nback to work. Acoording to her it will be alot easier to work for a change in the system when people are over their personal dislike for leaders. When the gross mutations that are produced by the system and are supposed to represent us are replaced by someone that is a more pure manifestation will we change? Will society change. Will we become communities? Will we have the power or will we be happy and go back to our lives now that Bush and Howard are out of power?  To paraphrase an article in Adbusters, if Kerry gets in when the next war comes you will either be with him or against him. In Australia its more complex than that. Latham will get our troops out of Iraq but we will stay involved in the dubious 'war on terror', Pine gap will stay and there is no objection by Latham to any 'joint training bases' in northern australia. The Labor party has also passed the FTA, backflipped and increased the PBS co-payments, banned gay marriage, and finally and most damning will retain the policy of mandatory detention. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok news from school. m3r posters have been replaced with some starving children posters and an anti sweatshop poster and some other one. However these posters are not affiliated with any group. It would have been nice if they asked us before taking down the m3r poster. Really quite rude. It shall replaced on thursday. Also all blogspot sites have been banned at school. If anyone out there has cable internet and Windows XP contact me as there's some sort f shindig you can do so people can get around the filter at school. We asked Woody what the deal was and he was all like 'some kids complained because there was derogatory language about womens bodies or something'. this may be true, Natasha's post about Lyndie England could be what they were referring to. Anyway its bullshit that they can just block all the blogspots. He said if we wanted to get certain sites exempted from the ban , then we could. So we might delete that post then submit m3r. Any thoughts? 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Do you believe in freedom of expression at school?         Absolutely.        As long as its not's offensive.        Only when its limited to a small student billboard which can still be censored by the vice principal if there is anything vaguely offensive.        Not at all.               urlLink  Free polls from Pollhost.com       
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Over the last couple of months the Paramedics Union and the Government have had a major dispute over working conditions for paramedics. With both sides not backing down, the dispute looks like it's going to continue. I'll summarise the issues:  -Paramedics in Victoria are amongst the highest trained in the World, and deliver exceptional services statewide. -In Victoria, Paramedics are rostered to work four shifts in a row i.e Monday day, Tuesday day, Wednesday day, Thursday day, and then get four days off work.  -Paramedics are in short supply in the state, and so are forced to work in the four day break period, and also are forced to work overtime in their shifts (it is not uncommon for paramedics to be forced to work 15 hour shifts-in very stressful and time critical conditions) -Paramedics work in difficult situations,  their four day break is supposed to help lessen the stress that they face and is now being infringed on. -Paramedics requested two things from the state government 1-more Paramedics (as this is what I want to do when I finish school in two years, I hope they do increase their annual intake-many student paramedics are forced to work at isolated ambulance stations in the country for four or five years before they are ablke to transfer back to their families and friends in Melbourne) and 2-Better working conditions. They have offered to increase the number of paramedics employed, but have not improved conditions. Obviously the government cannot directly stop emergency situationns from being stressful, but they can assist with increases in pay and upholding working hours and ensuring that the ambulance service does not have to call paramedics in from their break days.   -The government did not improve conditions, they did offer a margional pay rise to the union but did not adress the other issues that the paramedics have. The union, after 6 months, decided to strike. -The union/paramedics striked in 30 differant areas, the main strike methods that they use were 1-Ignore hospital bypass (Hospitals have a limited capacity with their emergency wards ie 50 patients. When they fill the majority of them, they will advise ambulance crews to bypass their hospital and go to one that has spaces. Ambulance crews ignore this call, making already full emergency wards go into meltdown). 2-Transport ALL patients (Often, paramedics are dispatched to cases where they are able to treat the medical problem on the scene and are not required to transport the patient to hospital, ie for small lacerations that paramedics can clean and apply a bandage to- they will be transported to the emergency department) and so on. -The government and some obscure body have said that these actions would endanger lives which is BULLSHIT! Paramedics save lives daily, they don't endanger them. And surely having a tired sttressed paramedic who has worked for 15 hours before they attend an emergency that you are involved in is going to be more dangerous... -In the past, paramedics just walked off the job, with disasterous results. The state govenrmnet called on St John Ambulance, a voulentary first aid organisation of which I am a member, to be the ambulance service for a day. St John did the job well, and the paramedics union was mighty pissed off with the way things had turned out. When St John Ambulance staff called for an ambulance when they were working with the public i.e @ the football, the paramedics either refused to attend, sent too many ambulance crews and told us off for it or came too late-we were up shit creek! -The government is being tightassed about this issue that has been brewing for a while now, they need to help out!  We should all support our parramedics and emergency services statewide, they do fantastic work!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An anonymous reporter has reported to m3r that her dad used to smoke up with Peter Costello in university. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Remember a day, many months ago, when the first air-strikes were launched against Baghdad? There was a rally held that day, marked not by a date, but by an event and a time. It was an outcry voiced by some 250,000 people, right in the heart of Melbourne, and was repeated all over the world. Together, millions of us expressed our grief at the plight of our world: specifically, the violence that would now sweep Iraq and possibly more of the Middle-East, and the fear and hatred that had entered the minds of those millions who supported an un-justifyable war. This unified expression of grief and anger did not go unheeded on the international stage.  What if, a few weeks before the impending US Election, posters begin to appear for another rally. These posters state something along the lines of: "On the day the US Election is decided, we will rally in grief, or in celebration." If Bush is re-elected, the world erupts in a series of synchronized protests - a simple, powerful message to the Republican government: that the world is far, far from happy. If Bush is denied a second term in office, we rally anyway... We hold a big fucking party in the streets.  Most likely, this news will be mourned or celebrated by the individual - by small groups, organizations, and families. I just think, wouldn't it be nice, if we could  all  come together and deal with this, whichever way things turn. Bush's antics affect us all, so why not respond to their continuation or end on a global scale?  And I guess that's the end of my hypothetical.  --- Hillary
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Take a look at the falsities being peddled to prospective students at this website.  'Princes Hill is the centre of a vibrant community of parents, students and teachers. All play an active part in the daily life, decisions and programs of the school. It is a community united by a shared belief in the importance of the following values: Community: belonging together and caring for each other Diversity: respecting and valuing individual and cultural difference Social Responsibility: a passionate commitment to ethical and socially just action Creativity: nurturing a spirit of innovative inquiry and expression Achievement: striving to set and reach challenging personal goals Self-reliance: the self-discipline and resilience required to achieve these goals  You will find that these beliefs permeate and inform everything that the school does.' Oh yes you can clearly find these beliefs informing the school's policy against free speech. 'Nurturing a spirit of innovative inquiry and expression' of course by limiting students ability to express themselves. Brilliant!  In a subsection titled Freedom of expression we get these 'facts' presented to us.  'The college encourages the expression of a range of opinions unless they are perceived to be racist, defamatory or sexist, to threaten the harmony of the college or otherwise contravene equal opportunity legislation.'  This is fucking bullshit. How dare they try and sell new students on our beliefs of social responsibility? How dare they say they encourage inquiry and expression when this is clearly not the case in practice? 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As of now we have are restricted to a small billboard on the third floor. This was facilitated by Ms Farrel. Ms Forster however still maintains her opposition to widespread free speech at PHSC. We may not put up posters unless they first come through Ms Farrel and then Ms Ford. They must be of the form of public notices and will only be limitedly put up. We as students should have the right to put up posters with out going through this political process.  The reason why this is not possible according to Ms Forster is that some teachers have complained. An unnamed teacher said: 'We should hunt them down and beat them up'  or words to this effect i support this notion put forward by this anonymous teacher of North American extraction. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Providing Hilare is used in a sarcastic way, because this website is probably the best satirical anti-US Government website on the net, and it is:   urlLink http://www.whitehouse.org    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is there any justification for the invasion of Iraq? Is there any reason why the occupation forces should remain? Iraq was unjustly invaded and now is being unjustly occupied. This perhaps is a key reason why people should support Latham over Howard. Howard may even commit  more  troops. Kerry will maintain the occupation. What actual advantage would a Kerry led US be to the world?   Iraq to Explode Can't Blair see that this country is about to explode? Can't Bush? by Rober Fisk;  urlLink The Independent  ; August 03, 2004 Bagdhad: The war is a fraud. I'm not talking about the weapons of mass destruction that didn't exist. Nor the links between Saddam Hussein and al-Qaida which didn't exist. Nor all the other lies upon which we went to war. I'm talking about the new lies. For just as, before the war, our governments warned us of threats that did not exist, now they hide from us the threats that do exist. Much of Iraq has fallen outside the control of America's puppet government in Baghdad but we are not told. Hundreds of attacks are made against US troops every month. But unless an American dies, we are not told. This month's death toll of Iraqis in Baghdad alone has now reached 700 - the worst month since the invasion ended. But we are not told. The stage management of this catastrophe in Iraq was all too evident at Saddam Hussein's "trial." Not only did the US military censor the tapes of the event. Not only did they effectively delete all sound of the 11 other defendants. But the Americans led Saddam Hussein to believe - until he reached the courtroom - that he was on his way to his execution. Indeed, when he entered the room he believed that the judge was there to condemn him to death. This, after all, was the way Saddam ran his own state security courts. No wonder he initially looked "disorientated" - CNNs helpful description - because, of course, he was meant to look that way. We had made sure of that. Which is why Saddam asked Judge Juhi: "Are you a lawyer? ..Is this a trial?" And swiftly, as he realised that this really was an initial court hearing - not a preliminary to his own hanging - he quickly adopted an attitude of belligerence. But don't think were going to learn much more about Saddam's future court appearances. Salem Chalabi, the brother of convicted fraudster Ahmad and the man entrusted by the Americans with the tribunal, told the Iraqi press two weeks ago that all media would be excluded from future court hearings. And I can see why. Because if Saddam does a Milosevic, he'll want to talk about the real intelligence and military connections of his regime - which were primarily with the United States. Living in Iraq these past few weeks is a weird as well as dangerous experience. I drive down to Najaf. Highway 8 is one of the worst in Iraq. Westerners are murdered there. It is littered with burnt-out police vehicles and American trucks. Every police post for 70 miles has been abandoned. Yet a few hours later, I am sitting in my room in Baghdad watching Tony Blair, grinning in the House of Commons as if he is the hero of a school debating competition; so much for the Butler report. Indeed, watching any Western television station in Baghdad these days is like tuning in to Planet Mars. Doesn't Blair realise that Iraq is about to implode? Doesn't Bush realise this? The American-appointed "government" controls only parts of Baghdad - and even there its ministers and civil servants are car-bombed and assassinated. Baquba, Samara, Kut, Mahmoudiya, Hilla, Fallujah, Ramadi, all are outside government authority. Iyad Allawi, the "Prime Minister," is little more than mayor of Baghdad. "Some journalists," Blair announces, "almost want there to be a disaster in Iraq." He doesn't get it. The disaster exists now. When suicide bombers ram their cars into hundreds of recruits outside police stations, how on earth can anyone hold an election next January? Even the National Conference to appoint those who will arrange elections has been twice postponed. And looking back through my notebooks over the past five weeks, I find that not a single Iraqi, not a single American soldier I have spoken to, not a single mercenary - be he American, British or South African - believes that there will be elections in January. All said that Iraq is deteriorating by the day. And most asked why we journalists weren't saying so. But in Baghdad, I turn on my television and watch Bush telling his Republican supporters that Iraq is improving, that Iraqis support the "coalition," that they support their new US-manufactured government, that the "war on terror" is being won, that Americans are safer. Then I go to an internet site and watch two hooded men hacking off the head of an American in Riyadh, tearing at the vertebrae of an American in Iraq with a knife. Each day, the papers here list another construction company pulling out of the country. And I go down to visit the friendly, tragically sad staff of the Baghdad mortuary and there, each day, are dozens of those Iraqis we supposedly came to liberate, screaming and weeping and cursing as they carry their loved ones on their shoulders in cheap coffins. I keep re-reading Tony Blair's statement. "I remain convinced it was right to go to war. It was the most difficult decision of my life." And I cannot understand it. It may be a terrible decision to go to war. Even Chamberlain thought that; but he didn't find it a difficult decision - because, after the Nazi invasion of Poland, it was the right thing to do. And driving the streets of Baghdad now, watching the terrified American patrols, hearing yet another thunderous explosion shaking my windows and doors after dawn, I realise what all this means. Going to war in Iraq, invading Iraq last year, was the most difficult decision Blair had to take because he thought - correctly - that it might be the wrong decision. I will always remember his remark to British troops in Basra, that the sacrifice of British soldiers was not Hollywood but "real flesh and blood." Yes, it was real flesh and blood that was shed - but for weapons of mass destruction that weren't real at all. "Deadly force is authorised," it says on checkpoints all over Baghdad. Authorised by whom? There is no accountability. Repeatedly, on the great highways out of the city US soldiers shriek at motorists and open fire at the least suspicion. "We had some Navy Seals down at our checkpoint the other day," a 1st Cavalry sergeant says to me. "They asked if we were having any trouble. I said, yes, they've been shooting at us from a house over there. One of them asked: That house? We said yes. So they have these three SUVs and a lot of weapons made of titanium and they drive off towards the house. And later they come back and say 'We've taken care of that.' And we didn't get shot at any more." What does this mean? The Americans are now bragging about their siege of Najaf. Lieutenant Colonel Garry Bishop of the 37th Armoured Divisions 1st Battalion believes it was an "ideal" battle (even though he failed to kill or capture Muqtada Sadr whose "Mehdi army" were fighting the US forces). It was "ideal," Bishop explained, because the Americans avoided damaging the holy shrines of the Imams Ali and Hussein. What are Iraqis to make of this? What if a Muslim army occupied Kent and bombarded Canterbury and then bragged that they hadnt damaged Canterbury Cathedral? Would we be grateful? What, indeed, are we to make of a war which is turned into a fantasy by those who started it? As foreign workers pour out of Iraq for fear of their lives, US Secretary of State Colin Powell tells a press conference that hostage-taking is having an "effect" on reconstruction. Effect! Oil pipeline explosions are now as regular as power cuts. In parts of Baghdad now, they have only four hours of electricity a day; the streets swarm with foreign mercenaries, guns poking from windows, shouting abusively at Iraqis who don't clear the way for them. This is the "safer" Iraq which Mr Blair was boasting of the other day. What world does the British Government exist in? Take the Saddam trial. The entire Arab press - including the Baghdad papers - prints the judge's name. Indeed, the same judge has given interviews about his charges of murder against Muqtada Sadr. He has posed for newspaper pictures. But when I mention his name in The Independent, I was solemnly censured by the British Government's spokesman. Salem Chalabi threatened to prosecute me. So let me get this right. We illegally invade Iraq. We kill up to 11,000 Iraqis. And Mr Chalabi, appointed by the Americans, says I'm guilty of "incitement to murder." That just about says it all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The young liberals have set up shop on the net. Obviously seizing this great democratic power to pursue their evil purposes. Disgusting. Have a look at the depravity  urlLink here.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Greens say Labor fails to address major FTA concerns Mark Latham's amendment to the FTA legislation fails to fix the major concern of an appeal process opening up PBS price reviews by US drugc ompanies, Greens Senator Bob Brown said today."Nor does Labor's amendment on broadcasting guarantee local content on new media," Senator Brown said. "Labor has failed to address a raft of critical issues including: * Higher cost to libraries and researchers of extendingAustralia's copyright laws to match the US, contrary to earlierrecommendations; * The absence of sugar from the FTA, the long lead in timefor lower tariffs for Australian dairy and beef farmers, restrictions inaccess to US markets for avocado, citrus, stone fruit and pork; * The threat to as many as 50,000 Australian manufacturingjobs; * The increase in the threshold that triggers ForeignInvestment Review Board examination of takeover or investment proposals; * The review mechanism of the PBS with its commitment toallow the right to price reviews. The provision to allow directmarketing to doctors and consumers via the Internet. (Labor's amendmentdoes not touch these major concerns.) * The constraints on government, increasing Australiancultural content in future (including digital) broadcasting anduncertainty about the ABC, SBS, and the Australian Film Commission.(Labor's amendment does not cover these major concerns.) * The inclusion of an expropriation and compensationclause that will hamper governments protecting the environment. "The Greens have moved to defer Senate debate on the FTA until thegovernment orders a public review and environmental impact statement.    Have a look at  urlLink this site . 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As of today i'm making Seth Cohen/Adam Brody an honorary member. Witty repartee such as this must not go on unrewarded.  Summer: What's happening with the A.C.?  This heat's messing up my hair Seth: Oh really my Jewfro's fine Summer: You're jewish? Seth: That's why i'm so comfortable in this desert climate  Oh its pure brilliance. Never have i heard the plight of the jewish people summed up so brilliantly in such a small snatch of dialogue. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Find out your politics.  urlLink Here's the test . I'm a left liberal, surprise surprise.  urlLink Here's another longer test  which is the same sort of thing. I ended up in the bottom left hand corner which means i'm a left libertarian i suppose. Have a go. Post your results. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not many people are coming here anymore. Most likely because the discussions are too boring for people. We are going to still keep these serious discussions, but need your help in sexing m3r, up so to speak. Submit your suggestions for making m3r more interesting. I think what m3r needs to do is apply its philosophy more. Soon we will be postering the school to a greater extent and we aim to take greater control over the school environment in this way. I think people should be reporting to m3r the discrimination and problems they have faced at school from students and staff. This will go along way towards making m3r a more interesting and more useful website. Your submissions for posters to do with any issue are welcome too. Thanks. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>