<Blog>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      this is my blog, i'll be posting alot about online games and alot of paintball.  
     
    
</post>


<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is a new blog for me, i have another blog on blogspot too. and i know how it works, this blog will just have random stuff.
     

    
</post>


<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      animal crossing is only for the nintendo gamecube, its really fun. you move into a new town that is populated by animals. you  talk to them, reach goals like getting you house upgraded ( you do this by paying off nook, who owns your house) buying certain items such as clothing, unbrellas furniture, and lots more. its really great! the only down fall is that it never eall ends and you really dont win or anything.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      neopets is really awesome for  all  ages. adults and children alike. you can have up to four neopets ( little creatures that you take care of and other stuff )you can meet other people from across the globe, and it's pretty safe for kids to chat on. they don't allow any profanity, talk about sexual things, and other inapproprite things for children. i've been a member four over a year, and i've never became bored with it, try it out, you may like it!   urlLink  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                  i love cats! i have 4 of them!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i went to church this past week (i just got back today, its extreme camps owned by teen mania) and Phil Chalmers, founder of true lies   urlLink   mentioined that some people think tupac is still alive, and that he faked his death. i think he posibly faked it because i mean come on! a movie and a book about his life came out, i mean, they wouldnt really sell well if he was'nt allready dead! and his music is selling more now also, and has anyone else noticed he died like the same time biggie smalls did? i mean, does'nt anyone else find that a little odd? leave a comment.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok, i was just thinking about something i'm concerned with to write about and this thought came up. now, being from the south, i have a natural instinct to be a little (not alot) racial towards blacks and i admit it. but some things just are'nt fair! BET, black entertainment channel, now this really dosn't seem fair, i mean we could'nt create a  white  entertainment channel, could we? we'd get sued or something! and at school one day, i reffered to someone ans that  black  kid over there and got in trouble, and then he called me a cracker and didn't get in any trouble. i mean, does anyone else notice how unfair this is, i'm all for racial equality and all and they act like they are but are they really?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bonnie and shae's fried onions 1 cup onions 1 small strawberry 1/2 cup vainilla syrup 1/3 olive oil and lots of different peppers throw all ingridients in a pan and let it sizzle tell the onions get sorta clear, eat and enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm just thinking about john kerry's wife. she's an heiress to heinz ketchup (my favorite ketchup, sadly)and my dad says if you buy heinz ketchup,your supporting john kerry, so as of now, i'm boycotting heinz ketchup. oh and does anyone else think its weird he's married to an african-american? i mean, she's from mozambique which is in africa.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i like to share my opinions of current news topics, and some other stuff, but since i really have'nt been watching the news lately, i'll just share my opininon about animal rights (yeah, i know what your thinking, you think i'm a tree hugger) for one thing, animals should NOT be used for drug testings or testings of cosmetics or any other products (excluding animal products), nor, should they be used for the studying of viruses. just think, your an adorable chimpanzee, and one day some human injects you with the AIDS virus. i mean, how awful! well, now that i have this blog, i'll be more up-to-date with the news.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      * To study the result of head trauma, primates were strapped in machinery to recieve high-impact blows to the head that left them with severe brain damage and cruel taunts from vivisectors, as documented by video tape. (University of Pennsylvania)   * To examine severe burns on live tissue, pigs were restrained to prevent their escape and then burned alive with a flamethrower until the charred flesh could be removed from the live animals in large pieces. (U.S. Army)   * To measure recovery from injuries, dogs were strapped down, and vivisectors mutilated the dogs' kness by cutting apart skin to leave flaps. At the end of the study, all dogs were killed. (Uniformed Services University- Department of Defense)  * To demonstrate the eye's protein levels are not different in sight deprived monkeys compared to normal ones, animal experimenters sewed the monkeys' eyelids shut. (Emory University, NIH project P51 RR00165-38)   * To test the hypothesis, among others, that it "will result in reductions in body weight, body fat and lean body mass" vivisectors withhold normal amounts and types of food from monkeys. (University of Wisconsin- Madison, NIH project P01 AG11915-05S1).   * To demonstrate that deaf cats 'meow' louder than cats with hearing, kittens' aural canals were destroyed, and then researchers measured the loudness of their cries. (UCLA, Brain Research Institute)  Funding for Experimentations Every year, the U.S vivisection industries spend over $18 billion on animal experiments. We could be using this money for poor starving hungry children, or library funding, but no our taxes fund the death and cruelty of billions of animals!     
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can you believe that horse slaughter is an issue in the U.S? It is! Every day horses are sold to the slaughter houses where they are killed and then sold for their meat. This horrible act has been going on for too long! These horses consist of pregnant mares, young foals, healthy geldings, old work horses, retired race track horses and more. The worst part is that the USDA promotes horsemeat! (U.S. Department of Agriculture Food Safety and Inspection Service) Most of the horsemeat is sold countries where it is more common to eat horses. In 1994 109,353 pounds of horsemeat was shipped overseas. You can only imagine the increase over the years!&nbsp; Is it okay for perfectly healthy horses, even pregant mares to be butchered?? I THINK NOT!!!!   my thoughts on this article:  as a horse lover, this hurts my heart, but lets think, if you have an old horse that has a bad knee ( take my neighbors for example) and it's in pain even when it walks, it should'nt have to suffer, and it should be sent to the slaughter house, it will die and will never suffer again, and it will be sort of recycling. BUT if the horse is healthy it should'nt be slaughtered. it should be allowed to live happily. if its preganant i mean your killing two horses. its not fair, thats my opinion. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      anyone who reads my blog, should definatly read my dad's blog. my mom allways says i'm my dad's daughter. i think pretty much kind of like him. (except on my strong thoughts on animal testing) check it out!  mostlycajun.blogspot.com
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay! my computer is finally fixed! it had loads of spyware/adware (and if you've had spyware on your computer, you know how bad it is!) it was really hard to get off. i had to delete allmost everything. but it's fixed i am happy. i'll be posting more now.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok? so i was just thinking about that song umm. bop. now, thats when you know the world is coming to and end, when they have a song called umm.. bop. it doesn't even have real words in it!    read the chorus,        Mmmbop, ba du ba dop     Ba du bop, ba du ba dop     Ba du bop, ba du ba dop     Ba du     Mmmbop, ba du ba dop     Ba du bop, Ba du dop     Ba du bop, Ba du dop     Ba du          what the heck is mmm bop?  i don't know! it just bugs me so much so i had to post about it!     
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (from crazythoughts.com)  Why is it that when adults have multiple personalities it's schizophrenia, but when a child has imaginary friends it's cute?  Can you put a gay man in a straight jacket?  When people say, "I’m so tired it's not even funny" or "my head hurts so much it's not even funny", why would it even be funny in the first place?   When French people swear do they say pardon my English?  Why did Yankee Doodle name the feather in his hat Macaroni?  Who was the first person to look at a cow and say, "I think I'll squeeze these dangly things here and drink what comes out"?  Who was the first person to say, "See that chicken over there ... I'm gonna eat the first thing that comes out if its butt"?  Isn't Disney World just a people trap operated by a mouse?  If an atheist has to go to court, do they make him swear on the Bible?  Why is it illegal to park in a handicapped parking space but its ok to use a handicapped toilet?  How come we say 'It's colder than hell outside' when isn't it realistically always colder than hell since hell is supposed to be fire and brimstone?  here's one added by me.  if jelly bread allways lands jelly side down, and a cat allways land on its feet, what would happen if you super-glued jelly bread to a cat?  i'll probably add some more one day. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      on the fourth of july, i went to see fireworks on my dads boat in lake charles. they were really great. when they were over, we got to the dock and my dad handed me the ice chest, and i feel in the nastiest, dirtiest water with the slimiest mud in the world! something touched my leg and i panicked, my dad had to pull me on the dock. he was laughing so much. i was really rude to him and my brother that night and i deserved it, so sorry dad, sorry corey.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i took an IQ test and look what i got!  Congratulations, Bonnie! Your IQ score is  124    This number is based on a scientific formula that compares how many questions you answered correctly on the Classic IQ Test relative to others.   Your Intellectual Type is  Visual Mathematician . This means you are gifted at spotting patterns — both in pictures and in numbers. These talents combined with your overall high intelligence make you good at understanding the big picture, which is why people trust your instincts and turn to you for direction — especially in the workplace.  not bad for a 13 year old don't you think? 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i love rap music. i love its awesome beat, rythm, and flow. but the lyrics, there just really really bad! one day, i decided to get some lyrics for some songs i like, and as i was reading the lyrics, i was like woah! thats really bad! i never really listend to the full lyrics, just the course, but still what they were saying is really bad! one song i got the lyrics for was tipsy. tipsy means drunk. so the song says errbody (not everybody) in the club get tipsy, but what it really says everybody in the club get drunk. in one part  it talks about getting high. the sad thing is, these types of lyrics are very common. eminem's lyrics are really bad, so bad he wont even let his own daughter listen to them. but, he wants other peoples' children to listen to them? do you know what eminem does every morning? he wakes up, eats fruity pebbles with his daughter, watches powerpuff girls with his daughter, then plays barbies with her. he says he sings about his life, so if he really does, where's the song about powerpuff girls? barbie? fruity pebbles? i'm pretty sure jay z doesnt call beyonce a "hoe" like he calls all the other women in his songs. he's teaching teen boys to call women hoes. thats really bad. some lyrics are just so bad, i don't even want to talk about them! they call them self a pimp, they are not pimps! they make so much money already. so it teaches kids to call themselves pimps. there really degrading to allmost everyone. and if you see the videos of the songs? the way the women dress, dance, and act,, the way the men will be acting is just wrong!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      gosh, i never new what they did to animals, i just knew they hurt them, but this is just awful! animals are innocent creatures, and we use them for this? its not fair at all! please leave a comment on what you think about animal rights.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is an article from kfccruelty.com  Dalai Lama Demands That KFC Stay out of Tibet  His Holiness the 14th Dalai Lama Tenzin Gyatso is the head of the Tibetan government-in-exile and spiritual leader to the more than 350 million Buddhists worldwide. The Dalai Lama, winner of the Nobel Peace Prize in 1989, has long been known to speak out on social justice issues ranging from China’s occupation of Tibet to the problems associated with globalisation. Now, His Holiness has lent his voice to the 750 million chickens raised and killed for KFC each year by writing a powerful letter to KFC, asking the company to cancel its plans to expand its growing Chinese operation into his homeland of Tibet.  His Holiness writes in his letter, ‘I have been particularly concerned with the sufferings of chickens for many years. It was the death of a chicken that finally strengthened my resolve to become vegetarian. … These days, when I see a row of plucked chickens hanging in a meat shop it hurts. I find it unacceptable that violence is the basis of some of our food habits. … It is therefore quite natural for me to support those who are currently protesting against the introduction of industrial food practices into Tibet that will perpetuate the suffering of huge numbers of chickens’. Click here to read the entire letter.  The Dalai Lama wants KFC to stop slicing the beaks off baby birds without pain relief, stop breeding and drugging birds to grow so obese that their legs break and stop scalding millions of chickens to death in slaughterhouses every year.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      article from peta.com  There are tests run on helpless animals for everything from eye shadow and soap to furniture polish and oven cleaner. Millions of animals suffer in these tests and the results do not help prevent or treat human illness or injury. It is still going on.  Following is an example of an eye irritantcy test:  In these tests, a liquid, flake, granule, or powdered substance is dropped into the eyes of a group of albino rabbits. The animals are often immobilized in stocks from which only their heads protrude. They usually receive no anesthesia during the tests. After placing the substance in the rabbits' eyes, laboratory technicians record the damage to the eye tissue at specific intervals over an average period of 72 hours, with tests sometimes lasting 7 to 18 days. Reactions to the substances include swollen eyelids, inflamed irises, ulceration, bleeding, massive deterioration, and blindness. During the tests, the rabbits' eyelids are held open with clips. Many animals break their necks as they struggle to escape this is just one thing they do to to the poor innocent animals. we have to stop it, its not fair that they are suffering for us. i beleive no one should suffer, even animals.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i've been having to wear school uniforms for four years. i hate them. i really hate them. if we were allowed to wear what we want to wear, we would be using self-expression. i am totally for self-expression, even if we still ahd a dress code (a not so strict as uniforms dress code)we would'nt have to use self-expression in ways such as piercings, tatoos, hair colors (because of uniforms i dyed my hair), and other things like that. we have freedom of speech, and i think what you wear is a part of speech. We should get to choose what we want to wear, not the school board, not are parents, and no one else! we could have responsibilities  of what to we can wear, and we should follow a dress code at school or at home, and anywhere else, but we should never have to dress all the same, and if they want us to wear uniforms, they should give us a style and let us have the choice of color, we should ahve the choice to have our shirts tucked or untucked. its only fair!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i took a test on tickle, it was an ink spot test 56 pages, these are my results  Bonnie, your subconscious mind is driven most by  Imagination     urlLink   You have a deep desire to use ideas to change the world around you. This drive influences you far more than you may realize on a conscious level. You love to brainstorm and imagine new possibilities. The world is a fuller, richer place because you can contribute new ideas to any experience. Your natural curiosity inspires those around you and encourages them to come up with ideas they wouldn't have discovered without your help. Your psyche is very rich; the more you learn about it, the more you will understand who you really are.   that really describes me. its sort of freaky... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you all know abouit john kerry saving that hamster and usually when someone saves an animal i get all aww how sweet-like, but in this case, i just wanted to laugh. how can someone who wants to save little furry rodents believe in pro-choice? did you know, in california, if you break a california condore egg, you have to pay a hefty fine, because you killed a baby condore, but also in california, abortion is legal! so, you can kill a baby human, but if you kill a baby condore, its illegal!  i am all for pro-life! adoption, not abortion! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry i haven't been posting lately. i've been real busy. well, i've started thinking. probably all you people who read my blog are sick of all this animal rights so i'll get over to a different topic. i'll be posting on a new topic very soon. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>