<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DARWIN FINALISTS ANNOUNCED   They are finally out again. You all know about the Darwin Awards--It's an Annual honor given to the person who did the gene pool the biggest service by killing themselves in the most extraordinarily stupid way. Last year's winner was the fellow who was killed by a Coke machine which toppled over on top of him as he was attempting to tip a free soda out of it.   And the nominees are:   1.) A young Canadian man, searching for a way of getting drunk cheaply, because he had no money with which to buy alcohol, mixed gasoline with milk. Not surprisingly, this concoction made him ill, and he vomited into the fireplace in his house. This resulting explosion and fire burned his house down, killing both him and his sister.   2.) Three Brazilian men were flying in a light aircraft at low altitude when another plane approached. It appears that they decided to moon the occupants of the other plane, but lost control of their own aircraft and crashed. They were all found dead in the wreckage with their pants around their ankles.   3.) A 22-year-old, Glade Drive, Reston, VA, man was found dead after he tried to use octopus straps to bungee jump off a 70-foot railroad trestle. Fairfax County police said Eric Barcia, a fast-food worker, taped a bunch of these straps together, wrapped one end around one foot, anchored the other end to the trestle at Lake Accotink Park, jumped and hit the pavement. Warren Carmichael, a police spokesman, said investigators think Barcia was alone because his car was found nearby. "The length of the cord that he had assembled was greater than the distance between the trestle and the ground," Carmichael said. Police say the apparent cause of! death was "Major trauma."    4.) A man in Alabama died from rattlesnake bites. It seems that he and a friend were playing a game of catch, using the rattlesnake as a ball. The friend, no doubt a future Darwin Awards candidate, was hospitalized.   5.) Employee in a medium-sized warehouse in west Texas noticed the smell of a gas presumed a leak. Sensibly, management evacuated the building extinguishing all potential sources of ignition: lights, power, etc. After the building had been evacuated, two "technicians" from the gas company were dispatched. Upon entering the building, they found they had difficulty navigating in the dark. To their frustration, none of the lights worked.   Witnesses later described the sight of one of the technicians reaching into his pocket and retrieving an object that resembled a cigarette lighter. Upon operation of the lighter like object, the gas in the warehouse exploded, sending pieces of the warehouse up to three miles away. Nothing was found of the technicians, but the lighter, being at the exact center of the resulting melee, was virtually untouched by the explosion. The "technician" suspected of causing the blast, had never been thought of by his peers as "all there."   And the Winner:   6.) Based on a bet by the other members of his golfing threesome, Everett Sanchez tried to wash his own "balls" in a ball washer at the local golf course. Proving once again that beer and testosterone are a bad mix , Sanchez managed to straddle the ball washer and dangle his scrotum in the machine. Much to his dismay, one of his buddies upped the ante by spinning the crank on the machine with Sanchez's scrotum in place, thus edging them solidly in the mechanism. Sanchez, who immediately passed his threshold of pain, collapsed and tumbled from his perch.   Unfortunately for Sanchez, the post of the ball washer was more than strong enough to support his body weight, and his sack was the weakest link. Sanchez's scrotum was ripped open during the fall, and one testicle was plucked from him forever and remained in the ball washer, while the other testicle was compressed and flattened as it was pulled between the housing of the washer, and the rotating machinery inside. To add insult to injury, Sanchez then broke a new $300.00 graphite shaft driver that he had just purchased from the pro shop, and was attempting to use as a cane. Sanchez was rushed to the hospital for surgery, and the remaining threesome was asked to leave the course.   This last one wouldn't normally count, because the golfer didn't die. Butbecause he cannot reproduce as a result of his qualifying act of stupidity, we have allowed it.   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey what up,  well i haven't blog in alike a couple of days know..let start off. tuesday, boring, micheal came home. and i got a mass virus on the computer god damnit it sucks ass. i sat on my ass form 6pm...to 5am. i was trying to kill the virus and finally at 455..i killed it..but i wasn't sure. so who cares the parents came hom and i went to bed.  wednesday, everybody was at home here. micheal wake my ass up to get me to go get some breskfest. so it suck, play counter-strike, and got talk some ppl on the computer. nuttin really.  thursday, quess what i did today, not a damn thing again. play video games. talk on the computer. did about nothing..that been like that forever now. i miss hangout with ppl..but that the way it got to be.it all coool. play until about two..then talk to miranda.  now friday, woke up around 11. got a phone call today at 8am. it was the director exective of boyscout in the mountianlakes dircits. if u don't know that don't worry. that just saying that he the big guy for the boyscout around here. ok who cares. he told me i'm getting another award or something. monday, woah. NOT REALLY CAREING BUT I PUT A SMILE ON MY FACE AND GO WITH IT.  i sent val birthday gift to her.  i hope she likes it. mostlike yes when she talkes to me.but maybe a NO. this present means a lot to me. and i want to give her something nicce . well i hope it get there before her birthday. well play my PS2 GAME UNTIL FOR EVER THE COMPUTER WAS SENT TO THE ARMY. to get it fix. so i was never on the internet today. well it 12 . i did talkt o jess and to miranda val call me tonight. and i know she really want to talk to somebody else. watch a little tv. and tommorrow another day...another boring day. well be good i'll talk to u guys later.  *S*
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up around 11, took a shower. went to get some food.got home around 1..clean the car..wash the jeeps. at 4, mom and dad left to get micheal for the airport. he finally came home form greece. well i was looking for a long night of counter-strike. but damnit i open a email..and found a virus...damnit..it one of the big virus...so i had to get off the computer, and no counter-strike... that start at 5...5 until 5am..i was so bored..nobody to talkt to..sent a message to jess..SORRY i woke u up. but took me that many hours before i beat it..it sucks ass. but about 5 this morning i beat it..and i think my computer is ok... so it suck...so i didn't do much...i didn't know that there is a shit load of cops on the tv. I LOVE COPS...there aight must to talk about..didn't do must...watch tv..work on the computer..that all.. now today my computer fine and all it good..
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up around 11. talk to jess for a little bit..took a shower mowed the yard...took me 3hrs...started at 12...the damn mower broke down...damn i suck...sit on my ass for the rest of the day...took the movies back....there nothing to do anymore...micheal getting back tommorrow...yea...then maybe next week i can got get my stereo..and my little system...don't got must to say...i don't want to brang my personal life back into this anymore...so that all i did...i'm not kinding u...i sit form 5 until 9....in front of the tv...never left the spot...damn i'm going to dead of boring....yeall be good don't do nothing crazy tommoroow...peace out
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up around 11..told the old man happy father day...to a shower...talk some ppl...on the computer then went to chattonage.. drove the whole way there..and in chattaoge...went to see my little girl....savannah...then went to best buy to look at the stereos..and sound systems..sorry jess no AMPS...my car a piss of shit..sorry...well...i got me a stereo in mind...a 6 disco cd player/fm/am/XM...it looks bad ass...I didn't do must when i got back to talk som ppl...then got on counter-strike... played a little..then finally talking to jess on the computer...got nothing else to talk about...  peace out...have a buetiful day tommorow
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what up, let me tell u about my day...got woke up around 930...went to bed at 3...woke up around 930 took a shower..then dad called and said that i'm getting new tires...so i took the jeep down to walmart...found out..i'm getting the green jeep tires. but still those are better then the ones i have..then went to get so food a firesides...then to shoe show...got me some thongs sandels...then to walmart to get my jeep and for grocrieys.i finally got me jeep back around 1...got on counter-strike.. then talk to some ppl...then around 430. i got a call from aubrey asking if i want to go to the drive in. i was like sure. so the venture crew round up..and went..got the best sit in the house DOGDEBALL IS THE FUNNIEST MOVIE I HAVE EVER SEEN..yall got to go see it.. garfield suck some ass...need to work on that got to scottsbore 12 30. i was hunrgery so i got me some taco bell. the came home..it been fun but i'm going to get going..
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up around 11, took a shower. talk a little bit on the computer. then played counter-strike from 12 until 4. went 125 and 56...then got off talk a little...then back onto counter-strike...went form 530-7..went to get some food. KFC...then aight..and back onto coutner-strike...8-11..got off a little bit to talk..not must to talk...everybody out. hope yall had a good day...  still have something on my mind..but it ok...after killing a bottle of jake dainels...i'm good now...thanks jermiah..and thanks jess. hope yall have fun today..ttyl
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this going to be a long one...i'm not going to send it to nobody.  i'm here listerning to whiskey lullaby by brad peisley, in a dark room. my day was going great until i went over to jermiah. then life got the hard again. it aight going to get better.  all my life, i want to turn my life around, and when i turn 16, i think i can. got my eagle scout. but really life got harder. the days are longer. i can't sleep anymore. and it all the fault of a girl that i wish i never met.a girl that screw my life over not one, not twice, not three times, some many times i lost count. i'm not saying the girl name. u just have to think. well i lost my life finelly. i'm tired of everything, i want to relaxed and i can't even do that anymore. i'm just tired of everything. my life got worstier by the day. i find new thing out i wish i never find out. thing ppl did or doing.. and i'm like damn i'm not going to do that for ever. i'm tired of this shit. i'm not going out must anymore. i'm going to retirener to my house. even then i sit up in my dark room looking at braclet. i'm wish why the god i met her. thinking why my life sucks so hard. yall all think your life is hard. u got to know mine. i got to be a state champion in something. i got to be an eagle scout. i got to pass with falling colors at school. yea saying u can do that.  my mind is saying that i can't do that. i got most of it. my mind is gone. i'm a vegitable. my mind is gone. i'm not thinking, i'm just sitting in a room with blackness all around me. i'm just sitting and wishing god strike me down with his thunder blot. god, why can't i just leave this world.i not helping must. i'm not in a good mood anymore. my heart is in a lions den. with the lions hitting it left and right. my body can't handle this anymore. my spirit is gone. away form my body. sitting in a chair wishing that i had a gun.. and i'm gone with this shit.love aight going to find me..it going to jump over me like everything else..i wish i can just hold a girl and think god i'm glad i'm going out with u...i'm gald your always there for me. well i'm tired of waiting. and i'm tired of everything.yall don't understand. my life sucks. i wish i had words of what i'm feeling. but i just can't explain of what i'm feeling. yall need to listern to WHISKEY LULLABY. u got a good picture of the way i feel. the way i want to do to my self.   jerk-o-mia...no more of that house. be good, we been through up and downs...i'm sorry for the times i always took chris side witht things. it will never happen again. and i'm not around chris anymore.so no more jerk-o-miah house  jess, i love u but i dont' want to talk...i'm going to go in my room and listern to my musics. and wishing i had something..   THINGS THAT WILL MAKE ME HAPPY...A BOTTLE OF VODKIA AND A 9mm...  GONE INTO MY LIAR, DON'T LEAVE A COMMINTED I DONT' WANT TO HEAR IT.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOKE UP AROUND 10. WATCH TV. TALK SO SOME PPL.HAD TO GET SOME BLOOD WORK DONE..AND GET A SOME PAPERS SIGN FOR PHILMONT. GOT TO TAKE PILLS FOR MY LUNGS..SOMETHING..WITH SOMETHING...IT NOTHING...HE SAID I CAN HIKE AND DO ALL THAT..JUST GOT TO KEEP IT ARE SELF ABOUT IT. I DON'T CARE. WE OVER TO JERK-O-MIA, SORRY MAN U CAN'T SPEND THE NIGHT. BUT WHO CARES. GOT HOME AROUND 9 WENT TO THE MOVIES NOTHING GOOD HAPPEN TODAY.   I KNOW IT SHORT AND SWEET.  I KNOW MY OTHER ONE LONG.. SO I'M GOING TO MAKE THIS SHORT.  I LIKE TO THANK ADDRIENNE, JESS, AND JERK-O-MIA FOR THE COMMINTS AOBUT YESTERDAY. THANKS ALOT. WITH LOVE, GOOD NIGHT...
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm sitting at the end of the mat (at wrestling). watching the little children wrestles. and thinking.let me tell u what i'm thinking.   I'M TirED, i'm tried of wrestling..i been wrestling since 3 grade. and look at me. i got to go to sleep with ice on my knees. want have i got to say about these years i been wrestling...NOTHING... i trained new guys, and a couple years later..they can kick my ass. let me tell u, 1 example of this. i got chris killian into the sport of wreslting i taught him everything i know. his frist years of wrestling lost 2 matches. i felt proud of my self. then look at this. i can't even touches chris now..he killes me everytime on the match. i was like damn. then there trevor brown, micheal got him in to wrestling, but coach mcnutt got me to teach him. i did....now he killes me...i help a shit load of ppl. what do i get in to return nothing... i felt like a dumbass. getting my ass handed it to me by BO MATTHEWS. damn i'm looking out into the little chrilden and warndering ..and picking out the state champions. we are going to have twins to get the state champion in 2010. but, i don't think i'm going to get it. i been working to hard. (i think)...it just doesn't feel like i'm going to get a state champion...i really don't...i can say i do..but in my heart i don't...and wrestling is a mind game.  i'm tired, of friends. i lost a lot of them around. but can't be tried of jerk-o-mia..and jess..and val...ok i'm tired of her... most of everybody else..i can handle..i love to talking to...but not everyday...i'm sorry.. once an a while yea...catches up on things..yea...how do i forget about..kala..she the oldest friend next to jerk-o-mia...she been through a lot..and i'll miss her when she gone to YALE...i'm starting to like talking to addrienne.. can't forget about her...i know i'll get some shit about this. but who cares. yall are good ppl..and with must love..but not everyday..once in a blue moon sounds good..  THIS IS GOING TO BE A LONG BLOG GOT SOME THINGS IN MY MIND..TAKE THIS IN SECTIONS OK...   LOVE,  yall new it was coming, thank to addrienne got me into that today been single 16 years 2months...i did have a girlfriend for 3 weeks..really 1 weeks and 2 weeks that we couldn't tell each other that it over. ok her telling me..it was chelsea...this was before she went skater girl/bad chick. i think i turn her into it. yea..but i been single all me life mostly. most guys can not say that. well i'm tired of beeing single, wake up and find none body to say i love u..or i like u...or i'm glad we are dating... i'm tried of seeing assholes always get the girls..esp. jerk-o-mia and jess...and addrienne and tristan...those are nice couples. i'm glad u found somebody. but it makes me sick just looking at u guys just loving on each other..a boy can only handle a little bit at a time.but i grind my teeth and get through it..that why i leave a lot of times at jermiah...but also that my dad fault too..but i'm tired of being single...so here a hot sign for u.  mackenzie stout 16 single 180..muscles :p.. like candle light dinners and long walks on the beach. (that always get the girls) like and color hair..no blues or pinks..reds are hot..not too smart. and got to be able to walk a mile... find somebody for me...cell number is 256-244-0889...call me   ok there..fine me a girl...please ppl..need a girl.  ok, time for the day, woke up around 10...took a shower then took shade running. got some food at buger king..and talk on some ppl on the computer.. then play counter-strike for 4 hrs..went to wrestling..then came back home watch sex in the city and play some counter-strike..got a phone call.. then now bloggin at 1106. there is my day..  ok now the phone call, val called. for the last times she called i say chris she got to go..bullshit...well i THINK..she has a problem with the asshole. yea..i been friends with chris for a long time..but i dont' like him anymore. he love playing with girls feelingS..(sounds fruited)but i don't..i like val and i like talking to her..but since she fell in love with chris..it like she a bitch more.. and i'm tired of it. i don't want to be her guy friend. that she can cry on..and tell her mother everything bad about...but what about chris..he did a shit load of thing to u..but your mother love chris. yea..bullshit..eagle scout of the year right here. i hate this shit. u ask me to find somebody..hell no...u find them your self..no more where jess, ask her to call me, where chris ask him to call me...no  more...she can do it her self..i'm tired of her drama..i'm really am..i love val,..more then a friend it took me 3years of loving her and 1 year to end it...i can't handle her drama and lifestyle anymore...and i'm tired of her..that final i'm over her. and she can find another man to bull shit now..i'm going to send this to her when i get done...  yall be good i'm gone..                                  ~*STOUT*~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I CALLED JESS BLOGGER...GAY...SHE USED THE USHER LET IT BURN...  then i read a little down and found her really one...it cool so i'm sorry.  woke up around 11, took a shower, talk to jess for a little bit. then took SHADE (my poodle)running. talk around lost a couple of friends only one really.LIKE TO SAY MY LAST GOOD BYE TO AUBREY. took another shower because hell just want to get off the computer.  two shower i feel fresh and clean clean...wrote a letter to val...thanking her for telling chris things...that another day...took the letter to the postoffice before it closes..spent 3 dollars for stamps. went to the venture meeting, then to wrestling.  got out of wrestling and went to the gas station to get out slush puppie...that all...came home that all. talk around a little bit.  i'm tried, i'm tried, i'm tried...i'm tried of my life...i'm tried of boyscouts..i'm tried of wrestling...i'm tried of friends...i'm tried of everything...what is wrong with me..I'M TRIED...THAT ALL I CAN SAY...  yall be good, there some more thing..but to personal for this..i keep my personal things inside..                     ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what up,  let start this off. woke up around 11. got a shower got dress. and clean some more..about 11:45 marshall and L.A. came by with sannavah. she my nesices. she 7 months i think. she big. she going to be come a state champion wrestler. she so pretty to. got slobier all over me. but i'll still love her. i let marshall look at my jeep. he laugh. they still don't blieve i hit a tree. but who cares. well they left around 4. had to go get some gas. was on E. so dad want to try out my hand radios for my kayak and backpacking. it was great. dad watch me drive home..and say my wheel vibrationing like crazy he told me to be careful. well i can't be careful if my wheel falls off. he doesn't have to money to buy me wheels. cheap basterd. who cares think jerk-0-mia for getting me out of the house. i been stuck in it for 3 days. damn it sucks. i wish i could have finish that movie but who cares. damn i had fun jess was there. i want val to call. god i'm going to cruss her out. i wish that she never like chris. god damnit, but she tell him everything. one time i let it go..twice i talk to her about it. three time, hell no she aight going to get away with this one. val tell ppl what u talk about. and i'm going to talk to her about it.  jessi, so must love is here. god u got me in trouble being in my bed. with no clothes god girl i told u to get dress. but no. jk. be good i would love to know about the email. but tell me.fine no more help. i want to know something.and u need help so it works out.   yall be good i'm tried,  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what up,  nuttin much here bored off my ass, woke up around 10. took a shower got on cleaning. i clean my room, my bathroom, the outsides. had to mow the yard. and didn't do must. yea...i had a great day.   jessi, i try to help u in to a guys mind. i hope u got to think what u want to do...but don't wait. on him. ok, please don't waited on him. u'll become a "redneck women". that u'r choose. but i'm trying to open the light. but don't be hard head it. LOOK AROUND. THAT ALL I'M GOING TO SAY.  adrienne, i'm still need a good back rub. we can do it with out tristan nothing about it.jk, ok maybe not jk. for real. just a quicky. notbody has to know. ok now i'm kidding.   miranda, it over, let ends this. we can talk to each other like we use to . so have a good life. and maybe we'll cross again in the road life.i'm just tried of talking to u guys.  yall be good today, be safe driving, don't have too must fun,  yea, my little girl is here, sannavanha stout. so be good guys,                                 ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SUP GUYS,  woke up around 745, round out of bed. got my gear ready for wrestling. went to wrestling around 845. wrestling went good. just review, talk a lot. had lunch, and at 1 check my phone had 5 miss calls form a 256 259 2117, think it was jessica. but it wasn't. so who cares. got back into wrestling didn't do anything. he let us out at 4. when to get a slushs. a green apple one. got home around 430. took a shower. want to get out of the house. but couldn't. nobody wasn't doing anything. so i just chilled at home all night. watch a little tv. got a little into counter-strike. went to bed by 11.  val call last night, talk a little bit, got her piss at me to let me go. by talking bad about her men (Chris). i don't care anymore. she made me write her number down and give it to jess. so i did do that. i'm like  a running dog for her. she always knows that what she will ask i will do. well we hang up. and she called back on a cell phone. and ask me where chris at. well let me tell u..i don't give a fuck. i'm not careing where chris at. i don't give a fuck if he jump off the bridge. well i told her that. she got a little mad.. i really don't get it. i not going to find chris. when i know that i can. but i'm not.  well if yall know, i talk to some girls from where chris use to leave. name miranda and jen. well i'm tried of talk to them. i love to talk but i'm tried of talking to them. well me and miranda, got in to it a little as a joke. and she think i wouldn't hang up on her. i'm not afraid to hang up on anybody even if it the president. she dared me that i wouldn't do it. i did it. so she send me a message saying that i felt something there when we talk a couple nights ago. well here there question i got for everybody.   what is the distance (miles wide)for a long distances relationship. can  u feel anything talking to a girl for a long time and but u never see her. what do u think. u think yes, u can feel something. or no, u can't feel anything. post your comminted  peace out guys, ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I REALLY FELT GOOD FOR THE FRIST TIME.  i been wrestling since 3grade.. me and micheal start out together. i couldn't handle him then and now..but freestyle is different. i went a match with him.and i for once got 3 points. the match is quick. u have 20 sec to do a move to roll or something. 20 sec. aight that long. but when u'r going at it hard u damn right it hard. well micheal kill me 15 to 10..i did got a slam. it was nices. but payback a bitch..damn i still i got 10 points for that throw.. but damn micheal throw me like crazy. got 11 points and final got me.with a roll. but i hang with him. it was great. for onces can't waited until wrestling camp tommorrow the last day.   woke up around 746. i remeber the time because of the song that came on. concert angel. i like that song. ate some breskfast. and went to wrestling.wrestled for 5hrs. making fun of chris and trevor, his little bother. all the cry babies. that quit. chris cried about his knee. wednesday and went to the doctor. I THINK, the doctor told himt that there nothing there. well, jim called coach that chris had an ear infection. (BULLSHIT)and trevor had sunburn and his little bother had to see his grandmother that came down form utah. she there for 3 weeks. hell i paid 250. i'm going to get my 250 dollars out of it. shit.even if i'm dead sick i'm still going. shit, i'm nothing going to be a pussy. who cares. well got home form wrestling at 5..and talk to somepeople  then going to head to bed.  jessi, let me say FORGET HIM, u need to move on..i'm glad that u are. because it will work out in the end. i'm always here. u got val when she gets back. and u got jerk-o-mia. he will be there as a friend and a b/f. DON'T wait another year. it really hurt u in that year. so don't do it again.i love ya and be good. i can't believe miss bates letting u out. damn she must want to get drank really really bad. i think she loosing her mind.So be careful tommorrow i'll talk to u later  i miss val, yes i'm saying it. she got that voice that i like to hear. well let me get that out in the open. i hope she having the best time  of time.  question for the day, everybody comminted on it please why are the hotties guys and the strongest guys, are trully pussys insides. why is that. think about it and post your commineted on it.think of a guy that look strong and tough. but are really pussies inside. tell me about them.  yall be good peace out,                                            ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THE FUNNIEST WRESTLING STYLE,  let me tell you, freestyle is nothing but throwing ppl around..u get points on picking a guy up and trying to throw him as high and far u can. and hurt him. well i got to try it out, it was fun. so tommorow i get to learn and wrestle like it. with are very on national champion micheal c. in freestyle wrestling. so it was fun. i could actullay hang with micheal a little bit. it was so fun. the camp dictorer want to train me more. but i couldn't do it. so i'm going to work with micheal and  help him train for the next national thing he got at the end of the summer. so it going to be cool an all.   woke up around 750..had to roll out of bed..couldn't bend my back form the waste..but more pain killier i got in to me..the better i felt. and to day it was free style..think god i got pain killers. because i was throw by micheal 6feet in the air and a a drop that hurt like hell..then i got to do it to him. if was fun. had lunch. and back to wrestling. more freestyle. then i got off around 5. went home...took a nap.went to get subway. time to sleep.  jerk-o-mia, damn that sucks. i would fight it so hard. and i would take ti to the superatinedited...but u can do must...u got 18 days of just sitting in a classroom. and look your closer to jess know..u can go see her when she at her aunts house. yea. dude u can't do must..but damn i'm sorry.  jess, what can i say. your hot and u'r a great person. and i would never let u out of my sights.(if you was my girl) but your not...i wouldn't let him do that..but all u can do it wait...but don't wait another year..u need to move on..wait a couple more days..then get over him..i love ya, in all..but u got to more on...u already waited a year don't do it again...  aubrey, i'm not appoligizzes about aly. we might need to move on. but i still want to know why. but u aight going to tell me...so we need to move on. i'm sorry hurting u in that time we try. i like u..u'r be a good president.but i'm not appoliges about aly. i hate her and i hope she would leave the venture crew. but she your best friend and i can see what your wanting to do. but i'm not..i try to be nice to her. but she hates me and i hate her. that final. and i'm sorry that going to end are talking. but i'm always is here to talk to u...but u just don't want to talk to me. so peace out..bye   peace out, ppl..need some sleep for another of wrestling,                                     ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHAT UP,  I feel like SHIT, 5hrs of wrestling with are very one 4time state champion, yall all know him. yea, he training for a national freestyle tournment where he might faces the 1 rank guy in his weight and junior league. so i TRY to help him. and got my ass kick. men i got thrown and hit and basely splat my michael. hell fuck me up. but it cool, me and him are cool.  woke up around 745, got shower and left home around 820 to get chris, the off to wrestling. wrestling sucks. wrestled until 1 ate lunch then back to wrestling to 5. got out took chris home then back home. lay on the couch. fell asleep unitl know  832.woke had to get my blogger done. men i feel like hell...and i got 3more days of this.. damnit. i think i'm going to die. but not.  jess,how was rookie week. i hope u had fun. i would love teaching assholes to learn how to marched the wrestling. but i had to quit. but i'll try to see u guys when ever i do...footballs game, we can chilled after football games.   peace out ppl.                      ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what up...ppl,   woke up around 745, rolled out of bed, i was like SHIT. GOT WRESTLING CAMP TODAY. damnit. well got there around 845. and got my wrestling shoes on. and paid 150 on a check to go to this. this will make me stronger. bull shit. make me feel like shit more. well got out for lunch at 1. Had to take chris to jerk-o-mia house to get some pills for something. well my jeep wheels suck ass. and i slide form 50 feet..it was kind of fun. and hit a cube on the side. damn it sucks..and got my banlces out of line.but men it sucks..ass... well finaly got to his house. and we eat and got back to wrestling. the longest 3hrs of my life. but i got through it. want to go over to jerk-o-mia to swim but got there and didn't really feel like it. so came home and sit on my ass. the me and dad got in to it. about the wheels and and tires..he still don't blieve i hit the tree.. he think i hit a post or something...i was like dad i hit a tree. well we just don't have the money to get new tires and blances it..so it get to slide and fishtail every time it rains. so who cares. yea..dad will died when i wreck it .because my tires suck. my tires are blod..when u do a penny test..u can see god we trust. yea. i got nothing else to say..i think...val gone..yea...there nothing else.   be good.                 ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I STAY UP ALL NIGHT. AND DAY. GOING ON  40HRS. DOING GOOD  I stay up for one reason to talk to val, before she left. well i got to say bye to her..when she was leaving. she gone. will be back in 1month. it going to be different. really it is. she call me and told me she staying with a yankee, name allison (I'm pretty sure that her name don't hold me too it) she form colorado, 15, blonde and a runner. she out of my league right there. jk. she seem like a nice girl letting val use her cell phone to call ppl during the weekend. we joke around in the phone call. i had to let her go...i don't know why i did..but i did.  went over to jerk-o-mia, about 6 yea..then we went over to jessi. aunts house frist. where jermiah was trying to hit the dog. then we final get the right houses..jess house. but who cares we got there. then we talk a little bit. jess your room is cool a little girl.but would be a nice room to f**k in...i don't know about that chair. look like it can do anything. look like it been through a lot. well i'm glad u have a ass..because there is no padding in that. ok, we went back to jerk-o-mia. where i KNOW that they took my car. but who cares. i got it back in one pieces. yea to make her happy,,i was scaried. but i know. remeber pay back a bitch. don't know what i'll do but it going to be a bitch. came home around 9..i got wrestling tommorrow until friday god damnit..form 9 unitl 5..who cares it will be ok. jess have fun a rookie week. and jerimah have fun at football..(like u guys do something shit). yall be good...peace out                              ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHAT UP,  well it 647 am, june the 6, i'm going to talk about june the 5. that day was crazy. let me tell you.  woke up around 6, damn dog woke me up. u damn basterd. to let him out. well lay down on the couch until about 2. the hell broke loose. me and jermiah want to do some shit. well it to goosepond industry park. well let me tell u...we didn't get out there until 3:30. my jeep doesn't have any tires. they are a pieces of shit. i promise u on that. well, i got out in a open field. with only 3 damn trees in that field. i did a fish tail around one tree. and i felt like i'm going to a dougnut in to the out on my side. i got scaried and turn my wheel really fast...and slide right into a tree. i didn't think it was that bad. but till we got out of the field and got into a warehouse to look..it was a bitch. damn got me sick to my stomach. well i was happy i didn't have airbags, man i might have been in a wheelchair. I'M GLAD I GOT A JEEP. the bumper save my life and my raiditor..the bumpers on old jeeps are 5miles away for the car.. now the bumper it 1inche for the car..i hit the tree in the middle it was funny as hell. i had to brang a lie up to tell my parents because they think i was at jerk-o-mia. so we think of one. after we took it over to chris to see if we can fix it.we can't. it really not that bad. after i took my fog lights off. we the lie was we was at jim rental house and i got into the grass and slid into a tree. there was a tree in mind.that i think was great. we took that idea. and went on it. i call dad. at frist i was ready to get my keys pulled. but damn dad was laughting his ASS off about it. i was scaried. after he found out nothing was hit in the raditor. i stayed in the house unitl 645. laying on the couch to make dad think i really felt bad. then dad came in and said "SON, get out of the house, and go to jermiahs" i was like ok. then he calls and says be home at 11. i was like shit. damn right on. well at 1015. i call him and ask him if i could spend the night.he said yes. me and jerk-o-mia watch some movies.   VAL, i hope u had a good time  talking to chris. that could hit the spot.and u can leave on happy memories. i can't believe that u want jermiah to do your dirty work. and he couldn't remeber what it was but i told him. he was like yea..i got it. well, i love that phone call.i really want to talk and say my good bye by voice. but i quess u had better times on the square. yea i saw u. didn't see me did u. jk. but i  want to say    GOOD BYE  and i'll miss u. i don't know what i'll get u for your birthday, aight going to be gas. shit u aight that important to me. 2 dollars for a gallon hell no. so u can think whatever u want. u'r going to get something that will scaried u. or something that u really really wants. that u aight going to get. so be good and give some nerds some loving.  well i been up since 7 yesterday morning and i had only 4hrs of sleep then. i think i'm going to stay up for a littlebit longer. the chrase really really quick.yall be good, and be safe.                                     ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      let me see where do i start, woke up around 11, watch a little of the maurey show then turn on the radio.. 103.7...clean my room. eat a watermelon about 3. then took shade running. he was show happy to get out. yea i know he an uguly dog..but he the gayest dog around just like AUBREY (val guy). jk. jermiah call around 4 saying that he will come over. didn't come over until 6..thanks buddy. let see..i really didn't want to spend time with chris and nappy *aka* KIM. so val was really badly wanting chris to come over. i could tell. well he didn't.but she got me. i went over there to talk with her. but i couldn't have the words to say. but who cares..i think i might miss val, MAYBE A LITTLE BIT. go have fun with dauphlin island. and u go find u a nice guys.(better the him). well i went to her room and saw the clothes on the floor. let me tell u. the girl need to better panties/thongs. one day we going to go shoping for those. get new style. granda panties or jsut plan panties aight sexy. well she got scaried and hide them. one thing i do know''''I KNOW HOW TO PACK'''''. and if you want some help give me a call tommorrow. but u should be pack by now. well jermiah ran into are love makeing damn him.jk. he showed up to talk. get way form chris and nappy. well we sit on the back patio. and chilled talk. val one word...pdicure..and wash your butt hole...take away on them weges... val went to get the mail. well nobody love her. because there isn't any. iwant val to give me a piggy back ride. well see couldn't hold me up..where was them gunnys she always talking about. couldn't hold me up. yeap..made me loses my wallet. thank god. val is a dectevies. i would be drive with no licnecess.jerk-o-mia left. then me and val went to get her some food. and abreys was the place. she didn't want to pop a twenty and only had 4 dollars so i was nice effect to let her use my only twenty. then i took her home. well i gave her a hug. and i went over to jermiah house. then went home around 10:45 because there was nothing to do. watch a little of texas chainsaw masteride. and a little of NO LOVE. (THANKS TO NAPPY. DIDN'T GET TO FINISH TCM)want to watch a chick flick. well what ever. eat some food...then talk to jim a little about relationship.   jermiah. jim likes jessica. and likes kim. so that means u can do anything with jessi. it will be cool with him. we to val, what does jim say SHE AN CRAZY BITCH. it  semi true. just a little. may be a centimeter. but that what he thinks.   last thinks, when u get into a fight with a close friend. it will never be the same as it was before a fight. what do u think yes or no. post thinks.                                      ~*STOUT*~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I WANT COMMINTES FOR EVERYBODY ABOUT THIS SUBJECT,  Why do nice guys don't get the girls, most girls fall in love with assholes. they get sewered over by the guys many of times. but the nice guys away are there to see that happen. but can't do anything about it.because what u get something into your head. you will always believe even if everybody else thinks it bullshit.then why does nice guys get no girls. i'm not talking about any person or anybody that dating anybody. just think about it. all the nices guys u know. really don't have a girlfriend. but nice girls aways get guys. WHY. all the nice guys u know. that never hurt or did anything to anybody. maybe a couple of time said or did somthing to hurt u..but didn't srcew u over. all those guys. do they have girlfriends.MOST, don't. when the guys are young. they learn that they can't get girls. they are afread of them. or just know he likes them more talking. so they get into sports or become smart. where they don't have to deal with girls...what do u think DOES NICE GUYS GET THE GIRLS?i gave u my reason why i don't think so. let me hear u'rs. yes or no...and why.think about it really hard..     ok,woke up around 10. sit on my ass...what to do something but val was going to hang out with chris.and jess she jerk-0-mia women. so u really can do must around here. so val i heard chris was to be sick. don't bleive that for a minute. but if he gives u that reason why he didn't hang out with u. then bleive it. i got my reason not to. SAT ON MY ASS from 10 until 3. got some food in that time for my neighbor,(she afried to get out if she doesn't have to)so she glad i have my licesnces. i don't care. she like my grandmother. makes me food and give me money i help her out. i'll miss her when she goees to the big pool in the sky. let see start to play some computer games. didn't really talk to anybody. went to wrestling 7..then got out at 8. want to go to jerk-o-mai. but i smelled. and i just don't feel comfortable there anymore. jermiah i love u in all. but i just don't like some ppl there. alkfjlakjfkaKIMlajflkajlfkj. but it cool. might come over tommorrow. well it 841...nothing to do...i feel like a LOSER. shit i forget i am one. yall be good tonight. talk to u tommorrow i want some commints for the subject.    before i go. KALA (not forgetting about u) be good. don't do anything nasty at that new job. i was there monday. but u wasn't around. me and val was chilling in the shoes dept. all the time. but i'll come  and see u one  day...i still want to meet AJ. tell haley HELLO FOR ME WHEN U TALK TO HER. tell her we need to go out sometime..to get some food. but it cool.  peace out ppl..                                   ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      LET ME TELL U. DAMN MOUNTAIN PPL NEED TO STAY ON THE MOUNTAIN.  I GOT SLIDE WIPED IN THE BACK BY A WHITE LITTLE OLDTOWN CAR. TOOK ONLY PAINT. DIDN'T LOOK TO BAD. THE MOUNTIAEER GOT PAINT OFF IT. AND THE BITCHS DROVE WAY. FUCKERS. DAD YELLING AT ME FOR NOT GOING SLOW EFFECT FOR PARKING. WHEN I WAS ALREADY PARK AND OUT OF THE CAR. WHEN HE HIT ME.FRIST ONE TO GET THE NEW MOUNTAINEER HIT.  let me tell u about my day,  woke up around 10. Eat some food around 10:30. Cereal the best. Was going to mow the yard..but my damn knee was killin me. so i ices it down until about 2. the let me see. was going to mow at like 4.but became lazy and still didn't do it. i'm lazy i know. well. sat on my ass until about 6 then val was crying that her blog wasn't lettin her get commints i try form my computer helping her. but i didn't work. well. i went to her house and fix that. then took something off her main that. know she crying that her address bar aight working right. well val. i'll come fix it tommorrow.that all i can say. but get in to your rececly bin and restore everything before u 12..or it gone. then if u still don't like it. i'll come fix it for u. ok. i fix her blog thing then we went out to sonic. val mother hates me. and she didn't know i was there until she got home. i was fucking scary. thanks val. i know she said something about the eagle of the year thing. but who cares. we went to sonic got me some slush. val got a rootbeer float. a LARGE rootbeer float. we sit there for a little bit. the went to kmart. where val want buy a damn 20 cards for $6. if 10 for 3...then 20 would be 6...yeap...that right.. then took her home got home around 9.. i had to lie to mommy and dad saying that i went to wrestle. (i skip wrestling to help val). can't do that tommorrow.   if you want me to fix that..call me when u get up. so that i can get that done then we can get some lunch then jcpenny for your watch. ok.  val, i really don't care if your talking to "him". really i don't. it make u more happy then talk to him it will be ok. everything will be ok if you talk to "HIM". i wouldn't cry if you do talk to him. just want u to know that. i see a better smile today then 4 days ago.or 3 days. because somebody talk to "HIM".  HAVEN'T PLAY COUNTER-STRIKE FOR LIKE 3WEEKS AND 4 DAYS I'M GOING CRAZY. I'M TOO LAZY TO PLAY. YALL HAVE A GOOD NIGHT PEACE OUT                                  ~*STOUT*~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SUP EVERYBODY,  eagle scout of the year, why me. i think i got it because of nobody but me and thomas the only ppl that try out for it. Think about it. i'm not the best guy for it. i live like an ass. i'm an ass to everybody.  LIFE SUCKS ASS, my family life became hard to bear. since that talking to. i can't do anything.let me give u a list that changes: 1.i lost the right to drive the mountareer when ever i want. well that sucks. 2.i got to be home by 9 clock, i get out of wrestling by 9. so yea.i use to get home when ever i want..like 10,11,or 12. it use to be i had to be home by 10 unless i'm over at somebody house 11. weekends 11 to 12...well it 9 for anyday..10 if i beg really hard.i don't beg.. 3.i can not go anywhere with anybody. they don't want me to do anything. 4.can't go to anybody house. jermiah or chris or jessi or val. can't go...i have to sneek over there. tell my parents that i'm working out or something. to get over there. 5.the parents fallow me to the place i'm going. i see them drive by the gym twice to find me there. when i make them stop the car. they say that they was heading to walmart to get some food. wandering if i need anything.when i tell them i want something they don't get it..what the fuck is up with that.   they think i'm some pot head or something. they know that i quit that. it killes your system. what started this was me and val. i did something bad to her.i left her at the fair when her parents was gone (didn't know her parents was gone)but i did.her mother hates me and so we start to fight.well we end it monday.but back to the story. she told my bother. about i'm disrepectful and drama queens or king because i'm a guy.well dad was behind micheal while val was talking to micheal.. and tell him things. i had to call jess to get her to stop. but i started it all. there are more thing besides these 5thing that changes. if u don't know me. val knows me the best anybody does. and i think she know that i don't cross my personal life and my family life. but she cross that.and my personal life is down in the toleit. but hey i had it coming to me.  well to miranda and jen. i love talking to u guys really. but i'm not ready to talk to ppl that question me. when u clear could read that it was a joke.but u had to talk to val. when val was piss at me. well i don't know what was said.but who cares. i'm not ready to talk to u guys anymore.  jess. damn girl u'r hot and now u'r not single. damn u jerimah. why do u get all the hot girls. u basterd. jess why can't u look at me. jk. i'm hot i promise.just playing. but i'm happy for u. really i am. ok...about the P.A. thing. u love him..but u'r taken.that final.don't want to hear about that anymore.that all. no more..keep that mouth shut. slient.  ok, well this july 17 i'm going to be gone. for two weeks with no phone or anything.just a backpack,tent,and my exprise of hiking.i'm going to be at philmont new mexico.i'll be on the rockymountain trail. and the santefa trail. that the wagon trail. be i'm ready. i think that it will be ok. i'll get to kayak the randa granda river (something like that).but i get to kayak..yea. i'm a kayakier, backpacker,and a hiker. well wrestling practices start for the summer training. damnit, my knee can't headle it anymore. i have to ices it like forty times a day. my knee is swelling like a pumpkin.but i can't go to the doctor. to find what it is.but damnit it hurts. if i go to the doctors (NO PHILMONT)i know there something wrong with it. but i'm not going.  val, i'm glad that we got are mad out to the open with are time together. i'm going to miss u when your gone.but it will be cool, life will get better i promise it will. when your sister gone. u'll miss her for a little bit.but u'll love it when everything settle back down. i promise. no gettin off the computer. u can do what u want to do. u get new clothes and everything a new room too. but it up to u what u want to do. but it will get better. my bothers left, and i was sad for a couple of days. i miss them i can't blame anything on anybody but the dog. the the dog can't keep the bread out to the open.but it will be ok. go to dauphlin island, have fun. find u a men,(a nerd person will be ok too). i'll send u your present. on your birthday. i promise it might get there a little early or late. i hope i get the address right.but it will get there i promise on that. well have fun. and be good. don't do anything that mary quince wouldn't do..  peace out ppl,                                               ~*STOUT*~  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what up guys,  &nbsp;  val,   be good...don't get into any wrecks...or get a ticket....don't do any thing crazy....if something happen to u...or to anybody i might care about....u call my cellphone an leave me a voice message...so i know when i frist turn it on...i know what going on...ok... u take care...i think we have been getting closer...and when i get back...we are going to became better friends...and when i get back...we are going to get some BV....that friday....ok....AND WE ARE GOING TO GET A MOVIE...TO...u be good when i'm gone...and u take care...i truth u val....so i don't have to worry anymore....I'LL MISS U...    &nbsp;  j-mar,   u take care....when i get back...that monday...we are going to start working out together...so we can hang out more...ok...monday and wednesday...and friday....ok....so we can hang out and&nbsp; talk about manly things....ok....u be good...and don't get into trouble .....lay off the acholol...w'll i'm gone...u can't drank with out me...;)...and if something happen to somebody i know..tell val..and let her call me...so that i can have a women voice on my cell phone..that will make me feel better...aight...   be good...don't get into anything...with out me..    &nbsp;  jess,   u have fun..being band leader...don't kill all u'r rookies...and don't be the nasty ass wipe section leader....i'm just playing...we all know u'r going to do good...make me proud... be the best u can... i hope u had fun on that cruises...and don't do anything dirty...u can tell me everything that dirty...when i get back....:P...and be good...and don't get a ticket for LOUD MUSIC....    &nbsp;  kala,  be good..talk to u later...have fun at work...i'll take u out to lunch on day...before school...ok...have fun don't do anything fun...hope u get u'r car...and have a good days at work.. &nbsp; if i miss anyone...sorry...but u have fun...and yall don't do anything fun with out me...hahah...so be good don't play around and i'll talk to u later... &nbsp; be back around JULY 30 about 4 or 5.... &nbsp; *S* peace out...   &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what up ppl,  wake up around 9 because my neigbor need some help...so she calles me.. i help her out until 12. then lay down most of the day..because my damn teeth hurt like hell....so i got to see the butieful dentist around 9 tommorrow...at philmont i could be sent home because my teeth aight the best in the world...at philmont they go through u'r physical and see if they can fine something wrong with u...and when they do u'r sent home....as quick as u came..but anyways... i was in a piss off mood when i came back home and got my ass yelled at for some bullshit...so i lay around most of the day...and finally got on the computer...and hell nobody is on...damnit....so i just talk and clean some gear to get ready...hell somebody wants me to get out of this places...and i'm ready to leave this places and go to the outback..but around 3 i had a meeting with the director of CAMP JACKSON...ANd gave him these maps...and got some cash for it... but told him that if we open this trail up to everybody...4 wheelers will start coming into camp...and so i told him if u want to hope this trail up...call me frist i still can hide the part to get into camp... he all cool about it...and we talk ..and then off to  home where i sent on my ass...and did nothing..  val, i miss spell/told what i want to say on the last night thing...most of it is...but it aight u'r fault like it said on the other one...i fixed it ...and told u....i just want to know...i'm really trying to find what to say...and i'm sorry i piss u off...but damn hell u'r u don't need me...    jess, man u are having a ruff time ...damn that sucks...i'm here to try to help u out with thing.  j-mar...damn i'm so bored...we are can be bored together...  damn i'm going to go and play some coutner-strike... *S*
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what up,   woke up around 8. because last night i was ask by boyscout to map some trails out...so i met a friend at camp jackson we went to pigah gap. and started there. we started at 940 and hike to willer cabin..chilled there and water up..then went to the ice boxs...it and open cave...that old air flows out of it and feels damn good..that where we ate some lunch there. SORRY NO mickey-d's...but form there i map it out a little bit and started on the trail that go alone JONES CREEK...my dude just set a hammock right between some trees and sleep i try to sleep but i haven't been out on that trail in a long time..so i did and went back up the mountain again back to the bridge around CR235. so i took around 5 miles to do that...it was 5 miles to get to jones creek...so i had a lot of time to think about shit...and i will tell u what i think. but anyway i map the area out and found a nice place to camp  by creek great places. then i'm off to cross the creek and then off to camp jackson i didn't get to the jeep until around 430..then drove him back to his truck. then off to home..got home...got bitch out for leaving the house early and not tell anybody...then i showed him his phone and my message where i told him what i was doing...he like ok...and left me alone...anyway i really hate come back home because i got nothing to do when i get back...what the point i would love to get lost in the woods it would be great... so i'm leaving friday to go to philmont...i have to be navagarite because i'm the only one that know how to read maps and compass..and can use a GPS...any way let me tell u what i think about looking a a class 2 whitewater..  val, u know i want to have a better friendship with u...it been going down shit sinces u met the asshole...i want back to the way it was before. when we frist met..but i tire...but it looking to me that u'r not wanting to do it..tell me now....i can't stop being like i'm trying to do thing with u...i know u would love to be with jess more then me....and i know u would be with asswipe more then me... i'm getting tired of this shit...i'm trying to brang my wall down for u..but it look like nothing in return....and i don't like that...it up too u...u can tell me what u want in a personal thing..but i want to know before i go to PHILMONT...u got until thursday night...u know what i want...it up too u...  everybody else i don't got anything with u...j-mar we are all cool, i'm always going to be with u....i'm just trying to get something back the way it was..anyway, we are all cool together.  jess, damn u'r always busy and damn that sucks for u..that all i got to say.  yall be good, *S*
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what up,  got up around 11..because the dog want out..got on the computer and talk to val alittle...want to do something before i had to go...but u know her...she would rather go with her girl friend...then me..but anyways...i got off..because i know the talking aight going nowwhere...so lay down on the couch and watch tv...until 230...then took a shower and got ready...didn't really want to leave until 3 something...but nobody was on..to talk too...so i just turn the light and just left...did really worried... got to huntsville around 4...and my meeting wasn't until 5 so i stop at a gas station got something to drank and went to the meeting room of this church and wait until it started...well we talk and talk and talk...i had to teach them how to read maps and use a GPS...(jess u know what it is)...finally it was about 8 i got out...and went with some of the leaders to LONGHORNS STREAKHOUSE... got me some streak.. and talk a lot about what coming up over philmont... then leaving i was on the phone from huntsville to woodville with a leader asking me a lot of questions about hiking/backpacking...anyway... i set up a hiking with a couple of ppl...around pigeon cap to jackson a 18 mile hike that i  will get done quick...it a shack down for there hike in end of this month... finally got home around 10 to scottsboro...and had to go get some food for this hike tommorrow to that what i did...got home around 1040...and talk with the old man for a little bit about what happen today...and what going to happen tommorrow...and finally i pack for this thing tommorrow know i'm going to talk a little bit then go to bed...so leave a good comminted...  looks like everybody had a good day, so that good.  hope everybody have a good day tommorrow..peace love, and hairy greases. *S*
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what up,   let me tell u about my day, i woke up around 11 to 12...then just chilled pick up my room...getting a little nervous about philmont...anyway.. about 2 something val calles and says that she want me to do the ad-ware program into her computer...i started at 3 and got done with the computer until 4...sorry val, i delete u'r music...but u don't need it u got online radio....i show u how to do it..when it works. but anyways...me and her just chilled and talk to some of her ppl...i started to get bored...and started messing with her...:)...i lick my finger and stuck them in her hear>can't remeber the name of that. then i got the drill to her..but finally she had to washes the cars..big mistake on me. well it started ok...she keep getting me a little wet..so finally i was hosing down the car...and val walk right into it...she got soak...it didn't happen 1 not 2....not 3 times....like 5 times....u'r so stupid...but i still like u...maybe....anyways...so she try to get me back....ok she did get me back not 1 but twices...and i had a rag that i was washing it...and sure i did...dump it on her head...it was funny...she freak out...so i had to wash it off for her..but she got me back when i doing the wheels...that val was crying. i can't do it anymore...so i said i do a wheel...and she got the hose...sure she did get me....right in the ass...finally i got the hose...and she only had a couple of dry spots...i couldn't let her go... not dry...so i got her right in the ass too...then she turn around...i was like hello soak girl...she didn't have a dry spot when i got done..i want to stay longer i wish i did..but dad was wanting to be gay..and said i was over staying my welcome...so i had to go...and when i went...i had to drive in wet underwear...thanks val...i actully had fun...monday u'r come to my house and u get to clean my jeep with my thing....good tooo... ok...finally got home...and dad was crying...he in chattoange... sorry val..i would have take u to arbey...but i didn't even get to go...i would love to have some chicken fingers...but i did have fun...  i wish things was different too...and i wish u could tell me thing..but i still like u any way....  so yall be good..  *S*
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys...what up  well went to bed at 4...and woke up around 12. took a shower..talk to j-mar and jess on the computer...U GO GIRL. my cedit card finally came in...so i had to use it to get it started..and i had to depsoit some money around 3...i called val up to see what she doing..and i want to talk...remeber val...what we talk about...u'r right..i can't remeber what got me on the computer but i was helping val get her computer faster...so i think i did...it was funny too i couldn't help to laugh....its alway vals fault with the computer...always....it was funny...but anyways...got to see val pictures of the dauphin island...and talk to her mother...val u better be quit...u'r mom going to throw u against the wall...send u down to three springs...  but anyways...after i try to fix the computer...and the val telling the stories about me hanking into there computer...we finally went out to eat...because val was hungary...but anyways...we did...and we saw some ppl..and talk to some ppl...SORRY VAL THAT u'r mother remeber the talking we had about me getting a lower time period....i hope u got no greafe over that. any ways...we got done eating...and i need some money so i went to use my credit card...and got me twenty bucks and fianlly came home...were i'm sitting her talking some ppl..and getting ready to play some counter-strike...  val, TELL YOUR MOTHER THANKS FOR THE MEAL....and also tell her tommorrow i got the disk thing...so i'll might come by to get it on u'r computer...but anyways...THANKS FOR THE FUN FILLED NIGHT.  *S* 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up around 12. took a shower and sit around until about 230... talk to jess thourgh text messaging..said she going get val present...if i want to come...so i said yes. but at 3 i had a hair appointment...so got my hair cut off. not all the way...just a little...mom paid me to get ready for philmont...so i said ok... and then i met jess at walmart..and we look at some thing got her some cards..and talk a little bit..then off to hibbits...and foot actions..(one of them damn foot places)...then off to the movie gallery...to take a movie back...i want to see haley short hair...say said it looks good...i want to see it...well then we found jothatin B...i just can't remeber how to spell names..we went inside to get some dranks...at foodworld and see the baby...j-mar.....Then we and johntan...we back to walmart to drop me off..didn't really feel like val wants to see me...saying that i'm makeing everybody to screw her over... yea...so i got in my jeep and went home...well there wasn't must to do...laydown...for a little bit...then went to wrestling...moves some mats...and finally i got home to find that i'm blogging early ...and to wacth TV...so yall be good...  jess, i told u to get the lemon bag...thanks for giving me a text message to see if i can come with u...thanks...we can do that some time...  val....what u'r deal...i don't want to get into it anymore...it u'r call this time...u think i hurt u more then what u did to me...bullshit....but it u'r called...u know what i want...it piss me off u blame a shit load a thing ...and lie to me...about saying thing...i don't care...u know what i want...it u'r called...  yall be good.  *S*
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      let me tell u about my crazy monday,  MONDAY, i can't remeber anything at the begin...but i got a phone call form micheal...saying that we don't spend effect time together..and mom is making u get out of the house...PIKES ARE HAVING A GET AROUND CHATTONAGE...TOLD ME TO MEET HIM AT 5...AT SOUTH PISHURBURG, SO I SAID OK.. next minture i was off to SP. and meet micheal at the walmarts parking lot. i got to drive the moutineer. micheal left his jeep at the parking lot and we jump in to the mountianeer. and took off...i was ready for a long drive..but it wasn't...we keep going stairt  down the road..to the right of walmart..pass it..ok here where it get a little bad. can't remerber all of it. but here we go...we got on to the grave road..and went about 4 miles back..and hit the mass big cabin. it was big ...as soon i walk in...there was a 3 storie BEER BONG. i was like what the fuck...THERE WAS THIS GIRL TAKING HITS ON IT..AND GETTING ALL OVER HER...IT WAS LIKE DAMN....but micheal said got relaxes and find me when u want to go...i was like see ya....i walk around an meet some pikes i know form marshall and micheal..and i talk around with them..and meet some girls...well i went to get a beer..here is the funniest thing i saw....the kegs was hang upside down....so u didn't have to pump it...they had 2 kegs like this...then u have the hard acholice...and there where u got the money in...it was bad...cost some money to get a jake and coke...but it was free beer think about that...which on do u go to...well i drank a little bit..watch some dude do something..talk to some ppl...then i remeber getting thrown into the mountianeer..i was what the fuck...then i wake up on my floor with my mouth on a porno...thanks to micheal...it was 12 when i wake up...MASS OF HEADACHE..then i hear the storie...micheal said that a pike try to drove home and hit a pole...right next to the house...cops was all over it...we was gone...i was laughting my ass off...but i had a headache...and dad like go get the jeep some oil...i was ok...then about 145...about to get home...dad calls and said u got a dentis appoinment...i was like damnit...spent 1 hr there...getting hurt...like hell...but get out..and drive home...it sucks....got home..and lay my asss on the couch...then off to wrestling....it was raining like hell and if was fun...driving ...damn that all i got to say...it was the best..anyway...i about got wrestling...it was flooded...but we wrestled...so i got done...quess who i got to wrestle with CHRIS..it was funny...got some anruger out of each other...but got home..and talk to ppl..watch a little tv. and i'm going to bed..   val, nobody screwing u over...i just want to get shit off my chest about u...jess loves u like a sister...hell more then a sister..and j-mar is u'r best friend...a great friend to everybody...adrienne..i can't say must..she likes u too...and u know what i want to do...and hell if u want to stop this shit...i'll be u'r way...u got what u want...and i got nothing...so it up to u.  j-mar...man i'm sorry for what i said and it will never come out of my mouth again..i forgot about the crazy girl that u date...and all that bullshit...i plum forgot until i said it...i was like damn...i got to go..and get out of this talking..sorry man...  jess...hellli got to leave u a comminte...i need to read your thing...sorry but i will leave u one before i got to bed..  peace out,  *S* 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what a buetiful day,  just another boring day here.. not must happen..really anything happen...i had a lot to think about...i wish i could chances alot of things in my life...i'm getting tired...nothing really great coming out of this...but i'm trying to keep my personal life out of this..last night was the great night went bad...i think it bull shit..but i don't want to start anything...jess n j-mar my mouth going to be shut to u...i don't want to get anything start ever again....so there...who else do i got something to say too...but i just want to say thanks to all the guys that turn my great night into shit...and this morning i really just want to crussing somebody out......but "u" finally did it...i'm tired of u'r bullshit...i think we squared it away that we will stop fighting or shit..getting shit started...well u did it agian...u was far away too....that the last straw...i hope u'r happy u kill my life...and i'm tired of trying to fight it...i'm done with this shit....the white flag is up...i'm not really wanting to work it out...u got it...and i hope u'r happy...so that is tell u i'm over with this shit...so there...i see that adrienne got a good NEWS...i new it was going to work out...and i'm happy for u...so happy fourth of july...see yall later  *S*  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      quess what, i finally got out of the house...  well it july 3...and scottsboro having their annule fireworks show. THANKS TO JESS, AND JERMIAH. i went. for the best time i had. thank u guys...it really means alot. see if u havn't been up to speed. i can go over to jermiahs to because somebody said something to chris...yea..so i been stuck in a house for 3 weekends..no where to go...nothing to do....not a damn thing to say about it. we finally i got out...had somewhere to go...ppl to see. well i got gas, met jess and jermiah there. val told me to call her...well if she doesn't answer her phone then there no point of talking...well she calls her best friend...jess... because of a un name person...i can't ride with anybody anymore... i have to drive...well so i went to see her...yes she home...so i went to see her....well she look the same...nothing new...then we went to mary jeans party...i hate partys and i don't care if u  know...well we got into the rich neighborhood.. i had the uguliest car there....i'm damn proud of it...my jeep...damn right...i don't care...well me and jermiah sat out there for a good 30 mins. well finally, we went to the fireworks show. thanks to j-mar...we got great parking places. we sit there...the girl want to go to the brigde....not me...i want to watch a show anywhere but the bridges....so we chilled for a little bit...and finally thank god for adrienne calling...she said something to jess...and jess said ok...we are not going to the birdge...thank u adrienne....well we was off walking to the some place..(forgot name)...but we got there...but before we  got there...valerie ask somebody for a ride...they jump into the jeep. val and jess...left me and jermiah out to cleans are selfs. well we just went what the fuck...and said we needed a dranks...sure effect we found one...the slushes...a masses long line...and we sat there...and found a good friend brett. who showed us to adrienne. and some other girls....one of the girls val made a death treat too...or something...what up with that...(can't remeber her name...but seeem like a nice girl...somebody sister...the sister is jermiah cousin). yea what up with that...when i find that name...i'll post it...it got adrienne a little upset with u...but adrienne u going through a hard time...I NEED A BACK RUB...GIVE ME A CALL SOMETIME...jk...hope things work out...well since val and jess left us...i wasn't sweating it...i sat down with the girls and brett and listern to some SOUTHREN FLIGHT....damn good band...well i got some phone calls...i didn't answer didn't really care...u listern...and finally got a call...and i answer it...damn it was jess...saying that she has to get home..and everything...i was like damn i'm having a great time....i hated to leave...for once i was having fun...u just don't understand...u never left the house to do anything...and finally u leave the house and u want to have fun...damn right i did...sorry jess u didn't...and jermiah u didn't....and val...nobody cares for u...jk...u didn't either...but damn i was...i'm not going to let nothing brang a great day down...that what i did....not a damn thing...so thanks u jess for letting me have a great time....and thank u for inviting me....and thanks u j-mia for riding with me in the car...we had some damn good times....  i wish one thing before i go to bed...i wish friends could tell the truth...that all..  THANK YALL FOR THE GOOD TIMES, adrienne i got to get some number with that girl...jk...i can't date jermiah family...hell i'm like family to him...he my big bother that all cool and shit...yall have a good night...i'm going to be online for a little bit...send me a message  peace out, ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      let me tell u about my day, well woke up at 12...really 11. but didn't get out of bed until 12...lay on the couch and watch 360 until when ever the race started...then played counter-strike until 6...ate some dinner. then back to counter-strike until 12...got off to see that everybody is asleep. well that was my day...o yea...i started dranking again...i don't care anymore...  LIFE WILL GET BETTER UNDER A BOTTLE OF WHISHEY.  yes val, i been branking since i  can't go anywhere...no jermiah. yea i been dranking everytime my little picture of jack daniels up..that means i dranking make it feel better..and when i quit i see the world again...and got to start back over.  VAL I BEEN DRANKING SINCE U RAN U'R DAMN MOUTH TO CHRIS. yes, i aight blaming u for anything it old news. but that why i been dranking ...not a lot of ppl no it..i try to quit...i almost had 5 months..but damnit it got hard. and i started agian....  i'm out...later *S*
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      BY:BRAD PAISLEY, AND Featuring Alison Krauss Bill Anderson/Jon Randall  She put him out like the burnin' end of a midnight cigarette She broke his heart he spent his whole life tryin' to forget We watched him drink his pain away a little at a time But he never could get drunk enough to get her off his mind Until the night  1st Chorus He put that bottle to his head and pulled the trigger And finally drank away her memory Life is short but this time it was bigger Than the strength he had to get up off his knees We found him with his face down in the pillow With a note that said I'll love her till I die And when we buried him beneath the willow The angels sang a whiskey lullaby Sing lullaby)  The rumors flew but nobody knew how much she blamed herself For years and years she tried to hide the whiskey on her breath She finally drank her pain away a little at a time But she never could get drunk enough to get him off her mind Until the night  2nd Chorus She put that bottle to her head and pulled the trigger And finally drank away his memory Life is short but this time it was bigger Than the strength she had to get up off her knees We found her with her face down in the pillow Clinging to his picture for dear life We laid her next to him beneath the willow While the angels sang a whiskey lullaby  (Sing lullaby)        THIS IS MY SONG..IT BEEN ON MY MIND GOOD AND BAD. IT BEEN THERE I WANT U TO KNOW THE LYRICS. IT A GREAT SONGS. YALL SHOULD DOWNLOAD IT 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      let me tell u about my week, MoNdAy, eagle scout of the year once more..this time it was the council not vfw. yea woopie. we went to huntsville for that. got to hear so great quarterback for Alabama..didn't really care..so well i had a shit load of money on me..and i need it off my hands we to redstone credit union. i had account already was going to make a despoit to saving then me and dad was talking...i'm getting a credit card. and put that money into it.went to wileys outdoor. and got me some hiking clothes. then finally came home.not must pass that  TuEsDaY, no a dam thing, sit on my ass. didn't even get out. stayed indoors all day. play counter-strike. talk so ppl..that about all  WeDnEsDaY, NOT A DAMN THING AGAIN. at least i got out..went to get some food that all. let me tell u how many time i been out. well i haven't fill up my jeep in like going on 3 weeks. my jeep has a 16 gallon tank..that a small tank.. well my jeep get about 20 miles to a gallon. and that was 3 weeks ago...i'm just now getting on half way. half way.  ThUrSdAy, let me tell u about today, i finally got out side. mow the yard aight i'm good. well mow the yard. and went back in side again..hasn't got out any. i'm getting to hate this slinceness. i'm going crazy but i can get through it. well it the JULY 1, AND I HAVE 16 day before philmont, mom thinks i'm not ready because i couldn't work out..because of ringworm. they didn't want me to do anything because it got into my blood system. but i killed it quick and if i work out i could have got ever where.   FrIdAy, it a little early to be saying this but i can tell u what i'm going to do.  A great day of sitting on my ass. going to try to hit the counter-strike. but my clan is having a vegas party on 4th of july and i can 't go to it...no money ...marshall or micheal can't go..so i'm going to be up playing while they are having fun in vegas.   let me tell u about my subject, i haven't date anybody for a couple of years (hell been single over 99% of my life) and i got a girl start to liking me. i could tell that she really like me. the only problem is that this girl is 560 miles away. yes 560 miles. and i finally ask what do u think about us. and thank to ADRIENNE.i thank u personally because i could only talk to about this.but i didn't tell u everything just effect to get me on the right track and i thank u for that. i like to personally thank u for that.i finally got it out. Adrienne all that is true but she aight no (STALKER) i promises that. but we talked. and i think i ended it..because i couldn't think what to thank. she said some thing that got me afriad. and i fanilly learn that i'm afriad of GIRLS. yes i'm a little afriad. and i can't not finger them out. girls are complex. way to complex for my little mine. we i learn something, jermiah if u need help tommorrow give me a call i'll try to get that firewall down...i think it a viruses.but just give me a call i'll come and help u out. yall be good. sweet dreams. don't let the bed bugs bite.                               ~*STOUT*~
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey,      my day was good..i had a great day...   jess we going to have some fun in healthcare...my teachers in everyclass is crazy...not must to say today...i had a boring day...      through my life...i wish things were a little better and but i need to changes my life style...but who cares...  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHAT UP PPL,   i know i havn't blog in for a while...but it hard...yes i was gone for about 2 weeks ...if u want to know how my trip went u just have to ask...i'll might tell u some stories...i'll just give u the basics    on the trail for 11 days..at NEW MEXICO   for 14 days... that makes 2 weeks...   i hike 63 miles. and did 17 miles of side hikes the total is 80 miles...   pack weight first started off at 50 pounds...no water include.... in the middle my pack weight 65 pounds... at the end it weight was 55 lbs....   i pull the fuck out of my ankle   on day 3...finally got better after day 8 i think...   it rain, sleet, hailed...and high fucking winds...all the damn time...rain everyday on me...   yes to all the ppl that want to know...i did hike with girls...call my sister crew....did everything with us...and yes they was all girls form kanas city...crazy girls too...fun to be around ...miss them  a lot...got a lot of nice memorys (stories)...   food suck ass...a lot of can shit...nothing great...got a apple on day 5 (i think)....   saw a bear...and saw a shit load of animals...12 points MULE DEER....and a touches a mass cow...   there more but u got to ask me about it....yes i do have a map to show u all the places i have hike too in philmont...so come over i'll show u...and talk to about it...      coming back home....i felt a lot better miss SOMEBODY...but i did feel better....i got my head clear...and could look out side a box very nices...but when i got back i want a great last week...it didn't happen...i already talk to the person that i want to do this with...but my week suck ass...i got to see my girl one day...and i could have spend a whole day with her...but descied not to do it...my little girl got big on me...mom and dad told me she can stand up on her own....and crawl around...wish i could have seen that...got to see j-mar a little...dude got a big O ass...just playing big ass...got to see adrienne a little with her husband...yall really need some wedding cousnalling...we can trade jeeps anytime....i talk to daddy...he said he would think about it...but he doesn't know...sorry...u'r jeep is alot better then mine...but if u clean it sometime...then it would 100%better... talk to val a little...yes i did talk to jess today...hell she call me too...felt so proud of my self...then she said she couldn't find j=mar....i was like ok... but anyway...good to hear u'r voices....went to see KALA at her job... she look nice...u had to loose weight....and hell i think her butt got bigger...:p....yea...school startes monday...damn that sucks...what i can say about my summer....i lost a lot of shit...and i gain some things....think i got shit better..but found out i didn't....      j-mar....i told u everything will work out...thank god it did... i got u'r back with a 9....but no i don't have the vodkia ...sorry...it all cool...monday we working out ...that will be are hang out time...sorry we couldn't play some NFL...but damn eagle project got to me....i had to help out...damn i didn't think i always got to help...but who cares.....sorry want to kick ur' ass in some football...hell i wish i could have seen u kick some vasity ass in the scrimmes...but u know what happen...sorry man...i'll come watch u when u play...truth me...i'll be there...see u score that touchdown....i think i'm going to cry...my little boy all grow up....i'll be there...got to find me somebody to go with...but i'll be there...      i'll do some purple...   if yall every gone on a trip...when u come back...it like reality hit u right it the ass...hurts like hell too... i wish i never came back...in the backcountry was the nices shit i ever love... this place was the greates thing i have ever seen...seeing thunder just right out side u'r tent...i really wish i just stay out there...and came home for a couple of days....but that can't happen...and i don't got effect money to go back next summer...damn it sucks to not be able to do a whole month out there..and get the fuck out of this damn town....IF I HAD ONE WISH....THE WISH THAT I WAS NEVER COMING BACK TO SCOTTSBORE AFTER I LEFT FOR THE BACKCOUNTRY. this damn town has too many damn dama queens...in the backcountry u never seen anybody else....u could stay lost...for ever....and i would love it...      got to use a light gay color...   things i miss...   1. the stars, in a middle of a pasture...and thunder and lighting everywhere...but it aight raining..   2. the girls, crazies mother fuckers, coolest mother fucker...damn the bad ass girls..a lot of storie.   3. hiking...my feet hurt...my ankles kill me...but i know i'm never going to get off this damn trail.    4. miss my true friend..the friend that i look at a picture to see her...the friend that would tell me everything...the friend that i can trust....the friend that i could tell anything too...and that i can trust....   5. pissing on some trees to see if we can have a bear to come into r camp site...      i miss a lot of shit...but those are 5 that i miss..      yall holla (as jess would say)      *S*  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>