<Blog>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like the idea of writing an online journal.  This way my friends can read this and know what my life is up to without feeling clueless.    I've been thinking about joining the coast guard ever since last October. I've been so unsure as to what I want to do with my life for a long time! I think the Coast Guard would be an awesome experience!  4 Years seems like a long time, but everyone says that time flies so fast, so why not give it a try?!  I also think it would be a good experience because of the structured lifestyle.  I'm so unsure what I want to do, that they will tell me what to do, and when.  I like that I will be in better shape, and hopefully i can continue working out once I get out of bootcamp.  The Coast Guard has a lot of benefits too.  Medical, and Dental is included, so I wouldn't have to worry about paying for that.  I would also get a $5,000 signing bonus because i have a degree, and I would be enlisted as an E-3.  If I stayed in the military for 20 years, I would be able to go into retirement after the 20 years.  But who knows if that will happen.  I just want to give it a try.  Maybe after the 4 years, I'll know more about what i want to do.    My friends are cautious for me, making sure I find out everything before I sign the papers.  I have been to the recruiter 2 or 3 times, and I've gotten to talk to 2 girls that are in the service--and both say they love it!  My friend, Alahna's boyfriend, Wes, is in the Coast Guard, and i've got to ask him a ton of questions!  I think it would be fun to see what else is out there.  I want to be able to make a lot of friends, and possibly even find a Coast Guard man!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have talked with a lot of people who like the Coast Guard, but last weekend I went down to Seattle and met someone who doesn't like it.  I went and visited Ian and I met his neighbor who has one more year left in the Coast Guard, and he hates it.  He said to join the Air Force.  He also said that they "treat you like a bitch," and there's a lot of racism, and you can't trust anyone.  Of course they'll treat people like slaves (and that scares me), but I will be a piece of government property, and the government will be taking care of me.  I have never heard anything about not being able to trust the people you work with or racism.  I still think the Coast Guard would be fun because I love being on the water.  The only thing I'm concerned about is, What will I do after my 4 years if I don't make the CG my career?!  What kinds of jobs will I be able to get? 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>