<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So... Who should we invite?  Should we just invite everyone we know - or should we be mean about it? (I love being mean) We can't have everyone writing - ( then there would be no one left to read )  lol.  I think that we should maybe vote on people... Okay, so lets get some rules here:  [rules are subject to editing] 1. Member should post once a week. 2. Play nice.  [doesn't mean no cussing - just keep it professional] 3. Individual will not be invited if there is a problem with a current member (IE: if they just don't get along)  4. If two members don't get along - a vote will be held - one might get booted.  ... (this is starting to sound fun...) lol 5. Let's try and invite someone who brings positive energy to the group.  6. Let's invite people that will actually  write .  (I don't know about Jill, but I don't want to go through the trouble of sending them an invite only to have them be quite and never write anything.)  That's all I can think of.  eh.  (don't post a new entry to comment (let's actually use the comments below :P)  
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am here now.. where are you two?? haha i am glad that we have this blog together! you guys are great! love you both! 
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know what this site is going to be used for either but We will put interesting stuff on here. I swear it wont be boring!
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read this story about this  urlLink girl that didn't graduate because of her degrating  speech about her crappy school. .  *giggles*  That sounds like it could happen at Saks..
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, Jill.  My emails finnally were sent from  urlLink Blogger .  I guess they were just having server or mailing problems.  Anyway, I think the title should be renamed - but I can't really think of a name.    I still don't even know what this weblog can be used for...
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If only, if only...
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      **Want to be a member??  Do this.** 1.Make a blogger account. 2.Do a little sumpthin sumpthin with your profile. (sorry, my street language isn't that good) *make sure to  have your email adress on your profile , that's very important* 3.Comment here and there. Gah.  I'm not asking you to sacrafice animals or anything... 4.An invitation will  mysteriously appear in your email . 5.fin.    1. Member should post once every two weeks. 2. Play nice. [doesn't mean no cussing - just keep it professional] 3. Individual will not be invited if there is a problem with a current member (IE: if they just don't get along)  4. If two members don't get along - a vote will be held - one might get booted. 5. If Jill doesn't like them and everybody else does... Too bad they can't play with us....(even if I do get along with them I can still secretly dislike them very much ahaha!) 6. This is not a personal weblog. [meaning you can't claim it as your own - because it is a group collaboration] However, post as often as you like... 7.Every member must have an updated profile. [complete with full name, birthday, location, likes, intrests, etc.] 8.Especially ph34r Jill and her l33t kitty cow woof woof skills...Rick  oo... AND NO BAD LANGUAGE!!! well not really bad stuff.... 9.Don't use  distractive  HTML.    [last updated on July, 22: 12:19pm] 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    write a funny caption for this picture.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink very,  very , interesting. 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Always knew there was something weird about that logo.. find this and more at  urlLink Davezilla.com 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey yall! Well I went and saw Van Helsing! That is the BEST vampire movie I have ever seen and Ive seen many! It is at the top of my movie list! But on to the scary stuff! Tonite after work some guy followed my to my sisters house and was hollering out the window at me. then he turned around and did it again! I was sooo scared. if my brother wouldnt have came outside I would have called the cops! When I left to go home I had my cell phone in hand so I could call on the drop of a dime!! Well Ill see yall prolly tuesday.. lol maybe! Have a great weekend yall! -Me
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hmm.. What's going on here?
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ...
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally get my car!! I have been waiting all summer...i mean it is mine...but i mean i finally get it for good...my cousin, Josh, is fixing it today..then i get to start driving it to school and stuff!! yay....i am excited...just b/c i dont have to ask ppl to pick me up or anything anymore *smiles* ok...well thats all for now... 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just got back from seeing The Bourne Supremacy. it was a really really good movie. better than i had expected anyways! i give it 9/10 stars!! haha. i recomend it to&nbsp;everyone! well.. i guess i have nothing more to say!!  
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey all. I just wanted to say, it might be a little while before I post again. I just got my computer back from the shop and I have to fix a lot of things. Plus, my Favorites list in AOL is all fucked up so I have to straighten that up too.. I like how the blog is going.&nbsp; Keep it up.   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eww i am soo sweaty from Rookie camp...oh we got a rookie...she is a black girl named Lakia she is actually perdy good...but anyways....my head hurts so bad...and i cant seem to cool off....lalalala....i am sooo bored...i really have nothing to say just a bunch of useless junk....ok bye!!  
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A hip young man goes out and buys the best car available: A brand new Ferrari GTO. He takes it out for a spin and stops at a red light. &nbsp;An old man on a moped, looking about 100 years old, pulls up next to him. &nbsp;&nbsp;The old man looks over at the sleek, shiny car and asks, "What kind of car ya' got there sonny?" &nbsp;The young man replies, "A Ferrari GTO. &nbsp;It cost half a million dollars!" &nbsp;"That's a lot of money," says the old man." Why does it cost so much?" &nbsp;&nbsp;"Because this car can do up to 320 miles an hour!" states the young dude proudly. &nbsp;The moped driver asks, "Mind if I take a look inside?" &nbsp;"No problem," replies the owner. So the old man pokes his head in the window and looks around. Then, sitting back on his moped, the old man says, "That's a pretty nice car, all right... but I'll stick with my moped!" &nbsp;&nbsp;Just then the light changes, so the guy decides to show the old man just what his car can do. He floors it, and within 30 seconds, the speedometer reads 160 mph! &nbsp;&nbsp;Suddenly, he notices a dot in his rear view mirror. It seems to be getting closer! He slows down to see what it could be, and suddenly, &nbsp;&nbsp;WHOOOOOOSSSSSHHH! Something whips by him, going much faster! &nbsp;&nbsp;"What on earth could be going faster than my Ferrari?" the young man asks himself. He floors the accelerator and takes the Ferrari up to 250 mph. &nbsp;Then, up ahead of him, he sees that it's the old man on the moped! Amazed that the moped could pass his Ferrari, he gives it more gas and passes the moped at 275 mph. &nbsp;WHOOOOOOOSHHHHH! He's feeling pretty good until he looks in his mirror and sees the old man gaining on him again! Astounded by the speed of this old guy, he floors the gas pedal and takes the Ferrari all the way up to 320 mph. Not 10 seconds later, he sees the moped bearing down on him again! The Ferrari is flat out, and there's nothing he can do! &nbsp;Suddenly, the moped plows into the back of his Ferrari, demolishing the rear end. &nbsp;The young man stops and jumps out, and unbelievably, the old man is still alive! He runs up to the mangled old man and says, "Oh my God! Is there anything I can do for you?" &nbsp;The old man whispers with his dying breath... "Unhook... my...suspenders... from... your... side-view mirror." 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      everything is set so that I don't have to go. yay!
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I redid  urlLink the rules .  I also deleted you Tiffany... you just... ... ... didn't write that much; so, it's not big loss or anything.
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Not  going to orientation.  Fat Granny is going to phone in my schedule changes/requests.  I  DARE  someone to screw it up.  I'm also going to see if I can  reserve  a parking spot/locker (i'll  GIVE THEM THE MONEY THEY SO CRAVE  via Alesha)  I feel that they could at least extend me that curtousy seeing my parking spot was un-avalible to me half of last year becuase of someone parking in it. :P  Also, my locker didn't have 'hooks' in it, dammit.  
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We started bandcamp or Rookie camp today...what a waste of time...me and Jill are the only ones in our section...but we still have to go....but its ok i guess...its good to go and smell the roach infested hall ways again...what a smell i will miss....*lol* oh and this is a make up for the entry i deleted.... 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OKAY.  "Orientation is July 27-seniors at 9, juniors at 10 and so on! and  lockers went up to $15  and  parking perments are $20!  Plus you have to pay any unpaid fees before you get your new scheduales!! "  Info. stolen from  urlLink Rachel .    Sigh, I really hate comming back to Anniston.  I'm just comming for the orientation and then i'm comming back. [PCB,FL] *giggles* Bringing Alesha back with me.  As Rachel found out when she came down with her church, sometimes I get extremely lonely.  Especially during the day when Fat Granny is at work. -_-
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Micah, why did you remove your entry?  I just want everyone to know I didn't do it.  (will never remove an entry) [only edits]  You have to keep in mind that I don't have a life- (contradicting myself)  -and I usually notice minute changes; such as an entry being removed.
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am so happy that school is almost here! i miss you all, well most of you anyway! it was good going back in the bandroom today. it still smells like crap though! haha...
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Just wanted to show you guys the hottest girl on the planet.. Eye Candy!!
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm.. I have an idea.. everyone talk about something else..seems Micah and Jill won't be talking about anything though... they are too busy.. But anywho..  urlLink This article talks about people beating the login system on free registration sites   I actually use the Mozilla plugin for bugmenot.. It's a really good concept.. I hate being annoyed with registering stuff.. Just thought that you guys might be interested..
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dug this comment up.  urlLink He was talking to me .    Matt said...  Hmm.. To trash something like that. Thats sad that you have absolutely nothing to look forward to or live for.  This is the best entry I've seen ~~~~   Things I am looking forward to, Matt:  *in order* urlLink Fullsail , turning 21 and getting completly drunk for the first time, getting laid, taking over the planet, etc. etc.  Things I live for: My family, my friends, coffee, coffee-flavored ice cream,  reading  urlLink bill's  weblog, argueing with idiots,  like you , on the internet,  etc. etc.  So don't say I've got nothing to live for, I have  plenty  of things/people to live for.  So go outside and hump a goat or whatever it is you do in your spare time...
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The heaviest element known to science is Managerium.  This element has no protons or electrons, but has a nucleus made up of 1 neutron, 2 vice-neutrons, 5 junior vice-neutrons, 25 assistant vice-neutrons, and 125 junior assistant vice-neutrons all going round in circles.  Managerium has a half-life of three years, at which time it does not decay but institutes a series of reviews leading to reorganization.  Its molecules are held together by means of the exchange of tiny particles known as morons.
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyones offline.  Probably still mad from what happened last night.  Eh.  It was no big deal- If you don't make it one.  I just want someone to talk to; that's all...  (Jill would normally be online talking to me now)
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    old friends die hard.
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Look why dont yall just leave Micah alone? Yall know that I am undecided about all this stuff but still. Micah you came on to strong and yall dont down her religion... She said her piece and yall said yalls now can we go back to one happy blogger team!?!? Please! I respect what everyone said considering the circumstances but still It is just way to touchy of a subject to be goin on about... it can ruin friendships... believe me i know! But yeah.. thats all im gonna say about that subject! Oh and does anyone know what day orientation is? Id appretiate (sp?!) it if yall told me.... cuz i dont ever go by the school to see... love yall! -Me
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      look.. for all of you who don't think i am stupid: I am not gonna put what i believe on here bc&nbsp;i know that you don't want to hear it and if you did you would ask me.. you all know my email.. if not  urlLink KonaKia916@aol.com  there ya go.&nbsp;  and i agree with Tim that we not talk about our different religions on here . bc it only makes someone angry or it just pushes them away.&nbsp;so.. if anyone does want to ask me or tell me that you hate me for expressing my feelings than feel free. you all know that i am a devout Christian and I always will be. so don't email me and tell me that i am a bad person or that "I don't understand!" thank you for you time! *hugs*  
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Ok, this needs to be said. Everyone shut up about the religious bullshit and keep your opinions to yourself. I'm tired of coming on here and religious arguements is all I see. Everyone believes in different things.  Everyone  thinks they are right.&nbsp; No one knows for sure. No one, Micah. Christianity is no different from other religions in terms of belief. Do you not think other religions have holy sacred documents and shit too? I could sit here and argue about my truths, and what I believe in.. But I won't. There is no point. No one is going to change from one of our rants, so we might as well waste time on something else.&nbsp;So did you catch my drift? If not, here it is, condensed: Shut the hell up about your stupid religions, no one wants to hear it.     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, Cory.  Your gone.  *waives bye bye*  Thanks for all 3 words that you contributed.  But your not what we need right now.   -nod- 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok..so i might have come on a little harsh but i am not sry for what i said b/c its the truth..and no i dont want any glory what so ever GLORY BE TO GOD FOREVER AND EVER..he just wants to come and be with his ppl..my heart hurts b/c Jesus is sitting at the right hand side of his father saying please children WAKE UP...you need to wake up..can you not see him Jesus is sitting there crying for our souls he loves us and wants to be with us but we have to want him too..he will only come where he is wanted...i dont want any glory or credit..i am only this way b/c of God...he was branded me with his fire and that fire cant be keep in or it will snuff out...it has to come out so i can receive more..i know everything i am saying is problem hard to understand...and Rick...dont make some stupid comments on something i care so deep about..i wouldnt do that to you..I respect you...why cant you respect me...i am not asking you to do those things i was letting you know the truth....and if you cant respect that then that is your problem...Rick i love you with all i am.....I respect you, so please respect me...and i promise i wont throw that in your face anymore....i told you what you needed to know and someday you will rememeber what i have said....   
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i meant to mention this....ppl are soo decieved b/c they think that sayin a prayer will get them to Heaven...its not about the prayer...its about surrendering your whole life to God...i mean he gave it to you....so give it back to him....i am not saying you cant have fun..hey i am all about having some fun...just understand that God is looking for a generation to stand up for him...to love him...he just wants to come and dwell with his ppl..but we have shut him out...dont shut him out no more..its time to kick off the coffin top and get outta that grave.....God isnt boring he doesnt want us to sit in a pew and stand up and sing your fav. song then sit down then the pastor preach the same message....he wants us to be radical..if yall could have just been there...if you coulda seen how all 2000 teenagers were responding to God...i mean screaming, dancing, singing, crying, lifting their hands..it was awesome...worship is the only way to defeat the Devil..it makes him tremble....he knows what kinda worship God wants....remember the Devil use to be the worship leader in Heaven but he wanted to be greater than God he wanted worship so he was sent to hell and&nbsp;he pulled that worship outta Heaven and perverted it...as you see on MTV.  &nbsp; Dancing was made to worship God....how can you be at a football game or watching a concert by Britteny Spears...and scream your head off and dance and jump up and down...and then come to church and sit in a pew and just sing a little song and sit down....God wants you to worship him and love him with all your heart...please understand that....and if you dont or if you have any questions feel free to ask me...i want to help you....i love you with alllll my heart and soul........ 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok sooo if yall hate me for this it will all ok with me....i will still post on here but prob. not very often...Yall things have changed...i know you dont feel it but things have...i have...but my love for yall hasnt...its the only thing in me that hasnt changed...just please, as Micheal Rowan would say, WAKE UP!!! PLEASE!! I am begging you....dont let the world control you..i know you dont think it is but think of this....if your not serving God then who are you serving? Yourself? The World? The Devil?? Well if you said yes to any of these...then your serving the Devil its one or the other....God or Devil...there is no in between...but God loves you....he sent his ONLY son for you...do you understand what that means....Jesus beared all your sin just so you would have the chance of going to Heaven....he was beat...it says in the Bible that you could even tell he was human...then he was nailed on the cross and hung there for 3 hours and died...his lungs collapes..all for you......he loves you so much....and he just wants you to love him but the Devil, he hates you...he wants you to die and if he could right now he would come outta hell and drag you down there with him....he desipes you..he just wants you to suffer....but its your chose no one else can choose for you....and i am just telling you this so now your blood isnt on my hands....if yall want to know more about God and want to live for him then ask me about it....email me or im me...do something..my email is&nbsp;~~~~>  urlLink crimsongrl08@hotmail.com  but has i said if yall hate me then thats ok too...but i Love you with all i am........ 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey y'all, I missed you so much! but the thing is, I wont be online very much anymore so I wont be able to help Rick with admin. and it is a hard job for one person to keep up with everything, so I just wanted to give my notice, and ask if anyone can help Rick. Please contact him&nbsp;if you think you can help. &nbsp;Much love! byebye 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, by now you have noticed the new posting thingy.  Blogger staff had the following to say about it:  We've just released a new-fangled version of Blogger that'll let you fancify your posts using a feature-rich text editor. Go forth and align, colorify and embolden your words.  But remember, with great power comes great stylistic responsibility.    Notice the part I made bold. :P   Oh, also google bought the picasa company! yay! [The people that make hello]  Anyway, you can now  urlLink get a free copy of picasa .  I haven't tried it... But i'll likely do that later tonight.
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey everyone. It's about 10:45 in the morning and I'm bored out of my mind.&nbsp;How's everyone doing today? *waits for cheers* Great.. great..&nbsp; I see there's more options on the post page.. Can you put pictures on here now without having to use Hello?&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Anyway, Rick wants me to start posting the comics that I've made. He says they're funny but y'all will probably think otherwise..&nbsp; I'll post some later, I guess. I'm worried about the ACT.. I need to take it. But I have to go help my mother with the groceries.. Bye all.&nbsp;&nbsp; -=Tim=-  
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    So umm... Who is this really?  Choices are: ( Jill, Tim, Rick, )
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just needed to say [ yes , this late.] that I changed  urlLink rule #7 .  You don't have to have a picture anymore.  However, basic information about yourself is  still  required. Failure to comply with any rule(s) for longer than a business week [5 days] will result in termination of you membership.  
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever fallen asleep only to wake up a few hours later only to be still really tired and unable to fall asleep?? Just curious to see if I'm the only one.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you find yourself totally encompassed with boredom; and you feel like reading weblogs and such; Check out these  urlLink Alabama webloggers .    -sigh- Jill, hurry up and come home.    [the title was  purposely  misspelled to make fun of 'alabama'] 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok.  Matt, your gone.  *waives bye bye*  Plead your case with  urlLink Jill  if you want back on.  All in all, your just too damn stupid for  this  weblog.  I wish you nothing but luck for   urlLink your project .  Later.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so excited bc I am leaving for Panama City in about and hour! yay! I am gonna miss you all very much!! bye bye guys!!
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nanner head? What are we 2?  Okay maybe it is a little funny.. then again .. not really.  Hmm.. Anybody have any interesting features about themselves?  Does anybody have like 11 toes or anything?  I can freak you out by moving my eyes back and forth like really quick.. But then again Jill can do that too... I think Rick has 3 nipples .. But that's unconfirmed.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Just some advice for you all .  [some of you need it] 
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Umm...matt bain had to show me how to do this...so yeah. hello everyone.  Heh. Lalala i'm so bored and i really have no clue how to do this...so imma go, later.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aww..i am leaving for Fl. tomorrow...dont cry its ok i will be back soon *hehe* i will miss yall!! Dont have to much of a life without me!! HeHe...it will be ok! Well Jill is a naner head..ok i had a Matt moment *lol* ok bye love yall!!! 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I suppose I should post then so I don't anger Jill the Almighty. This blog thing has grown larger than I had.. hoped. I didn't check it for 2 days and there seemed to be about 10 new posts.. and 2 new members. Guess I have to try to get off the phone with Vickie more often to come check up on things.. Thank you for your time.    -=Tim=-
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright I don't want to edit you everytime I turn around! The rules state that if I don't like your writing, I will KILL you. And also we want everyone to post at least once a week. If you don't post for a really long time, you go byebye. OK thank you for your time.. 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, Matt you need some ritalin!    New rule:  Don't not abuse your privileges! You can easily be erased!
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG what day does school start back... orientation.... gaw.... i AM OFFICIALLY NOT ready! This really sucks... but hey I feel left out cuz I am the only Junior that is on this thing! Oh well This is okay! I am actually glad cuz that means Im accepted by the Seniors lol just kidding! oh and everyone of yall Have the Best year of your life!!!! Ill miss yall!... course I will be stuck by myself.. for another whole year! OH WELL! see yall
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow..i put my pic. on my profile all by myself...i am too smart for my own good *lol*
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am soooo bored...omg! I am babysitting....lalalala...i am excited about going to college b/c i get to meet lots of new ppl and i like making new friends...but i really will miss yall!! Especially you Rick...*wah* i dont want you to leave me...hopefully we will keep in touch on the internt or something.. i hope this blog stays until we are all old or something *lol*  
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My little bit of comment for the day: I'm not ready!! College starts up in September and I'm so not wanting to start classes. All of you who still have a year left should be greatful. Atleast you know people in your classes. I'll be alone in every one of mine. That's all for now. I just wanted to say I finally found my invite (stupid Spam Patrol) and am here to play!
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    *yawn*
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't wait for school to start!! This year is gunna be GREAT! It better be!! Lets all be friends now and play nice... I really have nothing to say here... but I just thought I'd give you something to enhance 30 seconds of your life, cause we all know you're bored.... 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For some reason the blogger invtie wouldnt let me on...it keep saying blogger invite error..but w/e! I am here now the party can begin! Hehe...omg 34 days till school!! ahhh...I dont wanna graduate i will miss you guys *tear* I will prob. see Jill the rest of my life..aha... *lol* i hope sooo...my bestest friend..dont leave me hehe..i am soo sentimental...I love you guys...hehe..ok i am being all gushy now...
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel compelled to tell you the purpose of this group weblog.  It is a place to share your thoughts, experiences, photos, comics, or poetry in a more mainstream or public environment.  This isn't anything official.  Just a little project that Jill and I started in our spare time over the summer.  I think it will be fun to read after we graduate; well, assuming everyone posts like they should.    The main thing to remember is to share what's on your mind with others.  And, as long as you do that-  you can't be wrong; Because, it's  your  oppinnion.  And, no one can take that from you.  
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi my name is Micah!! OK not really.. but I had to set this up for her so heehee... I thought I would be someone else for a little while.. k bye -Jill
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am the Bryan.. I can now post.. Isn't that an interesting concept?  Hmm.. I'm not in high school anymore.. Haha most of you guys got a year left.. muhahaha.. Well just letting you know.. I am now a contributor :-D
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just writing you to let you know that this site now complies with  urlLink current webstandards !    [That means no matter what size your viewing the site- it will always look the same. ( unless you make the window too small )] Try it!  Make the window different sizes, try fullscreen too!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      5 people have invitations in their inboxes.  Doesn't anyone check their email  hourly  daily like I do? eh.  stupid children.      crimsongrl08@hotmail.com    2004-07-07 pending     inspired05@aol.com    2004-07-07 pending     bryan0077@aol.com   2004-07-07 pending     harvard2be@aol.com   2004-07-07 pending    silverangel704@cableone.net   2004-07-05 pending     ** BTW: Okay, keep clicking refresh and notice all the neato quotes I put on the banner!  Comment your funny ones to add!  and in case you haven't noticed, "Rick + computer + free time = something added to the site."
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    while i'm playing with hello...
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Application for  SAKS HIGH SCHOOL JANITORIAL POSITION :  Do you Do drugs?             (x) (n)  Do you have AIDS?            (x) (n) Do you bathe regular basis?  (y) (x)  How many [crack] babies you support? (1)  (2)  (3)  (4)  (+5)  (x)  (+20)    Sex with the principal?      (x) (n) Gender:  ??? Age:  69 [thats my favorite #, i dont now my reel age]  Would you like your  lesbian lover  [oops]  roomate to work with you?    (x) (n) 
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, let me make sure I have everything correct.  Summer school (was/is being) held at Saks High School this summer.  Does that not mean that the school will look like crap for our final year? 
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *crys* It's so beautiful.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just wanted to say thanks for welcoming me in. I'm glad to be part of this which will usher in a new era of boredom and pointless paragraphs.  Really though, this feels important.. Like it's going to be our last piece of communication between eachother before we go off into our own lives. Let this live on. Thank you and goodnight.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welp. I added these two people... I'm gonna be sleeping in the a virtual dog house.  ( Jill may be mad that I added you guys - if she is... you might not be able to log back in )  *runs away into the night*
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! How have you all been? Good here! I am so happy that I am back and I just wanted to post on here and say hey!  ...OOO and I can almost promise you that I saw some preppy kids from our school in Flordia this past week. It was a scary sight. hahaha!! and I am happy that you took the invite Tim!
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey yall! I dunno what to type so i will just type any ol thing! So how is everyone? .... im okay lol! Well.... This is it for now..... sorry Rick! for I am an embarrassment to your invitation.... but I promise I shall Type more.... Promise!
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jill, I think we should just invite everyone for  one  week. (we give them a week of opportunity, to ask for an invite)   then  we can be picky.  I don't think it really should have anything to do with school anymore - although, school will likely be a constant topic.    My week (that I will invite anyone) Starts this  Wednesday, 7th  and it ends on  Wednesday, 14th .  So if you reading this (and it's between those days,  sigh  I will invite you)    ** Note: The only requirments (for me) is that you place a pic on your profile.  And, that you  urlLink follow these rules .    ***  urlLink Rick, shut up and let me ask for an invite... 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No, no, and no! Well just for now. We are trying to figure out what exactly this site is going to be used for, and when we figure it out we'll let you know. I don't want to add people and then find out that they have nothing to say, or that they make oodles of grammatical errors (I would have to kill you!). All that I know is that I want something with substance, we don't want to know every detail of your day! So if that’s all you have to say, don’t even think about asking… I want students (or former students) to be able to express themselves...is that so much to ask?!!
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been thinking.  To hell with it.   No , I won't be adding anyone until school starts.  (if I add anyone then - ...probably will)  If you ask me, your barking up the wrong tree.  Been getting a couple of requests for membership to the blog.  The thing is:  ( being brutally honest here )    "You might not write the kinda stuff we're looking for."   Jill and I haven't even begun to decide who we're letting in - I know one thing, "we sure as hell can't let everyone in." :(  Sorry.    If you don't like how slow we're progressing with this "project".   urlLink Start your own .  Don't ask me for help, tho. >0
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why am I the only one that posts? oh well....................boring.... 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    More original art from The Rick... It makes me smile too...*grin*
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Be afraid... be very afraid...
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      goodness what a day! I had to have my shedule changed like 3 times....it took all of 2nd period to get my shedule fixed....Now it reads like this: 1. Physics 2. Aleg. III 3. ACT (Rick you better stay in that class)...*lol* 4. Goverment 5. English 6. Band 7. Office.....so today went purdy good...i like my teachers, especially Mrs. Ford-she is crazy....I love it *lol* oh and i really like Mr. Gaddius...he was really nice....so Coach Toney left but Mrs. Ford has adopted his ways...she is making us keep a big notebook thing in memory of Coach Toney so she says..i think she just wants to torture us...since its our last year and everything *lol* but she is really nice...Also our band show is going purdy good too...but some ppl are being sooo disrespectful towards David (which he is our Band CAPTIAN) and other officers.....but anyways....~~> Aug. 20 you are all invited to a youth rally at my church..its going to be fun!!...the last one was awesome! Ask David he was there...he really enjoyed it and he is coming to our next one and bringing ppl from his youth....so come if you can! It will be fun....anyways...i guess i am out for tonight....*hugs* 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Omg...it just hit me...we have school tomorrow..wah dont make me go!!!! I really am dreading it b/c i had to get my schedule changed and i am scared to see what i have.....hold my hand...i have office assitiant but i really dont want to have it with a bunch of stuck up preps....oh well though i guess i will just get over it *smiles* Oh Rick i hope your finger/arm/boobie/ w/e else is feeling better....*lol* please dont die...hehe umm...did you get your car fixed yet?? I guess you will be walking...*lol* oh well...but i am gonna go now...bye!!! 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello. It's Katie (or Jessie Adams's little sister-for those of you who have no earthly idea as to who I am). As you can tell, I received an invite to the blog. *searches for something to say...* Well, I don't think my scheldule would interest any of you since none of the other contributors are in my grade. It has to be changed anyway. They put me in percussion band. *sighs* I just hope they can get it right in less than 2 new scheldules (unlike last year.)  -insert dull silence- ...  Wow, such an interesting post. Hopefully I'll have more to say later. 
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok so i thought i would post on here b/c once again i am babysitting and have nothing else to do....lalala boring....hrmm lets see....couple more days till schoool....*woot woot*...wait eww i dont like schoool...but i am kinda excited about being a senior...i cant believe it though...it feels just like yesterday i was in 8th grade...scared to death about starting school...and now i am a senior...time really does fly....well i hope to see all of yall Thursday...oh m schedule...  Parenting (being changed....to Choir...so my whole shedule might be differnt..joy) Office Assitant Physics Goverment English Band Aleg. 3  Locker # 913.... 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      physics english 12 peer tutor american government pe (needs to be changed, it's sports pe... don't need that) algebra 3 w/stats technology apps.  locker #893 (upstairs) 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What would you do if you woke up in the middle of the night and had to go to the bathroom.  When you get to the bathroom you smell a foul stench.  You open the door and a hairy fat stranger is sitting on your toilet taking a slam, reading your newspaper, and drinking your coffee.  What do you do?
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well since no one has posted in a while I figured I'd just waste some time.. School is almost here again.. I'm actually looking forward to it.  My schedule looks very easy.. I have a locker next to Kyle.. It's going to be weird without any upper-classmen here.. I'm gonna miss some of the seniors... But hey, they're livin the life now...   Anyway,  Rick, are you back from Florida yet? Wish you would have come to orientation.  Oh well. I'm done wasting time now.  Goodbye.   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    One of Tim's Office Supplies!
    
</post>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so... I've been blogging all day.  I'm tired.  And thanks to "someone" i'm ill too.  Not  really  ill so much as upset.   urlLink This joke  cheered me up though. :P
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        your bitch.    urlLink   What swear word are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Don't you just love hello kitty?
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Gtray  goodness.  Is it hot in here or is it you? *wink*
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My current desktop!  IIIEEEEE!
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is so gonna be my computer set-up... really...
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Sleep is a whore that services everyone at night." -Rick
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you reached this site from the URL  urlLink creamycoffee.2ya.com  then you will have a horizontal scrollbar.   If you came here from the URL  urlLink fullsailrick.blogspot.com , there is no horizontal scrollbar (which is what I want).  I've been trying to figure the problem out for some time now - any suggestions greatly appreciated. :P  **It would seem that Blogger has a problem when you use a URL redirection service.  Jill and Bryan are having similar problems.  ***Problem fixed.  ^_^  Jill, just  un-mask  your url @ shorturl.com.  That didn't take long.  
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And you don't seem to understand A shame you seemed an honest man And all the fears you hold so dear Will turn to whisper in your ear And you know what they say might hurt you And you know that it means so much And you don't even feel a thing  I am falling, I am fading I have lost it all  And you don't seem the lying kind A shame then I can read your mind And all the things that I read there Candle lit smile that we both share and you know I don't mean to hurt you But you know that it means so much And you don't even feel a thing  I am falling, I am fading, I am drowning Help me to breathe I am hurting, I have lost it all I am losing Help me to breathe   urlLink Download here  ( right-click link, save target as )
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's a tip for you:  Don't put dawn dish detergent in a dishwasher!!  I did that and the whole kitchen floor was flooded with suds.  * Priceless. *  When I asked Fat Granny for towels for no apparent reason - I think she knew exactly what I had done before I told her.  :3  Sigh, I love my Fat Granny.   She didn't get mad - she just laughed.  I was white as a ghost.  ( I didn't know any better because we don't have a dishwasher at home - We do everything by hand )  I'm sure  urlLink Jill  is preparing to grieve the loss of Trigun.  The last episode airs tonight, and It  hopefully  will bring her closure to a beautiful timeless anime.  **Get your Kleenex ready Jill. Here's to you,  Vash the stampede     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to the Summer 2004 edition of getting to know our friends. What you are supposed to do is copy (not forward) this entire E-mail and paste it onto a new e-mail that you'll send. Change all of the answers so they apply to you, and then send this to a whole bunch of people, including the person who sent it to you. The theory is that you will learn a lot of little things about your friends of which you did not already know!   1. What time did you get up?    I have no freakin' clue - Is that good?   2. If you could eat lunch with one person, who would it be?  GEE!  Really!?! I can pick anyone in the whole world???  Table for one, please.  3. Gold or silver?  Silver.  4. What was the last film you saw at the cinema?  The cinema? Who the hell are you? What are you like 80 or something its called "the movies".  Unless, your retarded... Which you probably are.  Van Helsing.   5. What is your favorite TV show?   Cowboy Bebop.  6. What do you have for breakfast?  ...I'm still asleep most of the time, but, cereal.  7. Who would you hate to be stuck in a room with?  You. Because you have so much freakin' free time to make stupid pointless quizzes...  8. Who inspires you?  *shrug* Janet Reno?  Spike Spegial.  9. What is your middle name?  Look. I don't know you. ...   10. Beach, city or country?  City.  11. Favorite ice cream?  Really, anything that Ben and Jerry's makes  12. Butter, plain, or salted popcorn?  ... If you don't eat salt on your popcorn your elderly.  Or so freakin overweight that it would probably kill you to eat popcorn.  Popcorn is popcorn to me.  Just hand it over without too much thought, k?  13. Favorite color?   Blue.  14. What kind of car do you drive?  Sigh, ...   15. Favorite sandwich?  Quiznos or Subway only.   17. Favorite flower?   Cactus.  ... They bloom!  18. If you could go anywhere in the world on a vacation, where would it be?   Anniston, Alabama.  *dies laughing*  Tokyo, Japan.   19. What color is your bathroom?  What kind of retard question is that- what? Are you mental?   20. Favorite brand of clothing?   American Eagle or Aeropostal or Abercombie.   21. Where would you retire?   Well, seeing how I'm only 17 and all... Unless I win the lottery... Three times... I don't plan on retiring anytime soon.   22. Favorite day of the week?  Saturday.  23. What did you do for your last birthday? I bought a gun.  So stay away from me "elderly-mental-quizmaker"!  24. Where were you born?   Jacksonville, Al.   25. Favorite sport to watch?  Watch, being the key word... Football.  *shrug*   26. Who do you least expect to send this back to you?  No one. Because its a stupid f*cking quiz.  27. Person you expect to send it back first?  None's gonna send it back!?!? Gah!  28. What fabric detergent do you use?  What the hell kinda freak are you!?!  29. Coke or Pepsi?  Ice water.  Sweet tea.  30. Are you a morning person or a night owl?   I'm a night owl striving to be a morning person.  31. Do you have any pets?  Micah?  **The person that made this left out a number 16.  I guess they didn't have enough fingers and toes? ***Thanks for the quiz,  urlLink Jeanette . ****I wasn't making fun of you Jeanette, but all these stupid quizzes.  Please, don't be afraid to send me anything.  lol  *****That was my first time taking one - and I don't plan on taking anymore, sorry.
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, here's the low-down on Bloggers sucky commenting.  I want you guys to help me decide on whether or not to continue using it.  Here are the the two choices:   Use HaloScan:  Pros: Ease of use.  Link back to commenters site/email.   Con: Old comments are deleted and lost forever after only 2 months.  Which sucks...alot. I would have to boot-leg my blogger account to get it to work.  Not that I have a problem with that - I obviously covered up the banner.  :P  But it's a lot of work nonetheless.  Or, Stay with the Blogger:  Pros: Comments stay with my weblog F-O-R-E-V-E-R.  (or, until the Dawn of the Dead)   Cons: It makes you be post anonymously, which is retarded.  There is  no  link to the commenters site.  And, everyone hates it.    So, what do think?  I need your help on this.  Thanks. 
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         ha!
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fat Granny left me this morning.  I woke up to an empty house.  I read in the sun in her absence.  She finally came home around 12 and we went an cleaned a couple of homes.  It rained on us a little.  :P    So, why do you care?  Well... I guess you don't.  Ha!  I really hate the way that blogger does the comments... I might break down and just use the old haloscan- but that sorta defeats the purpose of these fine people hosting my junk. :P
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, ... Due to problems with my time - updating the old fashioned way was  way  too inconvenient.   So, i'm gonna give  urlLink Blogger  a try.  Wanna fight about it?  But the Real reason I switched over (and you can verify this with Jill)  is because I ran out of room on my  urlLink Freewebs.com  server.  - go figure.
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been really busy lately offline. There isn't really anything for me to do. I've found myself stuck in a place that keeps repeating itself day after day. Don't get me wrong though, i'm perfectly happy sitting in the house. My Grandmother tried to get me to go out with her-I think she thinks I get bored here. I don't though. I'm just tired..
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hrmm... could this be something that will last?
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Guess what I did today?  Woke up at 8am and went to the beach with Ginger and Charolette.  Fun stuff.  After walking a couple of hours... I came home went to doctor with Doc.  Fat Granny, Ginger, and I went shopping.  ... I'm tired.  So, tired.  I've had a busy day... and sleeping  is  one of my hobbies... so...   urlLink     Boring pic I took     urlLink     Aftermath of a day in the sun... Rick, slightly toasty. 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fat Granny Got off early today!  yay!  She got off at 11am, which gave her plenty of time to clear her mind.  ( people she is working with are driving her crazy )  Went back to the pool today.  XD  Stayed out in the sun for  way  too long.  I was lightly toasted as I was reading my Resident evil book.  Charolette and Doc left for bingo early in the afternoon.  As a matter of fact, they have just returned.(o.o)    But that's okay.  Fat Granny, Ginger, and I went out too.  ( after laughing way too much taking "funny" pictures with my camera.  -none of which will ever be seen by another soul. ) We went to Taco  Hell  Bell.  Everyone that worked there was younger than me, seriously.  ( i'm 17 )  They were the slowest Taco Bell I have ever seen.  It was increadible how long it took them to prepare a mear two soft-taco plus hard-taco for this one lady.  Ginger  hates  Taco Bell.  She took "special" medicine before we went.  I just witnessed her throwing up the contents of her stomach in the hall bathroom, so  I don't think the medicine worked .  ( the only reason we went is because of "King Rick" and his bastardly constant ebil demanding-ness. )     urlLink     Something that Erika once said came to mind, " Crack heals. "    urlLink      Ginger: "Ask them if the have mayo for my taco."   Fat Granny: "Do you have lemon for my tea?"         urlLink     The storm that was approching us was faster than the production rate at that Taco Bell.     urlLink     Is that a storm, or is that a  storm ?!   Then we headed for Bealls... And this huge storm cloud spit lighting bolts out so near to us we could feel the ground shake.  We ran for the car screaming our heads off...  Of course, after we did our shopping, dammit. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Joseph's parents are leaving in the morning.  I will miss my shadow.  I will miss the sreaming, sounding something like, " SHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAKSHAK!! "  Eh.  OH!  I actually went out to the pool yesterday.  I took pictures... but umm...  your  never going to see them.  *dies laughing*     urlLink     I actually fell for his, "look at that"-trick.  I still haven't found my wallet.    urlLink     Yes, that  is  me in the laundry room. I was left in there trapped for hours after he closed the door.   Oh well, Ginger and Charolette will still be here to keep me company until next Monday.  So its not like i'm going to be lonely.  Not to mention  urlLink the game  and that  urlLink Feng Shui book  that Fat Granny bought me today.  Those will keep me busy for a long time...
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I mentioned before Ginger and Charolette are down here visiting.  The whole purpose of ginger coming was meeting up with her neice and nephew... and their two year old son, Joseph.  Gingers watching Joseph.  The two parents- who seemed really nice at a glance. ( I didn't actually get to exchange words with them because I had just gotten out of the shower )  Anyway, I'll be fine as long as the toddler doesn't touch my computer, camera, books.  Everything will be fine.  Breath in with nose, out with mouth.    Watching children is a very difficult thing to do.  Your entirely responsible for their welfare while guardians are away.  Its hard for me.  I felt really weird watching the kid for only a matter of seconds.  He's not nearly as bad as I first thought he would be.  I took a hint from  urlLink Micah  and sat him in front of the tv.  Switched on Nickolodeon and practically walked away.  That station has really changed.  I recignized one of the voices on one of the Nick commercials as an annoncer from MTV.  Go figure.   
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink *thoughly confused*  
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      UGH.  These people  weren't even at their condo an hour .  Look at the mess they had already made.  (we just had to clean around them... and their  stuff .)   urlLink       urlLink       urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *screams*  These people were filthy!  Gross.  Absolutely gross.  I just got back from cleaning on of the condos here.  #410.  Ick.  They had a toddler with them...He must of been some kind of monkey with grease all over him.  Picture this: There is a child's  foot print  on the tv screen; and the tv is like 5 feet off the ground.  I still don't understand that one.  Everything glass there had grease all over it.  They spilled spaghetti all over the dining room mats.  [didn't bother to clean it up, either]  OH!  And they didn't wash a single dish either.  Look, I know their on vacation and everything... But how can people live like that??  Wadeling around in their own filth for days.  Not washing dishes and smelling rotting food in the sink.  OH!  And there was hair  everywhere  in the bathroom.  Poor bald Canadians.  *sob*  I'm severely sleep deprived right now.  I don't really like sleeping during the day though... So, I'll try and hold off collapsing on the couch for as long as I can.    Ginger and Charlotte are comming down tonight at 10pm. (>_  that I managed to avoid orientation entirely.  yay!  So that means, I'll probably stay here until the 10th of August.  School starts on the 12th.  Anyway, I'm almost finished with "The day after tomorrow" so, I'm gonna go finish it.  
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      K, so Fat Granny and I just got back from this really good cajun-style restaraunt.  mmmmmm, cajuuuuuuuuuuuun *Homer Simpson drooling noises*  We brought the heavy breathing penguin (doc) back a hamburger and some fries.  Well, while Fat Granny was in the tub... he finished of a half a gallon of ice cream.  [that's why he's retarded]  Oh well... old people like him suck anyway...    Note to self: Need consort. 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *insulted*  I imed Paul with info about the orientation.  ...forgot to include the actual date. (i just said tuesday)  Anyway, he said, "need a date, fool" [or something close to that]  I gave him the date and told him not to talk to me like that- that he wasn't talking to Jeffrey.  His response you ask?  "die!"    -_- I swear, some of my friends treat me like shit sometimes. One day, it'll just boil over and i'm going to explode on someone.  Remember that the next time you say something like that to me, k?
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    way to much free time.
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another one dedicated to Jill:  I see right through to you See right through to you See right through to you  I see right through to you It's not like I don't feel your mood What you have for me is different Then the rest that moves I'll be positive I know that I could be that to Cuz you have it all, have it all  I see right through to you See your every move See right through to you See your every move  I know you now I reach your mind You've shown some how What I could find On the inside There you will see We're all alike you and me  I see right through to you See your every move See right through to you See your every move   urlLink Download here  ( right-click, save target as )
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Birthday.  I hate j00 though.  We sent your (and Amber's) birthday presents off this afternoon.  I was looking at things I might want and- ... some one better buy me  urlLink this...   ... and bryan, I already told you-  urlLink There is  NO  THE BRYAN .  The Rick will seriously cut your reproductive organs out if he see's that... and j00 can't stop him- he does it while your sleeping... o.O
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why do  urlLink people mess  with me when i'm angry? 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well... I guess there are such things as  urlLink parellel universes , where Micah... Is as funny as I am...
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The deer on the back patio.  Just before we feed them.
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love waking up to the sounds of pounding rain.  I did that this morning.  Hal and Kerry just came over and ate lunch with us.  They wanted to know if we wanted to ride to Destin, FL and go outlet shopping.  But, we have that unit to clean.  We also have a shelving unit that Fat Granny picked up at wal-mart that we are going to put together. She's also taking Monday off. yay!
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm tired, and extremely ill from cleaning all day today.  I had been waiting all day to come home and see if Jill wrote me back- she did.  I'm just way depressed because I lost a really good online buddy all because she was brainwashed over her vacation. But, It's what Jill wants to do... and I know more than anyone that  Jill's a stampede ; and when her minds made up about something- dammit, she's right.   Note to self: Don't argue with Jill, she will kill me.   And then, I read  urlLink Micah's preachings  on j00r saksy.  And that didn't help my anger problems much.  
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Traffic on the bridge sucks.
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Typical traffic jam in PCB, Florida.  Check out the tag in front of us.  [anniston tag]
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The back patio just before a huge rain.
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nevermind. On the entry editor, I can make it really close to the way that it used to be by clicking the 'edit HTML' box next to compose. Phew. Blogger scared me there for a second.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eh.&nbsp; I'm so tired.&nbsp; I don't have a legitimate reason to feel this way.&nbsp; All my body wants to do is sleep.&nbsp; I haven't  done  anything all day today.&nbsp;&nbsp;And then,&nbsp;I&nbsp;noticed the changes on&nbsp;blogger...  &nbsp;  Gah.&nbsp; I don't really like the changes  urlLink blogger  made to the entry posting section.&nbsp; Now,&nbsp;when you try and put a link on your site,&nbsp;all you have to do it 'type' the link in the&nbsp;editor! WTF! I don't like my links that way blogger!&nbsp; Switch it back!!&nbsp; Sigh, now any idiot that knows the basic functions of a word processor can use blogger.&nbsp; Oh!&nbsp; And for some reason my blogger ranking in the blogger&nbsp;listings in both the  urlLink Anniston  category and the  urlLink Alabama  category has been kicked way down in the listing.&nbsp; *shrug* I don't have a clue.  
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Gah.  Rachel.  I'm gonna miss you!  I'll see you when school starts! *hugs*  It was uber-fun hanging with you guys!
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Umm.  That's you Jill.  *giggles* That ride was so funny.  Rachel and I laughed the whole way through...
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Another one of Rachel and I on the roller coaster.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel and I on the front row of the Mirical Strip roller coaster. 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    They were happy.  I was braceing for impact.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bobby: "guys! stick your hands out like me!" :: Rachel: "NOOO! *followed by screams of terror*" :: Rick: *swears he heard a cable snap*
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    [L to R] Bobby, Rachel, and I about to "take off"
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Rachel and I waiting in line..
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Muah ha ha!  That was the best ride ever! [in the park]
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Blurry pic of the Ferris Wheel that I liked.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The big guy in blue on stage is puking.  AKA "Chuggles"
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The concert under the tent.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rachel called me this morning at 11:30!  I still can't figure out exactly how she was able to call here.  It was just a short margin of time that we were offline. She's an increadibly lucky girl!  I got Fat Granny [if she felt like it; she did- actually she asked me if I wanted to go before I got a chance to tell her Rachel had called]  to take me to Rachel's hotel.  So anyway...  *giggles*  Just got back from hanging out with Rachel and Colby and her youth directors and friends.  It was so nice seeing a friendly face in a crowd!  Finally, someone that knows my name; and I know theirs!  Gah!  That was fun!  First we went to a mini concert talent contest in a huge white tent aross the street from her hotel.  I saw one guy puke three times.  And another guy puke, too!  [They were trying to drink a gallon of water in less that 60 seconds] Then, we went to the Mirical Strip Amusment Park. (which is closing after this year) I rode everything with Rachel. (Colby has motion sick-ness, fear of heights) I felt bad because I wanted him to ride with her- (because they are going out)  But he didn't seem to care. ^_^   It was sooo soo good seeing Rachel and hanging out with them!  It makes me realize just how much I miss everyone.  It was also really really hard to say "good-bye" to her.  Ugh.  I wish I didn't have to clean tommorow... 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got my feelings hurt really bad tonight.  Sometimes down here I get really homesick and just want to "call" home to hear how things are going. Well, typical Mom... To busy to talk to her only son.  She had just gotten home from a stressful day of work; (it was 8pm when I called)  she had all sorts of paperwork or something or other to look over.  She was telling me she was stung by a bee, that she hadn't had a shower yet, that she was expecting  Misty over real soon.    It's hard to talk to Mom.  She's always distracted; worried; busy- with something.  Then, I heard a knock at the door.  I knew it was Misty.  They had already started talking while she was still on the phone with me.  It's like she's annoyed by me.  Like I'm some kind of outstanding burden on her shoulders.  I told her I needed to go; I said it quickly and without emotion.  She started to say, "Okay, bye bye I lov-..."  But I hung up on her.  
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Treasure ship.  MMM. The she-crab soup is the best!  [picture taken through passenger-side window]  
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Doc.  [also a small glipse of my 'awfice']
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Early this morning.  Near the house.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Intersection near the complex. [picture taken through front windsheild]  
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Entry way to the pool. [picture taken through passenger-side window]  
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Patches Pub.  My Dad's favorite.  [picture taken through passenger-side window]
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I stayed up really late last night for no real reason.   Other than to download a song .  I didn't wake up until 12.  I woke up and the first though that entered my mind was: " gotta take some pictures "  I walked around and took a few.  Plus there were some that Fat Granny had took before she went to work.  I feel confident in the fact that when I do leave florida.  I will have every detail with me.    Doc is generally getting my nerves.  It's nothing I suppose he can help... I just really don't like him anymore.  Blame me?  I mean, when you start cussing at a solitare game on pogo... your pretty f*cked up in the head.  It's a game, dude.  Chill.  Go have a cigarette and some cake.    Or, maybe i'm mad at him because he sits on the damn internet all the time- (i don't really want the phone lines tied up because Rachel is down and i'd love to see her) -and no one can call.   get a life ... sick bastard.  
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Looking away from the back patio. (beach directly behind me)
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The plant.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    late night snack.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A memory of supper.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Part of "the walk"
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The pier. 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Did I mention some of these make for good wallpapers?
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is my favorite spot outside of Fat Granny's.  It is a bench that I frequent.  I love the view of the bay.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The pool is strangly empty.  Maybe because of the lightning...
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The very much loved, couch/bed.  who's comfortable-ness is only surpassed by it's beauty.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the back patio.  o.O
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ... okay, so this is me being a retard... screwing around with the self-timer on the camera ^_^
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The next few posts will be some pictures!  WEEE!    **Please note: I suck at taking pictures of myself... and, i'm ugly.  So, spare me the comments about how ugly the Rick is.  *bows*  ...and now... the pictures!
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay!  I finally got my hands on a good digital camera!  Its a Samsung Digimax 301 (3.2 megapixel) Fat Granny bought me one because she said I had been working hard.  Thanks Fat Granny!!  So... umm... I've been messing around with it all afternoon- I love it!  We went shopping today... After I laid down and watched a little dab of tv.  Went shopping for my cousin's birthday, and for Alesha's upcoming birthday.  I got a lot of great deals on some AE stuff (back to school sale or something..)   Anyway... I have some pictures.  But I'm not posting any unless I have some really good ones that I wana share.  (because of invasion of privacy and all that jazz)  So, i'm gonna go lay down- i'm so tired from walking- and my feet hurt.  Thanks again Fat Granny!  *hugs* 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    You gotta love gmail.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Cleaned all day.   14 condos were cleaned .  I came strait home (after eating at captain Jacks) went to my couch/bed; which was around 6 o'clock, and died.  I just woke up.  Hence, the late entry time.    The only thing I hated about sleeping like that- Jill, Rachel and Micah are all comming down here to Florida and I didn't exactly get to say goodbye, which sucks.  Oh well, Goodbye guys! [asuming you are reading this before you leave- as I will likely be away all day tommorow]   Fat Granny and I are going shopping tommorow. >_ *
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We had a typical morning.  Went to bank.  Went and ate lunch.  Paid the rent.  Asked Doc if he wanted to go play bingo, he said,"no." So we went and got Fat Granny's paycheck.  At first glance, it looked like she had more money than she was supposed to.  We got to looking and that wasn't the case.  But it still had our minds 'active', nonetheless.  So, we go back to the bank- deposited her check and went home where something else dramatic happened...  It all started when She was watching Montel.  After the commercials came on, she came over to me and said, "a man that lies and cheats will just keep lying and cheating."  Keep in mind that she was talking to me. Well, sitting there on her computer Doc said, "sick bitch." Fat Granny didn't hear him; but I did.  Then Fat Granny said what she said again.  He said what he said again, mumbling.  She said, "What are you saying?"  And he said very clearly, "Your a sick bitch."  !?!?!?!?  That was the closest I have ever come to cussing someone out in my life.  I took another walk around the complex with my cd player right after it happened.  I needed to 'chill'.  She doesn't deserve that.  She practically does everything for him, really.  Makes his coffee.  Buyes his cloths/food, etc.  Cooks every night.  Fixes plate.  Always thinking about him when we are out eating...  [he won't ever go with us]  She's been nothing but nice to him for years!  They had a very 'light' discussion.  She asked him to move out.  When she said that... He started apologizing like crazy.  Nuh-uh, jerk.  Un-acceptable.  So, he's leaving. And taking her computer with him; She gave it to him.  She's being all nice to him while he gets his things out... If it were me... But he did apologize to me too.  I didn't say anything, just kept walking through the front door.  How would you feel about someone if they called your favorite grandmother a "sick bitch" ?   
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This makes me giggle. 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know how  urlLink Jill  feels, but I felt like I stayed up all night cleaning up after a party.  We were very busy last night.  We almost doubled our list of contributors for  urlLink j00r saksy .  I think that's quite an accomplishment.  I know one thing, I couldn't have done it with out you, Jill.    Sigh, So- we both just turned of AIM.  She needs to pack.  I need to umm... Sleep.  Rachel, Jill was the one that put your picture up for you.  I'm writing that here because, like many things in my life- If I don't write it down; it will be forgotten by tomorrow.  And she deserves a "Thank you or two"  The only two people that shocked me (not really)  with their overall attitude of the site was Cory and Matt.  Cory was very non-chalante with his post.  Busy with something else, perhaps.  If I were him- I wouldn't let  urlLink that  happen again.  And Matt, well... Was lacking self-control.  If I want to talk to  seven year olds , I will download AOL and enter a "pre-teen chat". I wonder where/how he learned HTML?  **So, on a personal note: My mood hasn't gotten any better.  I'm still "ill" and angry.  Which just happens to be a perfect time to call Dad and direct my anger at something.  ...Who needs therapy when you have free nights and weekends?  Before anyone emails me telling me it's probably a chemical imbalance- let me just beat you to it.  "It's a chemical imbalance, and it probably is related to the fact that I don't really sleep all that well."  There.  That's my official statement.  Heh.  
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trying to recruit people with  urlLink J00r saksy  is so frustrating!!!  I wanna kill half the people on the 'pending list'.  (just because they won't check their emails, even though i've only given them... 12 hours)  I'm just too impatient for this...  Dear world,   I hate you all.  Love, Rick
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been in a bad mood all day.  No reason.  Just... In a bad mood.  God, I love it.  My Big O soundtrack goes along with my mood perfectly.  (I get so much done when i'm pissed off at something/someone. Check out all I did with  urlLink J00r $aksy . 
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Okay, so i know the movies have next to nothing in common with the novels... But hey!  Who cares when you have a  urlLink kick-ass website ?
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You suck if you don't  urlLink download this cd .     [Nevermind, none of the links work. ugh.]   ** Also:  urlLink Something i'm doing for a friend .  (i'm a sucker for requests, :P )
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't care what you say.  The best show on sci-fi channel is Beyond Belief: Fact or Fiction.  They play out stories and you have to guess whether they are fact or fiction.  I'm never wrong!    It's raining! Yay!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    a wallpaper i made from watching "Kenya".
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink *giggles*   **  UPDATE:   urlLink Kenya live 
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Picture this, I'm lying on the couch with a white sheet over my head.  I can see brilliant light dance for me through straining eyes.  Its a light attacted to a kitchen ceiling fan.  It didn't exactly wake me up, However, the dryness in my mouth did.   I went into the kitchen and poured a small glass of green tea, and brought it back to my couch/bed to drink.  As I was lying there drinking the tea I was suddenly reminded of an old memory from long ago.  What was good times.    It was in the fourth grade and Blake Brodour had just told a joke about how green tea was made.  I remember thinking that the joke was the funniest thing I had ever heard.  He probably doesn't even recall telling the joke - or even talking to me a lot in the fourth grade for that matter.  But, Its funny how something so small- a laugh, a person, a thought; will stick with you for years and only be remembered when it seems like you really need a good laugh.  I am going to try and recall the joke in its entirety, but, I'm sorry to say it won't be nearly as funny as when it was originally told to me way back when:  " A guy who was a truck driver was hungry so he pulled into a diner for a hamburger late at night.  He was surprised to see many cars there however, no people.  He goes in and orders the hamburger and sees something on the menu that he's never seen before, "green tea".  He orders it and he eats the hamburger and sips the green tea and its the best drink he has ever had!  He askes the waiter, "you have to tell me how this green tea is made!"  The waiter said grimly, "you don't want to know."  The guy was heartbroken.  He paid the guy and quickly left the diner.  He didn't feel "right" sitting there.  He saw a light near the back of the diner.  He quickly realized that it was a cracked door.  He could maybe see the ingredients for himself!  He edged to the door and looked inside.  Sure enough they were making the "green tea."  He nearly fainted.  The people that had been posing as waiters and cooks actually were green... aliens.   And they had human remains- and they were scraping the "green" toejam off of their toes and making the "green tea" the the trucker had just drank. "  I've been racking my brain as to why that joke - or the memory of him telling me that joke stands out as a memorable moment in my life.  And, I think it was the fact that the green tea joke was the first time I had been formally introduced with a twist in a plot.  But Rick, you were in fourth grade!  I know, I've always been a little naive But, I was really naive back then.  I've grown out of it a little, I think.    So, this entry is dedicated to old friends and good times.  Whether the good times make sense to you today - or not.  And, whether or not the old friends even consider you friends anymore.  Maybe someone out there has a memory of something I did or said that comes to mind every once in a while.  God, I'm going to miss everyone.    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My eyes hurt.  That's all I have to say.  :P  But how can you not want to read/tan on a day like this?  The perfection of the sky compliments my book on global destruction perfectly.  The back of the book:  It's a fiercely hot summer, so hot that the north poles heat record is broken by fifty degrees.  Massive ice melt stuns the world as open ocean appears at the pole for the first time in living memory.  Deep under the Atlantic Ocean, currents crucial to life react, dropping south - and suddenly, storms of unprecedented ferocity start exploding over the artic as cold air returns, slamming into the heat with cataclysmic results.  The storms grow until they form a bizarre and gigantic blizzard unlike anything ever seen before.  A stunned humanity realizes that a second ice age is about to engulf the earth.  Forward reading...  climatologists Jack Hall tried to warn people of the approaching peril- but it may already be too late for any hope of survival.  Now he must not only find a way to reverse the rampant ecological destruction that is transforming the world into a frigid wasteland, but also rescue his rebellious son, who is one of the millions trapped in the icy depths of a frozen New York City.  So, anyway... The sun isn't really bothering me.  The book is making me feel "cold" all the time.  eh.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from a beautiful scenic walk around the complex.  I left with my bathing suit on and my cd player with a newly burn cd! XD (I looped "Gravity" the whole time I was walking - its a really good walking song..)  Twisting from condo to condo all the way to the small pool.  Then went and sat by my favorite bench here.  (it overlooks the treasure island bay)  Sat there for a while.  The walked through the boat yard.  Weaved along the outer fence of the complex.  Walked to the main entrance - then along the west side.  Then, I just walked the outer edge until I got back home.  Gah.  I'm tired. It's really too bad I didn't have a camera.  I saw so many boats and groups of ducks... Plus, you could even see me with a bathing suit on! XD XD XD
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rikkuson: you haven't been online much!?!? Gamewiz 82487: No..  Gamewiz 82487: Why?  Rikkuson: please, tell me the secret to escaping virtual purgatory... Gamewiz 82487: *whispers*  Girlfriend  Rikkuson: shit.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "There is always something stronger than ourselves, no matter how brightly burns the flame of confidence and power. There is always something stronger, something waiting to damn us for our weakness. Around every corner of the forest another monster lurks in wait for us; sometimes we can laugh at its feebleness. It appears horrible, but its substance is tissue-thin. It can be torn. The worst monsters we encounter have the faces of angels and the grace of devils flirting among the cold flames of hell. They can destroy us, merely because they scorch our souls unintentionally. Face such a creature and reason trickles out like blood from a cut vein. Is it decided before we are born who we must love?"  - Storm Constantine, Wraeththu (Book 2) The Bewitchments of Love and Hate 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My (brb) sometimes means i'll brb in  a few hours .  lol
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fat Granny has went to work.  (she's been sick, remember?)   Mom and Barry are here. (leaving at five)  (They are leaving  now )   And, Dad and Alesha decided not to come down.  >0  (This makes me mad)    I thought i'd do something a little diffrent and actually type an entry for today.  As you can see with the last few postes I have went picture/song crazy.  :P  Don't blame me, blame hello.  I just haven't felt like typing.  eh.   Nothing else is going on... gonna say goodbye to Mom and Barry...
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    well, it made  me  laugh.
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          R     Revolutionary       I     Intense       K     Keen       K     Kind       U     Unnatural       S     Shy       O     Overwhelming       N     Nerdy       Name / Username:       urlLink Name Acronym Generator  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Happy 4th of July everyone.  I'm going outside to watch fireworks.  *coughhailhitlercough*
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This looks like Micah .  Doesn't it?
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ah.  That's better.
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been a long road to follow Been there and gone tomorrow Without saying goodbye to yesterday Are the memories I hold, still valid? Or have the tears deluded them?  Maybe this time tomorrow The rain will cease to follow And the mist will fade into one more today Something somewhere out there keeps calling  Am I going home? Will I hear someone singing solace to the silent moon? Zero gravity what's it like? Am I alone? Is somebody there beyond these heavy aching feet? Still the road keeps on telling me to go on  Something is pulling me... I feel the gravity of it all   urlLink Download here  ( right-click, save target as )
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my current desktop background
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Feeling blue I'm thinking of you Oh, I was a fool to let you walk away.. (walk away) Tears in my eyes today make my world  The color of blue  Red with a twist Orange of fire Green of tourmaline Yellow mellow hello, hello Paint me a smile I'm covered and colored with one, only one...  'Cause baby I'm alone, alone without you What am I supposed to do? I'm alone, alone without you I'm the color blue!  Feeling blue I'm thinking of you Oh, I was a fool to let you walk away  Tears in my eyes today make my world the color of blue   urlLink Download here  ( right-click, save target as )   urlLink Download the Remix  ( right-click, save target as )
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mom's comming ( from anniston ) down to 'visit' - She's leaving tonight.  I think she might be bringing my cousin and my step-dad.  I don't know if they'll come though (she might leave 'em) :P    Dad's comming ( from chicago ) with alesha down here tonight too.  So, we should have a full house down here for a while.  I might not be on the internet too much either. ;p    and yes, Rachel,  urlLink I posted an entry for you .  Where the hell is Micah??
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I'm serious!  Download it.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey.  Fixed my computer.  Just needed a good 'ol system restore.  Umm... one quick thing.  You need  urlLink iTunes .  Your not cool if you don't have it.  As a matter of fact, I just don't think we can be friends if you don't download it.  :/    (be sure to download the  windows  version)   urlLink *giggles* 
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so... Evidently when I "cleaned" my computer I f*cked a lot of stuff up - now, I'm getting pop-ups out the ying yang... (I did system restore)  But, everything is still screwed up.    So, i'm getting pop-ups left and right... And just for fun (it seems)  Internet Explorer keeps closing on me every time a new pop-up comes up (which is frequent) Sooooo... I'm in a 'pissy-ish' mood.    Mom, Barry, Clint (my cousin), Alesha, and Dad (all in one car - which is weird)  are comming down here for the fourth so maybe i'll have Dad look at my computer - I think it's a lost cause though... eh. 
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay.  :P  My computer is super-optimized.  I cleaned out my registry this morning.  Killed some junk files.  Yada Yada - but my computer is running faster than the day I got it.  :P  hurray!  
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First day of school was today!!  It was so much fun (other than the schedule problems that I have)  Mark my words, they'll take me out of my favorite class, no doubt.  I came home and went strait to bed.  I was exausted.    Ms. Norton has me tutoring (which I think is absurd because of my stupidity and totaly lack of qualification) But hey!?! I'm honored.  They are bending the rules so that I can remain in Dual english... *cough*    I am just so happy that I got to see everyone- It is totally worth living in this place to have friends like that.   Oh! My car died on me today in the middle of the road.  The people behind me were to stupid to drive around... even with my hazard lights on.  **idiots** I finally got it started after like a minute of total embarassment.  ... Hrmm, I'm wide awake.  It's  2am... I guess I'll just stay awake until it's time for school.  (I have already had my 7 hours of sleep, right when I got home)
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The swelling and numbness of the hornet sting went down today.  ... I got my car back.  Oh, god... how I hate my life.  So anyway, ... my car has been in the shop all this time for no reason.  Nothing was fixed.  Oh, my driver's side door won't lock now... whipee!  Everything that was wrong with it before is still wrong with it.  ... Oh, It overheated on the way to the mall... Then, It overheated on the way back.  I could smell burning...   Sigh, when I got home I told mom and she started screaming, "Why didn't you pull over and put water in it?!?!"  ha!  Yeah, (a) I'm not pulling over on the side of the rode so people can see me.  (b) I don't know how to add water to whatever it is she is talking about.    "Well, i'll show you how to do it in the morning."  Ha!  the hell you will... tommorow is the first day of school... I'm not getting my hands dirty!   She is insane.  I hate these people. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went for a walk today.  It was more or less a photography mission.  Sat down and rested by this old abandoned building.  Just staring into the sky.  It was nice just to be able to relax and feel the crisp fall-ish breeze.  Then I noticed an insect in my collar so I went to get it out and  SHIT! SHIT!  SHIT! I was just stung by a bee!     The hornet that stung me fled and I was left with a throbing pain in my left middle finger.   My favorite finger .  So anyway, at first the wound just looked like an ant bite.. Then, my middle finger swelled...  SWELLED  to become this HUGE middle finger.  My hand was next, then my whole arm.  ...and then I remembered that I was alergic to bees.    Since Mom and I are fighting, I didn't ask her to take me to the hospital, though... I think I should have... It's been hours now and my left breast all the way down to my finger is numb and swollen.  What?! I'll be fine.  It's actually kind of funny to me.  It's funny when you don't have knuckles..  If i'm not in school Thursday, Its because i'm dead. *giggles ... then stops*    urlLink     This was taken  right  after the sting.. and you can already see the swelling in my middle finger.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah.  It's all coming back to me now.  I'm beginning to remember stress.  Stress and insomnia (in it's true form).  I kid you not when I say I desperately need medication for both.    My car is still in the shop.  No word on how long it will be until the repairs have been completed.  Foolish primitive car repairmen.  What could possible take a week to do?  That would be unacceptable in other careers.  Imagine, a baker that takes a week to bake a cake;  a web designer that takes a week to make a website;  a corporate employee that takes a week to send a simple email.  They would all be fired for taking too much damn time (if they worked for me).    I mean, these mechanics do that for a living so, you would assume simple tasks (and they were very simple tasks) would not require a week to fix.  Hence, It is me who must suffer.  I desperately need transportation.  I still haven't gotten my haircut;  I need to go to the school for several reasons; and I need to go back to AE to return a few pair of pants (because they were ridiculously too small [size:30x32]).     Plus, I would like to get a job sometime soon.  I've been wanting to go hang out (especially last weekend --- which was the last weekend of the summer) with some friends on several occasions.    It all goes back to my Mom's incompetence.  I'm away from home all summer in Florida and when does she put my car in the shop?! The day I return.  **idiots**     My mind is telling me that I need sleep.  My body is screaming, "Shut the hell up Rick!  Lets go see if there are some cokes in the fridge!!"  Hey, what am I supposed to do?  Caffeine is my best friend right now. *twitch* 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Being home sucks.  I've been stuck in the house all week-end, going mad because one of my printers is lying to me... I think we need to see other people.  *base-ball bat time*  I did manage to get the "stoopid spooler" going... But, still the printer's drivers  won't  install.  My computer's telling me that the printer is missing a module from setup.  (which is kinda impossible because the setup files are on a factory disk... and files don't just sprout wings and fly away.) Not from a factory disk, anyway.  Sigh, ...    I need my car back before I  really  loose it.  UPDATE:    urlLink here's your shirt, Jeanette 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eh.  The stupid printer doesn't want to be nice to me today... nor did it want to yesterday.  It keeps saying crazy things like, "The spooler service has not been started."  ... And It won't let me install the driver until it's been started... but it won't start.  So...  *pickes up baseball bat*  ...
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went shopping today with mom.  I bought some folders.  Came home.  Wanted to print some binder labels for the folders.  Discovered that the stupid printer doesn't want to play with my computer anymore.  After trying to fix it for 2 hours... (well, I was actually watching 'Day of the Dead' too...so)    I un-happily went into the kitchen and made a large bowl of Edys ice cream {cookies and cream}  ... that was wonderful.  So, forget the printer for awhile. 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Buy the "Your a Sick Bitch t-shirt"!! Here's the link...  urlLink Buy the shirt! !  Keep in mind I only get 10% of what you buy... *cries*
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      physics english 12 peer tutor american government pe (needs to be changed, it's sports pe... don't need that) algebra 3 w/stats technology apps.  locker #893 (upstairs)
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Paul called me yesterday and invited me to BAM!  I went as soon as Mom got home.  (my car is in the shop)  Lets see, who did I see?  Shannon and Analisa and Paul (of course) and Jessica and Roberta!  It was so nice to be around friends! ^___^   urlLink    Oink Oink Shannon!  *giggles*    urlLink    Oh, that's blackmail!   urlLink    It was so wonderful to see everyone! ^_^
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    say bye bye!!
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know that you're hiding things Using gentle words to shelter me Your words were like a dream But dreams could never fool me Not that easily  I acted so distant then Didn't say goodbye before you left But I was listening You'll fight your battles far from me Far too easily  "Save your tears cause I'll come back" I could hear that you whispered as you walked through that door But still I swore To hide the pain when I turn back the pages Shouting might have been the answer What if I'd cried my eyes out and begged you not to depart But now I'm not afraid to say what's in my heart  Cause a thousand words Call out through the ages They'll fly to you Even though we can't see I know they're reaching you Suspended on silver wings  Oh a thousand words One thousand embraces Will cradle you Making all of your weary days seem far away They'll hold you forever  Oh a thousand words Have never been spoken They'll fly to you They'll carry you home and back into my arms Suspended on silver wings   And a thousand words Call out through the ages They'll cradle you Turning all of the lonely years to only days They'll hold you forever   urlLink Download here  ( right-click, save target as )
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God,  I MISS YOU FAT GRANNY!!   I rode  home  with Ginger and Charolette.  I  HATED  comming home.  Though, the ride home was really fun except for the total dread of returning.  My room smells like:  dog piss , cigarette smoke, and must.  I'm back to my "white-trash" lifestyle.  It's not just the living conditions I hate so much...  I asked my mom for a new pillow.  She started screaming at me.  (they smelled like dog piss.)  She smelled them... "I don't smell nothin!!" she declared, holding my paper thin, piss stained pillow.  ...  There won't be as many pictures on cc.  (won't take any inside or around my house- too ashamed)  But whenever I go out I'll take some.  Also, It's SO HOT in this house.  It's "muggy".  The sickly air  literally  made me throw-up the first night I came back.  ...    I miss  EVERYTHING  about Fat Granny and living with her.  ... I'd get CANCER if I slept on the floor here...    urlLink     Charolette is a damn good packer     urlLink     me and my best friend      urlLink     mm cold coffee    urlLink     thank you so much for taking me home!   All and all, I've cried about the whole thing until I just can't cry anymore.  Life sucks without someone there who  really  cares about you.  
    
</post>


</Blog>