<Blog>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://mercola.com/2004/jun/2/soda_cancer.htm                    Stepping up on my soapbox  I went for about 5 years without a carbonated beverage. This was before it was the "in" thing to do. The only other options you had at the gas station were water and milk. Now you can find a bazillion other things to drink. You get anything from fruit juice to slushies to fancy teas!  I know you can come up with a huge list of thigns that they say cause cancer. I also know that a lot of ppl have the attitude of "You're gonna die from something" and you know who you are... But think about it. What does soda pop offer you? Not much. It might give that surge of caffeine you need or it might jsut be something tasty. But if you go awhile without it you'll realize you really don't need it.  My new resolution is: To drink water when I am thirsty until the thirst goes away. Then if pop or something else sounds good I'll have it.   I've been doing this for about a week and I find I don't have a desire to drink anything else! Plus, water is better for you anyway. It improves your skin, improves your energy level, helps you lose weight, keeps you healthy, keeps you hydrated, and helps flush your body of sickness and toxins!  Stepping off of my soapbox   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.congress.org/congressorg/issues/alert/?alertid=5834001&content_dir=ua_congressorg   This is outrageous!  I can't believe this might actually pass. Can you imagine calling up people like me? I have 2 small children and I'm only 25. So, theoretically they could call me up next spring. What about Benjamin?   Now, I can understand people joining the military. I can understand ppl feeling the need to join after 911. But come on, a DRAFT! I've read that the draft for Vietnam was able to draft those all the way to the age of 50 and this one is only to 26. In some ways it doesn't sound like it makes sense. By the time a person would get out of basic training they would only have 9 months. I guess that you would put on the list of ppl who can be recalled so that is where they see the point. But if you ask me...its stupid!  I blame the feminists :) I mean, before all the feminist junk the women were left out of the draft. See what has happened. Yeah, we have equal pay for equal work (whatever!) but now we can drafted...well, if it passes....  Its all crazy!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I figure that my very first blog entry should be about somehting close to my heart... well, at least omething really weird I found ont he internet!  ]http://news.yahoo.com/news?tmpl=story&cid=573&u=/nm/20040601/od_nm/odd_sweden_condom_dc_1&printer=1  What will they think of next! What a way to reach a nation. Forget abstinance, lets give ppl a way to get what they need without getting out of bed! (literally)
     
    
</post>


</Blog>