<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wad is love?  wad is really love...  For all you people who say, "I love you" when  you have no clue what love is exactly!!!  Something to ponder upon...   Are your palms sweaty, is your heart racing and  is your voice caught within your chest?? -It  isn't love, it's LIKE.   You can't keep your eyes or hands off of  her/him - It isn't love, it's LUST.   Are you proud, and eager to show her/him off?? - It isn't love, it's LUCK.   Do you want her because you know she's/he's  there?? - It isn't love, it's LONELINESS.   Are you with her/him because it's what everyone  wants??  It isn't love, it?s LOYALTY.   Are you with her because she/he kissed you, or  held your hand?  It isn't love, it's LOW CONFIDENCE.   Do you stay for her/him confessions of love,  because you don't want to hurt her/him?  It isn't love, it's PITY.   Do you belong to her/him because the sight of  her/him makes your heart skip a beat??  It isn't love, it's INFATUATION.   Do you pardon her faults because you care about  her/him?  It isn't love, it's FRIENDSHIP.   Do you tell her/him every day she is the only  one you think of?  It isn't love, it's a LIE.   Are you willing to give up all of your favorite  things for her sake? It isn't love, it's CHARITY.   =================================================  Does your heart ache and break when she's sad?  Then it's LOVE.   Do you cry for her/his pain, even when  she's/he's strong?  Then it's LOVE.   Do her/his eyes see your true heart, and touch  your soul so deeply it hurts? Then it's LOVE.   Do you stay because a blinding, incomprehensible  mix of pain and relation pulls you close and  holds you to her/him?  Then it's LOVE.   Do you accept her/his faults because it's a part  of who she/he is?  Then it's LOVE.   Are you attracted to others, but stay with  her/him faithfully without regret??  Then it's LOVE.   Would you give her/him your heart, your life,  your death??  Then it's LOVE.   Now, if love is painful, and tortures us so, why  do we love? Why is it all we search for in life?  This pain, this agony? Why is it all we long  for?  This torture, this powerful death of self? Why?  The answer is so simple cause it's...LOVE. It is  such an addictive thing that even people who are  not having it wish to experience it and share it  with others as well.   Pass this to all your friends so they don't make  the same mistake with their LOVE LIVES!! I like  the dreams of the future better than the history  of the past...   Love hurts our feeling, but it's also the reason  our soul heal..  But one day when u truly fall in love..remember  to let the 'someone' know..to suffer a moment of  embarassment is better than letting your  happiness fly away forever... 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You are the Primrose Sprite. A common creature wondering in gardens, brushing her  urlLink hair . She is the populer fey, a creature of class. Congratulations, rate my quiz, it would make you populerer in my eyes.    urlLink   What kind of element fey are you? (PRETTY PICS)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well your Happy, yes thats right your so happy, so pretty and witty and if i go on any more i will have to pay for the rights of this song so, great jop your one of the lucky ones.    urlLink   What Emotion Dominates you?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Reincarnation: You are nice enough to go to heaven, but Earth won't be as fun without you. So you shall come back as someone or something else. As a real optimist and lighthearted person, you always see the good in things. People probably respect you for your wonderful personality and love for life. People like you make the world a happier place (please rate my quiz)    urlLink   **Where will you go when you die?**(now with pics)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You belong somewhere out in the world, exploring and learning and spreading the knowledge that you find. When you love, that love will join you in your quest and believe as you do in a world of spiritual energy that is stronger than anything humanity could normally even conceive, although you may be able to. Council those you encounter, give them your wisdom, and stay true to yourself.    urlLink   Where do you belong?(ANIME IMAGES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're Element is Light. You are friendly, happy, social, bubbly, and can brighten up any one's day. You are very kind and a real people person because you have several friends (or atleast should). You're cheery nature makes you lovable and your stunning looks are sweet and stand out.     urlLink   What's Your Element(girls)? (PICTURES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Congrats! Your a Pure Angel! Angels, as far as most of them go, are all compatabile creatures, but Pure ones simply are symbols of God. Pure Angels always appear when a child is born, when a rainbow is seen, or when someone shares their first kiss. They never grow old, an can appear in the shape of a naked woman with white, bold wings. Pure angels are the carriers of god, and show their love to everyone in the world.    urlLink   What Kind of ANGEL are you? (For Girls only) This Quiz has amazingly Beautiful Pictures!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Phoenix: Phoenixes are litterally birds of fire. They are brave and majestic and have the ability to be reborn from their own ashes.  You are strog willed an confident- a true leader.  Although you can get down in the dumps occasionaly you are never there for long. Many people flock around you and like you as a friend.    urlLink   What Mythological Creature Are You (Many Results and Beautiful Pics)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You have a heartsick soul! Youre the type of girl who always has a crush and is writing their name on all your books. You are a hopeless romantic. Waiting for that prince charming, you take love seriously, but still play any chance you get. You can have a lot if boys who are friends, but waiting for that perfect boyfriend. Sometimes you are discouraged because there are no sparks but even if the smallest thing happens, youre on Cloud 9.  You believe in true love and wait for it. Just dont be afraid to take a chance. Love is all about risks.    urlLink   What Kind of SOUL do you posses? (For Girls only) Incredible Anime Pictures!     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Your Heart is Blue    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Your Heart is Blue    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You are a child's kiss.  Completely sweet and innocent and pure. You mean no harm and only love in your sweet kisses.    urlLink   What kind of kiss are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Blue Eyes    urlLink   What Color Eyes Should You Have?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        A GIRLY-GIRL. You dont have a lot of self-esteem and people are always bringing you down for being sad. What do they know, anyway? You feel like youre too mature for your age and are frustrated by the trend-followers who refuse to accept you because youre not like them.  Your virtues: Intelligence, understanding nature, modesty.  Your flaws: Lack of social life, inferiority complex, timidity..    You might like this game, but maybe it's not your thing.  Take a look anyway if you are curious:  www.life-blood.vze.com    urlLink   What kind of girl are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>