<Blog>


<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      All or Nothing  Uhh  I know when he's been on your mind  That distant look is in your eyes  I thought with time you'd realize  It's over over  It's not the way I choose to live  And something somewhere's got to give  As sharing this relationship gets older older   You know I'd fight for you  But how I can find someone who isn't even there  I've had the rest of you now I want the best of you  I dont care if that's not fair   Chorus:  Cause I want it all  Or nothing at all  There's no where left to fall  When you reach the bottom it's now or never  Is it all  Or are we just friends  Is this how it ends  With a simple telephone call  You leave me here with nothing at all (with Erik)   There are times it seems to me  I'm sharing you with memories  I feel it in my heart  But I don't show it show it  And then there's times you look at me  As though I'm all that you can see  Those times I don't believe it's right  I know it know it (With Erik)   Don't me make me promises  Baby you never did know how to keep them well  I've had the rest of you  Now I want the best of you  It's time for show and tell (with Erik)   Chorus   Cause you and I  Could lose it all if you've got no more room  No room inside for me in your life   Cause I want it all  Or nothing at all  There's no where left to fall  It's now or never  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Led by director Eimuntas Nekrošius, one of Europe's most respected theatre masters since the fall of the Iron Curtain, Meno fortas' theatrical world weaves a rich visual tapestry illuminated with powerful symbolisms of natural and material elements.   In Nekrošius' Othello, this four-hour tour de force of Shakespeare's tale of passion and jealousy has received wide critical acclaim everywhere it performed and will leave you yearning for more.  Without being indulgent, Nekrošius allows the dramatic action to unwind and decompress, imbuing it with a life and tempo of its own, creating a complex spiritual adventure arousing both anxiety and ecstasy. The recurrent laconic and perturbing elemental metaphors of water, fire and wood fill the space with astounding beauty.   "The shattering power of visual suggestion and the director's rare ability in a deep analysis of the text distinguishes the work of Nekrošius." — Il Giorno  "Passion raging in the performance of Meno fortas surpassed all imaginable boundaries. Five hours…passed by without notice for those who were lucky enough to get seats to the new performance by Eimuntas Nekrošius."  — Moskovskij Komsomolec     
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>