<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    i love this pic..haha&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      which is english???....'u' or 'you'..i have been typing too much short forms in msn ..ooh noooo.......i even typed it in my latest letter writing.but i did change it after my sister corrected me....i better start to type the correct form before it get worst...argh..... ;(..so now u might be seeing me typing perfect english..haha..maybe not perfect..normal..no shortcuts.haha
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yum..yum...bbq  went pasir ris chalet for bbq with my cuzzies and relatives..and there was a the water theme park..the wild,wild,wet!!..haha..but when i got there..it was already closed..i had a fun time there.the adults there were playing mahjong..while we were bbqing half way..it was drizzling...but it was ok after that. i even went bowling there.we waited for quite a long time...we had to buy socks n borrow the 'stinky'  bowling shoes...haha...we played until abt 12.45..then we went home...  yummy..'n'.first time bowling... 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Had netball training today..ar...sun quite hot.Met our new coach..she's quite friendly..haha :)...training under the not sun for about 3hrs..hehe.hope can lose weight!!..after the training..i walked home with Rachel..thts being GREEN..we save the Earth..yah..haha..we talked about how we can get home faster and without wasting any energy...haha...we talked from kidscooter to escalator;P.We were like walking very slowly..almost like limping.....argh...i'm verytired when igot home..can't move any more...
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i went to 'bukit china' in melaka...however when i was about to walk up the steps...a uncle sitting near it warned me not to go up...and other stall keepers around                                                                      ITS HISTORY' As the name implies, 'Chinese Hill' was the official settlement of the Chinese entourage that arrived with Princess Hang Li Poh. She was sent to Melaka by the Emperor to marry the sultan to mark the advent of diplomatic relationship until Portuguese occupation in 1511. The Sultan constructed a palace on top of the hill. Today Bukit China is one of the largest Chinese cemeteries outside China with many of the tombs dating back to Ming Dynasty. It is located at Jalan Puteri Hang Li Poh. '  i was quite pluzzled at first..why don't go up and take a look at the cemeteries ...then my father told me that once a female tourist went up n got.....er..u think about it...and it was rather deserted up there ever since that has happened...oh my..that was ....however..i still went up a few steps..and took a look. Its was a little scary as there were only trees and cemeteries. hmm...i thnk tht those pple who r buried in the cemetery should have decomposed now and become fertilsers to the plant and soil.....Up to now..i'm stil curious abt it...
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today went to bukit timah hill with family.After coming down from summit,i went to hindhede park.hmm...guess wat i saw a flying fox gliding to a tree!!!...wah...tht was nice..its wings spreaded out like a kite!haha...i also saw it passing out bowels..yikes...i tried but capture it in my dad's hp..however it was too dark can't see it clearly...aw..what a waste.but i had a fun time there..haha...thts all...:P
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       very first step   hmm....this is my first time creating a blog...hmm...quite a lot of hard wrk..my other frens one are very nice!..i will make mine a nice one too..haha...   very first step 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       sigh.....So many tests.....hope to clear 'em as soon as possible..................  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        hmm..i miss her alot...  next time hmk got no people teach me  ...went to the airport ..long time never go liao...  hmm..saw some changes there....sigh...nxt time when i'm going back there is to fetch her from airport..  hahax...waiting for that day!!... 
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        HaHa... National day= school holiday=more sleep!! ..Netball yesterday was pretty fun..although only 5 of us went . we learnt quite a few useful skills.. The seniors came back and played a match against us. At first i thought thought that we surely can't score a goal..however we somehow managed..with the help of our     coaches..hehe.And today was our captain's birthday..!!...we managed to trick her and poured water on her..and she was all wet.she was unprepared..muhahaha..;P...hmm...it was fun..However i need to inprove more on my passes and speed...sigh...      After national day, there would be lots of tests coming.... man!!!!.....going to die T.T..Science practical exams are coming too....sigh..Lets look on the bright side...Days would get better each day?!  
</post>


</Blog>