<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "haih..i have an exam tomorrow. i really want to get good results for it. is the only way of achieving this, is by studying?? isn't there any machine that can just insert every info i need into my brain?? well, looks like i have to study. but there is a great show later, and my eyes feels heavy, maybe i will take a nap before i study. you know, so i will feel fresh. or maybe i should study at least a while first...zzZZZzzZZZzZZzzz"  sounds familiar. first you hesitate whether you should study or take a nap first or watch tv etc. five minutes of hesitation, then you go take a nap, ending up drifting of to dreamland for 3 hours. there is no more time to study because there is a chinese series on tv. you swore you would study later or wake up earlier to study. BUT you did not. your results..BAD..so you tell yourself to be more hardworking next time..when 'next time' comes..you repeat the same thing again..like dejavu.  if you are going through this..well sound the alarm..you are diagnosed with a dangerous disease..LAZINESS..i have been suffering from this disease for, let's see, forever..the only cure is willpower. without it, you will be trapped in the horrible world af laziness until you plan to get come out. the only person who can cure this disease is yourself. well, easier said than done, obviously. i haven't been able to that but i am trying and now i am getting nearer to the open door. nearer to the exit of the "lazy world". wish me luck. and good luck to everyone who is trying to do so..  tips: get something to motivate you..something really strong.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      they are there when you are at your happiest moments, when you are at the bottom of a hole, or when you are experiencing "funny" moments in my life..they are my  best friends..   how are best friend(s) different from friends?? they are always by your side..whatever happens..i am talking, of course, about best friends..they know our deepest and darkest secrets but you don't regret telling them and they keep it a secret(well, at least all that 'bribe' worked)  i have 4 best friends...they are the greatest..they are ida, suet li, sarah and esther..eventhough i only got to know esther and sarah closer this year..they are still amazing friends..we are the 5 musketeers..hehe..we do nearly everything together..i said NEARLY everthing...we need to give space to each ather at times..you know time to do other stuff that we like..especially *erm erm* time to spend with their boyfriend..  i can never imagine my life without my other musketeers...     from left: ida, sarah, esther, suet and me..     the REAL charlie angels!!!     three words.."JUST PLAIN CRAZY"   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      now and then u can read about rape case in the newspapers..actually it's all the time...it is so normal now that it has become part of our lifes..  i cannot imagine the pain and torture a rape-victim has to go through. it is sickening to read about all these rape cases..all these animals preying on innocent victims..later on taking their dignity away from them as if it is theirs...the most pathetic part is they just leave without regret or remorse..well of course they do not feel it..it is not them who has to suffer the physical and mental pain...it is not them who is being haunted everynight by this nightmare...  victims go through hard times..what they need is as much moral support as possible..unfortunately many people look at rape victims with dislike..as f they ask for it..so hear me out people..understand the situation these people are in..they did not ask for it..     "Rape... just because she was afraid to kick, scream, bite, fight, cry, scratch doesn't mean she wasn't raped."  "Rape... when it happens to your mother, daughter, sister, girlfriend, buddy, cousin, niece, aunt, grandmother, wife will you say she was asking for it?" 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you know..i have always wondered what is life about..is it worth it, achieving your goals just to know that you will have to let go in the end??  i have thought about it for quite a while..we achieve our goals for the sake of making the most out of our lifes..right?? well its the only answer i can think of..but there are lots of people out there who fail to achieve their goals due to unavoidable problems..some accept the fact..sadly some don't..because of this they suffer for the rest of their lifes..  life is short although 70 years sounds long...but keep in mind that our life is like a thin thread that can break at any moment...fortunately i realised this earlier..i have learnt to appreciate the wonderful people around me more, to enjoy and not be too serious and reserved, and to do stuff i want to do..  although my dreams are not fulfilled yet, all i can do is be sastified with what i have and just try as hard as i can to achieve them..as long as God allows me to...     me after a party..enjoying life..hehe
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i would never forget the day 40 students of SMK USJ 8 went on a trip to InventQJaya and the Star Media Hub.."learning and discovering" was what it is all about..besides having fun of course..a day after exams seems like a perfect day for a school trip, so we told ourselves to  "enjoy enjoy enjoy" ..this is what happened..   0830, school canteen..  all of us are excited..well at least only five of us. but the most excited one is esther. all of us cannot help it but giggle and laugh out loud..we are definately the noisest. 'we' includes me, ida, suet, esther, sarah and hwee yeen. all of us were so exited until we began asking ourselves.."why are we overexcited?"   0845, at last we go to "THE BUS"..  all of us began to feel tired while waiting for the bus driver to finish his breakfast. the tiredness was noticable because the noise had lessen. all of us got up an air-conditioned bus. 6 of us got up first so that we get the back seats..and we did. the bus was comfortable except for one thing - food wasn't allowed on the bus. on the bus the excitement among us crept back into our veins. we started singing and making lots of noise. we were the noisest (actually we were the only ones making noise)..   0915, outside on the way..  first stop: inventQJaya. barely half an hour have passed the back seats of the bus stopped making noise. all of us were tired. suet li started reading while a few of us dozed off. that meant peace and quiet for everone else.   lost track of time, at inventQjaya..  i wasn't really fascinated by the building because the erricson buliding beside it was better. but i have learned to not judge a book by it's cover. inside was a spacious lobby. we were greeted with messages n 3 flat-screen tvs. it said "welcome SMK USJ 8 students". it was actually a great feeling seeing my school name on the screen.   still clueless bout the time, start of a great trip..  honestly i did not expect myself to enjoy this trip to inventQjaya very much..it turned our otherwise. i enjoyed myself alot..first all of us went into a hall where we were briefed about the company's history. it was opened on january 2003. next we were given a chance to enjoy a 3D movie.i enjoyed the 3D effect very much. i did not quite understand the movie. after that we were amzed by an electric scooter. sure your may be thinking,  its just a scooter running on electricity. ..but the scooter it very very quite..and most probably easier to use than the normal scooter.   don't ask what time it is, splitting up..  we were splitted into two groups..it was kinda sad because the six of us were splitted up..but i was cheered up later on...they showed us a few of their inventions..they inventions are based on their motto - inventing for humanity..i was fascinated by their inventions that can really make this world a better place.    group photo before departure   1200(very sure), stomach growling..  goodness, it's already 12..i am so hungry. all of us are off to have lunch at our fav restaurant..McDonalds =)...unfortunately the journey there took such a long time i slept on a empty stomach..we had an hour to eat before continuing our journey to the STAR.. i thought i can eat alot..wait till you see ida.. seh ate a doublecheese burger and two pieces of chicken..and still feel hungry..    at McDs..the 6 noise makers...hehe   1330, off to the STAR  slept again..i really felt tired..at the STAR..we were introduced to the process of printing newspapers..believe me it isn't easy..it invovles a few machines that cost millions each and a complicated process....   1600, back home..  after a long but fun and enlightening day, we head bac to homebase..school..i was so tired that i slept all the way home..hehehe..but i was happy and satisfied..i met great people, and learnt plenty of stuff..definately a day i will naver forget..  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>