<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sophie is turning 1 on 3rd of July. I am breaking my head about her birthday party. I found this on one of the sites:   My daughter went to a summer birthday party when she was 3 and they had all the kids wear swim suites and they played Hawaiian music and gave them all lays and. They had a bunch of kiddie pools some filled with sand others with water and lots of beach balls. They had a hula contest and gave out sea shells for prizes. They took individual Polaroid photos of them in grass skirts and had each child make a frame decorated with shells and sand, that was their favor along with the skirts and lays, which she still uses for dress up. The cake was a pineapple upside down cake and the balloons were decorated to look like coconuts and pineapples what fun it was.    May be I could do something with shells and stones and wooden sticks. What about party favors? I could not find anything decent yesterday> i think the idea od decorating their own picture is fabulous. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is it that everyone  feels the same or is it just me? It seems that age is some outside game. I am the same me I was when I was 7 still waiting to grow up. It seems that the world is crazy running past me with a mind spinning speed, looking sort of back on me (who is out of breath dragging behind).....   Is age an idea in consciousness or a reality I am to accept? Is it that the one who is meant  to be hung will not drown? Should I make effort to preserve and improve the body or should I leave within the waves of conventions? After all what fun it is to be well and alive when all your friends are gone, and no one  remembers your favorite movie star? Haven't you yourself looked at a granny sporting low rise jeans with pity?
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got an excellent book yesterday: "Siblings without rivary". Really great and very very practical.  And the main point is always something you know about, but forget to do. In this case: letting in be and allowing all the feelings (in regards to Sebastian, my 21/5 year old boy). Yes, when he is angry, or overexcited and he hots her, what do I do? I scream at him and punish him by putting him to another room. Does this allow his feeligs to surface - not of course. I do not even acknowledge them. Would rather say something like: I see you are feeling angry. Would you like to show me how you feel with the pillow ( or crayons). Teaching children from early on to express their feelings artistically is probably one of the best things ever I could do for them. Don't we all wish we learned it when we were babies too?  Another good tip from another good book: the magic of a word may. "You may hang your clothes now" - isn't it elegant?
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Are my two little guys. Sophie is  just about to turn 11 months and has already taken her first steps. Sebastian will be 3 in the end of September.  Being with them is both enormous challenge and pleasure. I am striving to be the best mom I can possibly be, and that does not seem to come easily on automatic. Just this morning Sebastian smacked Sophie with the door on her head. But in the end everyone was scared because of my screaming more then anything.   My own reactions and responses - this is what I am up to. Something I did not think I would have to ever deal with.  I opened this little lovely book I bought recently on Waldorf education "Beyond the rainbow Bridge", and the author is talking about how important it is to be calm and quiet durinig a tantrum  and not agrue with the child and how our inner discipline is teaching them through silence. I hope I will remember that the next time I am bout to scream.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are firts breaths, first steps and here is my first blog. Lucky am I to have found this. I am sure it will be a great new addition to my life. I have been thinking for a while that  I would love to have a personal webpage, or some place where  I could  keep a journal. I tend to have pieces of paper all over the place that just make their way to the trash bin when I have no more room to keep them. I hope this will work. And I hope to find people I need  to connect with. Skol for the first try!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>