<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In case I turn up missing, don't bother putting my face on a milk carton.  Instead, I want you to send some sort of special forces into my house.  I'll probably be buried underneath a pile of dirty laundry and used Kleenex.  You see, tonight Rusty and I are going to clean the house.  For those of you who know me well, you probably think that my house couldn't be that bad.  Let me assure you, it's bad.  I've been sick for a month, and haven't been too eager to clean the house...and now it has to be done.  His brother and his brother's significant other are coming to stay Friday and Saturday nights.   So if you hear screaming, and probably sobbing, off in the distance...it's probably me cleaning my bathroom.   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, I confess...I checked that other girl's email again.  (If you have read my Moments of Pure Evil post, you'll know what I'm talking about.)  Reading her messages has become like my own twisted little soap opera.  It's sick, but I'm kind of enjoying it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is yet another one of those days at work.  The only thing redeeming is that it's payday, which means I can pay bills and be even more pissed off when I realize that the lousy paycheck around here doesn't go as far as I want it to.    Anyway, the idiots here never abide by any sort of office procedure until they realize that they may get their ass chewed.  So what do they do?  They pretend that they've been doing things the right way all along...and those of us at the bottom of the totem pole get OUR asses chewed.  Oh the joy of working!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a weekend.  First of all, we found and bought a minivan.  We are now the proud owners of a silver 2000 Pontiac Montana.  I love that van.  Dual sliding doors.  Rear temperature control.  CD Player.  Stereo controls on the steering wheel.  Oh, yeah....  Went yesterday with my Mom to see the third Harry Potter.  Good movie.  Cute kid.  Probably gonna be really hot when he's older.  Makes me think of the time that Sara and I were discussing Jonathan Taylor Thomas, and she said, "I'd do him...if I were a pedafile."    I also stopped by the after hours clinic while we were in Jefferson City.  This bronchitis is still kicking my ass.  I'm now on my second round/type of antibiotics.  Please, dear Lord, let them work.    Today I am amazingly tired.  Just do not have the ability to concentrate.  Thank goodness that this coming weekend is a 3 day weekend.  I will be very happy to have Monday off.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is it about a new pair of shoes to make you feel all perky? I'm wearing a pair of sandals that my coworker gave me.  They've got the highest heels that I think I've worn in 5 years, but they're really cute.  I'm feeling kinda girly.  Hmmm...maybe I'll repaint my toenails at lunch.  Well, last night was SO exciting at my house.  Rusty fell asleep at 7:30.  I put Sierra to bed at 8.  I went to bed a little before 9:30.    I would have gotten to bed earlier last night, but I had to take some time to fight the ants again!  They've found yet ANOTHER place to come in.  This time they came in through the floor of the closet in the laundry/computer room to the cat food.  I brought out the 409 again.  They were back by this morning.  Bastards!  So, the cat food has officially been moved to another room.  They'll probably come there too, but I'm at least gonna make it a challenge.    This is looking to be an action packed weekend.  Tomorrow morning we're going to test drive minivans.  In the afternoon we have a birthday party.  Our friends, Will and Angie, have a little boy who's only a few months older than Sierra.  His first birthday is tomorrow.  Sunday I'm going to see the new  urlLink Harry Potter  with my mom.  I'm very excited.  It's gonna be us and all the 10 year olds on the edge of our seats!  A new family bought the house next to us.  Their side yard connects to our back yard.  I've spent the last week trying to figure out how many kids they have.  I've been watching them through my kitchen windows.  I know it's only a 3 bedroom house, and I swear they've gotta have a dozen kids. They're everywhere!  I think it's time to get out my binoculars so I can see more distinguishing features.  That will make it much easier to count the kids.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is one of those days where I have no tolerance of the ignorance around me.  And let me tell you, the legal profession is full of ignorance.  These are people who can go to law school and pass the freakin bar, but have no idea how to transfer a phone call.    On the 14th I had a job interview and was told that I would probably hear back sometime the end of this week.  So now I play that little game with myself where I pretend that I really don't care.  Of course, I know that I don't mean it.  If they don't call me by the middle of next week, I'll start doing  that little "should I call them?" thing.  I hate this whole process. It's like dating!     I've been searching websites of local car dealerships for minivans...and drooling all over myself.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Big hugs today to my Sara today...the Cagney to my Lacey.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please feel free to sign the guestbook that has been added over on the bottom left.  I'd love to know you've stopped in to read my little blog!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's not really a bad day, but not good either.  You know the ones I'm talking about.    Sierra crashed early last night while she and I were watching that  urlLink AFI 100 greatest movie songs .  I didn't necessarily agree with all their choices and rankings, but I don't exactly remember being asked.  Overall, I think their number one pick was on the money, but the rest needs work.  Also, one more interview with  urlLink Celine Dion  and I think I would have slit my wrists.  I don't quite know why, but that woman irritates the crap out of me.    The cold is still not going away.  This is my seventh day of antibiotics.  Still no change.  Between the coughing my hubby, and my two cats, I slept very little last night.  When I got comfortable, I'd cough.  There were several times that I was almost alseep and then Rusty or one of the cats would start snoring.  Now, it's not that Sassy or TJ snore loudly, but it's kind of an annoying sound.  More of a battery powered screwdriver than an chainsaw, but annoying none the less.    All is momentarily quiet at work today.  People are working, or so it appears.  (You already know what I'm doing.)  Must be because the boss is back today.  Hmmm.  Makes me wonder who's running hell when he's here.  The great hunt for a minivan has begun.  I want either a used Caravan or Grand Caravan.  The tricky part is gonna be finding one in the right price range.    Ok, I have to admit that I checked that girl's email again.  I'm awful!  But she still doesn't have anything exciting.  Not even any cheezy forwards.  How disappointing!  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...but it was even harder being pink.  Had to change the page color.  I just kept thinking that the page looked like it was sprayed down with Pepto Bismol.  I think we'll try this look for a while.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A big   Howdy   to the employees of  urlLink Jeffrey E. Smith Companies  who have found my little blog entertaining.  Just a little FYI, Michelle is even more twisted than she appears.  Don't be deceived.   Pop Tarts everywhere still fear her.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like to think that at one time I used to be at least kinda cool.  I drank on school nights.  I had a car named "Big Sexy."  I could pick the locks on my friends dorm rooms if they locked themselves out.  I was hip.  Cool.  I could get down with my bad self.    Those days, my friend, are apparently gone.  The signs that they have been replaced are too much for me to ignore.    Sign number one:  A teenage boy with an apparent hearing problem (note the sarcasm) went cruising through our neighborhood last night.  I stood at my living room window, cursing, watching him go by.  First, I screamed at him for driving "too damned fast on a street where little kids play a lot."  After that came a long grumbling about the volume of his stereo and his choice of "music."  (I hate to admit it, but hip hop just gets on my nerves.  Give me Aerosmith anyday.)    Sign number two:  Rusty and I have been discussing selling his truck and buying another vehicle.  At first, he wanted a Chevy Tracker.  We had one a few years ago, and he's still got separation anxiety.  I admit, I liked it too.  Loved that convertible top.  Anyway, now I think we have decided on a mini-van, which I have wanted for a while.  The thing here is that I'm starting to get really excited at the prospect of getting a mini-van.  I watch the commercials on tv and just drool all over because they have so much room.  I could get the car seat in and out so much easier!  Groceries would be a breeze!!!    Oh well.  So some of the coolness is gone.  Now, where's my Geritol?
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The ants who have decided to make my house their place of residence one-upped me this weekend.  After cleaning my kitchen cabinet and bombing several of them with Formula 409, the sneaky little bastards decided to take a different approach.  Apparently they found a way to get into my computer/laundry room.  I discovered hundreds of them under my desk (this is personal now) headed in a straight line toward the catfood bowl.  As if Meow Mix were somehow better than my cooking.  (For those of you who have eaten my cooking, please refrain from laughter.)  So, out came the 409 again.  It's really sick, but I felt quite satasfied in my temporary victory.  I even chased down the non-conformist "stray" ants to squirt them too.  Vengeance is mine!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I finally admitted defeat last Thursday.  I gave it up and went to the doctor.  The cold won.  Actually, it has surpassed the level of "cold."  I now have a nice rip-roaring case of bronchitis.  My world has turned into a whirlwind of used Kleenex and cough drop wrappers.    The trip to the doctor was pretty interesting.  Belle has one doctor.  Dr. Daugherty.  I switched to him as my primary care physician just so that when I'm sick I don't have to drive 45 minutes.  There's nothing worse than having to drive a long distance when you're miserable.  ANYway, this was my first visit to the Belle clinic.  I have to say that it was a little unnerving.  First of all, Dr. Daugherty was very nice, but I just couldn't get over the fact that he looked like Ron Howard as Opie.  I kept waiting for Aunt Bea to come in and take my temp.  Secondly, one of the girls I went to school with from kindergarden on is a nurse there.  I find it so hard to take her seriously.  It's nothing personal, but I have a difficult time seeing the people I grew up with as responsible adults.  Hell, they probably feel that way about me too.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here's a good ethical question:  what would you do if you accidently logged into someone else's email account?  Would you log back out when you realized it wasn't yours, or would you browse around a bit and read the messages?  That question presented itself to me yesterday.  I was logging into my Yahoo account, which I very rarely use, and made a little typo when doing it.  Well, apparently someone with an address very close to mine also uses the same password.  What were the chances?  So what did I do?  I read her e-mail, of course.  I couldn't resist it!  Sure, maybe it's wrong.  But it was just too compelling.  As it turns out, this girl is extremely boring.  Judging by her messages, I'd say she's a bible thumping, pseudo-intellectual who's addicted to the Home Shopping Network.    In other news...for weeks now I have been fighting with the ants that are trying to take over my kitchen.  At first, they came in groups of about 4 or 5.  This, I feel, was very poor ant leadership.  Usually I would just smoosh them or flick them down the drain.  Somewhere along the line, however, they became more organized.  Now they're coming in huge numbers, which has left me only one choice.  Chemical warfare.  It's amazing how fast a few squirts of Formula 409 will kill of a few hundred ants.  Still, the thing that puzzles me is that they have apparently tasted my cooking, and continue to come back.    I'm still suffering through this cold...which has turned into something slightly more nasty.  I've decided to finally admit defeat and go to the doctor.  I hate going to the doctor.  The idea of paying someone to harp at me for not taking care of myself like I should.  I can get that for free from my family!  Also, in another brainy moment, Rusty and I went with our friends Angie and Will on a little road trip to Lebanon, MO on Friday.  They have a Tracker, and we drove down with the top off.  Apparently, my feeble mind forgot for a day just how painful a sunburn is...and that sunblock would have been in order.  I passed the point of burn, and ended up completely scortched.  Of course, I then had a job interview on Monday.  Let's just say that I looked like a lobster in a black dress.  Hopefully they're lovers of seafood.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to a Friday-like substance!  I don't have to work tomorrow, so it's just as good as a Friday.  Better, actually, because it's a 3 day weekend.  The only improvment that could have been made was if it were payday too!!!  Have you noticed that Nancy Reagan looks like a really old Sally Jesse Raphael?    I have to confess that I looked up all the cast members from Kids, Incorporated.  Ryan Lambert is now in what I assume is an alternative band of some sort.  So are Stephanie Ferguson and Martika. Most of the others disappeared into oblivion.  I love  urlLink IMDB .  The source of all great random entertainment knowledge.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is one of those days where I have the attention span of a fruit fly, and can't seem to get two brain cells to work together....  I've had another non-eventful day at work.  Still fighting the cold, but it appears that the Dayquil is working somewhat.  Sierra just absolutely crashed last night, so I actually managed to get everything done and was in bed by 10:30.  On the other hand, she decided she was starving this morning at 4:20.    Check this site out if you get the chance:   urlLink http://www.johnkerryisadouchebagbutimvotingforhimanyway.com/ .  Do you ever wonder what happened to the cast of Kids, Incorporated?  I was just thinking about that show this moring.  Ryan Lambert was such a hottie.  Hmmm...may have to look them all up on the net today.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's yet another day moving slowly by after a mere 4 hours of sleep.  No one in my house seems to be sleeping lately.  We've all been sick.  Sierra is getting over an ear infection and cold.  As for Rusty, I've spent the last few days shoving Dayquil at him.  And now I'm starting to get sick.    Now, for those of you who are Moms, you know that being sick is out of the question.  I remember very few times that my mom was sick when I was little.  It's not because she didn't get sick, it was because she wasn't allowed to  BE  sick.  The Mom seldom gets to stay in bed all day surrounded by a pile of kleenex.  (One of my favorite activites when I'm ill.)  Always reminds me of my junior year of college when Sara and I got so sick that we both laid in bed and called each other on the phone because we didn't want to walk through the bathroom to the other one's room.    I'm starting to wonder if anyone would notice if I just curled up under my desk.  Probably.  *sniff* *sniff*
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I was surfing around the internet last week and ran into the blog of  urlLink a classmate from college .  That got me thinking that perhaps I should start one of my own.  I could bitch to the masses instead of just my friends and family!  And yes, it is cheaper than therapy!  Thus, here's my blog.    I'm married, age 27, have one daughter, and I'm a 1999 grad of Stephens College.  I've spent the last four years working for state government in jobs that have absolutely nothing to do with my degree.  Where did that $100,000 go again?  I was hoping for something monumental to start with...some sort of life changing event to tell you about.  Alas, here I am...and the best thing I've got is that I just got one of those "buy a 20 oz Pepsi and you get one free" caps.  Whatever happened to just getting a free soda?  Now you have to buy one to get the free one.  Sounds like an evil plot to keep me hooked on caffeine.  Good for them, cause it's working.    This is such a Monday.  Ick.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some new pics have been added to my online photos.&nbsp; (I love unlimited storage space!)&nbsp; The rest of the pics that Chelle sent me from her trip have been added, as well as those from Sara's visit and a couple new ones of Sierra watching the Belle Fair parade.&nbsp; I also uploaded some earlier pics of Sierra and 3 from Rusty's snagging trip with my dad.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      See how well you know me!    urlLink http://connect.tickle.com/test.html?id=qPeGEvJgOXHYz34Q   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, I personally have never tried any illegal drugs. I just don’t think I’d make a good druggie. Mostly because I’m too cheap to spend money like that. If illegal drugs were cheaper, there are days when I might consider it. In the meantime, I have come to the conclusion that sleep deprivation is a pretty decent substitute. Everyone told me while I was pregnant that after Sierra was born, I’d never sleep the same again...if I slept. There’s no way I could have prepared myself for this. Silly me. I have come to feel that it’s the only part of parenthood that I have serious issues with. I’ve been drooled on, puked on, pissed and shit on. Everything I own has just the slightest smell of Enfamil. These things are livable. It’s the sleep that I miss.   To be fair, Sierra is an exceptional baby. She usually goes to bed between 8 and 10pm. If we don’t wake her up, she sleeps until between 7:30 and 9:30am. (Truthfully, I sometimes keep her up later on the weekend so that she’ll let me sleep in.) All rules, however, go out the window when she’s sick.   She’s had a cold since the middle of last week. She’s been miserable, and so have Rusty and I. Over the weekend she also developed an ear infection. All I can tell you is that there was a lot of crying...and that was just us. Last night she was up until 11:30 or midnight. For those of you who don’t know, I get up at 5am during the week. (Otherwise known as "Freaking Early"). It’s now almost 5pm. I’m reaching the state of delirium.   Back to the drug reference, I found out today that the nitwit nurse I talked to from the pediatrician's office told me the wrong amount of Dimetapp to give her.&nbsp; Essentially, we've been trying to overdose her for the past few days.&nbsp; Poor kid!   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a visit from my little insect friends again the other day.&nbsp; In typical fashion, I sprayed the hell out of them with 409.&nbsp;   Here's a little helpful hit for those of you battling the little buggers:&nbsp; spray bleach, 409 or Pine Sol around the area where they appear to be coming in.&nbsp; Don't wipe it up.&nbsp; Instead, let it air dry.&nbsp; Someone gave me that same tip, and it appears to have worked.&nbsp; I sprayed all around my windowsil above the kitchen sink.&nbsp; I haven't seen any ants in that spot for several days.&nbsp; Interestingly, I did see them on my kitchen floor.&nbsp; An entire colony of ants came in for a small bit of pizza crust.&nbsp; (Obviously they haven't heard of delivery...not that there is delivery in Belle.)&nbsp; I was in the middle of trying to deal with a screaming baby, so I didn't have the chance to kill them.&nbsp; I remembered the next morning, and went to look.&nbsp; All of them were gone.&nbsp; Apparently they got full, or like me, figured out that I had left that pizza in the oven just a few minutes too long. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       All right, I’ve just gotta rant a bit. Today’s topic: gay marriage. The whole thought of a constitutional amendment banning gay marriage just absolutely sickens me.   Once upon a time, I remember being taught about separation of church and state. If I remember correctly, it has something to do with keeping religion out of government. Now, every time I have a conversation with someone who opposes gay marriage (not to mention homosexuality itself), it usually goes a little something like this:   
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Ok, lets see. Where do I start? It’s been a busy week.&nbsp;&nbsp;   First of all, this was the weekend of the Belle Fair. In a small town, the entire world nearly comes to a dead stop during the days of the Fair. Thursday evening was the parade, so we had to take off early in order to pick up Sierra from the daycare. Both of our sitter’s kids were on a float, so she closed a little early.   Sierra did wonderfully through the parade. Although even she made a nasty face when the high school band went through. I swear, those kids play worse every year. When I was in band, we had to do it right or not at all. Hell, they didn’t even have to march! They rode on a hay wagon! I’m a little bitter. As Michelle will recall, we even marched one year during the parade in the pouring rain! I had to stop periodically and dump out my saxophone. We were also expected to try to memorize the music. Now these little pussies are riding on a float and have sheet music in front of them. Frankly, from the way they sounded, I’m not sure if they were all playing the same music.   Friday was Sierra’s six month checkup. She now weighs 15 pounds and 8 ounces. She’s where she should be on size and development. Rusty and I have been trying to tell the pediatrician for a couple months that she has allergies. Finally she’s old enough to take infant Zyrtec, so she’s now taking that. Also, she has been rolling from her back to her belly for over a month, but wouldn’t roll from her belly to her back. We asked Dr. Voss about it, and she just laughed. It’s a lot harder to roll back to belly, so there’s no reason that she shouldn’t have been doing the reverse, except that she didn’t want to. The following day, Sierra rolled from her belly to her back for the first time. Apparently Dr. Voss blew her cover.   Friday and Saturday nights I went up to the fairgrounds. The same stuff as usual. The fair smells are always what get me. It’s a mixture of exhaust from the rides, body odor, funnel cakes and fish sandwiches. In combination it’s not so bad, but very distinct. My daughter came home with a gigantic stuffed blue dog, which her grandpa (my dad) couldn’t resist winning her. Always interesting that I get to see all they people I spend the rest of the year avoiding. This year, however, I saw few people that I know. Belle only has a population of about 1500 people, and it’s amazing to me how many of them I don’t know. When I was growing up, everybody knew everybody else. Maybe it’s just because I moved away for a few years, and because I don’t have any kids in school yet.   Anyway, Sunday I napped and cleaned. Rusty tried to kill the lawn mower, but fortunately he and Dad were able to fix it. Shanna, my cousin stopped by for a while. Yesterday, I stayed home with a stomach flu-like substance. SO much fun.   Isn’t my life exciting? Doesn’t it just make you want to BE me? Don’t even try to deny it.&nbsp; I can feel the envy.  
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        In among all the other craziness, Sara came to visit over the weekend! I hadn’t seen the other half of my brain since November 2001. I took her to the fair, which I’m sure seemed like the biggest redneck fest she had ever seen. She was even lucky enough to be there the night of the tractor pull! (We avoided the tractor pull.) We walked the fairgrounds and lost our asses at bingo...damned old ladies. It was a nice, but busy weekend. Hopefully we haven’t completely scared her off, and she’ll come back again.        
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I must publicly declare my envy of Michelle's hard work.  I opened up my e-mail this morning to find a picture of Michelle and a coworker on the beach.  Uh-huh....  Nothing was really written to go along with it, but nothing was needed.    I was thinking that if there had been something to go along with it, that it would have needed a translator.  I think it would have gone something like this:    Dear Friends (unlucky wenches),  We've been working so hard out here in California.  (Recovering from hangovers.)  This has been a great conference (health spa).  I've learned so much (gotten so many pedicures) while I've been here!  I've also made some very important business contacts (hairstylists) and met so many nice people (ladies night at the strip club).  Attached is a picture of myself and a coworker relaxing in our down time.  (It's on the beach!  Ha!  Can you people hear my evil laugh?!?!?)  She and I are looking very forward to our next business trip.  (Drying out at Betty Ford.)  Right now I have to get back to work (tanning)!  Love,  Chelle (The Bitch Who's on the Beach While You're Not!)   It's just a rough translation...but Chelle knows how much I love still love her.  Even if she does come back all tan.    That reminds me.  Gotta remember to put some aloe on my forehead.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sierra speaks!  Well, sorta.  "Dada!"  It's very cute, and obvious that she knows what she's saying.  Needless to say, her daddy thinks it's the greatest thing he's ever heard.  Meanwhile, I'm sneaking her off in the other room saying "Momma."  Tonight I did that while I was giving her a bath.  She looked at me and says, "Dada."  Hmmmm....  By the way, Rusty says hi to those who know him...or know infamous stories about him.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I survived the weekend.  Well, I have almost survived the weekend.  It's Sunday night.  It's almost bedtime, but the weekend isn't officially over yet.  I suppose that something profound could happen within the next hour.  Given how exhausted I am, I don't think that I would comprehend it anyway.  The family reunion was hot and uncomfortable...and the temperature was bad too.  A few dirty looks were there to be had between family members who have barely spoken in years.  That's always a lot of fun to observe.  My dad is one of five kids.  One of his siblings has been a bit isolated from the other four since my grandma died in 1999.  There's always tension when that one's around.  I apparently missed some sort of to-do about my cousin's daughters referring to their aunt as Mommy.  (I always miss the good stuff!)  Something about spending more time with her than their mother. Otherwise, I think it was fairly uneventful.  I ate dinner with one of my younger cousins.  I am in total denial that he is as old as he is.    Actually, he's like 23.  Engaged.  I will always think of him as being a kid, which he is no longer.  This is the same boy that I called Apeface.  I would turn him upside down over the toilet at my grandma's house and threaten to flush him.    Saturday evening we spent with my parents.  Mom and I hung out while Rusty went with Dad to the driving range.  Rusty has taken up golf again.  He played a little when he was in high school, but never REALLY got into it.  Now he's doing it again, and he's into it this time.  Seems to really be enjoying himself.  I have to admit, golf is just not something I was able to take a great interest in.  Dad tried to teach me once.  Once was more than enough for me.  I took several swings and managed to dig a hole in the grass large enough to fit the entire population of Belle in.  I think the ball moved about 2 feet.  On the other hand, I drive a golf cart with great skill.  (As long as you ignore that time that I hit my cousin's truck with Dad's golf cart when I was driving it around in the driveway.)  Also, I do admit that when I was younger I took great joy in driving around the course and watching my dad play golf with some of his buddies.  I found it hilarious to watch a man wander around screaming, "I lost my ball!"  Always sounded like an intensely personal problem to me.  Today was a great day.  Angie and I had a Mom's Day Away.  She's got a membership to Lost Valley Resort.  We spent the day in the sun at the resort lake.  In my usual style, I came home with a small sunburn.  I was smarter this time, I at least used sunblock.  Still managed to burn my forehead and my nose.  Another wonderful look for me.  Don't hate me because I'm beautiful.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...especially when you wanted to be purple!  I created the prettiest little blog, all in purple.  However, when I tried to publish it, the backgrounds wouldn't work.  I don't understand it.  It worked on the preview.  So, I went with another green one.  Don't think I'm gonna leave it that way though.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday a woman came wandering into the office asking where her interview was.  Now, I work for a state agency that is spread over 4 buildings in Jefferson City.  She did not have the name of the woman who called her to set up the interview, nor the division it was with.  She had not written down WHERE the interview was to take place.  Maybe it's just me, but I think this would be important information.  Please!  You don't schedule an interview at Dillards and show up at Sears.  Sure, they're both at the mall and they both sell clothes, but that's where the similarity ends.   Worse yet, she was coming to interview for an   investigative   position.  Perhaps that's why I found the whole event mildly disturbing.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been hitting that damned thing all morning, and I'm STILL here.  By "here" I mean work, of course.    It's Friday and I couldn't be more overjoyed.  After all, Saturday comes  after Friday.  If you're reading this and thinking about what a silly, obvious statement that is, you are missing the profound meaning in those words.    Saturday implies a day of potential greatness.  No work. No hurrying around my living room at six o'clock in the morning franticly looking for the clip for Sierra's binky.  Most importantly, Saturday means no alarm.  I hate my alarm clock, and that obnoxious noise that it makes.  It's just as well to scream, "Hey bitch, get your ass out of bed!"  That would actually be friendlier.  This Saturday is somewhat marred by the fact that I will be attending yet another family reunion.  Fortunately, this will be the last one for quite a while.  Years, I hope.  Anyway, this is the Thompson family reunion.  For those of you who don't already know it, they're all nuts.  Well, not all...but most.  Now I'm going to spend a nice fun filled day with all of them.  I love my family, but sometimes they are enough to make you want to climb to the top of a water with a semi-automatic rifle.  Please, Lord, give me strength.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As you may have noticed, in a poor attempt at dressing up my blog and learning a little html, this page is getting a little remodel.  I promise to eventually stop screwing around and get it back to something that will be something approaching normal.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please note the addition of the link to my Yahoo photo album.  I hope to get several pictures uploaded soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, I think I have a new idea for a reality show.  They should have contestants repeatedly clean and prepare for house guests, survive family functions and clean up the aftermath.  Eliminations would happen naturally.  See who cracks first.    I have enjoyed the company of the few people who have come and stayed a couple days with us.  It's just exhausting.  We always stay up a lot later than usual...and I just don't have the stamina for that anymore without a good afternoon nap.    We had a good holiday.  Rusty's brother and his brother's significant other stayed Friday and Saturday night.  Good times.   Wish we saw them more often.  Usually only see them once every couple months.  Saturday night was the Reid family BBQ and fireworks bonanza.  My in-laws are a pretty small group, but they buy enough fireworks to blow up Rhode Island.  Every year my hubby comes home covered in ashes with scortched fingers.  I must tell you, there's nothing funnier than watching 3 adult men inspecting and lighting fireworks...and then running away like little girls.  Rusty swore that he was not running this year.  Thus, he came home covered in a little more ash than usual.    Sunday was yet another BBQ and more fireworks.  Our friends had a small gathering at their house.  I was truly disappointed in one thing.  I brought a bottle of wine with me, and had such high hopes.  Angie poured me a glass, but unfortunately with this damned cold I could barely taste it!  Ugh!  Doesn't that qualify as some form of alcohol abuse?    By Monday morning my house looked like the set of a war movie...after the war.  Clothes, dishes and baby toys everywhere.  There were even clothes on the kitchen counter.  I'm still not sure how they got there.  Anyway, my day was spent trying to reassemble the house into something livable and getting enough laundry done so that we wouldn't have to go to work naked today.  That last one was accomplished, thankfully.  I'm thinking that naked wouldn't pass the office dress code.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Like every other parent on the planet, I believe that I have given birth to the single cutest child ever.  Sierra confirmed it for me Saturday night.    I missed the better majority of the fireworks that Rusty’s family set off because I couldn’t stop watching Sierra.  She sat on the laps of either my mom or dad and watched with great interest. The fountains seemed to be her favorite.  She got all excited, threw her arms back, and squealed.  Meanwhile, the other kids around her were falling asleep.   Oh yeah, my kid is the cutest one.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have momentarily outsmarted the little buggers.  (Note that I'm disgustingly proud of this.)  I haven't seen any ants for a few days now.  We moved the cats' food to another room.  (Aren't we sneaky?)  I've also been trying to be better about leaving any dirty dishes on the cabinet. Maybe they've figured out that the food is gone.  Or, just maybe, they've gone to visit the family that moved in next to us.  Maybe they'll be nice enough to come back and let me know how many kids are living in that house.  I still haven't been able to figure it out.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love the van.  It rocks.  We have discovered, however, that there are a couple glitches.  We're having some problems with the headlights.  It has dayrunners, and instead of just the dayrunners, all the lights are coming on.  Playing with the switch and cursing at it doesn't seem to help.  Beyond that an actual mechanic will have to do something.  Fiddling with switches and cursing is the extent of my expertise.  Fortunately, we have a warranty.  The other thing is that I still don't have my own key yet.  It's one of those keys with a computer chip in it, so we have to get one from the dealer.  Goody.  I just love all these antitheft devices so no one can break into the van.  Unfortunately, if I were to lock my keys in it, I wouldn't be able to do it either.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is one of those days where I don't want to do anything for anybody.  I'm feeling a strange mixture of perkiness and sarcasm.  This is often a deadly combination.  It's probably a good thing that the boss isn't here today.  I'm sure he's off somewhere performing some sort of ritual sacrifice.  It's not that I think he's REALLY the devil, but at this point I wouldn't eliminate the possibility completely.    My goal today is to do as little as I can and look really busy.  I've been doing it for years, so what's one more day?   Slacking can really be an art.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, it's time for a little input on your behalf.  As so few people in this world ever get their dream job, I'm taking a little survey....  What do you wanna be when you grow up?  What's your dream job?   All responses posted in the the comments would be greatly appreciated.  I'm looking for ideas.  =) 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thursday night Sierra coughed and coughed...her daddy and I decided it was time for her to take that dreaded trip to the doctor. It's not that bad for her, but terribly painful for us. Neither of us are all that crazy about the pediatric clinic she goes to. The doctors are very nice, but the staff stinks.  Friday afternoon we made our way to the clinic. Of course, no matter how sick Sierra is she's always cute for the nurses. I swear that kid could have a limb just barely dangling and she'd still take a minute to charm the nurses. These people must think I'm crazy when I tell them that less than ten minutes before she was screaming her head off. Probably explains why they give me that look like I'm the dumbest woman on the planet. Anyway, her doctor was booked up, so we saw one of the others. After waiting more than an hour, he finally wanders into the room. Apparently Friday was some sort of dress-down day. Standing before us was a six foot tall man with highlighted sandy blonde hair, a hawiian shirt, stonewashed baggy jeans and sneakers. He was like a thirtysomething Doogie Howser. I don't remember my doctor ever looking like that. Actually, my doctor when I was a kid looked more like the Pillsbury Doughboy. Doogie gave us good news. No new ear infection. Just a virus of some sort.  Overall, the weekend wasn't too bad. Rusty played golf on Saturday. His cousin was in town over the weekend and we went to visit her. She was accompanied by her two kids, who were way older than they should be. When Rusty and I first started dating, her daughter was two. Still in diapers. Now she's twelve, and almost taller than me. Granted I'm only 5'2" or so, but it's still just wrong.  Yesterday was spent cleaning and doing laundry. We now have somewhere to sit, and no one had to go naked today, so I've done my job there. On the other hand, naked would be pretty comfy, don't you think? 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those of you who have had a similar experience, you'll appreciate this short story. I don't really have a point in telling it, just wanted to share it with someone. I've chosen all of you. Lucky you, right?  Yesterday afternoon while I was cleaning the house, I sat down for a minute to appreciate how good the house was starting to look. Ok, not really. I sat down because I convinced myself that after a cigarette I could work my way up to cleaning the toilet and bathroom sink. Anyway...while I was sitting on the couch a very unpleasing odor made its way toward my nose. I gazed over at the only thing it could have been. Sierra was in her swing giving me her innocent "I didn't do it" look. Dead giveaway.  I picked her up to discover that she was not only the cause for the odor, but it was runny and green. And it oozed out of her diaper, up her back and soaked though her sleeper onto the cover for her swing. Ick. I stripped her in the kitchen sink and hosed her off like she was covered in toxic waste. I love those Huggies disposable washcloths.  Thirty minutes later my child was bathed. Her sleeper and swing cover were soaking in the sink.  And me? Well, I was pooped.  ( Yes , I  know . It's a  cheap  pun. Admit it. You laughed.) 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Perhaps because it’s pouring today, perhaps not. Gloomy looking clouds are nothing new in Missouri’s capital, but I think it’s even gloomier today. It’s that post-election disappointment. The only thing redeeming is that Save a Horse, Ride a Cowboy is on the radio right now. I love that song! I’m desperately trying not to sing and dance in my chair.  Today I’m feeling so far apart from my fellow man...or at least my fellow registered voters. The amendment to ban gay marriage passed by 70 percent. I have no words, only that I am disheartened that we have allowed such blatant discrimination into our state constitution. Also, I’m deeply saddened for the people of Rockaway Beach who had hoped that casino gambling would revitalize their community. I’m on the No-Call list, but I didn’t have the heart to tell them when they called me about 20,000 times to ask for my support on election day. In good news, however, Bob Holden lost the Democratic nomination for governor. For those of you who are unaware, he is our current governor. State employees, including myself, aren’t very happy with him. He’s been screwing us like a dime store hooker on nickel night for the last four years. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My shower is now complete again. (I know how concerned you all are about my happiness while showering!) Our shower radio died a few weeks ago, and we finally found a replacement. Rusty picked it up the other night. (I love that man!) I missed washing my hair while listening to  urlLink Bob and Tom !  Sierra finally finished her antibiotics. I’m extremely happy. It was that pink liquid stuff, and the smell just makes me gag. I can handle the smell of poopy diapers, but that pink stuff is nauseating! Anyway, I think she’s starting to feel better.  Last night Rusty and I were watching David Letterman in bed. When he finally gave up and rolled over to go to sleep he handed me the remote. I wanted to see the end of the Bill Clinton interview, but joked that I’d probably just fall asleep with the remote. That was the last thing I remember. At about 1:30 I woke up, curled up to Rusty and the body pillow...with the remote in my hand.  Right now I have some clothing missing, and I’m finding it greatly disturbing. I have a couple pair of underwear that I cannot find. They’re not in my drawer, and they’re not in the laundry anywhere. This leaves a few options, and none of them are wonderful. First of all, I accidently threw them away the last time I cleaned out that drawer. That option isn’t very likely. Second, my house has been infested with some sort of underwear-stealing gnomes that use socks and underwear as a form of currency. I threw in the socks because Rusty has some socks missing. This alternative is somewhat likely. Third, and this one has happened before, thanks to the miracles of static electricity they are stuck in the leg or arm of one of our shirts or pants. In the meantime, I’ve gotta figure out where those damned gnomes could be hiding. I wonder if 409 will work on them too. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Betsy sent me some pictures from her outing with a few coworkers to watch practice rounds for the Senior Open, which was in St. Louis last week. I have added them to the photo album.  Tip: For those of you who don't know her, Betsy is the one in the vertically striped shirt with long hair! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Michelle sent me a nice little article this morning. If you want to know what this post is raving about, give this a read.   urlLink http://www.showmenews.com/2004/Aug/20040801News025.asp   The first paragraph is a study in the power of perception. Maybe it's just me, but after four years at a women's college, I think my perception of feminism is much different from that of the Vatican. Fortunately, I'm not Catholic. My perception of feminism has nothing to do with bluring the differences between men and women. It's about acknowledging the differences, celebrating womanhood, and recognizing that even as we are different from men it does not mean that we are incapable. We are not inferior, nor are we the weaker sex.  I shall not begin the debate over how good or bad the Catholic Church is. I feel that each person is entitled to their own belief system. However, there are a few things from the article that disturb me. For starters....  1. Clergymen, who by their own religion are not allowed to marry, and yet the spout off about the impotance of family. You want to profess the sanctity of marriage and the value of the family? Get married and have one.  2. The Pope's admiration of women and their talents. What talents are those exactly? I don't know why this statement got to me, but I found it kind of unsettling.  3. This paragraph:   It said women should not be stigmatized or penalized financially for wanting to be homemakers. It also said women "should be present in the world of work and... have access to positions of responsibility which allow them to inspire the politics of nations and to promote innovative solutions to economic and social problems."   Does this mean that women should be paid to stay home? Also, what's this thing about having access to positions of responsibility which would allow women to inspire the politics of nations? Are we to be decision makers or merely a muse?  4. Last, but certainly not least, was the final paragraph:   The Rev. Thomas Reese, a commentator on the Catholic Church, in an e-mailed statement noted that "although most American feminists would express their theology differently from the Vatican, on the practical level, they are on the same page (in terms of equality in education, politics, workplace) except on abortion and women priests."    If this statement is true (note that the statement is from a commentator, and not a member of the Church), the Catholic Church essentially agrees with feminists...unless it comes to making a decision about what to do with our own bodies or if we think we may be as capable as men at spreading the word of God.  Hmmm....   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I feel like one of those people who comes out of a coma to recognize the world around them, and then slips back in again. Last week Rusty and I both were just absolutely exhausted. I finally got some sleep over the weekend, and was feeling pretty good yesterday. This, however, was to be short lived. Last night Sierra didn't want to go to sleep. She finally crashed sometime just before midnight.   Last week I made a major change in my life. (Hold on to your seats for this one.) I converted. No, I didn't change religions. I have changed from My Yahoo to My MSN. Hey, don't laugh. A person's homepage is sacred! (The only thing more important is choice of desktop wallpaper.)  I think it was the pretty page options and MSN videos that did it.  The weekend was not quite as packed as usual. It was a good one. Friday night we went over to Angie & Will's house. Played poker for a while. Used poker chips, but no money ever changed hands. It's almost too bad. I was seriously kicking ass! Quite proud of myself. I love Texas Hold'em. After that we played Bullshit. If you have never played this game, just let me tell you that it goes on forever, but it's really fun. I do find it a challenge, because as you all know, I would never bullshit anyone.  =)      Saturday I went grocery shopping with my munchkin and my mommy. I'm not sure who was the most worn out when we got home. Wal-Mart had some baby clothes on clearance, so Mom and I each had to buy something. It's so hard not to.    Yesterday Rusty and I watched the last Lord of the Rings movie.  Actually, I've probably still got a few minutes to go on it, but Sierra decided that she wasn't happy for a few minutes.  So I figure I'll go back and watch the last little bit of it tonight or tomorrow night.  Anyway, after that we went to the pool for a while.  yet again, I am nicely scortched.  Although this hurts a lot less than the last couple times.  Someday I'll figure out that I'm a REALLY white girl.     The day of rest and relaxation was topped off with a visit to Bob's Frozen Custard and Angie & Will coming for dinner.  Angie taught me how to make her chicken, which is to die for.  Boneless chicken cooked in italian dressing and some other seasonings.  YUMMY!!!  As my dad would say, it's so good it'll make your tongue knock your brains out.  I shall now make it for other people and take credit for it's genius.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>