<Blog>


<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So consider yourself lucky.  Two entries in one day!    The person who thought of releasing old 80's television shows on DVD is a freaking genius.  I may never leave my home again.  The A-Team, The Dukes of Hazzard, Knight Rider, you have got to be kidding me!  All I need are the complete works of Seinfeld and I'll be set, that is until they release Silver Spoons.  What kind of life that kid had!  Gold chains, a hot step-mom, a train he could ride around his house, a bed that looked like a Ferrari...even a best friend that could dance just like Alfonso Ribeiro!  And with a nickname like "The Ricker" the world was his playground.  Ricky Schroeder.  Now he's all grown up and he prefers to be called Rick instead of Ricky.  What's up with all of these child stars thinking they can somehow be considered serious if they start going by a more sophisticated first name.  I saw a commercial the other day for a made-for-tv movie starring Joseph Lawrence.  I don't know about you, but where I come from his name is Joey and he says "Whoa!" all the time.  Gimme a break! (no pun intended)   
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink www.homestarrunner.com .  This is the funniest website I've ever seen in my entire life.  If you haven't heard of Homestar Runner, then you must have been living under a rock for the last year or so, but it's not too late to enjoy the antics of Homestar, Strong Bad, The Cheat and the rest of the gang.  Hysterical.  But heed my warning: don't jump head first into the Homestarmy (you'll get this later), but rather ease yourself into it a little at a time.  It's better that way.  Strong Bad's e-mails are my favorite, and after they're done, look around the page for something else you can click on to continue the story.  Two brothers in Atlanta came up with this in 1996, and after launching the website this thing has EXPLODED!  Good for them.  If someone would like to pay me large sums of money to crack wise about pop-culture and current events, please e-mail me at youare@stupid.com.  Until that time, I'm just glad  urlLink The Cheat is not dead . 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ronald Reagan passed away this weekend.  I hope we realize what a patriot this man truly was.  A greater American I don't know we've ever seen.  I would encourage you to pick up the book   urlLink Reagan: A Life in Letters  .  It's a great book that really gives you the inside view of a man that literally changed the world we live in today.  Does anyone else think it's a bit scary how W's tenure is shaping up in a very similar fashion as Reagans?  People thought Reagan was a cowboy, that he shot from the hip, that his foreign policy was dangerous, that he wasn't very smart or polished as a politician.  Militant Islam is our modern-day Communism, and I believe W will go down in history as being the president who played the key role in defeating this enemy.  Say a prayer for Nancy tonight, and let's win one for The Gipper.   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, this is my first blog.  Man I hope it goes well.  I've got such high hopes for this little bloggling.  I want to nourish it and comfort it and teach it right from modern liberalism and watch it grow into a bright, healthy blog!  Seriously, I'm just going to use this space to share my daily thoughts and ideas.  Let's begin the journal, shall we? 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So  The Day After Tomorrow  is doing quite well at the box office.  I've heard the effects are incredible, but that the premise of the film is quite ludicrous, unless you're a tree-hugging, left-wing wacko.  Apparently a new "ice age" takes over the globe, and somehow this is caused by man and the use of our fossil-fuel burning automobiles.  Hmmm...Here's my question: what on earth did the freaking cave-men do when they got slammed with the ice age the first time around?!?!  Do these greenies not know, or do they just choose not to acknowledge that the eruption of Mount St. Helens was responsible for the release of more greenhouse gases than every automobile ever manufactured???  God made the earth complete with processes that it uses to warm and cool itself.  Man is just not that significant when it comes to manipulating the earth's climate.  Although Rolling Stone would like you to believe this, my SUV has no bearing on whether or not Brazil has a hurricane or France has a heatwave.  It just doesn't.    Which leads me to an idea that a friend of mine had.  I think it's brilliant.  He thinks we should make a documentary about the myths surrounding the Greenhouse Effect.  Kind of like a truthful, conservative version of  Bowling for Columbine .  Working titles include  Debunking the Greenhouse Effect Myth ,  The Smoke and Mirrors Effect ,  The Greenhouse Myth: Exposed  and  Democrats Are Evil .  I think it would be fantastic to get footage of Al Gore and John Kerry riding around in their gas-guzzling limos and SUV's.  "Vice-President Gore, is this a V-8 you're riding around in?  Can't you hear Mother Earth crying Vice-President Gore?"  Hysterical. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>