<Blog>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another quick post to see if being an active Blogger will get me a GMAIL account.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If Comedy Central fires the retards working programming, hopefully someone will come to their senses and play this movie again. Let me say that this is bar none, the funniest movies EVER. I will be one of the first ones to make the purchase as soon as it comes out on DVD. You can find short clips at comedycentral.com. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you're a current user of Gmail, you may be given some free invitations to distribute. Where are my friends when i need them? I haven't posted anything in a few days and if I stay an active blogger, I might get an invite. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The hardest thing in the world is coming up with a starting point. So I’ll kick things off with the meaning of CyVault. I came up with this name for a computer company I started about 2 years ago. However, I had to put an end to this small endeavor because I deployed to Iraq. I really liked the name, so now it’s used as an ID, my little mark in the world. Now I need to figure out the purpose of this blog. Do I write about the things that happen every day, rants about things that piss me off, or goals and how I plan to attain them. I think a combination of all three will suit me just fine and since I made this blog for public view, I should do my part by breaking down my perception somewhat so you can better understand me.   TRUST: My first lesson in trust was when I was a little kid growing up in an environment where selling something to someone means everything. My father gave me five dollars once while in the scope and crosshairs of a salesman we’ll call “The Wave”. After my father walked away, the Wave approached me and said “If you give me the five dollars now, I will give you ten on payday.” At the age of eight, ten dollars is a lot of money by simply lending five to someone and getting twice as much back just a few days later. When payday arrived, I did too looking for the money that could buy all the things I thought about that week. I found the Wave and after asking for the money I quickly found out that two weeks earlier he bought me a Coke at some gas station and we were going to call it even. Sixteen years later, I can count the people that I halfway trust on one hand and the people I totally trust does not exists. Trust to me is something that is very hard to give to someone and is usually earned through actions over a very long period of time and I’m still leery because why would someone want me to trust them. Being burned many times and growing up in such an environment is the greatest thing that could have happened to me because it made me aware of people, the things they do, the things they say, and how they react to certain situations. For me the cycle of meeting someone goes exactly like this.   1)	I meet someone for the first time and I look for what I call red flags. A very strong feeling that I get whenever I meet someone and then hundreds of things start running through my mind and I break down every little thing they do so I can put this person into a category and like I said, I look at every fine detail.  2)	Now that the person is flagged, I make fences so the person can’t get close to me, at least not close enough to ask for money and I sit back and wait for that person to do something wrong. If this happens, and it does, I place that memory with the flag.    Just like a Rolodex, as soon as I see a person that has been flagged, I bring up an index card in my mind that list everything I gathered about this person and everything and anything that person has done, in my opinion, wrong. The whole process takes about a second and I can’t turn it off. Then you have the people that get what I call warning flags. I’ll be thinking about anything, like things I need to get done that day and out of the middle of fucking nowhere someone will walk by me and I get the sensation of heat across my face, then thoughts and feelings indicate that this person, who could look like an innocent school teacher, is walking around with either major skeletons in their closet or is planning something straight up fucking evil. There is no way to prove the accuracy of this ability, but that’s ok because it’s what I do and I think I’m right.  LOVE: What can I say about this word that hasn’t already been said? So I’ll break it down into list of things that I attach this dangerous word to.  1)	  Women: If she has the eyes, nose, lips, and hair, I’m looking her way. The body ranks second because I think about what will happen in the morning. Let’s say I hook up with a girl that has a 9 for a body and a 3 for the face. As I slowly open my eyes that next morning and look over, I don’t want to shit my boxers because there’s a fucking gremlin in my bed. So I give much slack for body as long as she’s trying to keep fit.  2)	  Boats: I don’t care too much for fishing; I just like the idea of escaping and traveling to the middle of nowhere. Nowhere is a place where people aren’t trying to tell me their problems and bull shit, assholes aren’t trying to sell me something I don’t need because for some reason they have this uncontrollable urge to take the paycheck I worked hard for, and lets not forget the very special people that like reading the serial number off my exhaust pipes because they ache to drive right up the ass of my car. It’s called a brake check bitch and I do enforce this policy.  3)	  Cigarettes: Since the age of five, I’ve always felt something was missing after eating a hearty meal. Ten years later I found my 2 best friends, the Marlboro Man and Joe Camel. Thanks guys for always being there and all of the good times. Now I’m the master of GPC’s due to the cost of name brand shit being more expensive then my monthly rent.  4)	  Fish: I’m allergic to cats and my son is allergic to dogs, so I keep fish. No barking in the middle of the night, no pissing on my favorite shirts, and no expensive visits to the Veterinarian. “Hello Sir, oh, so your dog needs a shot? That will be $6,000; do you want me to bill that to your Visa?” I don’t need shit like that haunting my ass.   There is a few more things on the list of things that I love, but don’t worry, that will come at a later date.                   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>