<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ronaldo shines as forecasted in my y'day blog. guess i can earn some quick money from betting, ;). c. ronaldo was the first one to strike, in y'day game btwn portugal & holland. nistelrooy was disappointing. figo, was simply superb. his gallop down the left flank, was a nightmare for the holland defenders. figo, deserved a goal and his ball kissed the left goalpost also. davids and deco were as usual great in the midfield. in fact, they were everywhere. when i think of these two, i always remember roberto carlos. the energy levels that these guys have are amazing. they run around for full 90 mins like power packed machines. its time for another forecast folks -final is going to be played btwn portugal & czech rep and figo and baros are the guys to watch for..  lastly i have to mention maniche's goal. it was a delight to watch. the holland goalie was struck with a thunderbolt. maniche standing at least 3 yards out of the box, and hitting it across from the left, to the top right side of the post, over the goalie. oh, mannn.. you get to see such sights in years. last, i remember, was when england' seaman was struck by brazil's ronaldinho..  enjoy, ;) 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      portugal vs. holland today. the players i would like to watch in action are - edgar davids, nistelrooy, ronaldo, figo. its going to be ronaldo's day. place ur bets on him, ;3
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      its england vs portugal as the first quarter final of euro 2004 on june 24th. will be a delight to watch two pretty aggressive forwards, rooney & ronaldo (not the brazilian. he is a new star from portugal who plays from Man U). owens, as always is a delight to watch, :) beckham? i don't like.
     

        
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      y'day bought one of my favorite books - GEB. i am so happy. now..,  i just have to read it once. ;) btw, dougals hofstadter's page is here, http://www.cogs.indiana.edu/people/homepages/hofstadter.html. did you know, he got a a pulitzer prize for GEB. chalo, jaane do..
     

        
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Blogger Help : What is BlogThis! ? 
     

        
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      want to have a gmail a/c desperately. searching for it.. but yahoo gave a relief.. its already increased my  storage limit to 1GB. whoaaaaa.. 
     

        
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today my blogging activity was to reply to these lines.. Reached there by clicking on 'Atlas Shrugged' link in my own profile, ;) -- “You're the color,  You're the movement and the spin... Fail with consequence,  Lose with eloquence, and smile... Never leave me paralyzed, love Leave me hypnotized, love.”  -The Notwist, "Consequence"  - Summer Smith, 1:17 PM  Comments:  hi. read the meaningful lines. i have this hobby of collecting snippets, trying to understand, drar analogies.. its like decoding some complex pattern. sending you couple of 'sufi' singer's lines. hope you like them, :)  --  h: naina tum hi bure ho, e: oh, my eyes, you are the sinner,  h: tumse bura na koye, e: you are the worse,  h: aap hi preet ki agan lagaye, e: you ignited the fire in the heart,  h: aap hi baitha roye.. e: and now are crying?  legend, h: is for hindi e: is the english transalation  # posted by Joshi : 5:29 AM 
     

        
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      lets talk about 'sufi'. i got introduced to this by listening to punjabi folk renderings by baba bulle shah. the turning point was when listened to 'ghoonghat ole na luk sajna..' by abida in her album 'baba bulle shah'..  i haven't listened / liked any other 'genre' of music after that.. ;)  listening to the 'raw' voice and music gives you high.. literally, but the real high comes when you start understanding the words coming out embedding 'hidden code' like short messages..  the real philosophy of sufi is: - there's only one love. and that is towards god. loving some one is like loving god. very simple, isn't it? difficult to digest.. ;) more later .. in next blog.  accha.. 
     

        
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      don't know where to start from? i am looking for god.. confused.. no one guides me. no one knows about about 'it'. there are claims.. of ppl meeting .. feeling .. can i also see it, meet it..  (i am calling god - 'it') 
     

        
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      today, got to listen to some of the pakistani folk songs by 'Maaii Bhaagii'. I just smiled by seeing the titles in the list at  . Two of them were, * Kharrii neem kai neechai * Chirimii ro Bilal saan piyaar which are the two most famous folk of my district jhunjhunu in rajasthan, india. these are so popular all over the rajasthan state. chirmii, supnno, hichki are some of the famous folk songs in this part of the sub continent.. also the other songs like * Bhenar'a munhja hujan'a hayaatii * Lorh manjhaan lurhndii achai were sung in the style typical of the haryana-vi 'raagni' in india.    so much so for the 'seperate' pakistan & india.. i want to unite india & pakistan, again.. any like minded ones out there? by the way, if people can divide states, why can't the same people unite?  love to all. just give it a thought..
     

        
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Dance, as though no one is watching, Love, as though you've never been hurt before, Sing, as though no one can hear you, Work, as though you don't need the money, Live, as though heaven is on earth.    - Rumi  some more inforamtion on rumi:  The name Mowlana Jalaluddin Rumi stands for Love and ecstatic flight into the infinite. Rumi is one of the great spiritual masters and poetical geniuses of mankind and was the founder of the Mawlawi Sufi order, a leading mystical brotherhood of Islam.   Rumi was born in Wakhsh (Tajikistan) under the administration of Balkh in 30 September 1207 to a family of learned theologians. Escaping the Mongol invasion and destruction, Rumi and his family traveled extensively in the Muslim lands, performed pilgrimage to Mecca and finally settled in Konya, Anatolia, then part of Seljuk Empire. When his father Bahaduddin Valad passed away, Rumi succeeded his father in 1231 as professor in religious sciences. Rumi 24 years old, was an already accomplished scholar in religious and positive sciences.   He was introduced into the mystical path by a wandering dervish, Shamsuddin of Tabriz. His love and his bereavement for the death of Shams found their expression in a surge of music, dance and lyric poems, `Divani Shamsi Tabrizi'. Rumi is the author of six volume didactic epic work, the `Mathnawi', called as the 'Koran in Persian' by Jami, and discourses, `Fihi ma Fihi', written to introduce his disciples into metaphysics.   If there is any general idea underlying Rumi's poetry, it is the absolute love of God. His influence on thought, literature and all forms of aesthetic expression in the world of Islam cannot be overrated.   Rumi died on December 17, 1273.  courtesy: http://www.khamush.com/life.html 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      arun joshi's home page is here: http://www.geocities.com/joshipilani  his blogs are here: http://j0shi.blogspot.com
     

        
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      now this IS some news, folks.. i think the pupose of my blog yatra is over today, ;). tried, 'arun joshi pilani' as a search string on google, and lo.. my blog profile was the first link. btw, 'arun joshi' is a famous indian novelist who writes in english.   i have to beat this guy in the google listings at least, if not by the literary contributions he have made to the society, ;). from now onwards, i will be a bit more serious in my postings. this means, i will 'copy & paste' only class A material..  love to all. j0shi.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      whenever the pilani word slips out of my tongue, somebody definitely shoots the question - is it the same 'pilani' as in 'BITS Pilani'   and i have to say yes. then along, i have to clarify that i just live in pilani. my father works there in CEERI..Pilani  yeah 'Pilani' same as in 'BITS Pilani', :# 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Reached Pune!! navi peth. pune is cool. lots of green  everywhere, and the weather is pleasant. hope it rains today, ;)  chalo then, bye.
     

        
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      found this on the j krishnamurti site, http://www.jkrishnamurti.org/ i first found his reference in the book 'The Tao of Physics'. it seems he still holds a solid following amongst the people down south of india. this is a cut & paste done from the above site on him,  ~ Beyond all experiencing ~  Understanding of the self requires a great deal of intelligence, a great deal of watchfulness, alertness, watching ceaselessly, so that it does not slip away. I who am very earnest, want to dissolve the self. When I say that, I know it is possible to dissolve the self. Please be patient. The moment I say "I want to dissolve this", and in the process I follow for the dissolution of that, there is the experiencing of the self; and so, the self is strengthened. So, how is it possible for the self not to experience? One can see that creation is not at all the experience of the self. Creation is when the self is not there, because creation is not intellectual, is not of the mind, is not self-projected, is something beyond all experiencing, as we know it. Is it possible for the mind to be quite still, in a state of nonrecognition, which is, non-experiencing, to be in a state in which creation can take place -which means, when the self is not there, when the self is absent? Am I making myself clear or not? ...The problem is this, is it not? Any movement of the mind, positive or negative, is an experience which actually strengthens the `me'. Is it possible for the mind not to recognize? That can only take place when there is complete silence, but not the silence which is an experience of the self and which therefore strengthens the self.         
     

        
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      felt bad about it. portugal lost. TOI put a heading  'it was all greek for portugal'. feeling sad for figo. i think the blame goes on really to portugal's midfielders. they were not able to penetrate. deco & rui costa (though he didn't got that much time also) were just not able to hold to the ball. but still my heart is with scolari & portugal. the kind of football portugal, brazil, mexico, senegal, holland play is unmatched. may be ppl have forgotten, that we play sports for only one goal - 'entertainment'  ;)
     

        
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      heard alam lohar's song:  dil wala dukhda nahin kisse nu sunaida, aap dian galaan whichon, aape muk jaayida..  padh padh namajan, gaffar nu manaida, de de nazraanen sarkar nu manaida, tu ki jaanen kiven russe yaar nu manaida.. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      greece vs. czech was the most boring match of all the euro matches. the greeks deservedly, got a goal. leave, pavel nedved, all other players were crap. and, yes koller doesn't deserve to be a football player, leave alone having him play in the semi final. his body language was similar to that of a indian or pakistani cricketer who have fixed 'it', beforehand.  ;), enjoy.
     

        
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      going to watch 'greece vs. czech rep' tonight @ 0015 IST. i will cheer for the czechs. this will be the first time i will be seeing 'baros' play.. will put a blog on his performance tomm. chalo then, leaving now.. 
     

        
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      today is special. just did a google on 'arun joshi' and lo.. i was there on the the 6th link. happy i am, :) bye..
     

        
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      bahadur shah zafar, the last mughal emperor of india (1775-1862) was a great poet too. heard a gazal written by him in abidas' voice - 'yaar tha, gulzar tha'. it immediately became my yahoo status mesg of the june month. can have more on him, here http://www.urdupoetry.com/zafar.html
     

        
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      olympics onyl 8 days away. waiting eagerly. the schedule is here,  http://www.athens2004.com
     

        
</post>


<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      with love to sareen, :) a new couplet (from the sindhi version of Mainda Ishq vi Tu)  deen dharam din, maiku lodd na kaain, ik darsan yaar ki loddaan.. kafarr - kafarr har koi aakhe tab hargiz moonh naa modaan..  mareen bhaaven jhidkiin, tedaa daaman moor na chordaan.. gulam faridaan, o tut vanne sab passon, tab hik yaar kannon na todaan..   Menda Ishq vii Tuun, Menda Yarr vii Tuun, Menda Deen vii Tuun, Imaan vii Tuun, Menda Jeesm vii Tuun...   adding more.. joshi.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      found a  cool site today,  http://www.sufimusic.org  feels great to know that there are people there, who listen to the *real* music, ;) this site is heavy with stuff. lots of abida audio's  hit the url & enjoy, love..
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      this blog is been created for the sole purpose of discussing abida parveen's singing magic. i will request all other good souls also to come along .. and we can make this a nice & cosy place to discuss her albums, lyrics, and all other stuff..   every one's invited.. love, joshi.
     

        
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      u r free to update these lyrics..  alaap> thaangar kanu, thoongarr changa.. jhan which laggan kutte, tain kanu utte  moollan kanu, kukkad changa.. jeda yaar jagaye sutte, tain kanu utte ..  bhaanbhan utte kalaal changa.. jeda khade piyave chukke, tain kanu utte..  ve miyaan bulleya, tu sohe-niind karandeyan aye, saari raat bhonkde kutte, tain kanu utte..  ishq na dard maut kanu, tonne sooli chadna pai jaave.. nach nach ke yaar mana lena, bhavin kanjari banana pai jaave..  log panj namajaan padhde, peeche saara din vele firde.. aashiq dum dum de vich padhde, bhaaven teg tale sir lah jaave.. ishq na dard maut kanu-2, tonne sooli chadna pai jaave..  namaaj padhannn, kam zanana atte roja sarfarotii.. unchiiyaan baanga oh dende, niyat jinnan di khoti.. makke-madine ohii jande, jede honde kamm de totii.. veh miyaan bulleyah..  jeh ho gayi huk yaar millan di, te rakh saaf under di kothi.. panj vele log aashiq har vele, log masiti aashig kadmaan viich aashif waqt kazaa nahin karde, bhaaven kaafar bananna pai jaave.. nach nach ke yaar mana lena, bhavin kanjari banana pai jaave.. ishq.. 
     

        
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      mann mann mann taan peer manvaan.. mulla kaullon tavij likhavan sad sad 'joshi' palaan paavan.. main kardeen sawal hazaran.. main ro ro vaat niharan.. kaddi savaln morr muharaan.. 
     

        
</post>


</Blog>