<Blog>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Been quite for a few days. Went on a trip to Sellafield to see some stuff. Quite good. Got pretty pissed for other journos when we got to our hotal at 9.30pm but we were delayed by 2h45m on the way back and that meant I missed my chance to vote.  The girlfriend was in a strop with me when I got back. Probably just because she was tired - I hadn't done ANYTHING! I reckon its because she's an only child. If things aren't going her way she can't help herself but to take it out on whoever's closest.  She did more of that the next day (Friday). We were both late in from work and were chatting for a bit when I got in. Almost in the middle of a conversation she said, "Aren't you going to ask me how my day was?" After staring straight at her for a moment I said, "How was your day, darling?" And then we weren't really talking for the rest of the day.   We took a train over to Putney and on the way our conversation died out. I knew she wanted me to finally ask her but I was just like, no way. What she said to me earlier was just plain rude, confrontational and unprovoked so I'll be damned if I'll jump through silly hoops to be what her image of an ideal boyfriend is. Fucking bullshit! If you've got something on your mind, then tell me but don't play little 'how much do you love me' games. She always wants me to make 'the effort' WTF!  /There's more but I'll fill it in another day... 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dozed and slept almost all evening yesterday. The girlfriend tried to make me feel guilty about not buying milk on the way home but it didn't work because I fell asleep. After I went out and bought it and made her a cup of tea, obviously.  Milk's a political issue in our house. When we need it, it's my job to remember and I suffer a moody-attack if I don't pre-empt the situation. Though, frankly, I don't give a shit if we run out - we can easily pop down the offie and get more. But it's not organic!  So sleepy, though. I was whacked after trying to get the stereo my brother gave me to go in the car. For some reason I couldn't get the old one out. I'll sort it out one day.  Need to get the car in a garage, becuase the bonnet-popping mechanism is shagged and I can't seem to sort it out. If it's going in the garage I may as well get them to fit the stereo and the new clocks too...  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, managed to have a good one on Sunday. A couple of mates came over (SO cool, and SO successful) and we went to a nice pub, had a bite to eat, went back to the flat and swapped a bit of software, went out to get some noodles. Nice.  Then our mates bugged off and we went home. Tried to watch KPAX but the tape was knackered so continued the werewolf theme with  An American Werewolf in London . Featuring, of course top posh totty of all time, Jenny Agutter.         Jenny Agutter  Uuuuhhhh...
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes there is. And it seems to come up every time we go out in Wimbledon. This was a long story though. I'd gone over to see my mum and dad (although mum wasn't there) while the girlfriend was down the road at her grandad's. I cleaned the car and got stickers off it and all that sort of thing with dad on the drive (very pleasing) while she was with her Da.  After that, I was late to pick her up and she was quiet - complaining about me waking her up with kisses in the morning. I'd been awake all that time (10am-6pm) and wasn't really tired! Anyway. We got back to the flat and she warmed up some dinner while I found out more details of the plan for the night - a comedy club in Dulwich.  Once I'd got the details and agreed to drive there to save time she reveals that she doesn't want to go: "If you arrive late at comedy you always get the piss taken out of you". You could always hang out in the bar until the interval or something but really it was just an excuse not to go - but a bit embarrassing for me, 'cos I had to text our friends and say "Sorry, not coming now. Running too late." Whether or not I wanted to go had nothing to do with the decision.   A few minutes later, when our mate rang up to ask what was going on, she perked right up and implied she might have wanted to go when she learnt that the comedy club was only our first stop before a bar or two. Well, I thought that if you were late for comedy "you always had the piss taken out of you" whether you're going to the pub afterwards or not.  Oh, also, in the car on the way home, some moose driving a giant car tried to boost past us up the inside into a gap that simply wasn't there. I held firm and she slammed on the brakes but Liv shouted "Fucking hell!" I think she opened her eyes to see a car about one inch away from her face. I tend to get the blame for these things... Mind you, sometimes, in fact often, I am badboying it. But hey, I don't try to overtake people if it means someone has to slam on the brakes!  What else... Oh yeah, getting off the tram, after talking about hoovers. She says, "I wonder who thought of the name Hoover?" and I go "Mr Hoover. It was his name!" And flash a big smile, in an attempt to soften the gag.  It didn't work, she got in a mood that lasted all the way home and into bed. Ah, fuck it.  Get over it darling! You said something daft and got picked up on it. I wasn't being mean - anyone would've said the same thing. If one of her mates had said it she'd have rolled with it and kept laughing and joking. It's just that I have a special ability to piss her off at the moment.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Feel a bit bad this morning. Spent an hour or so dozing and holding onto the girlfriend - love cuddling her, but most of the time I was thinking about another girl, my fancy woman.  Now, I've never done any cheating but it's like this: Me and the girlfriend aren't going to last forever, we both know that. And I'm aware she's getting increasingly fed up with me. One day, we're going to call it quits. Personally, I think we should do it amicably and in advance of the Final Argument.  But I met a really exciting girl a couple of years back. She really sent a bolt of lightning through me with every smile. I've managed to keep in contact (barely) with her.  I just keep imagining her. She's been cropping up in my dreams, too, which probably isn't a good sign of health. Anyway, I really want a date with her but we're both connected to others at the moment... We'll have to see... But I've really got good feelings about her - I think she's one of the best - I can even image soppy things in a soppy future with her. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hmmm, dunno what to say to start things off.  Had a bonkers dream last night: I was taking Angel Dust with a bloke from my university course and we were kinda skating (without skates) all over a strange urban environment. It was like cyberspace, we went into buildings which were almost infinitely large and represented space that businesses could set up in.   It all had something to do with GameCube, because it was sadly empty, although a couple of companies had strange interfaces installed there.  Before long I was searching for something. Then I was with my family at a railway station. I was a werewolf on the verge of change and I knew I was about to eat someone (seen Val Helsing and Ginger Snaps recently!) and my mum was urging me to escape, which I think I did. But maybe I bit a few people on the way. I kinda wanted to go ape-shit!  Then my car cropped up, and I made breakfast out of sherbert which stuck together into a wierd sheet of goop.  Then I woke up. How boring for you to read!  ---  The drive to work was stupid. Stuck behind a garbage truck. What the fudge was it doing on the road at 8.55am? They're supposed to piss you off by waking you up, not making you late. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>