<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gavin plays groucho while his sister Alliyah wonders who this stranger is.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      On our way back from a fishing trip I saw something that made me do a double-take.  Some things just defy reason or explaination.  We passed a semi on the freeway, and attached to the left rear mud flap, was a rubber chicken. I'm a person that likes to know....why? Now that's going to bug me.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So as not to encourage unacceptable behavior, I   did'nt   take a picture of Gavin emptying his little sister's bottle....one...drop....at..a...time,   over her head.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My grandson, Gavin, keeps me on my toes. He's always asking questions I'm not sure how to answer.  Today he wanted to know if horses burp. Guess I'll have to do some research.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When we were growing up, my dad used to come up with some crazy things to keep us intertained and mostly to exercise our brains.  He invented the "Ong" language. You spell out a word by adding an "ong" to the end of each letter and pronouncing the vowel. For example:  The word LOVE would be....Long O Vong E. It's a little tricky at first, but it's kinda fun. Try it for yourself.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gavin, my 3 1/2 year old grandson, likes mulberries too.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I couldn't help but crack up when Pogo, our pomeranian, smiled at me with purple lips and tongue.  We irrigate our back yard once a week.  We have a mulberry tree that is dropping loads of ripe fruit. The berries float.  Pogo spent 1/2 an hour wading around eating berries off the surface.  By the time he was full, his little mouth was oddly discolored. (The picture was taken later, so he's not purple here) Later in the season he munches on cherries, apricots and pears.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, you talked me into it.  I started a blog. Now my life will be an open book. As soon as something exciting enough to share happens, you will be the first to know about it.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A storm blew through last night. We watched as the sky grew black.&nbsp; Lightning flashed and thunder cracked and rolled across the valley. Then the rain poured down filling the air with a fresh clean smell. The sun dipped down below the storm clouds and created a double rainbow against a light orange sky.&nbsp; Lightning spread through the clouds and the rainbow.&nbsp; It was incredible.&nbsp; Gavin watched and cheered, "That was a good one!" One part of the sky was clearing up and had a few light whispy clouds.&nbsp; The lightning&nbsp;flashed&nbsp;again and Gavin said, "Look, the lighning blew up the clouds."  &nbsp; If you couldn't tell, I just love summer storms.&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gavin was in the car with me the other day when we drove by a couple horses in a pasture.  The owners had not removed the manure, but had scooped it into a 5 foot pile.  Gavin saw it and exclaimed, "Wow, look at all that.  When I get big I can poop like a horse."    I remember when Kristina, Gavin's mom and my oldest daughter, was little.  She wanted to be a garbage truck driver then decided she would rather ride dolphins. She never realized her childhood dreams, but perhaps her son can someday achieve his goal and enter and win a contest.  I have no doubt that he will at least be able to join the ranks of most adult men and be able to  fart  like one.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>