<Blog>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ive decided to write a novel, now I dont know what of or what type either, but I have decided. A topic that just popped into my head. Smart people, what goes on in theres? is it tones of complicated math like in the cartoons, or there somthing else. Do they think like we do, on how life really isn't treating them fairly or somthing. How they are too fat or have a poor social life. I guess people dont see that there are people that are seen as nerds and geeks that actually the same IQ as you do, but just work very hard. Or maybe their head is filled with compicated math I dont really know, im not smart...    (Jake Wright -> I.Q.=127 and yet im still stupid)
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever noticed how fate seemes to get in the way most of the time? I mean really it is always changing things from how they should look, to a completly different situation! I would have to say that the person in charge, of fate that is, should be shot serveral times.  I though fate was supose to help me, not fuck up my life. It is getting really anoying. Now I have to spend the weekend arguing with my cousins, HOT FUN! o well I guess I just have to deal with it.
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just dont know what to talk about...
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont take these stupid tests, but this one was good, I liked it so for god sakes dont make fun of me for most of the answers i know there too romantic, i guess thats how i think  layers   LAYER ONE: Name: Jake Vernon Wright Birth date: 1/2/88 Birthplace: Toronto general, Toronto, Ontario Current Location: King City(very very small town), Ontario Eye Color: Light blue Hair Color: dark brown (but its dyed alittle) Height: 6'0" Righty or Lefty: Righty Zodiac Sign: Aquarius – the lazy  LAYER TWO: Your heritage: Scottish, English, Canadian! The shoes you wore today: I wear many shoes, HEY Y DO YOU CARE, normally I ware a size 10.5 airwalk Your fears: being lonely, gay men that hit on straight ones, and failing Your perfect pizza: I like all pizza Goal you'd like to achieve: pass accounting (haven’t got report card back yet)  LAYER THREE: Most used phrase on AIM: nice guys finish last (the saying is so true) Your best physical feature: coming from me, that’s hard I would say… eyes? Your bedtime: Varies Your most missed memory: Ashley, "I’m sorry, where ever you are now"  LAYER FOUR: Pepsi or Coke: Coke McDonald's or Burger King: McDonald’s, only because I rarely have the chance for burger king Single or group dates: Group dates can be good, but I would say single is better Adidas or Nike: I don’t wear either (but Nike I like their ad campaign) Lipton Ice Tea or Nestea: Nestea Cappuccino or coffee: TEA!  LAYER FIVE: Smoke: I don’t, don’t see what the appeal is Cuss: I do, but only when needed, rarely at home Singing: singer for a band Take a shower everyday: yea, don’t you feel greasy if you dont Do you think you've been in love: coming from me, yea Want to go to college: or university, yea Like(d) high school: the school part is not fun, but I like being around my friends yea so it balances out. Want to get married: no comment (don’t know right now) Believe in yourself: when it counts yes Get motion sickness: reading or playing(choke yes I play game boy) game-boy in the car Think you're attractive: sure could be fun Think you're a health freak: not at all Get along with your parent(s): I would say very well, unless school and computer are involved Play an instrument: Guitar(badly) and drums (better, but still badly) Have a crush(es): ha ha a few to many  LAYER SIX: In the past month... Drank alcohol: nope Smoked: nata Done a drug: sorry Made Out: ...yeai cant lie about that Gone on a date: yarg no Gone to the mall: yea Eaten an entire box of Oreos: eaten a few, but a whole box, that’s like major stomach cramps. Eaten sushi: nope. Been on stage: not a real stage, but in front of people making a total ass of my self, trying to be funny. Yes Been dumped: so lonely I almost wish I had been (ain’t that pathetic) Gone Skating: yea, not for long though I fell off the board then stopped Made homemade cookies: nope Gone skinny dipping: nah Dyed your hair: no it has dye in it (small amount of dye) in it already Stolen anything: nah, that ain’t my thing I like to spend money  LAYER SEVEN: Ever... Played a game that required removal of clothing: yes, but I won every time, I don’t know why, lucky me If so, was it mixed company: yea good thing Been trashed or extremely intoxicated: once I think, and that was enough Been caught "doing something": if "doing something" means sex or making our, then not caught (but no sex) Been called a tease: uh, hunh. NO Shoplifted: This question came up before, why would my answer change… NO Changed who you were to fit in: no, maybe clothes  LAYER EIGHT: Age you hope to be married: 28-38 (I don’t really know I’m 16 gimme a break) Numbers and Names of Children: 18 o wait… you fool NO KIDS Describe your Dream wedding: Out doors, with falling apple blossom all around. A tradition wedding, with all my family and friends. Now when I say traditional I mean tucks with a bow tie, kilt and sporran. Laugh if you must, but it is heritage. My bride (who I don’t know oddly enough) would be dressed in a beautiful dress that would be made entirely of silk. We will meet in an alter where the priest will read our vows, he must have a either English or Scottish accent, then the wonderful kiss. After that there will be a huge after party. (Money is no factor right?) And that’s my sappy romantic ideal How do you want to die: at the age of 101 I will jump out of a plane over the 68,000 feet over the city of new York with no parachute. Where you want to go to college: A good one, probably in Canada What country/place would you most like to visit: Europe  LAYER NINE: In a guy/girl.... Best eye color?: Amber (like a friend of mines eye colour) Best hair color?: any thing but red (yikes) Short or long hair: I like hair that is short, but not shorter then mine, and not curly Tall or short: 3 inches shorter then me, I don’t want to date an amazon… Best weight: Thin, but not for me, for herself, and healthy thin Best articles of clothing: pants, skirt? Tank top with sweatshirt that zips at the front, which is open with a hood, but I don’t know… Best first date location: I would like to take her some where romantic, but probably the movies… sad but true Best first kiss location: there are a few places 1just before it starts to snow in the middle of a park at night 2In front of a huge fountain, in a town square 3Just as the sun sets, on the beach 4At night under the stars at her door step etc… Man… I really am lonely  LAYER TEN: Number of CDs that I own: good question Number of piercings:  none (sorry but no) Number of tattoos: not now, but if I were it would be a Canadian flag, or maple leaf behind my left shoulder Number of scars on my body: good question, biggest is either on my ankle or my knee, nope my ankle If I were a month I would be: February, my b-day If I were a day of the week I would be: DUH Friday night If I were a planet I would be: Earth -» I like earth If I were a sea animal I would be: a shark If I were a direction I would be: 43.6 degrees north If I were relaxing on a piece of furniture I would be: lying down in my friends basement on her couch with my head or her lap If I were a liquid I would be: plasma in the blood stream, that stuff is crazy If I were a stone, I would be: probably a topaz, the reflection of a topaz on the ceiling is awesome If I were a bird, I would be: Hawk because their strength, but utter beauty If I were a flower/plant, I would be: a white rose, (its one of the only flowers I know) If I were a kind of weather, I would be: a light snow If I were a mythical creature, I would be: a truthful politician If I were a musical instrument, I would be: A guitar because it can be used to rock out, or to play beautiful classical music, because of the diversity.  If I were an animal, I would be: One of the big cats, probably a Lynx If I were a color, I would be: I couldn’t be just one colour it would be impossible. If I were an emotion, I would be: laughter, or possible love I don’t know If I were a fruit, I would be: an orange, or maybe a lemon that looks like an orange If I were a car, I would be: i dont own a car, i wouldn't know, one with 4 weels If I were a song, I would be: oh man just one… come on no way (river below – Billy talent, I hate the band love the song) If I were a place, I would be: An undiscovered island (I think I mean something by that don’t you?) If I were a taste, I would be: something you don’t forget If I were a scent, I would be: something you don’t forget If I were a cartoon character I would be: one of my own =P If I were a shape I would be: a shape of the 8th dimension If I were a number I would be: 17 (number from hockey, and it stuck, probably my fave)  And now that we are at the end, you know way to much about me, and you are going to use it against me. Grrreeeaaattt… sigh 
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After a long and painful time I am back. I was a total fool, and spelt my sign in name wrong 37 times (I counted). But an update on my life, I am still single, no surprise. I have been to 5 parties in the last 3 weeks, and didn't get drunk at any of them I am pleased to say, probably because I don't want to, but yea. I’m guessing that’s the 4-1-1 for now, but when I get any other things, be sure to stay tuned!  Foot note I’m terribly sorry you’re so beautiful (You know who you are) 
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah yes school, the place of learning. Some times learning is just too damn hard to cope with. I mean we should be able to pick which courses we want from the beginning. I mean really why did I have to put of with French for 10 damn years, just think how many wasted hours that is. Another thing I’m going to rant about is the exam. Yes the exam, the destroyer of marks. Have you ever noticed that almost every person that writes an exam does poorly on it? Any ways, I know school is essential to our futures, but come on. Could it be any harder to keep up? First the cut funding, Now they cut of my last year of schooling!?! I just don’t get it…  Well I’m sick of ranting, but you all know I’m right 
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got a problem? It seems that i am asking that question alot more often, and its starting to bug me. I guess I either like trying to help people or it makes me feel better knowing that my life isn't as bad as it seems. Either way i listen to alot of peoples problems, and I think im getting good with advice. Any ways. If u need some one to talk to, thats me, I guess. I make a good sholder to cry on.   Orange-Nose@hotmail.com  I.e. Dont listen to depressing music
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All I can say is the beginning is now, and the end is later. Now to get down to business, Nice Guys Finish last. It’s so true you know the question is why is it? Why do those dick weeds get everything the girls while I’m stuck here with my hand (bad joke). You know in the last month I’ve been told by almost four chicks "men you’re a nice guy Jake, I hope we can be friends." Friends?! Aren’t we already friends?! I mean really come on. If I wanted to be just friend I would have said so… you’re stuck in this Awkward friendship, because you look at the girl and think "man how can I get out of this, I can’t have her"…   Now I must say that my life doesn’t revolve around girls. I enjoy listening to music and hanging out in my friend basement. Another friends who applies to the problem above. Starting to see my point? O well, she’s a great friend. FRIEND to say the most. Ah man life’s a bitch, and then come exams. I think the teachers just like to see us in pain, sweating away trying to write the damn things.  Any ways I really don’t know why I have to be a nice guy…  Nice Guys Finish last (Green Day)  Nice guys finish last You're running out of gas Your sympathy will get you left behind Sometimes you're at your best When you feel the worst  Do you feel washed up like piss going down the drain Pressure cooker pick my brain and tell me I'm insane I'm so fucking happy I could cry Every joke can have it's truth but now the joke's on you I never knew you're such a funny guy  Oh nice guys finish last When you are the outcast Don't pat yourself on the back You might break your spine Living on command  You're shaking lots of hands You're kissing up and bleeding all your trust Taking what you need Bite the hand that feeds You lose your memory and you got no shame  Pressure cooker pick my brain and tell me I'm insane I'm so fucking happy I could cry Every joke can have it's truth but now the joke's on you I never knew you're such a funny guy  Oh nice guys finish last When you are the outcast Don't pat yourself on the back You might break your spine  Oh nice guys finish last When you are the outcast Don't pat yourself on the back You might break your spine  mmmmm Oh nice guys finish last When you are the outcast Don't pat yourself on the back You might break your spine  Oh nice guys finish last When you are the outcast Don't pat yourself on the back You might break your spine...
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever been in a situation that you know that you want to ask this person out, but you just cant. It's a tough problem to beat, and there is no way around it. You have two options. 1) you could just keep your mouth shut and just live with it. This way you don't have to worry about rejection or anything, and the relationship will never change. BUT you also have to live with the fact that the relationship will never progress OR 2) You could ask, and it could work out.  BUT it could not work out, and now you're stuck with this awkward situation where you both know, and the friendship is never the same. its a gamble that all I can say  and I'm stuck in that situation now 
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay its my tenth post, lets all have a moment of silance      HAZAH!! yea well times move on, and things change like im in summer school, and it sux. Well the course dosent suck but I mean its summer school so. I could be like a sex training class and i still would be board. I HATE SUMMER SCHOOL. o well SPARE NEXT YEAR!!!! yea its late, well its not but it feels like it... and i gotta go to bed HAZAH!!
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has been a while since I posted, so here it goes... SUMMER SCHOOL SUX.. what else is there to say. I know im taking it so i can get a credit, but i also know IM TAKING SCHOOL DURRING THE SUMMER, GAH!!!! Fer god sake its boaring, I COULD BE SLEEPING. AND I NEED A HAIR CUT... even though that was out of context IT WAS NEEDED... IM really angery for some reason. hmmm. gotta go watch tv or kill somthing on XB.  Ok back and still pissed. I GOT PLAY STATION 2 FOR FREE, well im barrowing it from matt {thanx matt} sp yea... life is grand.... Going to dinner with Britney Tomarrow (friday) Cant wait... I REALLY CANT, i think im going to go into a coma till then... I SOUND HYPER  ok im done  ZEPPLIN RULES!!!!!!!!!!.....
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a story/poem I wrote today while I had nothing to do today, so if u hate it.. Dont bug me wit it, cuz i dont care. If you have some suggestions for what should hapen in the future, feel free to speak up, cuz i dont know where the story is going.   Red on black  Chapter 1  She always was the smartest, and the best looking, though she tried to hide it. I can remember, if I can remember correctly, she use to sit in the back of my math class, alone. She rarly spoke, and when she did it was only to answer a question or proving the teacher wrong. Hah she was quite an interesting girl.  When lunch came around she would always sit alone at the table near the window, drawing. She would wear her thick, beautiful redish-brown hair over her face, trying to hide it I guess, and I could never figure out why she did. If you could catch a glimpse of her face the first thing tha catches your attention is her eyes. Ho man she had probably the most beautiful eyes you have ever seen. Almost impossible to descripe, for hours on end I have tried to figure out what colour they really are but never have. They are like a golden green, but its not that simple. He skin is perfect, absolutly perfect, she has the right emount of colour, and yet still is not too dark, just.. wel perfect. Then her lips... When you see her lips you think of yours touching hers, clear right then and there. Always forming a small smile, like she has just been told a joke that isn't funny, but still smiles.  She truly is stuning
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I Ok was talking to Brittney and she told me to just talk about random shit so what ever... SO to bring to u speed it has been a WHILE since I have put finger to Key in the blog area.
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Chapter 3   As speedily as it had begun, she was gone. Sitting there looking like a fool with my tomato sandwich stuck to the side of my face. I got up and left.  Maybe I could catch up to her, where ever she was. I started to wonder around the school to try and find out where she had gotten to. Then I remembered her locker number. “216...” I said out loud as I turned and bolted in the opposite direction. 216 was on the other side of the school and I had to get going if I was going to get there before recess was over.  I took roughly 15 steps then it occured to me. Why was I trying to catch up to her? Why was I so focused on talking to her? Just as I had stopped to think, the bell rang and I was late for math... Again...  I made it to the class room around 10 minutes late for class. Great. Math was never my best subject. every one said so, and I knew it. To tell your the truth It wasn’t that I was bad at math, It was that I never really tried. Most of the time I just use to stare at my teacher, and undress her with my eyes. They realize how gross that Is and start to draw. But still.  I noticed that she was in her regular spot at the back of the room, drawing as usual. her hair over her eyes and face.  “miss Jaina, do you think that you can just draw in my course and expect to pass?” Every one turned and looked at the back. There were wispers, snickers. Im sure that she could feel every eye in the room burning into the top of her head. She slowly lifted it, pushing her short redish-brown hair back and just peered at the teacher. There was a long and painfully pause, then “I have the highest average in the class, and probably know more they every you, in this field. So we are at a dilemma, here. Should I keep drawing, and let you get on with your little lesson. Or do you want me to teach the class?” She replied. A smile slowly stretched across her face. All eyes flashed from Mrs. Willies to Jaina.  “GET OUT! NOW!” Mrs. Willies screeched Still smiling “Ok miss, if thats whats you want” With a little chuckle she grabbed her stuff and walked out the door, and I know that every eye was fixed on her as she gave a quick look back at the class as the door closed.  I sure as hell had to pick my jaw up off the desk...
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are these kids that are comming over, and I think they are going to kill me. They have been nick named "the devils children" and that is with good reason. The last time I was with them, they lit there house on fire, just for fun and guess who has to look after them; Yours truly. Yupers its going to be a HELL of a time (pun intended). AND THEY KICK ME OUT OF MY ROOM TO BOOT... Im going to lock myself in the basement, I truly am!
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I finished it here, it is    Chapter 2  I Can remember it like it was yesterday...  It was a cold december afternoon, and lunch had just started. I was late getting out of class, And I looked around As usual she was sitting by herself at a table, and all the rest of the tables were full. So you can guess what I did.  "Uh.. hi, do you mind if I sit here?" I shakily said, I could just see in my head he stand up and leave, but she didn't. She just stopped what she was doing. "Do you mind?"  "Go sit some where else, I'm busy" She replied sharply" Fairly taken aback I replied  "the table was quite big, and I wont bug you" So I sat down "Are you deaf? just leave me alone!" "I just want to eat my lunch gimme a break" She looked up at me for the first time, I couldn't see her eyes at the time, but I knew they were focused on mine. I could feel it, I don't know how, but I just knew. "Fine eat your lunch quickly then piss off,  and if I hear a peep out of you, ill snap you in two" Trying not too laugh considering how small she was compared to me I nodded my head.  Time passed and nothing happened, I stayed quiet and she never spoke, just drew... Finally I got bored and spoke up "So I don't even know you nam...!" Next thing I knew My head had smashed against the table and was being held down by one of her hands!! The other was wrapped into a fist held ready to strike me again. I could just catch a glimpse of her face, teeth clenched and her eyes were filled with with rage. She looked like a wild animal, and I was the prey!    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im almost done chapter 2, im way ahead of where I though I was going to be. So if i continue on this pace ill be done by tonight, and it'll be up by tomarrow =P stop asking, wait and see
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im in the process of writing my second chapter, so it should be dont by wednesday or so, lol , Yea so when it done it'll be up. ANYWAYS im glad to say that me and britney are now "offically" dating so that a plus, =D.   there are som may people I havent talked to in a while, keep in touch plz lol, anyways its 5:45 and im tierd
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      graycat74... I am truly sorry that you got that impression of me, and im sorry that you think that way about that I wrote. It a bit amazing that you could just cut through the rest and just see that comment. Or did you just stop reading when u saw that? either way Im kinda depressedat that. But for one thing, if u are that offended by what I have writen, all I can say is go fuck yourself... That is all  I liked this one so i kept it Graycat74 tell me if u like it: Anonymous said...   wow cat you're fucking stupid. she doesn't "have" to sit in the back and hide her intelligence. and ontop of that if you paid attention you would notice that she doesn't hide it, she speaks up to prove the teacher wrong. therefore there is no gender bias. you just need to think and get the facts straight before you speak next time, fool. good work jake. the great beginnings of a story. ;) cheers bob  Cheers  = o P
    
</post>


</Blog>