<Blog>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! my weekend was awesome.  Friday- I hung out @ Nic's house with her and Brian...we just hung out and talked for a while.  it was her mom's birthday so we ate cake! lol.  Saturday- I went to Marshall's house and watched School Of Rock (great movie).  It was fun, but then again Marshall's house is always fun! Sunday- I got a call from Mrs. Quindlen.  She asked me if I wanted to go to the Blink-182 concert with Jack, a friend of mine who i've know since 3rd grade from SJC.  I was sooo hapyp and excited, but I wish she had 2 tickets so Marshall could go. :-(.  The I went to Shannon Munsell's graduation party with my family for a little while.  It was pretty boring.  Then Mr. Quindlen drove us to go pick up Jack's friend Henry.  Then we were on our way to take the ferry so that we would get to the Tweeter Center.  When we got there, we met up with Jack's friends, Zac and Dan.  So it was me, Henry, Jack, Zac and Dan all hanging out.  It was so much fun becuase all the guys were sooooo cool.  lol. Great Weekend...Blink-182 and No Doubt rocked my socks. lol I just felt like saying that.  That's all for now.  love always, ~mel  "Down"- Blink-182 (one of my favorite blink songs) The drops of rain they fall all over This awkward silence makes me crazy The glow inside burns light upon her I'll try to kiss you if you let me (this can't be the end)  Tidal waves they rip right through me Tears from eyes worn cold and sad Pick me up now, I need you so bad  Down down down down [x4] It gets me so Down down down down [x4] It gets me so  Your vows of silence fall all over The look in your eyes makes me crazy I feel the darkness break upon her I'll take you over if you let me (You did this)  Tidal waves they rip right through me Tears from eyes worn cold and sad Pick me up now, I need you so bad.  Down down down down [x4] It gets me so Down down down down [x4] It gets me so      
       
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! Weekend is going pretty good so far.  Last night I went to Nic's house with Brian George.  It was fun we basically just talked and sang Happy Birthday to her mom and ate cake! lol.  Today is Marshall and me's 9 month! YAY! lol. That's all for now...I'll write tonight or tomorrow...sometime.  love always, ~mel
       
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! I'm sick of Xanga, and Bridet told me to get a blogger.  I went to the pool with Marshall yesterday, it was fun.  Rachel, Shannon and Lisa stopped by to see us.  It's Friday! Don't know what I'm doing this weekend yet, but I know Sunday I'm going my cousin's Graduation Party..Andrea will be there and hopefully my aunt will have her pool open. Today is my last day of babysitting.  It was so cute yesterday they made me a card that said, "Thank you for babysitting and helping us with our homework." Aww, I feel loved!Ok, so the weirdest but most awesome thing happened last night.  Someone IMed me and was like "Hey Old Friend" and I had no idea who they were so I was guessing names of ppl that I've known for so long...and I said my friend Kris..and he was like "Kris who?" So I typed in the last name and he was like "Yeah!" and I was so shocked that it was him.  I mean, I haven't seen or talked to this kid since I was like 6 when I moved from Glenolden.  He still lives in the same house.  Supposedly, he was talking to my friend Nicole, who also used to live on my old street, and got my screen name.  It was so awesome to catch up and talk about things from when we were little.  That was the highlight of my day. That's all for now...I'll write later this weekend.  Have a Good Weekend everyone.  No that anyone reads this. lol love always, ~mel
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>