<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   loving this country is not easy.  everybody have plans of going away from this land, plans of settling in foreign countries, plans of working in countries they don't own.    you know what i think of them, of what they're doing?! ESCAPING... walking away from the poverty of this country which they themselves have been responsible for this distress that the motherland is experiencing.  they say, you can't blame us, but i say nobody's left to be blamed but ourselves for what has happened.  who voted these corrupt officials?  who voted these famous but dim-witted officials?  who have caused traffic in the streets?  who has no discpline of not following the traffic lights?  (and yeah like other basic traffic rules?!)  who has the guts of bribing the public officials so they could process their papers or documents effortlessly?  who does throw their litter just anywhere they pleases?  who doesn't come to work on time?    i don't think i need to answer all of these.  but after all these erroneous deeds we've done, and now that the country is left near the cliff of the pit, yes, it's so easy to just fly away to other land.  some would even pay a fortune just to guarantee their visas.  some choose to stay in that foreign land and hide all their life and sacrifice not going home.  if you ask a fresh graduate right now on what is their ultimate dream job, a big percentage would be of having an opportunity of working outside their country.  it's pride for themselves.  is it of some pride if you're working for a country other than your own?  making other countries benefit from a talent that is developed and hoaned in the country where you were born?  making them rich and looking back at this country and nothing left to feel but have pity on it?  i don't know what your answers would be to these gazillions of questions...i just thought of asking you, hoping it would affect you in some way. and if it's too much to ask, to change your mind.  to be continued... 

						
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Getting married is the greatest mistake anyone  can ever make.   Being wed is the height of insanity, the most  ludicrous commitment, the most totally illogical  decision any human being can fall into.   Tell me. Why should I commit myself to be with  one woman for the rest of my life - and thereby  reject 3.2 billion other females in the world?   Along the way, I'll meet a girl who'll be more  beautiful, or more intelligent, or more  charming, or sexier, or holier. So why nail  myself down to one choice, permanently -- and  suffer the agony of simply watching beauties  pass me by?   And in western countries, one out of two  marriages end up in divorce. That blows my mind.  That's a pathetic 50% failure rate! I would  never buy a car, a stereo, a shaver, or even a  nail clipper if there was a 50% chance that it  would conk out on me. I simply wouldn't.  And why stay with one person "in sickness or in  health, in riches or in poverty, till death do  us part"? Is my mind fried? If my shirt shrinks  on me because I eat too many pizzas, don't I  just throw it away and buy an XL?  (That will be the day.) And if I outgrow my  ancient computer, don't I just look for an  updated version?   And then there's the catastrophe some call kids.  I mean, I don't really want to wake up in the  middle of the night to entertain a self- centered, bald, toothless tyrant in diapers? Do  I really want little rampaging monsters to break  the most expensive furniture in my house? Do I  really want juvenile creatures to stay on the  phone for six hours straight, listen to noise  they call music that you believe came directly  from hell, and mope around uncommunicative,  catatonic, and depressed because another  demented juvenile creature (a.k.a.boyfriend)  hasn't called in the passed thirty minutes?   Why should I go through the torture? Marriage is  insanity. But few years ago, on my 32nd  birthday, I gave myself a special birthday  gift: I got married to a lovely woman -- and  committed myself to insane living. Marowe is her  name, the person I chose - out of 3.2 billion  females. Yes, we now have a tiny tyrant that  wakes us up at night, and in the near future, we  will most likely have little monsters that will  destroy our house during playtime, and creatures  from outer space that we will call teenagers.   Why?   For three reasons.   FAITH. We believe that God calls us into   marriage. And if HE called us there, that means  He'll be there to meet us. We will suffer all  things-just let us be with our God.   HOPE. We confidently expect the best blessings -- immeasurably much more than all the hardship.  God will bless us beyond our wildest dreams.   LOVE. Oh yes, there will be other females who'll  be more beautiful, or more intelligent, or more  this and more that. But they'll only be just  that - females - like flowers in the field of a  million hectares of flower fields.   But not this woman - my Marowe - the one  beautiful flower I have personally chosen,  personally picked from her roots, personally  planted in my own clay pot, personally watered  everyday, personally watched every day, and  personally loved every day. Because of my love  for her, there will be no one like her.   In my heart, she will eternally be the most  beautiful flower of them all.   Because in the end, there will be only be faith,  hope, and love.   And the greatest of these is LOVE.  

						
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   1.  the speed of light is 186,000 miles/second. 2.  this is equivalent to 6 billion miles / year. 3.  the closest star to earth is the alpha centauri and this is 4.3 light years away from earth -- roughly, 26 billion miles away. 4.  the average distance between stars is 30 trillion. 5.  the average galaxy has about 100 billion stars. 6.  GOD made the universe.   astounding. awesome.  that's what those facts are.  i did't make them up.  i picked them up from a talk given by Jake Yap fifteen years back.  fifteen years back?  fine--so maybe the facts aren't so recent.   maybe ernie baron has spotted new galaxies thereby raising the total count to 200 billion.  would it matter much?  plus or minus a few billions, it would still be awesome.  and God made the universe.  that's how big HE is.  i ususally take things as they come.  however, there are days when something inside of me snaps and I'm not the same person.  one of my highschool teachers calls it temporary insanity.  lately, I'm having more difficulty with my vision.  my bladder has its mind it seems and i've been falling down more often (does anyone fall up?!).  my gait is more unsteady.  the other day at a department store, someone went as far as watching me try a shoe on.  nope, she wasn't the saleslady attending to me.  in my mind i was saying, "buy your shoe, lady, and leave me alone."  i whined before God.  "this mystifying disease--is this what you planned for me as early as when i was in my mother's womb?" i was being sarcastic before God.  i was angry.  call that spiritual blackout.  the lights go off when you forget who God is.  it happens when you forget what you mean to Him.  it happens when you talk to God like you know him better.  it weighed me down so bad that i behaved and spoke that way.  i wanted to regain my footing and say, "Lord, i take it all back."  what good would that do?  would that change anything?  that afternoon, omy (my husband) and i and the kids went to Church.  after the mass they lined up at the confessional.  i followed, knowing i could seek sacramental grace to be put right Him again.  i needed God to receive me back.  it was from Him i had turned away; would He take this loudmouth back?  the old priest gave me a little scolding and then sent me home with a blessing.  i walked away with firmer resolve not to question God that way again.  before sleeping, i suddenly remembered a broadway play many years back.  it was entitled "YOUR ARMS ARE TOO SHORT TO BOX WITH GOD"  i think about the universe, and the galaxies.  how big and how great their Creator must be.  i think about how tiny and insignificant I am against the backdrop of the universe.  a tiny little creature waving its fist at the God that meade the universe.  so, if moments before this, you were too swerving your fist, put it down.  drop it.  don't even think about it.  your arms are too short to box with God.    

						
</post>


</Blog>