<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       While its been sometime since my lastpost, lots of garbage has happened in my life to more or less throw me into complete uphevial...   Where to start? I lost my job because i decided itd be best to not goto iraq, which well I thought was a good idea, but im now searching for a job, which sucks, im having to move back in with my parents and lets just say that sucks sucks sucks much and stuff... but oh well...   What else, I really dont know what else to say, Ive been hanging out with my TI friends a lot lately, and more or less havent hung out with my other friends...  I met a girl at a party last weekend, and she was hip... but she doesnt live around here so well who cares...   anyways this is short because im still at a loss ... this job and parents stuff sucks.. sucks much ass 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I finally get around to watching season 1 of ATHF tonight and damn, it has to be the funniest thing ever. I have been laughing since I put it in.   I mean damn who wouldnt love a floating thing of fries, a wad of meat, and a shake... there hyjinks are crazy.   Adultswim is awesome. I must say that over and over and over again. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As I sit on my laptop I realize that all my posts revolve around night and what I did during it... alas, tonight is no different from the last.  It started out pretty lackluster I must say, Charlie and I met at the D to drive to gentlemen jims tonight for the playboy photo shoot. We're driving along at quite the nice pace when all of a sudden my doors are blown off by danny in his ITR. We apparently met up with the Fairlakes crew and that was fun, I accelerate to catch up and look down and im doing 110 on 270, not the brightest idea in the world, however it happens, what are you going to do? So this place we get to and its mass chaos, 10 bucks to get in or not to get in, we dont know... hand stamps fly money is going around... regardless of which some people cant get in so they goto lonestar across the street understandable, you know food is needed by all. We go upstairs to this place and sit around for awhile until the playboy model comes in, she sticks around to sign the mag shes giving us, extremely uncordial about everything just kinda signs and proceeds to the next person, I guess you can do that when you're a playboy model. Sit some more and then eventually we do the car picutre thing outside where everyone is just oogling this girl. Hey, its what guys do. Regardless of which, I highly doubt ill go back, the drinks as well as the fact that you dont get free refills annoys me, along with the 100 mile round trip fun that it was.   Whatelse? So I get home at a relativly decent hour tonight to be called back to goto Denny's fun huh? Some coffee maybe some food, figure why not, its a weeknight should be a relativly calm night at my local hoodbridge denny's. Well thats so not the case, we get there and end up making friends with this blond which in my opinion was cute and her friend who happened to be a pretty hip guy. All of a sudden some jackass 16 year old punk bastard decides he wants to start shit, talking smack and whatnot... the true side of hoodbridge came out tonight. 16 years old, with a very attractive girlfriend and he's sitting there I guess trying to prove something, all because a comment was made at how attractive his other friend was. Thats all that was said, next thing we know he's talking smack, and talking it LOUD. It took a lot of selfcontrol to not go over and seriously strangle this kid for being a jackass, however mind over matter. The girl we were sitting with goes over to try and calm his lame ass down but he wasnt having it, more crap being talked and he tells this girl who is laughing and joking at this point that he's going to uppercut her. Who says that by the way, I hear yeah ill hit you, or im gonna knock you out, but uppercut? Apparently he was some kind of goldengloves kinda kid... regardless of which a person that young needed to be at home, dont kids have school in the morning? I dont know regardless of which the evening turned out better after him and his group of friends decided to exit the establishment.   What else about today that made me ponder. A friend of mine told me some disturbing news and well I was taken aback by it... I dont want to say exactly what was said but I was disturbed, I consider this person a good friend as well as an all around good person but well for one of the few times in my life I was struck with the whole I really dont know what to say to better this situation, I mean usually there is something, I guess just being a friend and someone they could lean on would be good, but well I felt as if I couldnt do anything... to me that sucks, I hate seeing stuff like that or that pit feeling in your stomach when you feel as if there is nothing, absolutly nothing that one could do. Regardless of which, I guess my prayers are the only thing that could help...   Still no word on Qatar, Im seriously thinking of finding a local job, and giving them the big middle finger, yep the big middle finger telling them you know what take this job and shove it up your ass. The money is great, but would it be worth dying over? Then again, what do I have to keep me here?   Another day down and its 6 in the morning and still not asleep. I got side work to do today but alas, it doesnt look like Ill be going to get much sleep, Ill sleep when done...  I hope anyone who reads this understands that well I just mean to help other people... I value my new friends so much, amazing this is what it feels like to actually be wanted around just because of being you, not of what you can do for someone... funny i dont think Ive ever really felt that way before...   Which reminds me, no matter how much you think a person is great and perfect for you, why bother with them if they wont even give you the time of day, buying someones love is almost like prostitution in a way, you're getting nothing but an empty wallet and screwing yourself in the long run...   maybe tomorrow I can actually get some sleep...  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so I comming to believe that women are just plain evil. maybe im wrong maybe im right but well I believe that im sick and tired of being the one shoulder to cry on and well after its all said and done, Im just her friened still, that isn't a bad thing to be someone friend, to be their rock, but well erosion sets in... that once strong rock tumbles just like everything else. Its like toying with peoples emotions is a fun thing to do. Why else call someone at 9 at night and sit and talk like nothing has ever changed yet we all know deep down that things have.  What else? A person whom I'm beginning to consider a real true honest friend told me something today that I believe might stick with me for quite some time. They said instead of sweetdreams, to dream sweetly. And you know what it worked. My nightmares have been back fullsteam lately, and while to some they might not seem light nightmares yet I keep seeing this image of me dying alone and old and then to my funeral where its just the band playing honors for me and blam I'm in the ground. Yes thats right I'll come out and say it, my greatest fear in life is dying old and alone. How messed up is that? Maybe it is messed up maybe it isn't but well to me it feels as if it might come true, the way my life has been going lately.  I've found new friends lately, funny, Ive known these people for well maybe 6 months through my integra chat forum but well honestly they've become such better friends people who seem to want me around just to have me around, not hey i need you to fix something or hey i need this done but they honestly want me around to do that. I've had friends for years now and well it seems to me that well these people are better for me then the people whom I call friends now.   Tonight was Hooters trivia night with local club RSX people and that was an enjoyable time. You know you cant go wrong looking at scantilly clad women who are paid to be nice to you. Too bad its just because they're paid.    4 in the morning and I want to sleep, however it doesn't come to me. Hopefully Ill be aleep before the sun actually makes its appearance today. Regardless of which, I believe I might try sleep, turn off the phone and just sleep... just sleep... 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I saw this picture and laughed my ass off ....     females with mullets... image provided from  urlLink Mullets Galore    This got me thinking when I posted the Captain Planet Pic 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm writing this in more or less as a write of praise for cartoon network. Its an insomniacs dream come true, I believe one of the few channels on comcast that plays cartoons 24/7. Yes you're saying yes dumbass, its cartoon network, but well look at comedy central, it starts playin infomercials.   What else to talk about for today. I slept till like 530 this evening, and well honestly, I dont care, what all did I have to do today? I went out to dinner with my roomate, which was good, you know pizza and beer at Uno's cant be all bad. The more I hang out with him, the more I want to be healthier in my own life. We know that wont happen, but hey we can dream can't we?  Captian Planet.... he's our hero, gonna take polution down to zero...  Yeah, thats whats on right now... these damn hippie tree huggers trying to save the world against these crack headed people who wants polution. Im all about some save the earth stuff, but damn you need to create a superhero to get these kids out of the cookiie situations they get themselves into... and captain planet has a mullet... mullets must go      yeah you like the mullet photo of captain planet...   whatelse... I think gameboy is by far the best thing ever created. I recently bought the new one, the advanced and well I cant put the damn thing down. Been playing the hell out of Final Fantasy Tactics and damn, its almost as fun as the old one on the PS 1.    I need a new orange hat, yep I need a new one. Mine has become faded yet i lack the funds to get a new one. Hopefully the best buy job starts soon so I can create some side funds.   Well I belive thats all, however I leave you with this from probably the best cartoon ever (maybe not ever but I think its damn funny)     Meatwad: Where the damn presents? Frylock: It's the middle of the day, Meatwad, that wasn't Santa Claus, okay? Meatwad: Ah, well, you know maybe Santa's just sort of getting a jump start on things this year, 'cause, you know, statistics they show that there are more children in the world today... That's China's fault.   
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Watching Sealab now at midnight going how did I get into this rut that I call life? I find myslef really not giving two shits about most things. I slept till 4 this afternoon and well going I really dont care that I wasted an entire day doing nothing but sleep. Went and helped my insane dad rip apart the deck at the house and well that was a good time, breaking things is fun and a great way to relieve stress apparently, as if I'm suffering greatly from that. Still greatly worried about this whol Qatar thing. I mean damn another bomb went off there today and honestly that scares my ignent ass...   Anyways, sitting here smoking a smoke, ashing in my empty cup o noodles cup filled with some water as a ghetto ashtray, isnt that fun?  Brek, this cartoon is kinda odd I must say, I really dont understand it regardless of which, another day another dollar. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok another random post while watching cartoons in the early morning... 6 AM and the sun has come up and cartoon network apparently plays cartoons from the 1960's and here is this show Top Cat     Yeah thats right, a conartist cat, thats right teach kids at an early age how to beat the system. Im less then impressed by this. However what else are you going to watch at this time of the day? I guess I really should start cutting back this caffine intake of mine.  However I must say the commercials on Cartoon Network are pretty good, some kinda kickboard with a waterblaster, thats right get someone wet when they're already in a pool  Its made by whamo, come on, its a top quality product you all know this ;)  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was sitting tonight with a friend of mine who lately has become someone who I must say I trust dearly, we were talking about my love life or lack their of and how we started talking about past and exes and the like. Background on all this, I dated a girl that was a single mom and we broke up due to her wanting to spend more time with her child...  Funny its been a year and well I still miss the hell out of the two of them, dont take this as some sob story or whatnot, but I was dating this girl for awhile and more or less she turned psycho on me. Funny thing is it isnt the first time it happened. This is what started this whole conversation, how well I seem to date these psycho females and I made an off comment that well I seem to only date looser females. She mentioned the ex with a girl how she wasn't a looser.   Funny, right person at the wrong time, maybe her and I were meant to be, just not at the current time? I dont know if that means anything to me or not but it makes sense. Again, another fruitless rant about how women can be psycho sometimes yet we need them in this world because well honestly, girls are hot...   I dont miss this current ex, she's been gone for a week now and well to me it really doesnt matter, yes, I said that, it doesnt seem to matter. Is that cold or heartless? I don't believe so, I just well honestly don't think its right to flip out on someone because well thier bestfriend is a female. Is that a wrong thing to have?  Regardless of which, Women seem to be crazy in the head... I believe that must be the case... crazy in the head ;) but I still love em though, guess through all this I'm not jaded, thats good right? There's always the priesthood.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So Bill, Travis, Matt and I all goto Hooters tonight, where apparently the girls that work there have the combined IQ of 12, Our waitress was cute and all but well I believe there are rocks around here that have more intelligence then that. Ahh, however the ammount of T&A was a sight for sore eyes...  Regardless of which, beer, wings and hockey... good times  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, while, I'm sitting here at 7 in the morning, watching the Flinstones,      I'm sitting here wondering, why the heck isn't life as easy things on this cartoon? I mean Fred gets upset, Wilma forgives him, he gets to go bowling every night, He yells at his mother in law, and gets away with everything...  I want a dinasour for a pet, I think that'd be cool what you think? Eat big ass pieces of meat for dinner having either stoner eyes or regular eyes...  Regardless of which I think it'd be cool 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My gorgeous baby, the day I got her back from the body shop...     
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I created this more or less to just have something to write in, something to log my well thoughts as I guess one would say?   I use the computer too much, which is why my posts revolve around it. Its, semi-sad I think, I'm 25 and well I have 3 computers, all running and in a room that well I call a room, most call it a basement. Regardless of which, I spend too much time, revolving around them, along with my scatered XBox and Playstation2 games on the floor because well sitting in front of my couch is so much better for my back then actually sitting on it.  Its 530 in the morning and my night consisted of sitting at my usual hangout drinking coffee and smoking ciggerettes till almost 300 this morning. Funny, we complaign (my friends and I) that there isn't anything to do, yet we all seem to congregate to the dinner everynight, somewhere around 830 or 9 everynight and drink coffee and I wonder why I'm still awake at 5 in the morning, watching some cartoon I've never heard of on Cartoon Network due to the fact that there really isnt anything else worth watching at this time of day.   About me? Well I've been waiting on a plane to fly to a great big sandbox in the middle east for the past 2 months and well honestly, my nerves are done, everynight going to bed thinking is this going to be the day I get the call to go over there? In March I was all about going there, however now that its June, I'm considering saying no way. The fact that contractors are being killed over there (which is what I am) and the fact that things aren't getting better, who knows what life will be like when I actually do get there.   I stumbled here via looking at a friends and figured well I could use this as my own online journal, who knows if anyone will actually read it, but well it does feel semi good to get some of these "deep" thoughts out, yeah thats right, to me these are deep, you know suffering from that middle class suburbanite angyst... (that was funny come on)    I drive an Integra, and right now, it seems to be the only love in my life I can keep without it turning psycho or wanting to stalk the hell out of me...  Regardless of which, I believe this is enough useless bantering for one day...   
    
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I spend most of my time here, a no nonsense, all integra site, dedicated to integras and thier maintainance.   urlLink Team Integra: All Integra, All The Time  
    
    
</post>


<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Read this tonight while looking around and it not only provided examples but well provided ways of securing your databases against this possibly deadly SQL hack...   urlLink SQL Injection 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Found this article and well wanted to post it here...    urlLink Underground War.com   Special thanks to undergroundwar to host such great articles
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Crystal Tech   urlLink Community MX   urlLink CSS Discuss.org   urlLink W3 Schools    Great place for tutorials on ASP and ASP.net
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Proxy 1    What is a proxy server?  A proxy server is a kind of buffer between your computer and the Internet resources you are accessing. The data you request come to the proxy first, and only then it transmits the data to you.  What is an anonymous proxy server?  Anonymous proxy servers hide your IP address and thereby prevent your from unauthorized access to your computer through the Internet. They do not provide anyone with your IP address and effectively hide any information about you and your reading interests. Besides that, they don’t even let anyone know that you are surfing through a proxy server. Anonymous proxy servers can be used for all kinds of Web-services, such as Web-Mail (MSN Hot Mail, Yahoo mail), web-chat rooms, FTP archives, etc.  Why do I need to use proxy servers?  1. Transfer speed improvement. Proxy servers accumulate and save files that are most often requested by thousands of Internet users in a special database, called “cache”. Therefore, proxy servers are able to increase the speed of your connection to the Internet. The cache of a proxy server may already contain information you need by the time of your request, making it possible for the proxy to deliver it immediately.  2. Security and privacy. Anonymous proxy servers that hide your IP address thereby saving you from vulnerabilities concerned with it.  3. Sometimes you may encounter problems while accessing to web server when server administrator restricted access from your IP or even from wide IP range (for example restricting access from certain countries or geographical regions). So you try to access those pages using an anonymous proxy server.  What is a public proxy server?  It is a proxy server which is free and open for everybody on the Internet. Unfortunately most of them are not anonymous.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some of these things are well known however, I'm amazed as to how many people have never heard of them.   urlLink Mozilla FireFox    Some of its features Tabbed Browsing  Firefox presents a fast and convenient way to browse the web - now you can open several pages in one window in separate browser tabs. Open links in the background while you read a web page, then continue to the links when you're done - pages are available when you need them, making the web feel faster even over slow connections. Read More... Popup Blocking  Popup advertising is one of the biggest web annoyances. Firefox shields you from unwanted popup windows. It also lets you allow certain sites to open popup windows if necessary. Read More... Integrated Search  Firefox makes finding things easy. The built-in Google bar provides convenient access to the best search engine on the web. Read More... Efficient Navigation  Firefox makes it easy to navigate without using the mouse. You can open links simply by typing some of the text in the link. Read More... AutoDownload  Automatically download files to your Desktop or another location with AutoDownload. Downloading becomes much simpler without windows popping up asking you where to save. Read More...   Mozilla Thunderbird  urlLink Mozilla Thunderbird   I was tired of outlook and outlook express's lack of spam control and its obvious hole's that microsoft hasn't fixed yet. It works better then all of them and by far one of the best e-mail clients out there.   Trillian I like most people have IM accounts on AIM, MSN, Yahoo, and ICQ. It allows you to tab different conversations, use IRC and all other services while conserving ram.  urlLink  Trillians Homepage   SpyBot Search and Destroy The best way to destory spyware and adware on your computer and its absolutly free   urlLink SpyBot 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink SQL Injection Primer     urlLink Hack this site   A great place to test your skills and learn some awesome webskills
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just like the topic says, the ISO on this website will allow you to hack a SAM file and reset an admin password on a machine that has been comprimised...   urlLink NT Password Hack 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      PHP 5 has been released today. You can read the  urlLink Changelog  here and download it from  urlLink here . It includes full support of the new object model of Zend Engine II, a remake of the XML engine, added a new SimpleXML extension for easily accessing and manipulating XML as PHP objects, included a database server called SQLite and many more features. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for all you people just getting into the apache / php world found this little jem and well I HAVE to share it with the world... installs a graphical apache / php into your computer with mysql... no configuration required just open and run and BLAM you have a working windows copy of php/apache/mysql that ties to your 127.0.0.1 address in your web browser and you can test and upload directly to it...   EasyPHP is a complete software package allowing to use all the power and the flexibility that offers the dynamic language PHP and the effecient use of databases. Package includes an Apache server, a MySQL database, a fully PHP execution, as well as easy development tools for your web site or your applications.   urlLink Easy PHP  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink ISO Powertoy   If you burn ISO images this it the TOOL for you  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>