<Blog>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      These are the things I wish I felt better about...  1.)  Health 2.)  Finances 3.)  Job 4.)  Paying for my son's college. 5.)  Family relationships   These are the things I want to do before I die...  1.)  Go on a cruise 2.)  See my son successful, married and happy 3.)  Grandchildren!! 4.)  Visit New York and the East Coast. 5.)  Visit California 6.)  Have no worries about my health 7.)  Retire!!! 8.)  Win the lottery   These are the things that I am Thankful for..  1.)  My relationship with the Lord 2.)  My wonderful husband 3.)  My son 4.)  My parents 5.)  My Mother-In-Law Betty   These are the improvements I am making in my life...  1.)  Health...which covers the following..      A.)  Losing weight      B.)  exercise      C.)  Healthy Lifestyle      D.)  Taking care of my Kidney problem.  2.)  Personality--I can be a real b**** sometimes.  3.)  Cleanliness is next to Godliness...my house and my garage are a mess.    4.)  My relationship with my husband.  NUFF SAID!!   I know that no one really cares about what I write here.  It is just for me to look at and remind myself.           
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, it has been several days since my last entry.  I went into the hospital on Thursday and just got out today.  I never in my life was so tired of a hospital.  Basically, I am anemic, have bad kidneys and something wrong with my head.  On the good side my blood pressure is low and I am not even on medicine for it and I have a very healthy heart.    I am so thankful that we have insurance.  I had to have test where they shoot radioactive stuff in me.  I should have been glowing!!!  Anyway, most of the nurses were very nice and attentive but there were a couple that I wanted to stomp in the ground!!!    I'm out now.  I have to go have an MRI and MRA done.  The Neurologist says she wants to do a spinal tap.  Yeah right!!!  If the MRI comes back ok...forget it!!  I guess this is all for now.    Take care...if anyone reads this.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I would like to tell you about my best friend.  Her name is Bobbie Jean Carnathan Ruffin McCauley.  She is my mom.  My rock.  She was the youngest of 4 daughters born to Walter Clifton and Clara Eunice Carnathan.  They were the best grandparents you would ever want to have.  My grandmother taught me alot.  Anyway, back to my best friend...  She married Joe E. Ruffin in 1955, I believe.  She was 17 and he was 19.  Yes, they were young and no she was not pregnant!!  A year later they had my oldest brother, Ricky, then a couple of years later they had my brother Greg.  Then a couple of years later it was my turn!!!  My mom almost died after having me.  I will never forget the stories that have been told to me.    I try to think back as far as I can and remember things about my mom.  I can remember a Christmas at Mamaw and Papaw's house in Oklahoma.  The house was on Osage street.  I was 4 I think.  I had a new step-dad, Buddy (a wonderful story in it's self!)  I remember they had gone out and cut down a tree for the Christmas tree.  Actually I remember them bringing in the tree.  That's the only thing I remember, except me having a Tea Party with my Auntie Doy with my new Christmas dishes.  I guess my clearest memories is when we lived on Sandy Meadow in Houston.  I can remember my mom ironing.  Isn't that funny?  I remember the smell of the starch that she shook out of a coke bottle I think with a lid with holes in it.  I remember I got an ironing board and iron (kiddie) for Christmas during that time and I was going to be just like my mommy.  (Today...Iron...are you kidding!!!)  I remember my mom and step dad, who I will call dad now watching bull fights.  I remember them making a candle out of crayons.  I remember when my sister Sherryl was born and they played a trick on me and Greg and said that we couldn't see her till we got home and they made us squat down in the back seat.  It was just a joke and we got to see her before we got home.  I remember mom and dad's bed.  It was always a safe haven.  Today's terms this may sound awful, or perverted or whatever, but it was a loving bonding time.  It was a time to have chats and just cuddle with my mom.  I loved it so much.  I remember one time she got mad at dad because he got home late from work and the weather was really stormy and she got mad at him for not calling her and telling her he was going to be late.  Isn't it funny the things you remember.  I remember I had a canopy bed.  I thought it was the greatest thing in the world.  Then there was the school years in Oklahoma.  My mom was at school it seemed every day.  She was even Santa Clause one year.  (Ok, now to a kid that would probably be really embarrassing, but then it wasn't)  I remember her coming in to my 4th grade class and looking for something in her purse and she pulled out some weird things...a baby sock (Sherryl's); a sponge roller, and Lord knows what else!!!  That time I was a little embarrassed.    When we moved back to Houston she worked and so she wasn't very involved in school.  It didn't really matter that much though.  She was always there when I needed her.    My biggest regret in my life is when I disappointed her so much when I like most other kids in the 70's experimented with pot.  She over heard a conversation I was having and the look on her face, the hurt in her eyes just killed me.  I will never ever forget that for as long as I live.  I was the good kid.  Never gave them much problem and then this.  It was awful, but I guarantee you one thing, once she was finished with me, I never touched the stuff again.  (Thanks Mom!!)    There was high school, graduation and then working.  Wow!!! I was an adult.  I had my own ideas and ways I thought my life should be and I learned many lessons from my mistakes and from not listening to my mom.  You know, you think, "what does she know".  Well, now that I am a parent of an adult, I realize that mom wasn't so stupid.    I got married at 21, had a baby at 23 and divorced at 25.  Wow...if it hadn't been for my parents I would have never it through that.  I was allowed to go home with my child.  Then after a couple of years I was back on my feet and moved into an apartment.  My mom was always a phone call away or right down the street.  Then I got stupid again.  Married for 6 months and divorced when he started hitting me and Jeremy.  Once again my parents took us in.  Then we moved out again after a couple of years and FINALLY I found someone who loves me unconditionally!!!  Even my parents like him!!!    My mom has always been there, either monetarily or in prayer or even in just a phone call for me.  In the last month or two I have found out that my health is declining and I was so scared.  I had to call my mom so that I could just hear her voice and after I was finished talking to her, I knew that everything would be ok.  One way or the other.    I feel guilty because I live so far away from my parents.  It is about 2 1/2 hours to Lake Livingston where they have retired.  You know with kids and work there are never enough hours in the day, or days in the week to take care of everything and I feel that I haven't visited her like I should.    I wish I was closer to mom so that I could see her regularly.  I miss her so much.  There are days I just need her.  I usually call her once a day.  Sometimes I can go a couple but no more that 3 or 4 days without talking to her.    Mom, if you do read this, please know that if I didn't have you for a mom, I don't know how I would have gotten through these last 41 years.  Thank you so much for being there.  For the words of wisdom.  Some I love to hear and others I don't.  Thank you thank you thank you.    I love you.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was 17 when Ronald Reagan was elected president.  He did so much for the US and foreign policies.  He was a family man, loving husband, and yes, at one point the most powerful man in the world.  Today as I sat and watched them take his body to the Capitol in Washington D.C.  and tears ran down my cheeks, I remembered words from his speeches, especially the one when the space shuttle blew up in 1986.  "They have passed the surly bonds of earth to touch the face of God."  (May be misquoted, but still beautiful.)    He came from a poor childhood to California to being an actor, to being the governor of California to being the President of the United States.  He will be on my mind and forever in my heart.  Goodbye Mr. President...we will miss you.    
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Due to the increase in rising gas costs I now carpool with my darling Mark.  It's great to be able to have adult conversations on the way to and from work.  Some times we argue and sometimes we laugh.  Thank goodness today was a laugh day.  I can really gripe sometimes.  Poor Mark.    Mark takes me to the Light Rail station and I ride the train to downtown Houston.  The train station is only about 5 minutes from the VA Hospital where he works.  So, it is a great way for us to save money.    Mark is off on Fridays so that is the only day I drive.    This week I won't have to because I am having a biopsy done on my kidneys to see what the matter may be with me.    I'm scared but I am sure everything will turn out fine.  I don't like pain too much.  Anyway, we enjoy driving together.  I gripe about his driving a lot!!!  I always tell him..."Don't cross the double white line!!  You will get a ticket!!"    Well, it's raining like mad here and the lightening and thunder has begun so I will close this now.    This is all for now.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today is Sunday and Mark works.  I hate him working on the weekend but that is his shift so he has to do it.  Sometimes I go with him.  I can't today because I have a long list of things to do...                 1.)  I have to finish work for my job and get it faxed to them.                2.)  My laundry is a nice pile now and I need to conquer the mountain.                 3.)  I need to go through closets and stuff and get things for the                      garage sale we are going to have soon.                  4.)  How much will get done?  Hopefully all, but knowing me?  Only 1                      and 2.    You see, it's not that I am lazy.  Well, maybe a little, but we cleaned this house for 3 months getting ready for family to come down for Jeremy's graduation and I don't want to clean anymore.  The thing is, that if I do a little now, I won't have to do a lot ever again!!!  Great concept, huh?    I need a maid.  That's what I have decided.  Unfortunately, it's me.  We can't afford to hire one.  You know, we played the Texas Lottery last night.  I wonder if we are millionaires?  The pot was up to 81 Million.  What could you do with 81 million?  I know what I would do.....have a heart attack, die and lose it all!!  Not really, I would pay off all of our bills, cars, house.  Pay for Jeremy's college.  Rent this house and build a house closer to my sister and mom and dad.  I would of course give to the American Cancer Society, and various other charities that mean a lot to me.  Invest, invest, invest...of course I would also be selfish.  I would trade in my Chevy Malibu and get me a Cadillac Escalade.  I would sell Mark's Jeep and get him the car of his choice.  And of course get rid of Jeremy's Tracker and get him what he wanted.  Dream dream dream...that's all it is.  Oh well...back to the real world.  So, I guess I had better get to climbing the mountain.  Thanks for reading.  R   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The love of my life.  My Mark.  I love you!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I thought I would share some of our family photos so you could see who I was talking about in my first post.  So, scroll down and enjoy.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Her Highness Heidi and her cat, Abbey.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Jeremy's night.  The medal around his neck is for being a "Texas Scholar".  We are very proud!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    My Mark and his mom Betty who was visiting from Michigan.  She came down for Jeremy's Graduation.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Jeremy at last concert in High School.  &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My name is Robbyn.  I live in Rosenberg, Texas which is about 35 miles southwest of Houston.  I have a wonderful husband, Mark and a great son, Jeremy who is now 18, graduated from high school this year and will be starting college in the fall.    We are allowed to share our dog's house.  Her name is Heidi.  She is a 2 year old Daschund and she is a mess.  She rules the roost!!!  She also allows our 5 year old cat, Abbey to live here.  We actually got Heidi for Abbey's 3rd birthday.  I don't think she was very appreciative.  The other animal in the house is a big mouthed Cockatiel named Bogy.  He is a screecher!!  He also whistles to call the dog, the kid, and laughs just like my husband.  Oh, he also likes to whistle the Andy Griffith Show tune.    I was born in Houston, raised in Houston with a brief period of 6 years in Oklahoma when I was in grades 1-6.  My husband on the other hand is a Yankee.  Southerners like to make fun of the yankees.  It has been a learning experience.    Let me tell you about my Mark.  A little over five years ago I had an ad in one of those online dating service things with a picture.  I got an e-mail from this guy.  It was quite the e-mail.  It was very poetic.  I could kick my self now for not saving it.  Anyway, he introduced himself and gave all the descriptors.  5'6''!!!  Oh no!!  I am 5'10"!!!   Anyway, because of the fact that the e-mail was so well written, I went ahead and e-mailed him back.  He e-mailed me again and said he would call me on Saturday at 9:00 a.m.  Ok, this was Wednesday and it was an eternity until Saturday rolled around.  So, at 9:00 on the dot the phone rang.  We talked until 11 and then decided to meet.  He was great.  We had EVERYTHING in common.  He asked if I wanted to go out to eat and to the movies.  I said I would love to but I didn't have a babysitter since my parents were out of town.  He said that's ok, bring him along!!!  What a guy.  Making brownie points already!!  So, he came by and picked us up and we went to eat and to the movies.  It was instant attraction!!!  So, then he took us home and stayed until about midnight and then left.  I lived on the north side of Houston and he in Rosenberg so it was about an hour for him to get home.  He called me to tell me that he made it home.  I told him to check his e-mail.  I told him in it I had a wonderful time and hoped that we could see each other again.  He called me back and said to check mine.  He said the same thing to me and that he wanted to kiss me but was afraid to make the move.  Isn't that sweet!!  Anyway, so we got together the next day and went to the lake to see my parents.  No he wasn't nervous.  (Yeah right!!!)  Anyway, same thing that night, stayed to midnite.  But this time he got his kiss!!!    So, he lived in Rosenberg, in a house that he had just had built a couple of months earlier.  He had a stable job and a home, I knew this guy was worth getting to know!!  So, I did and in September of that year we were married.  We have been married for almost 5 years now and happy as we can be.    Mark works for the Veteran's Hospital as a Recreation Therapist.  It's a great job and I love going and hearing the guys tell of their war stories.    I am a researcher.  I run people's names for jobs and apartments and lawyers and ...well, it's pretty boring.    Jeremy just graduated from B.F. Terry High School.  He is going to be a music education major.    I guess that's all for now.  I hope you like my intro and I will add more as I think of it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       We went to pick Mark up at the V.A. last night.  I ran straight in to his arms.  I was so glad to see him.  This past week has been a doosy.  Problem after problem, but now that he's back I feel so much better.  My blood pressure has been high all week.  Now that he's home it's lower.  Go figure.  Anyway, he isn't sure about my hair.  I don't think he likes it.  He'll just have to get over it because I love it.  Now, when we move to Iron Mountain, I may decide that the longer, the warmer!!        So we got home and he unloaded.  He got me pistacios (spelled wrong) grown in California.  He also saw olive trees, right there on the street where the hotel was.  Plus then also had a wine tasting and all kinds of neat stuff.  Anyway, we are so glad he is home.         I showed him the houses that I have looked at on the realtors websites in Iron Mountain.  There is this one that is my favorite, three bed, two bath, 1785 sq. foot., attached 2 car garage with a room over it.  I think we will make that an "apartment" type room for Jeremy when he is at home.  (If we buy that house that is.)  It's on a big corner lot in Quinnesec , MI, not far from Iron Mountain.         I showed Jeremy a school that is Northern Michigan University which is on Lake Superior and about 75 miles away from Iron Mountain area.  He was really interested because as part of your tuition you get a lap-top computer.         They do have a good music education program.  We will just have to see.         That's all I can go on about now.  Later!              
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Downtown Iron Mountain.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Winter in Iron Mountain, MI.  I can't wait!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Fumee Lake near Iron Mountain, MI&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       So I'm talking to Mark on the phone.&nbsp; He is still in California on business and we are talking about Iron Mountain and how badly we want to get the job.&nbsp; Anyway, Jeremy pipes up and says, "Oh there is a message on the answering machine from a V.A."&nbsp; I like to broke my neck running to the answering machine to listen to it.&nbsp; Sure enough, it was Iron Mountain calling!!!&nbsp; Mark called them and he has a phone interview on Tuesday at 3:00.&nbsp; Then, if they like him, they will fly him up for a face-to face interview.&nbsp; Please please pray.&nbsp; We need this so badly.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  I am worried about our house here in Rosenberg.&nbsp; I don't know if we are going to sell it or rent it.&nbsp; If we sell it, we would need to sell it immediately.&nbsp; There are 5 houses in this neighborhood for sale.&nbsp; Two like ours.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Jeremy said his friend Phillip's mom said she would love to rent it.&nbsp; If we could rent it for $1,000.00 to them, then there would be no problem.&nbsp; If we have to sell it, there may be a problem.    &nbsp;  I am ready to start packing!!!&nbsp; I want out of here!!!&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Please pray that he get's this job.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Thanks!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       So, we waited and waited and waited and waited and waited and ran the video camera, which was too dark to see anything anyway, but no one came to knock on the door, Tuesday or Wednesday night.&nbsp; Wednesday night I was watching out the upstairs window.&nbsp; I guess the cops coming stopped them.&nbsp; I don't know.&nbsp; Oh..by the way, no patrol as stated by the cop.&nbsp; Did you really think there would be???    &nbsp;  So, I guess the little vandals are gone now.&nbsp; I hope.&nbsp; Mark will be home Saturday night so I will be able to sleep again!!    &nbsp;  See ya!  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, the video camera is in the upstairs window just waiting to see what happens.&nbsp; I don't know if it will work or not because it is so dark outside.&nbsp;   Wish us luck!!!&nbsp; I want to catch the jerks.  Bye 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Last night I was upstairs watching a movie.&nbsp; Jeremy was downstairs and straight up 10:00 someone came and beat on the front door.&nbsp; Jeremy was standing in the hall when it happened so he opened the door up quick and they were already gone.&nbsp; I think it was a car that went by.&nbsp; Anyway, it upset me so bad I called Mark and gave him the number to Rosenberg PD and told him to call them and tell them what is going on and that I am here with Jeremy and this is the second night it has happened.&nbsp; So, we waited outside for the cop to come.&nbsp; Finally he did and basically he said "so what?"&nbsp; He asked what grade Jeremy was in and he said he was in College.&nbsp; He told him it was probably one of his friends.&nbsp; Jeremy said he had just called every one of his friends and everyone was at home and had been all evening.&nbsp; The cop said " You don't think they would tell you the truth do you?"&nbsp; Jeremy told him it wasn't any of his friends.&nbsp; "Then it is probably someone you knew in school."&nbsp; He said to stay in side.&nbsp; We are safe there.&nbsp; I said "You think so?"&nbsp; He said they would patrol at that time for a couple of nights.&nbsp; I politely said thank you, thinking other things, and he left.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Tonight I am going to be watching.&nbsp; I will catch the little suckers.&nbsp; I promise.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Thanks!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Lighting the torch at the Golden Age Games opening ceremonies, Fresno, CA.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Lee Greenwood again.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Country Music star Lee Greenwood singing "God Bless the U.S.A." at the opening ceremonies of the Golden Age Games in Fresno, CA. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The lobby of Mark's Hotel.  Beautiful Fountain.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Mark has been gone for 3 days now and I am so miserable.&nbsp; I can not wait for Saturday to get here&nbsp;so he will be home.&nbsp; Didn't sleep too good last night.&nbsp; Someone rang the doorbell at 10:05 and when I went to it, noone was there.&nbsp; Jeremy said to not get upset about it but I told him I didn't like it when people pulled that crap while Mark is out of town.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  He is supposed to be sending me pictures.&nbsp; I will post them when I get them.    &nbsp;  See Ya!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I went today and got a hair cut. I mean a real hair cut!!!&nbsp;The picture on my bio was taken today, after the fact.&nbsp; This other one was taken a while back.&nbsp; I am going to suprise Mark.&nbsp; When he gets back on Saturday he will either be really mad or really like it.&nbsp; I'm sure he will like it.     &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is me!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yes, that's right.&nbsp; I had to get up at 2:00 a.m. and take Mark to the V.A.&nbsp; He leaves today with 9 men and 1 woman to go to the Golden Age Games.&nbsp; This year it is in Fresno, CA.&nbsp; Their flight leaves at 6:00 a.m.&nbsp; So, why am I not back in bed after doing all this, and instead, I am sitting here at 5:15 a.m. typing on my blog...I don't know.&nbsp; Crazy I guess.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  The Golden Age Games is an annual event that takes place in the summer.&nbsp; Vets age 50+ participate in all kinds of sports from swimming..go Boomhower!!!&nbsp; To horseshoes...you can do it Morice!!!&nbsp; They also have dominos, shuffle board, bowling, go Gloria!!! and numerous other events.&nbsp; Mark is the Head Coach.&nbsp; Stacy is the assistant Coach.&nbsp; They will be gone a week.&nbsp; I miss him already.  &nbsp;  Hopefully this will be his last games though.&nbsp; When we get the job in Iron Mountain, he won't have to go away anymore!!!&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Ok...good luck guys!!&nbsp; Bring home the gold!!!  &nbsp;  Robbyn   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Jeremy hates it when I tell him he's my favorite son.&nbsp; He always says "I'm your only son".&nbsp; Anyway, he is actually my only child, unless you count Heidi and Abbey. (Dog and cat)&nbsp; Anyway, I wanted to brag a little on my College Man.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Jeremy did average work in High School.&nbsp; He had to be begged to do his homework and even when he said it was done, sometimes it wasn't and there would be very low grades.&nbsp; Since he has been in college he has studied every night.&nbsp; Done every bit of homework and has made higher than 90 on two tests.&nbsp; My how things change!!!&nbsp; He is loving college.&nbsp; I know at this moment he is only taking one class and will have a full load in the fall but this was just a taste of what is in store for him.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Please wish him luck!!!&nbsp; Thanks!!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Whitefish Point Lighthouse.  This is near the place where the famous Edmund Fitzgerald Iron Tanker went down.  There is a museum and everything here.  If you look north from the beach here you can see Canada.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Crisp Point Lighthouse, UP MIchigan.  My Lighthouse!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    U.P. Michigan...Beautiful falls...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Mackinac Bridge crossing over to the U.P.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      After all of the rains we have been having, it sure has turned out to be a beautiful couple of days.  Today is Saturday and it is just beautiful outside.  We can finally mow our yard and do yard work!!!  They said we have 60 % rain chance today.  Could fool me!   Jeremy started the second summer session of college on Tuesday of this week.  He had his first test yesterday.  He thinks he did pretty good on it.  He is a music major and he has to keep a B average in order to stay in the music major program.  Pray for him.  Actually he has been doing excellent with homework and studying.  I think he has studied more in this week than he did the four years in high school!!  That's a good thing.  If he sticks with it!!   Mark will be leaving next Saturday to go to Fresno, CA for a week.  It is Golden Age Games time. IT is the olympics for Senior Veterans and Mark is the Head Coach.  He can't wait to go, but I will miss him terribly!!!  He promises to call every day.  I guess that's all for this installment.  Oh...one more thing...I got the results from my blood work and my enemia is gone and the chemical in my kidneys that was causing kidney damage is only .5 away from normal!!!  I still have to have a few blood tests done to make sure it is going down.  Also, my blood pressure is still perfect.  Go figure.  I have been on blood pressure medicine for 20 years.  I didn't know you could just stop having high blood pressure.  Anyway, thank you Jesus!!!  See ya!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Mark came home the other day from work and said that there are two job openings for the VA.  One is for Prescott, AZ to be a Recreation Therapy Lead Therapist.  It would be a raise, but the cost of living in Prescott is very high.    The other one is in Iron Mountain, MI.  This is for Voluntary Services Head.  Yes, I said Michigan.  OMG!!!  I never in my life thought I would ever want to move to Michigan.  Especially the U.P.!!!  (Upper Peninsula)  Do you have any idea how this southerner is going to stick out like a sore thumb up there?!!!  That's ok though.  The cost of living is very low.  I wouldn't even have to work at first.  Then, after we save some money, I plan on opening a Bar-B-Q restaurant up there.  I've always wanted to own my own restaurant.    Mark is excited, I'm excited, Jeremy is excited...well, he will be once he moves up there.  He has to go to school a year here in Texas because he has already been accepted and has a scholarship.  Then, next year he will transfer to Central Michigan University where Mark went.  It's a great college that is known for it's teaching programs.  Marks concern is can I (me) handle the winters?  They are pretty harsh.  I told him I wouldn't have a problem!!!  I love snow.  (Yes, I've seen snow!!)  Iron Mountain has only a population of 8,000+.  That is something coming from a City that has 3 or 4 million.  Mark's family is in Michigan.  It would still be an 8 hour drive to see his mom, but it's a good weekend trip.  I think his sister Sue is a little closer.  Iron Mountain is actually closer to Green Bay Wisconsin.  GO PACKERS!!!  I will definitely miss my family down here, but I don't see them that much anyway.  Maybe once a month.  I will be in constant contact with my mom though.  And my sister.  My brother Greg drives a truck so I'm sure he will be up that way and we will see him.  So, please pray for God's will in this.  I am hoping it is His will for us to move.     One more thing...we would rent out house here in Texas.  That way we still have real estate.  Just until we can buy one up there.  Then we will sell this one.  Ok....please pray...and pray that I don't get my hopes up too much and be terribly disappointed if it isn't His will.  Thanks for listening!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I forgot to mention that we will know by Thursday of next week and then I have to give my notice immediately.  That's all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Mark got a phone call on Monday at work and it was Iron Mountain. They told him they wanted him to be there for a 3:00 p.m. interview on Wednesday. So, we broke our neck trying to find him a flight that didn't cost an arm and a leg. Flying directly in to Iron Mountain would have cost about $1400.00 Not good. So, he ended up flying in to Milwaukee, WI and rented a car and drove 3 1/2 hours to IM. (Iron Mountain) He said it is beautiful up there. So, they changed it to where he had to be there this morning at 9:00 a.m. and he had meetings ALL day. He didn't even have time to call me until he got back to the motel at 4:30. I of course was on needles all day waiting for his call.       It looks good. It looks very good. The associate director says that Mark is his pick. They are interviewing two other people tomorrow and Friday but they are not getting the grand tour and meeting EVERYONE like Mark did.       The Associate Director told Mark he had names of Real Estate Agents, churches, schools, etc. and just let him know what he needed. He said we don't have to pack a thing that the movers come in and do that. I am not comfortable with that so I am going to pack everything. They can move the boxes and furniture.       He figures that they will want us to move on Sept. 6 and Mark start the follwing Monday. Oh boy oh boy oh boy. Another good thing is they will pay 4 months for temporary housing until we get a place. They will also put our stuff in storage in IM until we need it.       That takes the pressure off of selling the house.       I guess that's all for now. Wish us luck!!! Thank You!!!!  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>