<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      check dis out!! ^_^  J.A.P.A.N Just Always Pray At Night.   H.O.L.L.A.N.D Hope Our Love Lasts And Never Dies.   I.T.A.L.Y. I Trust And Love You.   L.I.B.Y.A. Love Is Beautiful; You Also.   F.R.A.N.C.E. Friendships Remain And Never Can End.   C.H.I.N.A. Come Here.. I Need Affection.   B.U.R.M.A. Between Us, Remember Me Always.   I.N.D.I.A. I Nearly Died In Adoration.   K.E.N.Y.A. Keep Everything Nice, Yet Arousing.   C.A.N.A.D.A. Cute And Naughty Action that Developed into Attraction  K.O.R.E.A. Keep Optimistic Regardless of Every Adversity.   E.G.Y.P.T. Everything's Great, You Pretty Thing!   Y.E.M.E.N. Yugyugan Every Morning, Every Night.   R.U.S.S.I.A. Romance Under the Sky & Stars is Intimate Always.   M.A.N.I.L.A. May All Nights Inspire Love Always.   B.A.L.I.W.A.G. Beauty And Love I Will Always Give.   M.A.L.A.B.O.N. May A Lasting Affair Be Ours Now.   I.M.U.S. I Miss U, Sweetheart.   P.A.S.I.G. Please Always Say I'm Gorgeous.   C.E.B.U. Change Everything... But Us.   P.E.R.U. Porget Everyone... Remember Us.   P.A.R.A.N.A.Q.U.E. Please Always Remain Adorable, Nice And Quiet Under Ecstacy.   T.O.N.D.O. Tonight's Our Night, Dearest One.   P.A.S.A.Y. Pretty And Sexy Are You.   M.A.R.L.B.O.R.O. Men Always Remember Love Because Of Romance Only.   P.H.I.L.I.P.P.I.N.E.S. Pumping Hot.. I Love It! Please Please.. I Need   wahahahahahahaha!! pota!!! MABUHAY TALAGA ANG PILIPINO!!! ^_^
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this was taken from the ragnaboards...  urlLink Joke Time!!  have fun!!!  gusto nyo joke tungkol sa basura??? Wag na lang baka ikalat nyo e!  wahahahahahahaha!! :p  Q: Ano ang tawag sa mga supporters ni FPJ? A: Macaroni  Maca RONI!!! nyak! nyak! nyak!!  Q: why do witches dont wear panties? A: to get a better grip on the broom  BASTOS!!! :P :P  from Strangebrew: Tado: "Manong, ano po ba ang da best na panluto, kaliwa o kanan? panadero: "Kanan!" Tado: "kanan? Hindi po ba sandok?"  tadoh talga!! anak ng..!  Reporter: "Sir, what do you think are the major pollutants in the Philippines? Erap: Sisig, mani, chicharon, kornik...   pollutant!! hindi pulutan!! pota!  A bear and rabbit were in the middle of the forest doing their business. The bear turns to the rabbit and says "Hey buddy, how do you feel about having cr@p on your fur?" The rabbit replied "No... I don't mind it at all" So the bear suddenly grabbed the rabbit and used him to wipe his butt.   wehehehehehehe!!  from NU 107: One day agay guy went to see a doctor, the gay guy complained that his butt-hole really hurts bad. The doctor checked teh gay guys butt-hole but found nothing wrong. The gay guy told the doctor the to double check his butt-hole beacuse he still felt pain. The doctor checked the gya guys butt-hole again and saw something glittering inside. The doctor pulled out the glittering object and to his suprize the glittering object was actually a rolex watch! And while the doctor was pulling out the watch the gay guy was singing "Happy Birthday to you".   yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaak!! punyeta!!  Q: Ano ang cnabi ng kulangot sa sipon A: Pare...titigas k rin!  Q: Ano nmn ang cnabi ng utot sa tae A: Pare...una na ako!  Q: Eh ano naman kaya ang cnabi ng tae sa kapwa tae A: Pare...wala naman tulakan oh!   anak ng?! dugyot!! >p  may isang competisyon naglalaban ang mga hapon,amerikano at pilipino ang kelangan nilang gawin ay pataasin ang paa ng elepante ang ginawa ng hapon: tinawag ang lahat ng kamag-anak nya at sabay sabay nilang tinaas ang paa ng elepante pero ayaw prin ang ginawa ng amerikano: kumuha ng forklift pra maitaas ung paa pero wla prin ang ginawa ng pilipino: pinitik ang "utoy" ng elepante panalo ang pilipino   MABUHAY ANG PILIPINO!!!  A guy says, "I remember the first time I used alcohol as a substitute for women." "Yeah what happened?" asked his friend. The first guy replies, "Well, er, I got my penis stuck in the neck of the bottle."   parang popoy ah...  maraming pang iba.. just visit the site at tingnan nyo na lng ang mga jokes!! wehehehehehehe!   
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a line by line translation.. *grin*  Hehehehehe! Tagal ko ng hindi nagpopost dito ah.. (Hehehehehe!Its been a long time since i posted here..) Excited na ko!! mgkikita na ulit kami ng girl ko!! (Im really excited!! I will again see my girl!!)  Tama na nga! nahihirapan na kO! Barok ung English ko.. tingnan nyo n lng ung site nung friend ko. blog din! idol ko to pagdating sa English eh!  urlLink Robi's page!  Robi, kung binabasa mo to, idol kita sa English vocabulary pero master mo ko sa supalpalan at *toot*!! secret!!!  Tera Patrick is the best among the rest!!! wahahahahahaha! F.U.!!!!!!!!! wahaahahahahaha! if you want to know what is the meaning of F.U., just place a comment here and ill tell what F.U. means.. *tawa ng masama*  anyways, excited na nga ako dahil makakasama ko nanaman ang aking pinakamamahal at may kopya na rin ako ng my sassy girl na dadalhin nya!! wohoooooo!! kung may good news syempre may bad news!! quit na ko ng bisyo ko!! di na ko magraragna..  T_T  wala na kasi akong kasama kasi yung dalawa kong tropa eh nahack! fuck those hackers!! mamatay na kau!! tangina kasing LUG (Level-up-games) yan eh!! lang ginagawa! ok lng, ubos pera ko jan eh at least kabawasan na un sa mga gastusin ko! hehehehehe! excited pa rin ako!! got to go na!! knina pa ko nagtytype!! hehehehehe! comments nman jan!! 
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ang iba talagang tao sa ragnaboards, makikitid ang utak.. kasi ganito un.. last year, cguro ung 2 months after i-launch ung bagong ragnaboards, gumawa ako ng thread sa teh lounge named lasallian ragnaboarder.. tpos nung january yta, nasira ung link..  madami ng nagpost dun kya naisip ko, why not create another thread na ganun.. e di yan nakagwa na ko.. medyo konti pa lang nagpopost so ngpopost ako pra makita ng ibang lasallians tpos dumami ung post..  e di yan, ngpost ako kanina.. tpos bigla na lng may nagsabi, nagyayabang daw ako ng paggiging lasalyano ko.. here's the link, just read what the a-hole said. nasa baba, name nya sumumo_new.. meron pa sa next page..  urlLink A-hole's argument with me..   nga pla, ako c jacolyte13... just post a comment here or there in the ragnaboards... 
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just suck in doing this.. nobody wants to see this blog.. i dont know how to layout and make this better.. i just suck.. i need something.. i need someone.. my love?? maybe she'll cheer me up... i dont know..  too may things to do.. too little time.. im just too lazy in doing the things i must do... well i can say one thing, my grammar sucks!!! waaaaaaaaaaaah!!
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love the way i cram.. my adrenalin gives me energy.. right now, im cramming to make a speech for tomorrow.. im researching and im here in the internet laboratoy of our school.. kewl!!   im tired of cramming.. i was suppose to do it last saturday but i think i will not do it anyway because i have the "laziness syndrome" however, my saturday and sunday was fun cause im with my girl on those days.. unfortunately the reason i was there is because she was sick so i took care of her..i was there for two days and one night.. maybe ill post it some other time.. whoah! im off topic.. got to go! i have to cram.. 
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another day, another blog.. Sh*t tlga tong buhay na to oh... Hirap talaga pag nagawa mo na tpos pagsisihan mo sa huli..   Katulad kanina, nagsign up ako sa LSCS,org sa skul nmin, tpos may promo.. Bubunot ka tpos dalawa lang ung permyo.. ung isa M&M tska Games Master mag.. Eh gusto ko ung mag pero ang nabunot ko M&M and worst kinain lang ng tropa ko ung chocol8 ko!! waaaaaaaah!! haaaaaaaaay buhay!! *sigh* Naicip ko n lng na pwede ko plang dayain un tska nasisilip namn ung mga nakalagay! *sigh ulit*  Anyways, ganito tlaga ang buhay.. Dami ko pa palang gagawin.. May assignment pa ko bukas sa lintek na Filipi2 ko na mukhang ewan ung prof! 20 terms na galing sa cors ko?! la ako maicip dahil hindi pa ko nag-iicip! Malapit na rin akong magspeech sa encomp2 ko, my speech class.. Magreresearch na rin ako tungkol sa report ko naman sa founed1 ko, isa ko pang cors.. hirap talagang maging estudyante.. hirap mabuhay...
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mula sa una kong blog hanggang sa The Teleportus ay isa sa mga kuwento na kailangan kong gawin dahil sa isang activity sa school.English ang kelangan kya siguto ung iba sa mga terms dun ay wrong grammar. F*cksh*t naman kasi eh. Bakit ba ang hirap kong matuto ng English?? La Sallista pa man din ako..   Nakakahiya..  Hindi naman kasi lahat ng La Sallista magaling sa English ah. tama ba ko?? ewan ko pero pananaw ko lang un. Bahala na kung ano makuha kong grade dun sa pinasa kong activity. Ang pinapagawa kasi sa amin, mag-icip daw ng title sa isang future classrum tapos description. Yung mga gamit din daw sa loob ng classrum. Eh la akong maicip kya un n lng ung mga pinaglalalagay ko. Tingnan nyo n lng sa mga previous posts ko. Comment n lng kau. Ano kya makukuha kong grade kung 40 points ung activity??????
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Teleportus. The root word of this term is teleport which means getting to a place without using any vehicle or kind of effort to go to your destination. In the present life, this is very impossible but in the future this is so possible. It is very useful to the students and to the teachers as well. If the students are far from where the Digitalia is, they can teleport to the room by using Teleportus. As for the teachers, if they want to go to places, they can just use this innovative and incredible device to go to their destination with just a push of a button. 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The butler. This is a very incredible robot that was obviously invented in the future. This is an android that follows every command that is given by the instructor. There is only one Butler in the Digitilia because Monggiton is still studying its structures. Believe it or not, the Butler has a name and it is called Popoy.   Popoy is an android that can express emotions and registers in its system what is right and what is wrong. This depends on the inputs of the instuctor in the Butler. He is like a personal assistant of the current instuctor in checking the cubickes if the sutdents are doing what they must do. He is like a real human only lacking the human organs and the ability to produce a fertile offspring.  
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another gadget in the Digitalia is the mood cubicle. This is like the mood ring in the present only it is a cubicle or a room that changes its texture, color, design etc depending on the mood of its current owner. Of course there is a default color of the cubicle when no one is using it. The default color is dark blue and the texture of it is smooth. Maybe the favorite color of the original inventor and designer of the mood cubicle is dark blue? no one knows.. That is the future anyway.   The texture of the cubicle can be changed by the user according to his mood or what he wants. If the user does not want to choose the design of his cubicle, he can just sit in a digital chair and relax for a moment. After that, the main system will analyze his mood, attitude and all that is happening in his mind. Then, the room will change according to the results of the user's mind. 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The materializer. This is I think the most awesome thing in the Digitalia. This "thing" could materialize things in a blink of an eye. Monggiton did not know who invented but I think he loves it. Of course, this gadget can materialize bad things like a gun or a pornographic magazine so, the inventor placed an "anti-bad-thing-materializer" that only the teacher could prevent or obstruct the materializing.   The materializing can be done inside the cubicle by putting a headgear just like the one that cyclops of x-men uses but it is only larger to fit the head. This headgear will autofit in your head but only from the forehead or only half of the head will be covered. The instruction is to think of the thing that you want and concentrate on that thing. But first, it will go in to the "main system" that the teacher can only see. So if the teacher thinks that the material the student is trying to materialize is bad, the teacher will obstuct it and warn the student that it cannot be materialize. The only items that can be materialize is the things that the instuctor embedded in the system. Maybe sometimes, there will be free time to materialize anything the student wants. This is one of the items inside the cubicle in the Digitalia.
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Digital. A very intriguing and interesting word. Where does it came from and what does this term exactly mean? According to the definition of different online dictionaries, digital means the use of fingers or something that uses numbers or  digits  in performing different activities. This is the real meaning of digital but Monggiton will redefine it because   he saw the future  . He will tell us what is the real elucidation of this very mysterious word.   So, Monggiton, Monggi for short, saw the future. He wants to share it with the other people in the present. He analyzed the blueprints and the tools that he saw in the clasroom, in the future classroom. He worked for many days and nights just to figure it all out. New year has passed, His birthday has passed and a new president was declared but he is still studying the "future tools". After so many years, he understood all the things that was in there. So he decided to build this future classrum. He decided it to call   Digitalia.    This   Digitalia classroom   has many features. It has many innovative gadgets inside this room. For the moment, only one room will be built because it will still be tested if it will be effective for the different students. Of course, it has many "digital" things. Some of these things will be mentioned later. This place is not that big and not that small. It could contain about 30 students and each student has a cubicle to work in. These cubicles consist of many gadgets but the student is still comfortable inside it. There is a thing called the  materializer . This things materializes things that you like to appear. This gadget will be explained further in a different journal. Also, there are screens that the professor or the teacher will appear and teach the lessons. This will also be discussed in another section. The Digitalia is very ingenious in design because the cubicles can change its colors depending on the users. Its just like a Mood cubicle. The different apparatus will be discussed in other sections. Just read the different tools in other sections. If you will read the other tools, maybe you will fully see the environment of the   Digitalia.    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sa isang malayong lugar na mas malayo pa sa malayo, may taong nagngangalang monggiton. Ang taong ito ay maraming gustong gawin sa buhay tulad ng pagbubunjee jumping, tumalon sa isang mataas ng lugar, kumain ng palaka na lasa daw manok, pumatay ng tao(?!) katulad ng isang matabang "bata" na hindi ko maintindihan kung may problema ba o may sarili lang na mundo, at marami pang iba. Napakahaba ng introduksyon ko.   Si monggiton, gusto nyang malaman ang future kya gumawa sya ng isang time washing machine. Oo, time washing machine kasi masyado ng common ang time machine kaya time washing machine naman! Sa susunod ko na idedetalye kung paano nya ito nagawa kya nga introduksyon lang to eh. ano ba?! Dahil nakagawa na sya ng time washing machine, pumunta na sya sa future. Nang nakapunta na sya sa future, may nakita syang kakaibang Klasrum. Nakita nya ang mga blue prints at mga plano kung paano ito ginawa kaya dinala nya ito sa kasalukuyan at nagplano sya kung pano nya ito gagawin.. Dito nagsisimula ang mga adventures ni monggiton... 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3. The conventional self-contained classroom room as an organization is very effective because the students can interact with each other and they can share they opinions on the lesson. The teacher also can also discipline the child or student in this kind of classroom. While if you look at it as a setting for incorporating technology, it can be effective as well. Why? because the students can learn from the technology and they can be helped or they can be assisted by the teachers or educators while they do something..  6. The consequences of increased communication between home and school are the following: it can discourage the student to go to school and be laidback in the house since they can communicate to the school in their home... it can be a disadvantage to the parents because for sure the cost of this is much.. the students can also cheat in their homework since they can do it in their home and they can share it with their friends.. These are some of the consequences when there will be an increased communication between home and school. The importance of the home as a center for technology based learning could encourage the students to learn because its their environment. I mean that is the environment they are comfortable in. Also, they can study their technology in their own home because if the technologies are in school, the time is limited because of school hours..
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Knowledge can be obtained by many ways but it is more interesting to hear it from the real thing. I mean, the new technologies that are aiding in education are made by man. However, these technologies have advantages which I will discus later on. First, I will concentrate on why educators are still the best sources of education. So, why are the teachers the great sources of education or information? One of the reasons is that they are experienced and they are also experts on their field. Moreover, they are the ones who think of what to learn by the students. They know what to teach and what information that the students must learn. Also, they can discipline the students while they are learning. They can also control the technologies that are used by the students to learn or they can assist them personally if the students have problems. The teachers can exactly tell what to do or give suggestions. These are the some reasons why teachers are still the best source of education. But why technology is a help to teachers and to the students?   Technology is also a great source of education because you can control it in the palm of your hands. You can learn how to use a computer software by just clicking a link or a tutorial in the internet. You can find a lot of this in the cyber world. This is why I am thankful of these innovating technologies to help me in my school work and I will not always depend on the teacher. With these advantages, there are also disadvantages. The students can find information that is cannot help them in education. Like for example, there are distractions like online games and other cyber things. The cost of the gadgets or the technology is not affordable by ordinary students. That is why some of the students are well-equipped or they have advantage to the other students because of their gadgets. For me, these are the reasons why technology can be of help in educating students.  In conclusion, technology can be helpful to teachers in educating the students. But the educators should take precautions to students when they will handle the new technologies. Technology and teachers can be mixed but in the right amount. Too much technology, it can be risky. Too much teachers or old traditional way of teaching, it can be boring. Risky because students may always depend on the technologies or gadgets when doing their school work. Boring because it is the same old style of teaching and the students do not want that. These are my reaction and sides to what I just read. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just hanging out here in gox lab.. just surfing the net.. i miss this blog thing.. i forgot to blog everyday because wala naman akong internet sa bahay tska natatamad na rin ako.. besides, wala naman nagbabasa nito.. kung meron man, mag comment ka naman kung nababasa mo to..   ano bang bagong nangyari sa akin? well, kahapon nanood kami ng sine ng aking girlfriend, Maan, my bebe.. Spiderman 2 is the movie.. ok lng ung movie at parang ako lang ang naaliw.. anyways, umuwi kami ng 8 pm tapos kumain kami sa Mcdo na malapit sa kanila tapos 9 na kmi yta nakauwi sa kanila.. syempre ayoko pang umuwi kasi monthsary namin at patapos na ang gabi.. kay kuwentuhan muna kami.. i dont know kung bakit merong mga times na tahimik lang kami. siguro wala ng maikuwento.. umuwi na rin ako ng 12 kasi sabi ng aking ate ay masama daw pakiramdam nya! kupal talaga un!!   this is the end of my blog kaya tatambay muna ko dito sa computer laboratory ng la salle gokongwei 304B.. magmumuni.. magpapalipas ng oras.. hanggang sa maisipang umuwi.. tatambay na lang habang buhay..  
    
</post>


</Blog>