<Blog>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know it is the drone of every fake ass socialist university student union but man I can't stand the G8. I mean I was watching these guys on the TV sitting around a table deciding they are going to be real generous and give money to the poor. What kinda bullshit is that? I mean no one in their right mind can possibly beleive the that these leaders are the modern day incarnation of the mythical Robin Hood. Tigga please!!!  The more money they give to poorer countries the poorer the countries seem to get! Funny how that works.   On a completely different topic why is it that in movies when two people get busy one of them always leaves the next morning before the second person wakes up. That is a load of crap, maybe if the girl is an anorexic twig who weighs less than 100lbs she can get out of bed without shaking you awake but lets face it most lady's don't have that much grace when they wake up. The reality is a woman will wake your ass up rather than get up hersefl to get some water or some other dumb shit.   Anyways I am out  hate on   P.S. - Ben Aflack runs like a panzy.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God damn Tampa Bay Lightning. But I have to give it up to the Flames cause that third period hit on Martin St. Louis was top rank hating! Left him cut the hell up, DAMN! Hate on hater 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What's up with this green? It looks like cheap turf, something the Buffalo Bills know all about. I don't know why I chose green of all colors, I don't even like green.   Tampa Bay Lighting better not win the Stanley cup playoffs tonight or else their win will be marred by the fact that the world knows they should have lost game six if the instant replay people had been wearing their glasses and seen Calgary's obvious last minute goal. Besides that what the hell right does Florida have to winning anything even associated with Hockey? The same way Calgary would have no right to be winning a beach volleyball tournament against Tampa Bay, the lightning need to be put back into place. They are lucky that so many French Canadians love Florida, because without all those Quebecers on their team they would be worse than the Buccaneers. It is easy to discount that the Bucs won Superbowl 37 because the sucked so bad the following year. That and the fact that they won it over Oakland.  hate on haters
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To many people are doing well for themselves so I felt it neccessary to come in and start hatin on a World Wide Web level. There are too many people who escape the hating radar, like hip-hop's comeback kid/should have stayed gone  Mase . Yeah but no longer shall these oversights continue, I am here to hate on the hated and the not so hated alike.  You like em I hate em, you hate em I hate. Anyone doing better than me deserves to be hated on and anyone doing worse than me need to stay right where they are.   hate on 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>