<Blog>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Why not? I figured that if everyone else could post their inner-most thoughts, dreams, witticisms, whatever, on the web, I certainly could as well.   I attended a swanky (for Northwest Indiana) shindig on this past Fri-tag, with handmade lampshades, covet inducing behaviour silent auction items, and folks dressed up to the proverbial Nines.  All good and well, actually. Until the girdle I had donned to hide my present state of fluffiness decided to enact its inherent nature-- it constricted. I ended up short of breath, and panting like a teacup poodle. After shaking my proverbial groove thang, I never got my breath back.  My beloved spouse, a gorgeous example of the male species, was worried sick. Frankly, I was a little worried too. I had visions of me going to the ER, and tearfully confessing to some Pakistani doing his residency that I had made the almost fatal choice of combining a "waist nipper" with a pair of control top pantyhose. I had visions of my wake... people tearfully coming up, asking, "what was it, her heart?" and my husband responding, "No, it was SPANDEX." Not exactly a glamorous way to go.  The solution was obvious-- ditch the waist nipper. I slunk into the loo, and regretfully undid every last hook and eye. Rolled the thing up, with its shiny white jaquard printed SPANDEX boned fabric (bad, evil, bad, evil), and placed it carefully on the shelf next to the toilet paper. Needless to say, my diaphragm (the one under my ribs and responsible for the old oxygen in out in out) immediately picked up the disco beat in the next room, and recovered nicely. I dragged in a healthy breath or two, fixed my lipstick, and sashayed out. Bridget Jones has nothin' on me....  I'm off now, dinner awaits. A fine example of rabbit food and protein. The alternative is death by spandex, and that ain't pretty.  Cheers- Slappy 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so this isn't something that belongs on CNN, or Google News, or perhaps, even the web... Wait-- must refresh Manhattan for this particular disclosure. I'm back. I have a three-legged feline named Gertrude Stein. She goes by "Trudy." She a female tortoise-shell cat, and is generally speaking, about 14 pounds of lovin'.  Trudy was, for better or worse, put on a different food for a VERY short period of time. During that time, she developed an unnatural affection for my denim blue bath mat. She would sit on it, purr, and then stand and deliver.  What makes this a tragedy, rather than a politically incorrect bit of humor, is the fact that I DON'T CLEAN OUT THE LITTER BOX. That is not my job. I have lots of jobs, including cleaning the house, making certain that my beloved is happy, grocery shopping, boss is satisfied, etc. I don't do kitty poop. I feel like I did my "job" with this cat when I took her to the vet (me, in tears) and had her nasty, gangrenous leg taken off. Needless to say, there was quite a bit more of my involvement both prior and subsequent. I am also the primary pill-shooter, i.e., I'm the poor sod who pries open her furry kitty jaw and shoots down it an antibiotic, which she promptly delivers, half-masticated, on my yellow rug.  But now... with her pooping. It's multi-colored. It deserves a sound-track... Wagner's "Flight of the Valkyries"... It deserves tickets... it's in my bathroom, and she is a mack truck. Completely unstoppable. And, I am alone. My Other herds teenaged children in Walt's world at the Youth Gathering. Maybe all is as it should  be? Of Cats n' Kittens- Her Slapps 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have a new calling. A new "avocation." I still have my job, I still love my husband, I still make sure that my three-legged cat doesn't poop in my bathroom (more about that later, I'm afraid.)  My new calling is to bedevil the sanctimonious jerks who call themselves "confessional" in the LCMS. Those guys who revel in bringing charges against good men who love their Lord, adhere to the Confessions, and want others to love the Lord... yes, in that order. These confessional knuckleheads who are killing their churches, and driving people from the LCMS. The beauty here is that the Synodical convention has provided "laws," resolutions that bind all of those who have agreed to be part of the LCMS- Lutheran Church Missouri Synod. Where the beauty lies, is that I am a lawyer. I cannot out argue a theologian. I am not trained as such. But, I am a trial lawyer, dammit, and arguing over the finer points and precedent is what I do. I will learn the by-laws better than they, and smack them upside the head with it, like smackin' em with a 2 day old trout.  Jesus would do it. Actually, he used a questioner's beliefs/values against the questioner on a really regular basis! This is gonna be fun. More later- Her Slappishness 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>