<Blog>


<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I saw a 747SP take off today from twenty feet away. I had a ringside seat; the wings drooped with fuel weight until they picked up speed and flexed and lifted that aerodynamic impossibility off the ground. I grin as I realize very few people would know that a 747 with Rolls Royce engines is odd. A bigger grin surfaces when I realize that most people wouldn't know it was a 747, SP or no SP. That's what today was all about. 

						
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The Smiths on vinyl. I'm transported back to a London suburb, 1980, and I'm a rebellious youth with Morrissey speaking to me from a cheap plastic record player. I grease up my pompadour and roll the cuffs on my jeans. 

						
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A year ago today I was sitting on the aft jumpseat of a Boeing 737-2H4, registered as N73SW. As we approached Houston Hobby (HOU), there was a loud snap-bang from aircraft left and we rolled violently in that direction. Bins popped open, galley supplies flew out of their cabinets, and passengers screamed. I held my brace position as commands for an emergency evacuation began running unprompted through the front of my mind. Hundreds of feet forward, on the flight deck, the pilots corrected and we slammed our wheels down on the runway. I felt the contact with the tarmac all the way up my spine as oxygen masks dropped from their stowages and ceiling panels were dislodged. The thrust reversers screamed to life, slowing us until the breaks could bite and stop our aircraft. We sat there for what felt like ages, cabin silent and engines still. Then, as if nothing happened, the engines spooled up and we taxied what was left of our aircraft to the gate. Up front, the senior attendant couldn't even bring herself to make the "welcome to Houston" announcement. Anything said at that point would be meaningless, as our passengers sat shell-shocked, reflecting on the split-second of time when life and death intersected.  The pilots remained hidden behind their locked door, leaving us to deal with questions like, "What the fuck was that?" and "What is wrong with you people?" Once all of the passengers had left to meet loved ones and relay their own version of the incident, the pilots emerged, pale and shaken. "I think we struck our wingtip," said the first officer, as he collapsed into the first row of passenger seats. Maintenance had arrived, and informed the captain that the trailing edge flaps for the left wing had deployed, uncommanded, to their fully extended positions. "You guys are lucky you didn't flip over onto your back." He left to join the small knot of people now gathering under the left wing.  We finished our day after sitting around the HOU departures area waiting for a suitable replacement aircraft, ferrying the aircraft to Tulsa (TUL), and returning home to Dallas (DAL) with three passengers. As I sat in the back of the plane watching the scrolling landscape, future possibilities began unfolding for me. What would have happened had the pilots been unable to correct our errornous roll in time? Would I be alive or dead? Would I be in a hospital somewhere, not even able to communicate with my loved ones? What would they have felt, seeing our aircraft on the Six O'clock News upside down on the runway in Houston? That event would have sent out waves of consequences, each affecting the future in unforeseen ways.  A year later, and I'm making a cake for my husband's birthday. June 17 will always be linked to the celebration of Curt's birth for me. In one instantaneous eyeblink, that all could have changed with grief and mourning forever etched on this day of the year. I can't take this for granted. 

						
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Airport (1970) Starring Dean Martin, Jacqueline Bissett, and George Kennedy  As with all book-to-screen adaptations in the late 1960's, the celluloid version of Arthur Hailey's Airport is groovy, hip, and chock full of cheese. My mother, a reservations clerk during TWA's Howard Hughes heyday, would never pass up a chance to catch the one and only Original Disaster Movie on the Tuesday night TV flick of the week. I would sit beside her, spellbound, and receive more of an education than I ever thought possible.  "Working for the airlines was just like that," she'd say, watching the final credits roll. "Except for that part about the bomb."  At the time, I never really understood what she meant. As an elementary school connoisseur of disaster movies, the vital plot was the bomb being smuggled aboard a packed flight to Rome. I'd simply shrug and go play "explosive decompression" with my chairs lined up to resemble the coach section of a 707, screaming instructions to my stuffed animal passengers, each wearing a Dixie cup oxygen mask held in place by a stapled-on rubber band.  As I grew older, successive viewings revealed the swinging post-Pill world of pre-AIDS sex, and I understood what my mother meant. It was all sugar-coated and buffed to a high gloss...the film is currently rated "G"...but it was there for anyone with a junior-high schoolyard education and an American Heritage dictionary to see. The airport manager was cheating on his wife with the airline agent. His wife was cheating on him. The airline pilot was cheating on his wife with any number of stewardesses. His wife knew and didn't care. I'm assuming my mother meant that working for the airlines was like that for other people; as far as I know I was conceived without any really original sin.  The ways in which these various situations play out really date this movie; there is an unwanted pregnancy and abortion is mentioned as an option, but the word "abortion" is never uttered in the film. Divorce is discussed, but it seems to be an ugly, distasteful concept with genuine concern about the children coming from a "broken home." All the sleeping around is talked about in the most general terms like, "There's someone else" and "You've been bragging about your scrambled eggs. It's time I found out how good they really are." Everyone wondered why I sniggered at breakfast for years.  In spite of the blatant omission of sexual phraseology, the movie follows the book with remarkable precision. All the major plot points, character names, and locations stay the same. What the movie does is take out all the painfully detailed prose about the inner workings of the airport and airlines with which Hailey padded his book and presents a tighter package to the audience. It's almost presented as two movies in one; the story of a harried airport manager trying to keep Lincoln Memorial open during a winter blizzard, and the story of an airplane in peril as a mad plot ensues to collect insurance money.  The whole thing is one big tribute to Boeing, its 707 a featured player in the film. I don't recall the interior of any aircraft being quite that spacious; the coach cabin chairs look like Barcaloungers and the aisle is wide enough to accommodate a Volkswagen. As far as airline procedures and equipment goes, the whole thing stays true to life, even including genuine American Airlines Hostess Patty Paulson in the cast of stewardesses to consult on technical matters (she's the blonde).  The movie boils down to the will-he-won't-he-can-we-catch-him-in-time mad bomber plot. The bomb does blow up, and to their credit the effects people put together the most accurate portrayal of rapid decompression seen on celluloid. Paper flies, Dean Martin is dragged down the aisle, and Jacqueline Bissett is hanging onto the galley curtains for dear life. The suction stops, and the masks drop down. The little bags all inflate, although real flight attendants will tell you that they won't. There's only a single fatality; the mad bomber gets blown up and sucked out of the aircraft when his dynamite goes off. Quite a difference when you consider the massing body counts of subsequent airline disaster films.  The only cinematically important item from this movie is Helen Hayes' Oscar for best supporting actress. She played the little old lady stowaway. That's about as noteworthy as it gets, unless you count this as the movie that laid down the law for all other airline disaster flicks. Apart from the series of sequels (Airports '75, '77, and '79, respectively), movies such as Executive Decision, Passenger 57, and Turbulence all fall into that distinctive Airport mold.  Considering all that's happened in the aviation industry recently, it's nice to trace those roots back to a time before terrorism, security, fuel costs, and hard times befell the airlines. Grab the wide-screen version of Airport on DVD, tip your seat back, put your tray table down, and toast the past with a miniature bottle of whiskey.  

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Damn, I should know better than to break the seal on a whole mess of Eighties memories. Swept up in the whole "Reagan's Dead" craze, I retrieved a few yearbooks, put I-Tunes in a massive New Wave/Power Ballad loop and had a bad trip down parachute pants lane. I am occasionally assaulted by dreams in which I end up back in junior high or high school with all the knowledge and experiences I have accumulated after my parole from the public education system. The whole experience terrifies me as I try desperately to explain that I don't belong; that I have already paid those dues and have the paper and the emotional scar tissue to prove it. I know people who play what-if. They live with the nagging doubts and the desire to change things and the if-only-I-hads. Why in the hell would I want to go back to that? What good would it possibly do? Sure, I could probably tell off the handful of dried-up excuses for educators that I, at that time, felt ruined my life over some science-project diorama or ten-page research paper or drum major tryouts; all of those seemingly all-consuming adolescent goals that, if not reached, presented an insurmountable obstacle of crushed hope.  But what would that accomplish? At the time, nothing. What good would it do to piss off those who had your success and failure so squarely in the palms of their collective hands? Looking back, it was all pretty meaningless. I can recite, from memory, all of those fictional characters who held the post of Captain aboard the Enterprise. I can't, with any reliability, recall the thirteen original colonies of the United States; nor can I tell you the state bird of Florida, how to do that bizarre algebra thing where you rip an equation apart at the parenthesis, or the major exports of Canada (I'm assuming it's some variety of wheat, followed closely by that ham you see on pizza). At some point, my future somehow hinged on knowing these things, and somehow I managed to bluff my way through and came out the other side, none the worse for wear. But I'll be damned if I can tell anyone why I felt such concern over my success or failure at knowing such trivia.  In any case, my trip to the past reaffirmed my choices in life. I am, for the most part, satisfied with what has transpired since. I closed those yearbooks with a chuckle at the hair and a mild curiosity as to who was gay and if they secretly found me attractive at the time. The past is securely the past, and that's the way it should be. Let the historians worry about it. I'm more interested in what's up around the corner. 

						
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I first started keeping a journal in 1986, during the second Reagan administration. Eighteen years later, Reagan's dead, and CNN is chock full of photos and tributes. I drove to work this morning, wondering why flags were at half-mast. Not that I bear any specific grudge against the Gipper; he was the only president I know of that could have gotten away with joking about starting WWIII on national television. However, this was a president who wouldn't even utter the word "AIDS" during the height of the crisis. A president who ran up the nation debt and lorded our nuclear arsenal over our enemies. I remember going to bed worried about nuclear fallout and hoping that Lubbock was far enough away from Dallas to survive the blast.  Lord knows that in this day and age, any criticism of our leaders is looked upon as anti-American. Not that John Hinkley Jr. had the right idea...but as presidents go, his track record on the HUMAN issues left a little be desired. He has a library and an airport. Put his face on some currency and let it be. 

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I remember my mother singing "Bill Grogan's Goat" to me when I was a child, probably wierded out of my skull from a fever or an ear infection. Vomiting goats, trussed up for execution underneath the wheels of a speeding locomotive. No wonder I am who I am today. 

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's summer. Cloying is the operative adjective to describe that zone between July 1st and September 31st. Suffocating. Killing. These are crazy times of year; crazy things happen and logic tends to be out doing laundry just when you need a rational anchor for your dingy. Heat increases entropy. Too much energy going into a system, and poof! It tends to explode. Like tempers. Like wars. Like love gone bad. Like similies that go nowhere. "It's too darn hot," said Cole Porter. "Darn tootin'," I reply, and buy him another drink. 

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Saturday night promise is in the air, as thick as club-smoke. Promises that drive us to do the things we do. It's shaped judegement and decision for decades. It's what everyone looks forward to and what everyone regrets. It fills a social niche like no other night. Magic and nightmare both. Social order is hanging by a thread like a cheap button. I hear the words "normal love" spoken in conversation. Ya know, I'm not even sure I can comment on that. Is there such a creature? Should I attempt to define "normal?" Maybe I should just laugh like a loony, jump up on my jittery table, and dump my Americano over my punkin' haid. Yee-haw. 

						
</post>


</Blog>