<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      gosh. sometimes i just get so frustrated i want to scream. of course i cant because its 11:40 at night and everyone is asleep. but if i could i would. because im getting just so sick and tired of everything. i mean my God, im trying. i put forth such a freaking effort to see those kids. they could care less though. all they do is smartass and make excuses. which drives me to piss and whine all night long. NONE OF THEM CARE. not a one. and theres freaking five of them. gah! i would kill to see those kids, but i think theyd rather skate or something. usually i wouldnt care, i enjoy watching them skate. i love the kids, but when im not there it pisses me off. when im like 'lets see a movie' its never "okay yay we get to see each other!" its "a movie? how boring." well. hmm. okay, lets do something unboring. like lets all go raid some skate park. considering the whole group cant skate, but what the hell. who cares about the skating impared kids. they can watch. gah. well. this sucks. tomorrow i wanted to do something but it looks like just another boring ass day. welcome to my world. ugh. i give up. i just...give up. gah i am such the little emotional kid. sigh. farewell.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well. today was boring. but i got the sick SOB permit!!! whats up! only missed one question too. hmph! well then i watched the lion king and the last samuri. the lion king was better, hands down. timone and poomba still make me laugh. sigh. well tomorrow i dont know what the hell im doing. maybe a movie with clayton, maybe watch the boys practice. who knows. fare well
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay im bored so here we go. (i stole this from kay's melo)  HAVE YOU EVER... 1. kissed your cousin: no 2. ran away: yep. im damn good at it too. 3. pictured your crush naked: course not... 4. skipped school: ive faked sick? 5. broken someone's heart: i guess 6. been in love: eh, almost 7. cried when someone died: i try not to in public 8. wanted someone you knew you couldnt have: all the time 9. broken a bone: nope 10. done something embarrassing: oh yea 11. lied: haha :) ya 12. cried in school: i havent in a while. like since sixth grade.  WHICH IS BETTER...  13.coke or pepsi: pepsi 14. sprite or 7up: oh my gosh theres a difference? 15. girls or guys: guys. definetly. 16. flowers or candy: candy. but flowers from a boy. 17. scruff of clean shaven: only a selective few can pull off scruff. 18. blondes or brunettes: black. 19. bitchy or slutty: both suck. but bitchy i guess. 20. tall or short: this is just rude now. 21. pants or shorts: pants. hands down. 22. night or day: NIGHT.  WITH THE OPPOSITE SEX...  23. what do you notice first: clothes and posture. 24. last person you slow danced with: nick in feb. 25. worst question to ask: why did you break up with nick?  THE LAST TIME YOU...  26. showered: today 27. stepped outside: today 28. had sex: like a virgin, bitch. 29. romantic memory: sigh...  WHAT IS (YOUR FAVORITE)...  30. your good luck charm: lucky underwear? my rings. 31. person you hate most: man i dunno. the devil? 32. best thing that has happened: um...world without end. 33. on your desk: i dont have a desk anymore 34. picture on your desktop: world without end 35. color: black 36. movie: almost famous and other stuff 37. artist: favorite artists are overrated. no such thing. 38. cars: i dont care. 39. ice cream: chocolate. rocky road. chocolate almond. 40. season: fall right before winter. 41. breakfast food: bacon bitch  WHO...  42. makes you laugh the most: whitney 43.  sorry folks there is no forty three 44. can make you feel better no matter what: no one. 45. has a crush on you: no one. 46. do you have a crush on someone: hopeless. 47. who has it easier? guys or girls?: girls have babies, but guys have wet dreams. i dunno. guys prolly. 48. give you a funny feeling when you see them: what is this funny feeling we're talking about?  DO YOU EVER...  49. sit by the phone waiting for a phone call all night: oh yeah. 50. save msn conversations: log manager. 51. save emails: i have my special folder :) 52. forward secret emails: secret emails? that was like so sixth grade blah! 53. wish you were someone else: ...ya. 54. wish you were a member of the opposite sex: yea alot how sad. 55. perfume: sometimes 56. kiss: not lately 57. cuddle: not lately 58. go online for longer than eight hours at a time: not continually. thats what away messages are for.  HAVE YOU EVER...  59. fallen for your best friend: yep. 60. made out with JUST a friend: nope. 61. kissed two people in the same day: nope. 62. had sex with two different people in the same day: nope. 63. been rejected: many times. 64. been in love: like i said, almost. 65. been in lust: yes, sadly. 66. used someone: no. 67. been used: ...ya. 68. cheated on someone: kind of. not really. kind of. 69. been cheated on: ...ya. 70. been kissed: yeah :) 71. done something you regret: nah.  WHO WAS THE LAST PERSON...  72. you touched: martin i think? 73. you talked to: clayton 74. you hugged: martin 75. you instant messaged: nick 76. you kissed: nick 77. you yelled at: oh man... 78. you thought about: haha, i'll never tee-eell 79. who text messaged you: nick 80. who broke your heart: oh man, tons of kids. 81. who told you they loved you: kayla  DO YOU...  82. color your hair: ya 83. have tattoos: nah 84. have piercings: ya 85. have a bf/gf: no 86. own a webcam: nah 87. own a thong: nah 88. ever get off the damn computer: nah, why would i do a silly thing like that? 89. sprechen die deutsch: uhhhhhhhhhh, one more time? 90. habla espanol: nah 91. quack: oh yes im very fluent in duck.  HAVE YOU/ DO YOU/ ARE YOU...  92. stolen anything: from my friends, but they know about it. 93. smoke: no way jose 94. schizophrenic: i dont know. yes. shhh. no. YES. no. gadamnit shut up! you shut up! yes. NO. 95. obsessive: yep 96. compulsive: whats that mean? 97. obsessive complusive: uhhh 98. panic: paranoid as hell 99. anxiety: my friend lisa says i am very much so. 100. depressed: this questionaire thing brings up hurtful things and painful memories.  thats it kids. farewell.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well. its 11:11 make a wish. okay its 11:12, too bad. nothing is great. ive watched thumbelina and spiderman today. why? why not? sigh. i pity you blogreaders that come happening upon my journal thing. i must continually disappoint you with my boringlifeness. my sincere apologies to you. well time to go talk to nick and joe and the likes of them. farewell.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      kids, its like 8 40pm on a tuesday night in the middle of summer. and i am home. home and bored. home and chocolate chip cookie less. bored and hungry and tired and headached. woe is me.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just returned from kristin's. last night mark and martin and joe and nick all came over to her place. my dad's sickness is coming back so that is sucking majorly. not to mention jimmy woke up puking last night. well my mom gets to go have a 'moms night out' with other exhausted mothers tonight, leaving me to 'cook dinner'. word is im making "spaghetti". shouldn't be hard, huh? riight. we'll see.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You are Captain Jack Sparrow. You love to drink rum and you walk around like you live wherever you happen to be. You are a very dishonest person and therefore you can be trusted to be dishonest, honestly... You are very clever and never forgive people if they betray you. You are also very agile (good for climbing up ropes and standing on the masts of sinking boats).    urlLink    Which Pirates of the Caribbean character are you?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      U know Everything!!!!! (please vote!)     urlLink             How much do u know about Pirates of the Caribbean?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Fight Club!    urlLink   What movie Do you Belong in?(many different outcomes!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Emo!  You're very in touch with your emotions and that's what I like about you!  It's all about the music for you...  I have pity for your tortured soul...you're just like me...    urlLink   What genre of rock are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well kids, today has sucked some mondo assness. and it all started with me falling down the freaking stairs this morning before church. sigh. well all ive done again today is watched tv. nobody called to do anything today so im assuming the boys are doing something on their own again. i talked to nick at like midnight something or other once he got home from dallas. he said the tour was incredible. i am absolutely blue with envy. ugh. well im still bored. anyone wanna do something? eh, give me a call, anything's better than this. im currently watching romy and michelles high school reunion for about the fifth time. anyone feel like saving a poor soul? anybody? anybody?
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well all ive done today is watched old home movies because im so bored and so lazy and so incredibly envious of those stupid boys that are currently stationed in dallas, warping their brains out. hmph. well im getting ready to go to kristin's house and we're babysitting our little siblings while i parents go and have dinner with our principal? sounds like a riot night for them, eh? well im ever so bored. i look like butt right now too. but frankly my dears, i dont give a damn. sigh. later.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      good eye, sniper i'll shoot you run   im beginning my pissing and moaning over not going to the warped tour tonight, so beware. maybe call every hour or so to make sure i havent died in my dark little corner? thatd be nice of you.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, today was quite the boring, uneventful day im becoming accustomed to around here. i did the little vbs thing again this morning then watched tv then slept then went somewhere then came home and watched more tv then called clay to see about seeing a movie but then that didnt work out so i watched the top forty sexiest country music videos. it was interesting? well then i watched raven and phil of the future with my little brother and here i am now. i think i was supposed to go see the stepford wives today with a bunch of chicks but they never called or anything so nothing happened. nick bought a new deck today. a baker or something. never heard of it, but whatever. wow my life needs some kind of crazy good thing to happen right now. sigh, later kids.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      went to nick's today. watched martin and nick skate at some school parking lot. went back to nick's. watched mark and fergs and nick all skate. and watched joe read a magazine. and watched kristin twirl on the pick up truck and watched caitlin play with her little camera and watched kayla talk on her cell phone. its kind of weird going back to being bored forever after that trip, because we were going all the time in florida. i saw the boy of my dreams today on knock first. he had emo hair and was really funny and was my age and was in a band. he said girls dont tend to like him, he needs to meet me. sigh. well then, im bored out of my mind and dont know what to do with myself. so i think i will go because i think i will drive everyone up the wall if i continue. farewell.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's been a while, hasn't it my avid readers. well disney world was fun and such, however i am very very very glad to be home at long last. the days seemed to pass ever so slowly. dont get me wrong, i loved the trip and stuff, but id rather be with my friends than mickey mouse. nevertheless the trip was grand. anyways, from what i hear i missed a buttload of drama this past week, ... thank God too. well tomorrow i must awake early. EARLY. to work some vacation Bible school camp. its gonna be a nasty little obstacle with a bunch of third graders... well then, lates
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just kidding guys. cant update my pic because...i dont know, the little 'edit profile' link is gone. so sorry, i think you'll live though.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well blog readers, this is my final farewell before my weeklong trip to disneyworld with the van horns. i must admit, although im leaving on awful terms with a few people, i will miss them all terribly during my absence. i know its only a week, but a week from the gang is like a month practically. i hope they miss me, although im sure they are yearning for this break from becky and all the crap she brings to the group. oh well. this new picture is really me. not a very good looking me, but a me all the same. see you guys in a week or so. i love you guys. gosh i sound like some stupid chick when i say that, but oh well. goodnight kids.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well kids, today was my first day on the real roads. heres a tid bit of advice, no matter how much i pressure you into getting into a vehicle with me, dont do it if you cherish your life whatsoever. nah, actually i wasnt that bad for my first time out. there was one point i couldnt figure out why the car wouldnt move, the lady was like "honey try the gas pedal". comforting, eh? well last night at the guys' gig, they did really really well. guitars went a little nuts towards the end of the night, but they still did really well. hypocritical me, i got stuck with the damn video camera again. oh well hope they like it, if they dont, bite me. i tried my damn best. didnt talk to russell all night long, hardly spoke to any of them, really. mark was rude and nick wouldnt listen and joe blew me off for some short bleach blonde tube top ladies. sigh. there was one super hott guy there, of course he had to be the worlds biggest asshole according to my dear friend alice who has dated him before. sigh. i have the biggest problem meeting guys. stupid movies that make you think guys come up to you and introduce themselves and they are gorgeous and perfect, haha HELL NAW. its never like that, sorry ladies, one and all. someday i will find my beautiful little emo boy...maybe, perhaps. sigh. well yet again i have managed to surpass my expectations for the length of this entry. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well kids, today was my first day on the real roads. heres a tid bit of advice, no matter how much i pressure you into getting into a vehicle with me, dont do it if you cherish your life whatsoever. nah, actually i wasnt that bad for my first time out. there was one point i couldnt figure out why the car wouldnt move, the lady was like "honey try the gas pedal". comforting, eh? well last night at the guys' gig, they did really really well. guitars went a little nuts towards the end of the night, but they still did really well. hypocritical me, i got stuck with the damn video camera again. oh well hope they like it, if they dont, bite me. i tried my damn best. didnt talk to russell all night long, hardly spoke to any of them, really. mark was rude and nick wouldnt listen and joe blew me off for some short bleach blonde tube top ladies. sigh. there was one super hott guy there, of course he had to be the worlds biggest asshole according to my dear friend alice who has dated him before. sigh. i have the biggest problem meeting guys. stupid movies that make you think guys come up to you and introduce themselves and they are gorgeous and perfect, haha HELL NAW. its never like that, sorry ladies, one and all. someday i will find my beautiful little emo boy...maybe, perhaps. sigh. well yet again i have managed to surpass my expectations for the length of this entry
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello. im back at home, and bored again. sigh. the group i hang out with...we all have so many troubles it seems. and now that school is out, we see less and less of each other... but somehow i think im about one of the only ones who even cares. i mean GOD FORBID that any of the guys ever call me and ask to hang out or if i want to go do something. i always have to call. and make the plans. always. and when i ask if they will for once, it doesnt really work out because i dont think half of the lot of them give a damn. i mean come on, im not a 'friend', im only good for being the 'groupie' for their band. at every show, always taking picture, videotaping, etc. always. and it hurt because last year during volleyball, they came to one game...didnt even watch me. gosh i dont even know why i bother with writing any of this down. just had to get it out eventually. still mad at russell and nick. if russell thinks he can talk like that to me, he is sadly mistaken, and is in for quite the rude awakening. nobody talks to me like that. ever. not nobody.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello my sweets. today was interesting...for once. doesn't happen often, but it did. im at kristins place right now its one:27 am. we got into a few bickerments with some of our mates today. three i think. kayla and russell and nick. i dont know why everything is so uptight these days. its like this: everyone thinks they can keep secrets from everyone else, however, everyone else finds out anyways. in our group, it is never a two person thing, its a nine person thing. pitty, eh? oh well. not so much. makes things interesting i suppose. better than being bored silly. not that i intentionally try to fire people up, that would make me a clayton vaughan. anyways, so we are getting ready for bed. i swear, our lives are like dawsons creek...i mean, so much drama, so much sensitivity, so many secrets and such, but NO ONE HAS ANY SECRETS!!! EVERYONE KNOWS EVERYTHING ABOUT EVERYONE. whew now that thats been taken care of i think that we shall go to bed now, and share secrets. haha. wow im awful humorous tonight. this is turning out to be longer than i had anticipated, so good night, one and all.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you are very good at making it very hard to say goodbye. you know all the right buttons to press to get me to cry. ive always wondered why this happens to me, i know thats nothing to be proud of, its just sometimes, i crash and burn...but maybe i deserve it. just wanted you to know im sorry. i know ive een a prick- i cant help it lately. im gonna fix it, gonna change everything ive done wrong....im really bad with these apologies, saying im wrong, saying im sorry, it just isnt like me. but im sorry for everything. i know youve met your wits end with me- this is my last chance to prove that i can be the same old me. its just sometimes, sweetheart, i crash and burn, but ive been thinking and maybe i deserve it. just wanted you to know im sorry for everything.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh man that pic really isnt me, but lets pretend
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is just one more heartbreaking day; alone and surrounded by four heartbreaking faces: constant reminders of the luxury i will never have again. And if i had patience i would sit here waiting patiently, yet thats just one more virtue that i lack.  So i face the skay and i'm gonna bargain with God untill im black and blue in the face  i know my lamenting wont erase my mistakes. it's times like these i wish i could spontaneously combust on comand, but since i cant i'll just sit here quietly, wanting to scream, biting my lip till it starts to bleed, i need to know whats happening to my life.  So i face the sky and im gonna bargain with God till im black and blue in the face  I'm one more headache away from self mutilation...and i feel a killer coming on. Life's a bitch and im just so sick of it all.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is the price you pay for loss of control.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay so today during rehearsals for the play TOMORROW, nobody except me and like two other people knew their lines. it was GOD AWFUL. so, i tell everyone to stay afterwards and we stay till like seven just rehearsing and getting people to memorize their lines. then me and chelsea and marissa watched jole and sean fight with the 'sword' things. i ended up in the middle of it. it was funny. wow i love this camp so much...so so so so so much. i love the plays and shakespeare and the lectures and memorizing and everything! its so brilliant! sigh. im so happy! im excited to HOPEFULLY take stage combat classes! i feel bad i had to blow off analiese tonight though because i stayed to rehearse more. but oh well me and her will hang out some other time. well tomorrow is much ado! hopefully everything will go smoothly...hope hope hope. say a prayer for me kids. and in the senseless words of dogberry "be vigitant!!! i beseech you"&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; fare thee well 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahhh the sweet odor of shakespeare...tonight i stayed to see hamlet after my performance for yet the third time. that accumulates to nine hours of hamlet in the past four days. sigh. i love it. tonight thus ended the 'scene showcase' meaning, no more princess katharine of france, and no more poofy skirt, and no more speaking french and making french rampages in front of english audiences. but nonetheless, it has been a most enlightening experience. and i have a whole other week of it to come! happy am i! this week we will learn more about 'emotion' and more about 'shakespeare' and 'improvisation' and we'll have our rehearsals all week for this coming weekends productions of:  the merry wives of windsor  and  much ado about nothing . i play the fair hero in much ado and also the slimy verges,&nbsp;companion of the very witty doggsberry. t'will be very good plays and you all must come! im so&nbsp;very excited! its like these people ive just met are my family! i wish camp wouldnt end in just a week! every single one of them are so cool and unique and SIGH i just luvva them all! well, fare thee well, im off to bed. i awake early for more shakespeare. goodnight. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey boys and girls. so i found him.  him.  he's nothing like ive ever expected. complete opposite of everything ive ever wanted. i didnt know guys like him existed. he's tall...like 6'1''. brown hair, very very short. loves and reads shakespeare. brilliant, funny actor. gentleman. and the bad....he was a bad boy in his highschool. he got kicked out because of fights and yelling at teachers. (youd never know). he smokes. ugh. and uh... he is 18. GOSH. age is the most stupid number. hes so nice. and...he ACTS. not only any plays...SHAKESPEARE. and he READS it WILLINGLY. he's in my drama camp. thats how i met him. wow...i feel so incredibly stupid. sigh...i can only hope maybe he will by any grace of God maybe possibly like me and not care about how old i am. i mean, hes so nice and so funny and we talk and its great .... sigh. big fat sorry-for-myself sigh. ive been sighing out the wazoo lately. anyways......i hope. i hope i hope i hope... farewell kids. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what the hell, kids? ive been gone all damn weekend and i come home to no comments? sigh. i expected more from you. im kidding here but not really. at least i got some on my xanga. time to go check melo. im a bit sunburned but the jetskiing was worth it. farewell for now 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      was kind of sick today but i am feeling much better. everything is so much better. i mean i havent talked to a soul today but i feel so good knowing that im okay with everyone and everything. even though it meant swallowing my goddam pride for once. sigh. my mom decided to be nice today and made puppy chow. for those of you who have no idea what that is...its chex stuff mixed with chocolate and powdered sugar. it is very good too. sigh. tomorrow i want to see my friends again. then my im going to my gramma's house to spend the night and teach her about the wonderful manipulative satanic device we've all come to know and love: the computer. shes even paying me to teach her how to use the computer and internet with all its superpower glories. well as for now i am going to go and update my melo and i dont know what else. maybe relax. big sigh of relief: ahhhhhhhh. farewell kids.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don’t think its easy to sit here and keep a straight face when my insides are screaming for one more go round. Its been too long to just give up. We could be the next batman and robin. Just help me out here, let me know youre trying too.  My sincere apologies for everything ive screwed up in the past. You gotta know im trying here, for your sake and mine Don’t get the wrong idea, but I cant live without you.  There’s more to love than laughs and jokes and we would know better than anyone. Its not the easiest road, but im willing to conquer hell if you’ll just stay real close so I can hear you breathe. I need to know youre gonna be there, I know I know, just reassure me.  My sincere apologies for everything ive screwed up in the past. You gotta know im trying here, for your sake and mine Don’t get the wrong idea, but I cant live without you.  You are my calm after the storm My princess Zelda that id die for You are my better half You are the prettier side of my moods  You are everything to me You are the epitome of my sympathy The vital link The missing piece.   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ever wanted to just drop dead? yeah well right now i feel like my heart is going to explode and i am going to just die. doesnt sound too bad right now though, actually. sorry kids, i know im being depressing but i seriously feel like the epitome of the finest shit. sigh. i guess i prolly shouldnt really continue with this entry. i wonder if i will even post it. i think maybe i wont. but myabe i will. who knows. kristin returns tomorrow. finally some companionship. i fucking sick of being alone. i know my assholes of friends dont care. i could be dying in a god forsaken gutter in the middle of nowhere and they wouldnt give two fucks because they wouldnt know because they dont care. whew. feels good to get that out. farewell.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      in one of those moods. one of those GAHHHHHHHHhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh moods. spent the whole day with the family. maybe thats why. im listening to vindicated by dashboard confessional. i love this song very much. i think im going crazy. like i really think so.     VINDICATED I AM SELFISH I AM WRONG I AM RIGHT I SWEAR IM RIGHT SWEAR I KNEW IT ALL ALONG AND I AM FLAWED BUT I AM CLEANING UP SO WELL I AM SEEING IN ME NOW WHAT YOU SWORE YOU SAW YOURSELF.   fucking computer.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey bored again cause whitney left. so here's yet a third thing that i stole from daph..hope you dont mind.  FIRSTS:  First best friend: kendra cover First real memory of something:swallowing a music box key First funeral: some guy i didn't know. First Crush: sam hochenaur First pet(s): pepper and sandy i think First credit card: yet to achieve that First enemy: i dont really know First big trip: disneyland, CA or jamaica First play/musical/performance: preschool  LASTS:  Last kiss: its been far too long...like may. Last good cry: tuesday or wednesday i think Last library book checked out: merry wives of windsor from shakespeare Last movie seen at movie theater: DODGEBALL, hail vince von Last beverage drank: milk Last food consumed: grapes Last tv show watched: celebrity feuds on VH1 Last time showered: today Last cd played: hmm, warped tour 2004 or avril lavigne Last disappointment: everyday since disneyworld. Last soda drank: caffine free coca cola Last website visited: daph's melodramatic Three things you are often complimented for: haha uhhh. complimented? my hair on a good day i guess. You get embarrassed when: oh hell im always embarrassed about something  Yes or No...  You keep a journal: yea You like to cook: NO You have a secret you have not shared with anyone: yes. You set your watch a few minutes ahead: like twenty minutes You believe in love: almost...very very very close  Do You...?  Take a shower every day: usually Have any crushes: oh how i wish Think you know you've been in love: huh? Have any tattoos/where?: nah Piercings/where?: my ears  Think you're a health freak: hell naw  Get along with your parents: no. but i guess we have our moments   When you see this name you think of...  Ryan: short hair Rob: nerd or funny Drew: quiet Stephanie: like, like, omg! omg!  Heather: quiet Aaron: good looking Amy: pretty Paul: dork Eve: tall and skiiiinny Alex: boy or girl? Justin: wangsta Ricky: 'lucy! how many time do i godda tell you!' Jack: buck teeth. short  Random...  Screen Name: thecox182 Sign: sagitarius Natural Hair Color: something between brown and blonde Current Hair Color: blonde Eye Color: green Birthplace: holy trinity hospital in oakland california   Favorites...  Number: 2 Color: black Day: saturday Month: november/december Song: itd be sinful to name just one Food: chicken noodle soup Season: fall right before winter Drink: vanilla dr pepper and hot chocolate Vegetable: corn (its the only vegetable i eat.)   Preferences...  Cuddle or Make Out: oh cuddling wins over my heart. but kissing is nice :) Chocolate Milk or Hot Chocolate: Hot Chocolate  Dark or White Chocolate: milk chocolate Vanilla or Chocolate: Chocolate    In the last 24 hours, have you...  Cried: nope, for once. Helped Someone: nah not really Bought Something: no Gotten Sick: No Gone to the Movies: No Gone out for Dinner: ordered in pizza Said "I love you": no Written a real letter: yea Talked to an ex: Ya Missed an ex: uh Written in a journal: online one Had a serious talk: no Missed Someone?: ya kris is in stupid tennessee and the boys hate me Hugged Someone: no  Kissed Someone: no
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well whitney is upstairs showering and i'm eating lunch. chef boy r.d. and milk. pretty exotic, huh. well im super bored. today we all go pick jimmy up from camp. i decided to be a good sister for once and so i cleaned his room for him and made his bed so it will be nice when he gets back. mom never did that for me, so i figured i'd do it for him. make sense? oh well it doesnt have to. i did whitney's make up today and it look pretty okay. my mom even liked it. i was pretty impressed with myself. well so much for the boys. still am yet to talk to joe. its been like a week now i think that i havent said one word to him. i didnt talk to nick all  yesterday. mr. callaway leaves for friggin boyscout camp in colorado for a week tomorrow, so that will leave me no one to talk to online anymore. i talked to russell again, for a little bit about not very important stuff. but there was no fighting. yay for me. i havent talked to mark since the fourth of july because he never IMs me these days. and i havent talked to fergs since the fourth either because he's never online. sigh. its tough not having them around all the time. i always thought that this summer, id see them every single day and it would be like some movie summer and be just perfect. but then all hell broke loose. and now i dont even talk to them or see  them everyday. im sorry, but i dont know what the hell is up with that. i mean they are my best friends and now i dont even talk to them. gosh. it all just pisses me off thinking about it. and sometimes...most of the time, i think maybe they like it better without me around or something. i mean none of them really seem to care as much as i do that we never ever see each other and stuff anymore. so whats to make me believe otherwise? sigh... farewell kids.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      title provided by the one and only whitney. haha. well thank you daphne and kayla and caitlin for the comments. muchly appreciated and i will be sure to drop by your melo's and such sometime to return the kind gesture. dont forget my melo-emolovesongs! i need some friggin karma. well i dunno where everybody is but whitney and i are about ready to go chill and watch 'dolly dearest'... some horror movie about a doll that possesses a girl and lots of people get chopped up. :) well, farewell.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well guess what kids, i have one avid reader! wahoo! cait check your blogspot commentary box thing cuz i left you a note in there. also, this is my-what?-fourth entry today. i am insanely bored, people. well. well. uhh. at a loss for words. oh i am trying to start a melo thing too, i doubt it will work out as well as this, but in case youd like to check it out, my user name is emolovesongs. so go have some fun. buh bye.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay kids. i KNOW that SOMEBODY has to be reading this blog. please leave me comments. i feel lonely. where the hell are all my viewers? comments are good. remember that. leave me one and i will try to return the favor. im bored and farewell again.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      guess what kids? im bored crazy again, so you all get to read another questionaire post thing! have fun.  1. name? rebecca suzanne 2. are you named after anyone? nah 3. do you wish on stars? yah i do, why not 4. which finger is your favorite? middle..mwahaha. 5. when did you last cry? last night. damn friends. 6. do you like your handwriting? yeah sure, its not very feminine though. 7. what is your favorite lunchmeat? cajun turkey. oh yea 8. any bad habits? i bite my nails and smack gum and have bad table manners. 9. what is your most embarrassing CD on the shelf? first off, they aren't on a shelf, they are in a box. secondly it would probably be limited too store music CD. hey, it was cool when you're 9. 10. if you were another person, would you be friends with you? yeah. i have my moments...i can be fun. 11. are you a daredevil? with some things. not with food. sensitive tummy, you know. 12. have you ever told a secret you swore not to tell? yeah, havent we all. 13. do looks matter? haha yeah sometimes...how shallow of me 14. have you ever misused a word and it sounded absolutely stupid? yep yep 15. you think there is a pot of gold at the end of the rainbow? yes! SUPER! 16. do fish have feelings? yes. 17. are you trendy? haha nah not really i dont think 18. how do you release? music. always. singing. writing. im very odd like that. 19. where are your second homes? kristin's house. not really nick's anymore, but i guess so maybe? i dunno. and uh...i dunno. im pretty much of an in-my-room kid. 20. do you trust others easily? hell naw. 21. what was your favorite toy as a child? my banky. i still got it. oh and my barbies (hangs head in shame) 22. what class in school do you think is totally useless? all of them except the fine arts. oklahoma history is dumb. math and science...not necessary. 23. do you have a journal? blogspot. i have a notebook i write poetry and stuff in...does that count? 24. do you use sarcasm a lot? it is the foundation of my personality 25. have you ever been in a mosh pit? yes some are pleasant, some are scary. they are fun to watch from a distance most times. 26. what do you look for in a boy/girl? lots of stuff. i am insanely picky about my boys. usually how they relate to music. how cheesy. 27. what are your nicknames? beck, cox, coxy, rebecky, becka sue, beckster, quebeck, that tall blonde girl 28. ever bungee jump? nah 29. do you untie your shoes when you take them off? nah 30. do you think that you are strong? yah to an extent. 31. whats your favorite ice cream flavor? chocolate, rocky road, chocolate almond 32. whats your favorite colour? black (dont go 'ugh') 33. what is your least favorite food? any condoment besides ranch and honey (if you consider those condoments)and all that animal parts and bugs that they eat on fear factor. vegetables. man, lots of stuff. 34. how many wisdom teeth to you have? four i think? 35. are you in love with anyone? vince von, johnny knoxville, and tom delonge. thank you. 36. how many people have a crush on your right now? none. how sad :( 37. who do you miss most right now? all my friends. havent seen any of them lately. i miss sir romeo too! tis been forever! 38. do you want everyone you send this to to send it back? uhh 39. what colour pants are you wearing? jeans..blue? 40. what are you listening to right now? coheed and cambria-three evils 41. what are the last four digits of YOUR phone number? 7176 42. what was the last thing you ate? sonic 43. if you were a crayon, what color would you be? black. everyone needs a black crayon. when i was little i always needed it and could never find it. id make sure people could find me and get their money's worth outta me. 44. how is the weather right now? hot sunny, blah. 45. who is the last person you talked to on the phone? kristin. 46. first thing you notice about the opposite sex? what they are wearing, their attitude, how they walk, their face and smile :) 47. do you like the person who sent this to you? i stole it from kayla, but i love her dearly. 48. how are you today? bored, cold, kinda pissed, kinda lonely. 49. favorite drink? milk, vanilla dr. pepper. 50. favorite alcohol? "i only drink baleys." pssh. sorry kids, i dont drink period. 51. favorite sports? i like to play volleyball, i like to watch basketball and skateboarding 52. hair colour? right now, blonde. 53. eye colour? green. blech. 54. do you wear contacts? yep, im blind as stevie without em 55. what would you change about you? oooo you really wanna know? hell, prolly most everything. 56. would you like to be rich and have no friends or the opposite? the opposite. 57. favorite food? mmm chicken noodle soup, never gets old. 58. last movies you watched? dodgeball (vince von is genius) and stepford wives (bette midler and the gay dude make the movie) 59. favorite song at the moment? oh boy...down, a decade under the influence, favor house atlantic, lost without you, lover i dont have to love, maybe im amazed 60. are you too shy to ask someone out? yes. very old fashioned about that stuff. 61. scary movies or happy endings? i love horror, happy endings make me jealous. 62. summer or winter? winter 63. hugs or kisses? um, depends on the person. 64. relationships or one-night stands? relationships. though one night stands sound tempting... just playing kids. 65. do you fancy anyone at the moment? there was one guy but he's out of the question and i know it, so im looking for my perfect little emo boy :) :) :) siiigh 66. who is most likely to respond? what is it with you people 67. who is least likely to respond? sigh 68. what books are you reading? the merry wives of windsor (for drama camp) and catcher in the rye (for honors english) 69. girls: thongs or pants? pants. definetly. thongs are like one major wedgie all day long. 70. guys: boxers or briefs? boxers are nice 71. favorite board game? does twister count? haha good times. uh trivial pursuit junior. its fun to kick eric's ass at that game every new year. 72. what did you watch on TV last? uh insomniac music theater. 73. what are your favourite smells? some boys, cookies in the oven :) and uh... cat crap. kristin loves that smell too. haha. 74. what is the first thing you think of when you wake up in the morning? need more sleep or shit its cold! 75. wouldnt it be nice if whenver we messed up our lives we could simply press 'Ctrl Alt Delete' and start all over? it might be alright, but sometimes mistakes help to define who you are. plus i try to refrain from doing things i will regret. 76. would you ever do a one night stand? huh? as in sex? no. but sometimes i get lonely... def. no sex though. 77. whats your favourite choccie? chachi? what the hell is a choccie? 78. if you were famous who would you be? if i was famous wouldnt i be myself? sigh...to be famous... 79? DO NOT WRITE IN THIS BOX [box? what box? ooooo i get it! oh wait, no. no i dont.]  well kids hope you had fun with that. now you should know more about me than my parents. farewell.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well today i actually left the house. i bought a rug for my room and long last and have decided what table im going to buy. for the rest of the day, i believe i will sit on my butt and drink my sonic vanilla dr. pepper. it's quite tasty. im currently talking to nick. surprise surprise i know. im being very short though, which is probably very rude, but im still kind of pissed. very pissed actually, but not feeling very agressive. sigh.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its exactly 12.33 am. today i havent spoke to nick or joe. i said a few words to russell which, i admit, was surprising. even he realizes that none of us talk to each other anymore. im waiting for that movie-like moment when all of them will just stop what they're doing and they get all doe-eyed and suddenly understand me and what i've been trying to get through to them. that im not just choosing to be mad, but that i was really truley actually hurt by their cruel words. i know im just getting my hopes up and its not going to happen, but when you are home on your butt all day, you cant blame a kid for daydreaming. oh and im still looking out for some guy to sweep me off my feet. i have high standards though. sigh. well. farewell i suppose.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well kids, im not-so-proud to announce this is only the fourth time i have left my room all day. sure, its sad, slightly pathetic, but what the hell? kristin left for memphis today so its not like im going to be doing anything at all the next few days while she is gone. havent talked to the guys all day, either. oh well. lets see, havent talked to joe in a while. and i fought with nick last night. he pissed the hell out of me then expected me to be all happy and loving life the next instant. sorry but im not quite that artificial. im not gonna pretend to be all happy and okay with them. gosh they really know how to piss me off.  and as a result of being virtually friendless right now, i have the extraordinary privledge of spending entire days locked in my room in the dark. its been one hella summer so far, let me tell ya. hmph. farewell.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      saw dodgeball with miss alice dinger. it was a very good movie. i want to marry vince von. siiiigh. where can i find mr. right tonight? i feel very dumb when i say i miss being kissed. it is sad, you know? sigh. im gonna go kiss tom delonge or johnny knoxville or something. goodbye folks
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      home from kristins now. woke up at about 12.30 and now its about 2.08 and im bored. im going to be bored all day long. dad is still sick. jimmys gone to camp for a week. kristin leaves tomorrow for tennessee. this means i am a very very very lonely little girl for the next while. sigh it sucks. sucks very badly. well, farewell then.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well happy fourth of july my fellow free, patriotic american citizens and aliens alike. the boys came over to kristins house, where i am stationed right now, and we made lots of big noises and bright lights :) we even set little ferggie's shoe on fire and set off an artilery shell in his other shoe. it was sick and smoking afterwards haha. good times. joe didnt show up thought because he is in guthrie or something. the boys are going on a 'road trip' tomorrow, which is just driving around getting lost untill dark. i want to go with them, but they're prolly just gonna be stupid and not let me go because they do that alot. maybe i can persuade martin though since hes the driver and the nicest :) sigh well nicks mom brought cookies to the party and they arent all gone yet so i think im going to finish them off. still upset, but i dont know what to even think anymore. goodnight you firecrackers you!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well. i have alot to say and no time to say it all. sometimes i cant believe the things that are said about me. i hate being thought of as some monster. i hate not being sexy or anything like that. but i guess i did this to myself? i just hate how people can be sometimes. i know im probably being dramatic. im not going to deny everyone of the simple pleasure of telling me im hypocritical. right now i dont care. im just kind of drained. and tomorrow i have to wake up and go to church and then get ready for the boys to come over. i dont know why i bother with sick attempts at looking 'pretty' or decent at least. they are absolutely fatal and pointless attempts. well my eyes hurt and so i think i will go either cry or sleep because those are the only two things i feel like doing. farewell urchins.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well. i have alot to say and no time to say it all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      some friends, huh? you think you know a person. then they say something behind your back to turn others away from you. others that had potential too. im still not sure what was said, but i am going to find out. gerrrrrr. stupid stupid stupid. who was i to actually think my 'friends' would say nice things about me? i dont know.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well dears i chit chatted with joseph and nicholas last night on the internet. joe had nothing nice to say. all he did was tell me how i feel and what i think, and trust me, i did not like that. so i guess, according to joe, all i want to do is insist on stirring up trouble. because i guess i love to fight. and nick and i hardly said anything. im 'choosing' to be mad i guess. well screw them. screw them all. i didnt see any of them at all yesterday. probably will not see any of them again today. or saturday for that matter. i guess i may end up seeing them sunday at kristins party at her house, because we invited them already a while ago. i'd be very surprised if they even call to figure out what time it is or if they need to bring anything. sigh. its weird without them though.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      shit i forgot the best part of the whole damn night! kristin and i met... get ready... connor and seth! seth was so...ahhh emolicious. hhahah and kristin and connor had a LOVE CONNECTIONhaha well lates
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well it's been like, what? fifteen minutes since my last entry? but im bored and there's nobody online worth talking to. please get on your AIM and talk to me. please. thecox182 at your service kids. sigh.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello. just got home from quail springs mall. kristin and i saw the stepford wives. it was such an awesome movie, im buying it as soon as it comes out on DVD. anyways, in other news, no word from the guys at all today. sigh. oh well. like i said, i give up. hopeless i tell you. well i think im going over to kristin's tomorrow night to watch the new episode of degrassi. i love that show with all my heart. anyways. im bored. we saw brady my old friend from school at the mall, and his friend david. it was nice to see him again, he's a good kid. he's turned into a prep, but oh well. the light side is taking over the world these days. i took a quiz today and it told me i am a passionate lover. so according to all the quizzes ive taken i am a major emo kid that knows everything about pirates of the carribean and should be jack sparrow, i love passionately yet i belong in...fight club. hmmm. i dont know. well, well, well, im at a loss for words as of yet, so good night folks.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well hell. everything is so weird. havent communicated with any of the boys since nick last night. and certain 'things' are leading me to believe im not necessarily needed around them anymore. who needs emotional becky when you can fantasize about some girl youve never seen and never will. when theres a girl forever away, a year younger that says she loves your music, but is yet to hear it? what use is there for real fans anymore? stupid boys. gah. maybe someday they will learn that a band is only as good as the fans that love the music. sigh.   because i need you more than you need me because i want you more i know because we moved too fucking fast i think i really had to wish to make this last i know im sorry, please forgive me believe me, if you would because i cared way more because i really felt that you felt so much more i know
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sigh so ive been updating my xanga like crazy. so if you want to catch up on me, check there. basically ive managed to already get the whole band pissing down my neck. very pleasant, i assure you. gosh. well i dotn know what to say, ive got alot of everything on my xanga. ive got some pics from camp and like a hundred entries from today and yesterday or soemthing. so go check there for now. the username for that is savoreverymomentofthis. have fun kids. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its killing me. murdering me inside! i cannot, will not believe camp is over. all performances were beautifully and smoothly done. and now its over and i want to cry. i cried the other night when my mom drove me home because we were talking about highschool and i how i hate it so much and dont want to go. she was all "becky i know youre 15 and its hard to fit in" oh man that got me going. i was all "MOM IF I WANTED TO FREAKING FIT IT ID SMOKE SOME FREAKING POT LIKE EVERY OTHER SENSELESS LOSER THAT GOES TO FREAKING MCGUINNESS" ugh. pissed me off. so yeah i cried myself to sleep that night. my mom says that its hard right now for me in highschool because ive gotten a taste of what is waiting for me outside of the box. she says once i get to college i will meet more people like the drama kids from camp. man, the boys at camp were crazy. like tray would always say "have all the ladies gotten food yet?" before hed ever eat. and they ALWAYS held open the doors for you and never let you carry heavy things and never ever made you ride in the back seat. haha tray always made jole sit in the back. he said "pretty ladies get the front seat" :::::::smiles:::::::: oh how i will miss camp so sincerely. i didnt know kids like them existed. i pray to GOD that tray and jole and sean and lorryn get this youth thing set up quickly because its only been my first day off from camp and inside im already dying. camp made me so happy. like a happy i havent been in such a long time. everyone there is so secure and loves everybody and watches out for each other and dont care if theyre going to 'look stupid' or if theyre going to 'risk being cool' by singing or dancing or acting or any of that. its so great. so amazing. so DIFFERENT than everything im used to. its crazy. its like ive had a taste of happiness and of course it was only two weeks. i so wish it had been all summer. all year even. gosh it was so fun, so amazing. tyler, the director, is moving to new york in january, im gonna miss that guy. sigh. well. im going to part before i make myself cry again over lack of camptation. fare thee well. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>