<Blog>



<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "panapanahon lang yan"  i was about to complain about the bad weather today when okram said "ibira mu pa!" he was reffering about the wind "amihan" why? because he is a surfer and when the season/wind is right man! it's like waimea out there heheh the bad thing is that im not a freakin surfer! and they (baler boys) are the only ones wishing for the big storm to come in our town! the good things is that for 5 years or so this little town havent had any storm not even a weather condition near to be a called a storm. thank God for that! amen!  sarap matulog!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im bored that's all...  this has got nothing to do with all the drinking sprees with my friends...  im just freakin bored...  i wasnt able to sleep well last night because of okram.. di na rin kami nakauwi! sobrang sakit ng ulo ko and it's freakin me out right now...  detoxify muna..  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      happy 16th bday Jano! i dont know if you'll be able to read this but anyways, your 16 now... wag kang gagaya sa kuya mo! hehehe
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      pang apat na Combo drive ku na itu! makainip na! ngayun naman de aku makapag-burn ng CD peru pwede naman sa ibang file format! lugi na ako masyado sa PCexpress!   marami na naman akong 311! ewan ko kung bakit taka na lang aku at yun na lang ang lagi kong nabibili? ayaw ko naman talaga sa hip rock?  happy fathers day kay erpats!  uwi na kayu ditu!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i learned from okram my friend that 311 was actually from Australia. World Tribe is from California and the band have decided to go on their separate ways according to Ricky Guinto na pinsan ni tikbalang... pero magkatunog yung ibang songs nila sometimes pareho sila na boses s ibang kanta.. dami ko pala naripped na kanta ni Ben Harper from five albums courtesy of Okram and im planning to collect all of their albums!  natuloy din piknik ng sublime! as usual inuman pa rin pero this time with bulalo naman!  sarap siguro mag compose ng songs ulit! though wala akong inspiration ngayun wala lang gusto ko lang... try ko tonight..  mismu!  my mistake 311 pala is from Omaha... i checked the 311 website... si okram talaga heheh
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      anu na baga itu??? bat parang ayaw na yata nila magkaruun ng presidente ang Pilipinas? nakakapikon na rin si Nene Pimentel ayaw na nniyang tantanan yung ballot box no. 21 samantalang pwede naman desisyunan ng de na tumagal duun lang sa isang urna na iyun pero naiintindihan ko siya dahil biktima dinn naman siya ng dagdag bawas. wag naman na silang magpapogian/pagandahan at magpagalingan sa TV ilabas dapat ang katotohanan na dapat malaman ng taong bayan!   de natuluy picnic namin ng badfish wala daw traysikel si okoy sayang dalawang kilong bulalo pa naman iyun!  pass muna sa alak...  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have this terrible terrible cold for three days now... on the first day it felt like i was goin to die... just like a wounded soldier behind enemy lines... there's not much that i can do... all of my body parts aint workin like they used to... and i am hatin this nose of mine right now... parang gripong sira tulo lang ng tulo! eewww! but i am feeling better now... tomorrow is a big day for me and that woman... yeah! im still thinkin what to give her though...  ohh.. o-ohh.. o-oohh... hoo... yeah~
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nice sms...  RECD NOTICE APPROVAL OF PETITION. WAIT FOR LTR FR INS.  tagal pa niyan heheh
     

    
</post>


</Blog>