<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG I can tell ya right now this is going to be one very long marching Band season. My section is stupid and then none of my friends were signed up for cabins so i was kinda like SCREWED!!! O well i guess. Life shall go on (i hope) On a better note, well for me atleast, i get my permit tomorrow. YAY!! I am so excited. I get to drive a car and make it go vroom vroom. LOL> Am I ok?? NOPE Don't think so. yea but anyways....  Jake was talkin to me today about like grooms-men and bride maids and maid of honnor. I think i know who i want mine to be i just have to get her to agree to it first. (Jessi.....I don't know how to day this but.....Will you be my ...Maid of Honor???)Lol sorry had to do that felt this great urge to. O well u gotta tell me one way or another cuz i only have 6 more years to plan this. God i better get started tomorrow. LOL! J/K. Yea even Mr. Turner says he can't picture Jake's future life with out me in it. Suprise suprise. Hey wow i just thought of sumtin only 6 more days till i get to go to ceader point with my Jacob SWEETNESS.  Ok i got called an over-acheiver by Header. Of all the ppl to get called that it was me. She only said that because Turner said sumtin about how i help with the little kids. Speaking of the little kids, tomorrow in the concert i am playing with all 3 bands. So is Jake tho. In the 5th grade band i ain't even playin my clarinet, i am playin percution cuz Turner need more kids back there so he sent me back there then Kassie Powell asked me to play tomorrow in the concert and i agreed to. O well no biggie. I just look more uh.....well i don't know what i'll look like a fool more then likely but o well.I'll get over it i think.   Hey Jess many thanks to the comment. You know wut i am talkin about u so said the truth and that just needed to be said and it needed to come out of sum1 else other then me or Jacob. So Thanks if u get this while u r up north. U gotta tell me how it is up there and wut i am messin out on. Nah i ain't missin out on nothin i got all i need right here in Durand. Ok well i am outie P34(3 0|_|7
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yup that is from a song by Trapt. I love that band. But yea last night was so eventful. Kristelle decided to tell me that her and Jacob did stuff Sunday night at that senior camp out. Which i know they didn't Jake had already told me that she was gonna say that and that it wasn't true. I know if Jake had done anything with her he would have told me cuz i would forgive him. I would only get mad if he tryed to hide it. I know what it feels like to hurt someone by cheating on them and then not have them forgive you. It sucks and I would not do that to Jake ever!!! Besides even if Kristelle had gotten me and Jake to break up He wouldn't have gone out with her. He would be pissed at her for breaking me and him up. I mean come on i already had one person try to break me and Jake up so that he could go out with me (Lame attempt) I mean that is suck a dorky way to get someone to go out with you. I mean come on eventualy they are gonna break up so just wait. O but if u are waiting for me and Jake to break up again FORGET IT!! It ain't happenin. We have already had all our breaks up. We both know we want to be together forever and ever. I love him to much to break up with him again.  Ok nothing fun at all happened today. Pat and Dad are gone to sum retirerment party. I got to stay here. Which is probley a good thing cuz i wouldn't know any of the ppl there neways. Tomorrow Jake is probley taking me home tho. My mom and Dad both said ok. Well accutly my Dad was tryin to paun me off to go home with Jake cuz he had a golf game for tomorrow and his tee-off time is at noon. So yea. I don't know wut we are gonna do. I think mall sounds kinda good too me. Maybe some foodage. I got money this time too YAY. LOL Ok well i am out p34(3 0|_|7 
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok i don't know why i used that as a title other then i am hungry and i am waiting for my food to cook.I know i havn't written in a while but i seem to have been busy the last few nights and tired and goin to bed early. I got my show music tho i am happy now. I have been waiting to get it. I love bein able to have music that is harder for me. The shows is starting to sound really cool. I had my doubts at first with it bein another insect show but this is one is really cool.I have been playin with the lil kids latly or helping them. It is sooo fun.   Today i went and got my birth certificate so on thrusday i can go and get my permit so i can drive YAY. I am so excited. This should be so much fun. Heather drove yesterday to band praticce and screwed her parking up majorly. But today while i was in flint i saw a Durand Area Schools Drivers Training van. It was sooooo funny I have to say tho, I am not all that excited about going into Flint there is way too many one way streets. But o well i will survive (I hope)  Today i am supposed to go to my dads but i am not sure if i am goin tonight or tomorrow. It depends on which day he gets back from the road. The company he works for has been sending him out on the road latly so he is gone all week. He gets to see lots of places tho. That would be kinda kool but in the same way i wouldn't want to have to do it for work. O well he has done it b4 and he can do it now. Ok well i think i am heading out P34C3 0U7
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yea it is one of tho's nights when i am like tired as F**k but i can't sleep so i got back online and like no one is up in my house so it is really creepy. But yea today I talked to Jake and we worked everything out with the hole thing last night. I think we are both gonna work harder on bein better about things. But yea. He said sumtin about him and Kristelle gettin into a fight b4 he went to bed and if it is becuz of me i feel bad. I don't want to ruin their friendship. That just wouldn't be cool. I am sorry for everything Jake and Kristelle i should probley be k1|_|_3|) (killed) for causing as much trouble as i do. I am so sorry to anyone and everyone i have hurt.  Here is a happier note. Tomrrow i get to go work with the little kids again. \/\/007!! I like them they are so funny. O yea today i had to take the test for drivers training. I had the highest score out of our hold class. I had a 97%.\/\/oo7 go me! I can't wait till i can drive on my own. I shall be a good driver. I think i will be anyways. LOL. Thats sad i don't even know what kinda driver i shall be. O well. But yea. So wow Jessie and my brother friend Dave were talkin to me tonight i they are a trip. They both have this obssesion with shooting and killing ppl. That can't be good. Not at all. LOL. I think i shall just try to stay away from tho's two.  O Katie guess wut. MONKEY BUTT!! Ok i have no clue why I just said that but i felt the urge to put you in one of my blogs. LOL so there ya go you are in my blog how does it feel? Well you should have a thank you in here cuz u help both me and Jake alot. You give out really good advice. How did you get so good at that?? I would like to learn how to do it. :-D Ok well i am gonna go bed bed night folks P34c3
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a poem I wrote last night when i was upset or i might have written it two nights ago. O well w/e i still wrote it sometime when i was upset. LOL    Mind Games    Does he still like her? Why do i ask this? Trust i always had  now resides as fear I say it's alright your just her friend. but a picture dances in my head of a kiss from more then friends Then all of a sudden  you snap in my head "I love you babe she she is just a friend" I want to trust you I really do It just seems so hard My wondering mind makes pictures pictures of dsiloyalty  Why am I playing this game A horrible game with myself. I can make it stop for now untill the next night for when i lay down it all comes back again!!  By:    Kari        Locke
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yea well some ppl arn't gonna wanna hear this or like what i have to say but it has to be said. Last night Jake went to the senior camp out and there is nothing wrong with it and i don't have an issues with Kristelle anymore but i just have the feeling of untrust with Jake. Like last night i feel like he could have been tempted to do sumtin with Kristelle. I want to say that i trust him compleatly but he is a 17 year old guy wanting to experiment. Then it seem like latly we have talked very VERY little. He just wants to see me. And then when he does see me all he wants to do is well... use ur imagation. I'm sure u can figure it out. So it isn't that i mind doing it sometimes but it is a consent. Like everytime we see each other. We can never just chill out and sit around. And everynight my suspsion about Jake likeing Kristelle grows more and more. I just don't know where to ture anymore. So please if anyone has any advice (Katie talkin to you) Plz help me out here. I do love Jake but i just and a lil scared right now. Where do i turn. What do I do??? I AM SO CONFUSSED!!!  Jess to you my deepest sympthy to you and your "significat other" issue. LOL Two of us both crying over guys on the same night this is suckie of the assie. LOL. Ok well that is all for now lata i shall put my pome in here i wrote last night!! Peace out,
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am sad. Jacob is sickie. I don't want my Jacob to be sickie. I just want to make him better. *I hope you get better soon babe* but I went on a shoping spree today. It was so much fun. I got to go to the mall and I bought a charm and earrings. I bought a CD and i bought a bunch of farey stuff. I love Amy Brown so much. She does such need art work. Mom said that when she gets her two weeks off in August that we are gonna redo my room in my theam i want. I am so excited. I also got to help mommy pick out the new sofa and chair. It is a really pretty color green. I wouldn't mind having it in my house when I get older. O yes Jacob today was thinking of names for lil shit'lins. I like that Names Zach, Seth, and Kendra. Yea I am odd ball. *I know it is more then love baby I can feel it when I am close to you* Song by Los Lonely boys. I went and bought this CD today. My masha even likes it. 5\/\/33t.  Ok this week some time Jessie, Devin(her significat other), Jake and I all need to go see garfield. That would be 5\/\/33t. DOUBLE DATE!!!! YAY. lol. No I am not sane for all tho's who are wondering. Just thought I would clarife that small fact. LOL.   Ok well I have to wake up in the morning so I can go to church and get ahold of Jess to see wut is up with the us seein each other tomorrow situation. Wow that sounded wrong. LOL o well i will write more lata Peace out,
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, another long LONG day. I woke up at 6 this morning and it is now 11:30 at night.  But in one day i have seen the sun shine, The clouds roll in, and seen it pour rain. This is all metophicly speaking. The sun shineing was when i was with Jake today (which was a lot) The clouds were drivers training, wow so much fun to sit there. Well the pouring rain was seein the resault of my stupidity takein out. I talked to Kristelle today. She is upset about Jake. I thought that they were broken up when Jake and I started goin out. Well u can guess the next part. SHe didn't know so when she got back from where ever she was, camp i think, She found out the very hard way. Well i know that feeling like all you want to do is die. So we talked and we worked out all our issues. More like my issues but regardless we are friends again. And if for some weird reason JFT reads this he needs to talk out his issues with a cartin person cause she needs it right now.  Ok happier note. I got to go see Riddick it was a 5\/\/33t /-\55 movie. Me, Tre, Jake, and his sis Jill all went to see it. Then we went and ate at NewPort (Where Jake and Jill work) And i think i ate too much cuz right now i don't feel all that well. O well i think i will go to bed SOON. O yea u might wanna tell you this 5\/\/33t /-\55 accutly means sweet ass in leet speak. Stupid Tre teaching me stupid stuff that is totly pointless. Ok well peace out
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O my O my what a very long day today has been!LOL. No i am not ok but o well i guess  Jake still love me and thats all that counts. So do you wanna hear wut happened today? O well you are going to anyways (that is why you are reading this) Well lets see today i hepled Jake make his blog (you can read it. it is jacobloveskari.blogspot.com)while i was supposed to be helping with the little kids band this morning it was so funny. Then Mr. Turner told me to go help the lil 5ht graders keep time. They are really funny. So then when they were Tré come to pick me up and we went and got subway. YUMMY. Well then Tré and i decided we didn't want to sit in the house on such a nice day we went to the mall. I spent a bunch of money. I got the New Found Glory CD i got a book of art work by Amy Brown.(and if you don't know who she is she does really cool drawings of faries which i am obssesed with.)And i got a record (Yes record) of an old AFI cd. I felt very special. Wait i am a very "Specail" person.LOL. If you get my drift. So then Tre and i came home and started to watch 50 first dates and then Jacob called me with some very bad news. He said it was nothing to get upset about but his daddy and mommy might be moving. I guess i won't worrie about it yet but i don't want my jacob to move. I was planing on haveing atleast till the end of the year with him then i know he will gradumatate but that is still a long time. So anyways after i got off the fone with (cuz he had to go to work) i took a nap. Then at like 5 heather called me to ask me if i could give her a ride home then like 10 mintues later she calls me back to tell me that she doesn't So then i eat and go to pratice and goof around. So yea that was my day. How was yours?? Peace out
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW! Life is great. I am back with Jake I am happy with everything. Brenden took the hole break up thing really kool which is great. Sunday Jake and I went to see Harry Potter (which sucked) And we went out to eat and then he came back to my hose an we just chilled and crap. It was great. Today i went to work and Melvin worked along with Brenden. It was funny Melvin is sooo funny he was constantly making me laugh. He does scare me tho. LOL. o well. Lots of ppl scare me. PISTONS ARE GONNA WIN. Yes i wrote this b4 the game was done. I hate basetball! LOL yea i just like contadicted myself o well tho. YAY Driver traning tomorrow just lil kids band then i have my band. I love helping with the little kids band. They are soooo cute. LOL. Ok well i am out PEACE
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok well today was a good day. Jake and I are back together and we are happy. Me and my mom worked things out(i think). And I got to go to my daddie-o's. I love being here it is so relaxing and a nice envrionment. My dad was teasing me about Jake and Kristelle it was funny. My dad is really weird. Him and my mom have beem devorced sence i was like two so it doesn't really affect me that he isn't around me all the time. He is moving at the end of the year ,i belive that is when he is moving. I will be sad when he moves but i just keep thinking about after he moves how i get to go spend the summers down there in South Carolina. O well not like i can stop him from moving.   Drivers training is boring! I don't get to drive untill like next Thrusday and I am sad. Last time i drove i almost ran two stop signs. LOL. I didn't mean to, I couldn't see behind the cars. O well i havn't hit anyone yet. YET being key word. LOL. Nah i won't hit neone i am a good driver. I think.  peace out,
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today was an OK day i guess. I know that there is stuff I have to do and i am not sure how I am gonna do it yet! I will be back with Jake by tomorrow for sure. I am not sure i could take being away from him for much longer. I miss him so much. But last night was a lil rough. After i wrote my entry last night i read Kristelles blog and found out some things I didn't know. And in wone part she claimed that " ...so even when he was going out with Kari he liked me..."! So of course I was all upset and crying and all upset. I called Andrew and i started to think that maybe i did like him becuz Jessie told me that the guy who is really ment for me might be right under my nose and i just never relized it. Well i don't think that is true cuz i miss Jake way to much. So I gotta go take care of him and tell him that when i said that I like him that I was just a lil confused. I still have to break up with Brenden but I don't think that it will be to hard.  Ok I am so cold. Yesterday was so warm. Today it is SOOOOOO cool. I just wish there was sumone here to warm me up. (hint hint JACOB) LOL well that wasn't obvious. O well. Just thought i would throw that in there. Cuz I love my Jacob. Ok well I am out  Peace out,
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so not much happened today. I am doing a little better but still i am depressed. I just want my Jacob back so bad. I have not talked to Brenden or Jake all day. I have been gone most of the day and then when i do come home they both are working. O well i guess. I hopefuly will talk to Jake later tonight when he gets home from work but that depends on when he gets off. But if i do not and he reads this i just wish of him to know that I miss him and I love him.   On another note. I started accutly driving today in drivers training. I found out i have one very lead foot. LOL. Yea that would be me the lil speed demond that I am. LOL. O yea and I drove out by Bryon skools and i found out there skool is TINY. I never thought my skool would be bigger then anyone elses. This is short I know but o well.  peace out,
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I wrote some pomes and thought I would put them in here for you guys to read...   Last Hope.  A tear falls from her check it hits the animal she holds He gave her it, a birthday gift In the other hand she holds a picture all her hope she once had fades instantly.  They told her it was stupid, it wouldn't last she faught, she lost, got right back up finally she buxkled, her strength broke  They won she said, he left her there after The other force won.  She put down the picture she picked up the knife once again a tear falls hits the cold steel blade her breathing stops. He cries at her bedside, shes lost forever    Deadly Mix   Look at my finger, theres a ring flip it over, my wrist bleeds. This pain felt, it's loves fault this pain felt, it's influenced by the knife. Which is worse emotional which is worse phycial both caused by me my stupid f**k up I lost my baby. My best friend. The knife keeps me company the blood and tears mix death falls upon me a never ending slumber. Don't let another tear fall, thats why I did it. Just move on, she'll be there, she loves you too. Just pick and choose join me if you wish it is so peaceful here you'll learn soon my life is your life too!
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well once again a suckie day in my life. You know i really try not to wallow in my self pitty but i just am so upset right now. Jake is going back out with Kristelle. I am still going out with Brenden and to make things all the better my mom talked to Nan today and found out that i was going out with Brenden which i had not told her as of yet. O well she made me relize that i am not only hurting Jake but i am hurting Brenden and Kristelle which I really don't care about Kristelle but i do care about Jake and Brenden. All I know is that i want Jake back and i just can't bring myself to break up with Brenden. I don't want to hurt anyone anymore. Maybe so i don't hurt anyone else i will just hurt myself. I would rather do that then hurt some one else.  On a happier note I give thanks to two of my friends, Dean-O and Kim. They kept me from killing myself. They were there for me when i needed them and i relized that people really do care about me. I saw Dean-O today at our performance and he gave me a hug and just told me that i will be ok. He is such a great help to me. Kim tells me that I will live. I need to hear that sumtimes. They are both such great helps to me. Heather and others help me to i just hope they noe that.  I tryed talking to Jessie about this hole thing today. She just told me that being 15 engaged and trying to kill myself is stupid and she won't standby and just watch one of her friends kill themselfs. She hung up on me. I feel awful but I guess wut ever she thinks is wut she thinks. I know i just want my Jacob back.  peace out,
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok it is offical. Jake will not leave me alone. He doesn't get that i just want him to go away and leave me alone for a little while. I thought that ast night i still had really strong feelings for him but i think i was just in the moment. Today he came up to optimist where i was working and brenden was working with me and it was the worst thing ever. I finaly relized that i want to be with Brenden for a while and Jake is just like always there afarid to let go. Even Kim told me she doesn't think that Jake is getting it throught his head. I talked to Jake just a lil ago i stoped writing to talk to him. He said he might go out with Kristelle again. I don't really care anymore. Well i do but i just don't want to confess that i do. Life is so confusing to me. I just know that i want to stay with Brenden for a while. I do love Jake don't let urself be fooled there. It is just that i feel like i love him too much! is that posable? Well i guess now it is!!! O well. I'll write more tomorrow i must go watch eurotrip now ttyl
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey wow my very own journal everyone can see. LOL. Thats ok tho!  I guess I have a lot to put in here lets start with who I am. I be Kari and if you didn't already know that I live in Durand area. I don't know if much else should be put in here cuz if you are reading this you probley already know who I am.  Ok I shall tell about the mass confusion Jake and I caused yesterday. We went to see shrek 2 cuz we were bored and we wanted to hang out. So after we saw the movie we went to where Jake works to get foodage and all the ppl he works with saw me and as far as they know we are still together (which doesn't hurt my feelings any) So after we left they were talkin about if i was cute and the head cook said that i was and one of the waitresses said i wasn't. So the head cook said "she is cuter then you" and i guess she went and started ballin her eyes out. So when the manager told the waitress to close up she didn't tell the cook. So the poor cook had to stay late and finish closing up. Poor guy. I sorry I caused havic!  Onto my next thought. Ok I am stilling going out with Brenden and I know that in all honesty I don't really want to be. Yesterdday when Jake and i want to the movies we kinda....kissed. I know i shouldn't have but i couldn't help it i know i want to be with Jake I just don't know how to break up with Brenden cuz i told him that i would stay with him longer then a week and anyone who knows anything about this situation knows that it is weird and confusing but all i know is that i want to marry Jacob.  Ok no more sad story. I start Drivers traning tomorrow i am so excited. LOL.   So peace out
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One simple ring ment is good way can cause more trouble then anyone could ever exspect. God Jake buys me a ring and everyone goes apeshit. I think the world might end becuz he bought me a ring. And you know wut i am really sick of everyone thinking they can run mine and Jakes relationship. They all think they know what is best for me and Jake and they don't. Me and him kno wut is best for us so why does it seem like we can't run it? Everyone says "you guys are too young" or "you guys won't every last" i am sick of hearing it. It doesn't last&nbsp; cuz everyone else gets into our realtionship. I am so sick of all this. I am sick of Kristelle too i know i shouldn't be saying this but all i hear from jake it seems it Kristelle this and Kristelle that. She is always staring at him and i am just sick of it. I am sick of kim constantly comparing me and Jake to her and Keith. We arnh't them so stop tellin us to do the stuff you do. She just makes him more upset all the time. she thinks she doesn't but she does.O yea and on top of all this just to make this whinie bitchie blog even better i havn't talked to Jess in forever i think she is just tryin to ignor me. When she does call i am at band pratice she just desn't have time for me anymore and i guess i should just except it now.  Ok this is to clarifie and the ring thing. I love the ring Jake got for me it is sooooo pretty. It is just causin WAY to much trouble.  Ok on to a better topic i leave for band camp in like in two days. I am so excited. It should be fun fun fun....RIGHT. well in sum ways it well be but in others it won't be. O yea i evn missed a concert i really wanted to go to tonight so that i could be at band pratice. O well. well i am gonna go i think i am gonna go to bed i am too pissed to stay up. Night yall 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Hey all&nbsp;ya loyal readers out there. How is it all goin with you today?? LOL! Yea i am phycotic. But o well. But i think i might have a stalker stalking me AHHHHHH......LOL! Yesterday I saw my "stalker" at the BBQ and then&nbsp;I saw "IT" again today at the grocery store. Then i sware&nbsp;"IT" drove past my house today. O well maybe it is just my imaganation. I hope it is just my imganation. But today i went to the mall with Jacob and got my ring. It is really pretty. I am so excited.I am really hyper for some reason tonight. It might have to do with the yummy shake i made. SUGAR GOOD!! Well tomorrow pre-camp starts, kinda. We have the picnic tomorrow and all the freshmen find out who thier masters are and everyone finds out who is in thier cabin. I am not to eagar to find out my cabin seeing that none of my "friends" are in it. If you are wondering about my friends in quotations it is becuz as of right now i feel like i have no friends really. Like even Jessie feels like she is drifting away from me. She is always somewhere else having more fun then she would ever have with me. O well it don't matter i got Jake and a couple of other friends and that is all that matters. O yea Brenden won't be in band this year. he was over in Europ and he hyper-exstended his knee and tore a ligament. I feel so bad. That is just really REALLY suckie. But Matt returned home safely,&nbsp;I think. He said he was gonna come out and see me when he returned but he hasn't, o well he is probley doin better things then bug me. WOW i can't belive that the summer is almost over with, it has seemed so short but yet somedays it seems like it shall never end. I will be glad to go back tho. I want to see my "friends" again.&nbsp; I think b4 the summer is done with tho i want to take a cuple of friends and go play laser tag. It sounds like fun. I know that Katie would enjoy it. Megan might go with me again too. ok well i am done talking to the wall now so peace out ppl   ~*~Karebear~*~ 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey Hey yall. Long time no talk but there hasn't been too much goin on latly. Today i went and sat up for the chicken BBQ for tomorrow. (Go and Support the Band yall)&nbsp; And now i am kinda sore like my hands are like majorly sensitive to everything. O well tho it was fun and worth it. Cassie Spence and here lil sis were there Melissa Stout, Elizabeth Tomason, Coutney and Kenzie Howard, Fishie, Danielle Stratkin (sorry i know the name ain't spelled right) and Jake were all there too. Of course T and Nan were there too.&nbsp;I kinda learned today that the girls that i thougth were awful arnt all that&nbsp;awful.&nbsp;They are accutly pretty cool in there own way. But i am glad that we have the seniors we do cuz they are neat-o. But today was a lot of fun even if i did have to wake up at 7 to go there. I did get home till like noon but thats ok it kept me busy. I have to go clean house today to. But yea next week band starts. YAY pre-camp week is a busy one. There is a lot of pratice and a lot of getting used to the new freshman just like the upper classmen had to do to us last year.&nbsp;I remember not being able to read my drill the first day it was great. I wonder where Cassie and Kristelle shall put me this year. Last year Heidi put me where i was concently at the back of the feild but it was fun i could always find me. LOL. But i am giving up a concert to go to pratice this week i think sumtin is very VERY wrong with me. My mom got tickets to Seven Mary Three and i really wanna go but it is on Thursday and i don't really wanna miss pratice. O well there will be other concerts in my life. OMG&nbsp; Saturday is my family reunion and i like don't wanna go. But if i do go i have decided that i wanna take Jake with me. He might as well be part of my family. Sooner or later he will be they should just except it NOW!!! LOL. I am ok i sware. But yea my family reunions are boring and sin the only fun thing to do is go swiming in the lake. But even sumtimes that ain't all that fun. O well i shall survive i guess. My bro's b-day is the 1st of Aug. and that is the day i leave for band camp so i won't get to see him that day. O well he is a butt head anyways. But i should probley get going i have a bunch of work i need to get done. 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *tear* i miss my Jessica Marie she needs to get back to her house so she can come over and chill with her girl the one the only KARI!! Lol. nope i am not ok. But she does need to get back i need to hang out with sum1 other then Jake for a while. I mean i like hanging out with Jake i just need to have other contacts too.But i well i am screwed right now. But yea. Yesterday Jake and I went to the movies and dinner again. This is becoming our sunday ritual. I kinda like haveing this as a ritual. It is way fun. We went to  New Port yesterday to eat and Tim was looking at me. (Tim is the cook there and he always tells Jake he will bring him condoms) But yea Tim scares me. He asked Jake the other day if " he had taped that shit yet?" RIGHT!  NOOOO  But yea. Jake had the house all to himself till tuseday. Then Jill comes home. Other events are going on then too. lol. we won't mention tho's tho. lol. But i don't really know what else is going on. I am starting to think of ideas for my party i want. There isn't too much i can really do around here. I wanna do the water thing but mommy says that would be to boring! O well i think tho that i want a stero and a bon fire. I don't know what else to do. I need to ask Cameron if his band is still together and get them out here to play sumtin that would be kool too. I just wouldn't know who to invite cuz i don't have a lot of friends and i want a big party. O well i guess i will survive. (I hope) ok well i am out of things to say so i will talk to yall lata P34(3 0|_|7
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok i think something is wrong with me cuz latly i can't sleep and i can't eat and GRRRRRRRRRR...........this is pissin me off.but o well. Yea Tuesday i went to ceader point with Jake and his family it was cool. I was kinda in a weird position cuz like i don't like coasers but i went newayz it was a lil weird. But o well i still had a ton of fun. But yea. yesterday was my day to rest i did absolutly notheing like all day long. I was gonna mow lawn today but it looks like it is gonna rain and it is really REALLY cold outside. so o well  i guess whatever!  I can't wait till sunday i am hoping my mom will let me go and see Spirder man and go with Jake and go do our sunday thing. I like going and doing stuff on sunday it is fun and relaxing. But Jake wants to go eat at newport so one of the ppl he works with can meet me. Tim still scares me i don't really know why he just kinda does. O well...ok loss of things to say peace out
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all. Sorry about that last entry i was just a lil depressed but it is all good now so yea. But anyways I am like tired and wore out and i have to go to bed at like 9 tonight so i can wake up at 5:30 tomorrow so i can go with Jake and family to Ceader Point. But yea last night Jake and tre and mom and I all went to go see pretty lights in the sky it was fun. I had a family get together yesterday too. It was so cute Makenzie kept askin me and Jake if we were gonna kiss. Then she asked him if he wanted to  marry me and she said that we should get married today. It was so cute. I think it made Jake want to have kids. LOL. O well still have to wait till we are married and livin in a nice lil house sumwhere with......ok i'll stop day dreaming now.lol. but yea so i will go nuttin more to really say i guess peace out yall
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will be short and sweet and for anyone left who for some strange reason still cares about me. I am saying goodnight to the world. And if i may be so lucky i shalln't wake again. So goodbye for this shall be my last good......
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok this is kinda in responce to a comment i had posted on my last blog. One lets get this stright it is my section too not just YOURS and i was mad at one of them so you know what just shut up now. Too I never treated you like a whore if i had done that i would have belive that u and Jacob did something that would be treating you like a whore. And last but not least, how do you think you have the right to say that Jake and i our relationship "dead on the water" Do you live our lives or spy on us and know every tiny thing that we do? NO i don't think so!! So how can u tell me wut we are. You have no idea. So I wanna know who gave you this idea that u can just go around tellin Jake and I what and how our relationship is?? Stay in your own relationships and stay OUT of mine. I guess i thought if i left you alone you would leave me alone but i guess that ain't the case. Oh yea i don't want you to forgive me even tho you have to reason to be pissed at me you are the one that lied to me!!! Ok I am done with this sh*t!!  Ok now on a happier note. Well i don't know how much happier but more pleasent thats for sure. I have been so busy the last three days. Thrusday i went and did the concert in the park. That was really fun. Elizabeth Ward played with me when i played with the little kids. Hooch and Jason Ward played trumpet with all three of the bands too. I didn't play with the 6th graders cuz i let the percutionist play the stupid cymble part. Well after that i went out to eat with Jake and his parentals. I saw Jake and Harper there. They were being dorks. They were puttin the bibs on there heads and around there necks like capes. LOL it was accutly funny. But yea then Jake came back here and we chilled for a bit.  But yea then yesterday i cleaned bathrooms, did the dishes, and took out all the trash and my mom still wouldn't let me go to see spider man with Jacob i was so sad. O well. I have a feeling that Tre will go see it today but i ain't going with him he pissed me off to much yesterday. O well i guess. Today i gotta clean my room and mow the lawn. yippie joy joy. NOT!! O well. But tomorrow i get to go see fire works with Jacob. YAY! This should be FUN FUN FUN.I love fire works. but yea then Monday my mom has off. Maybe we can go somewhere so i can drive. O yea did i mention that i got my permit the other day. I was sooo happy. LOL. but yea. Then Tuesday i get ot go to Ceader Point with Jacob and family.(excluding Mr. Turner.) T has a class he has to go to in Chicago. He is gonna be there with Hutchie. :( i miss Hutchie. I wish we could get him back i mean i like Franks and all but he just isn't Hutch. But ok i am done talkin i need to go mow lawn and call jacob to see what is up with him. love ya Jake P34(3 0|_|7
    
</post>


</Blog>