<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay I am only taking one of the two drugs given to me by the VA. The mood enhancer made it harder for me to sleep not better and I didn't like how it made me feel. The pain inhibitor though is working well. I still have a dull throb but no serious shoooting pain.  Also fixed the bed sag which was of tremendous help to my situation. Back is still sore and stiff every morning but not intolerable. PRoper sleep is vital to one's health. The bed can make or break that. No nightmares anymore either. They have subsided foir now.  --Shaun
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well the VA Hospital at American Lake in Tacoma WA has begun to help me. I am now on two different drugs. One for pain and the other is a mild anti-depressent to help me sleep. So far it seems to be working. I actually awoke feeling refreshed this morning.  There are side effects of course but I so desperately needed a good night's sleep. I am actually feeling like myself. The pain medication works a little differently than others. It blocks the production of enzymes that stimulate the nerves. The idea being to reduce the over stimulation and return it to normal. My back is still sore but I don't have the joint pain this morning.  As far as fibromyalgia goes, I am showing all the symptoms and the drugs are the beginning stages of getting it under control.  Dietary changes now include eating breakfast every morning and taking a high potentcy mega-vitamin everyday. Since my potassium requirements are above average banannas are the order of the day as well.  Well as the weekend is the real test to see if long term help is happening I will keep things posted here.  --Shaun
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I toss, turn, I am up and down so much I'm keeping my Susan up at night. She is becoming irritable because of it. My problems with sleeping are making her a wreck. I need to do something soon as it will affect our relationship soon.  Going to the VA hospital today on urgent care call and seeing if something can be done about it. Right now the pain is making it to uncomfortable for me to sleep right and that just isn't good.  --Shaun  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When you realize a few things in this world, then things become so much clearer. I definitely believe in God and if you say I believe in a fairy tale then I'll just ignore you. I I know there is a god. The proof is there if you really look. Evolution is simply not a real possibility.  Anyway I am stronger than I know and despite my pain I give myself in God's hands and let him guide me. My life has been tremulous but with good reason. The disease I have is not to deter me but to motivate me. If you can't understand that I'm sorry but I know what I mean and in the end that is all that matters.  --Shaun
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well it took almost 13 years but the US Government and the The Veterans Administratioln are finally admitting the seriousness of the Gulf War Syndrome. Since the late 80's and early 90's many a service man was popping up with severe medical problems. I am one of them. Now I come to discover I may (and most likely do) have a condition call fibromaialgia (SP).  Though the condition is rare in men under normal conditions apparently many a service member who was in the Arabian Gulf is coming up with it. I already know someone else with this condition and have learned a few things already but I do know some things she doesn't.  One the best way to deal with the condition is to remain as active as possible. It is a mind over matter situation. The pain is phenonminal but if you let it keep you bed ridden then it will get worse. Drugs just aren't the answer as they also tend to be addictive and mind altering. Thanks but not gonna happen.  So simple low or no impact aerobics and a active life style are the preffered methods of dealing with it and the VA is already working on my case. I hope others who have been in the Arabian Gulf also seek help and quickly.  At least I know why I have been feeling the pain I have. I will be getting a disability rating as well. Finally some real answers.  --Shaun
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well here I am starting a BLOG. Why? Well maybe I'm tired of reading untruths, lies, manipulations and dealing with people who can't see just how black and white some things are anymore.  I'm no where near perfect but I do know right from wrong and I do see the failings of our society as a great many things are happening.  I am not politically correct and nor will I be. If you don't like what I have to say then don't read it. Otherwise read by all means but if you want criticize me then you'll be wasting your time because I just don't care anymore.  --Shaun
     

    
</post>


</Blog>