<Blog>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Kelsey the cat wrassler&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I did this so I could edit my profile. No? 
    
    
</post>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    what's a blueberry?&nbsp; urlLink    Today we went to "The Berry Patch to pick blueberries.  Yummy.  I am freezing them right now.  We didn't get a lot because they were smaller this year so I might have to go back.  We eat them like candy in the summer.  Matthew wasn't sure what to make of it at first but he got into it quickly.  A nice lady offered to take our picture but Matthew wouldn't take his head out of the blueberry bucket without screaming, so we just left it in.  urlLink    mmmmmmmmmmmmm blueberries!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    This is Jeremy's gross burned off wart that looks like a blueberry!&nbsp; urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been searching around on the web for Gaines family history.  I found this site here urlLink RootsWeb's WorldConnect Project: Cassady Family  with a lot of info.  This link should take you to a page on Stephen O and you can follow it all the way to our great ancestor Dafyyd Gam and beyond.  Gretchen Benson's research is on this Roots Web too.  Let me look and I'll paste a link in.  Hang on....  Here it is  urlLink RootsWeb's WorldConnect Project: GLBenson's Family  This is Gretchens "Gaines" page.  She has stuff on Grandma (the Crinks) too.  Plus a ton of other stuff.  On another subject.  By the way Happy Father's Day Jeff, Jerry, Pat, Clint and of course Dad.  We spent Father's Day at H. Roe Bartle Scout Camp because it was Family Day.  Jeremy and Trevor have been there since last Monday and will finally come home this Wednesday.  We always have fun visiting scout camp.  I have posted a two pictures.  One so you can see how awesomely cool the campgrounds are.  Missouri is actually a pretty scenic state.  I know it's hard to believe when you are from, say, Colorado, New Mexico or Washington state.  But it's true I tell you.   urlLink    This is The Point.  It's a lot farther up than it looks.&nbsp; urlLink     Anyway, the second picture is Iconium, Missouri's version of the chipmunk picture.  See if you can find the animal in the photo and what it is.  urlLink    I'm sure the feeders are a dead giveaway.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    It's just that...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    How does this blog thing work?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is Jerry finally chiming in.  I cannot figure out how to post pics.  When it comes to computers I am woefully inept.  I'll need help from one of you.  I love the pics everyone has posted.  Jeff, we'll have to start a silly picture contest.  Yours remind me of "Buck Mangor".  Remember him?  All for now.... Jer
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I figured out how to send pictures and posted several hehehe.  Jeff is a lot of fun :)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Official goof-ball....says Sammmy&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sillier yet&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Getting Silly&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jeff couldn't decide on one picture&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    "Now settle down"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My would-be profile shot&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Kelsey the cat wrassler&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just hangin' out with the kids. :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jeff and I had fun taking silly pictures to post here....We are having a nice visit.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in I'm inYeah!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Cute as bee by the flowers.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Here we are in Lincoln.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Who turned out the lights?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, If I did this right then you should be able to click on the link I found about dad in the tempest.  I couldn't find the review.  Here is a review of the LJS website.  "It stinks"  Sorry that's harsh.  I typed in a search every way I could think to find the review of Tempest but LJS gave me nothing.  I found this article by googling dad and Tempest.    So anyway now I'm sick, thanks Matthew.  That's what happens when you let your sick baby kiss you by sticking his nose in your mouth. Sammie let that be a lesson to you.  On a positive note having a cold helps me tackle the monster in the laundry room AKA Dirty clothes from church camp.  I also get some relief in the stinky diaper department.  Ok, sorry for being so gross - except for the dad thing.   urlLink Lincoln Journal Star 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Andi and Nisi recently visited this Lincoln landmark with Sam and Eliana.  Can you find what's missing?  &nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was so sad this week. The kids were all gone at church camp and mission trip.  But tomorrow I pick up two of them.  Yeah!!!  Meanwhile baby M and I are watching a lot of PBS.  I find the Big Comfy Couch annoyingly compelling.  urlLink Big Comfy Couch - BennySmart, Molly, pre-school toys, books   Toodles
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The kids and their entertainment last weekend at the Eagleman's reunion.   urlLink    bubble gun&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am trying to publish some pictures to my new blog.  It is not happening yet but right now the bottom of my screen is lighting up like a christmas tree so maybe something is happening.  I'll check it out.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi, I hope this thing works. Come back and see more stuff when I figure out what I'm doing!  Bye
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kelsey and I participated in the midnight bikeride this year.  The city of Lenexa does it every year around The Fourth.  We did the 12.5 mile ride which took us down into some caves.  These kind of caves are all around KC.  They are manmade caves with businesses inside.  I used to make deliveries to one when I worked.  Anyway, I think they are limestone or something.  They are pretty cool.  They remind me of the Star Trek TOS episode with the silicon based life form.  I didn't see anything like that though.  The picture is taken in downtown Lenexa.  I know I look like a dork but I don't have a light on my bike so I borrowed the boys caving lights.  Hey, I wasn't the only one....  urlLink    Kels and me on the midnight bike rideee&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eliana is sitting up now officially.  This means that I can set her down and step away and admire how big she is. Her little world of play is opening up and we are having a blast.  When Mom and Dad get back from vacation and bring back their camera I will post a picture.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For our fourth of July festivities we went to Worlds of Fun on Monday.  A few years ago we went ON the fourth and Trevor and I watched the fireworks from atop the Orient Express, before that first drop.  Remember that drop?  Well sadly we weren't able to repeat the experiance because the Orient has gone to the great amusement park in the sky.  Along with the Xtream roller and the shishboomer.  The Zambizi is still living somewhere in Columbia, South America.  I kid you not.  Anyway.  Remember our first trip to Worlds of Fun when Sammy was about 2 years old.  I'm thinking of the picture of her asleep on Mom's shoulder.  Well it's still a good time just not as good as it was with the Orient Express, my personal favorite roller coaster.  It is replaced with a pretty fun ride called Spinning Dragons.  It looks like a roller coaster but your car spins on the track.  It's fun but it's no OE.  Sigh. Kelsey wants to make it known that she rode both the Boomerang AND the Mamba!  urlLink    This is before they flipped them upside down on the Thunder Hawk.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Funnel Cakes mmmmmmmmmmmmmm.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    What happens when he doesn't get his piece of the funnelcake.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    Matthew wasn't sure what to make of Snoopy, and vice versa.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I Don't know if Dad ever looks at this but if you do, Have some cake.  Happy B-day!  urlLink    Happy birthday to you&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We've been home a week now but that's hard to believe. We had lot's of fun in Minnesota. We started out in Minneapolis. It was different this time. I've been there many times but never with a baby. Poor Matthew. He had a sore bottom. I don't know if it was the long car ride or what but he was not happy. Here is a picture of him after our visit to urgent care to get him some help for his poor sore bottom (not sore lor). urlLink    Owwwwwieeee&nbsp; urlLink    I'll spare you the gory details though. Other than that, and the fact that Greg and I spent the better part of the first night there out in the van with him screeeeeeeaming, Minneapolis as always was very............ARTSY. The Walker sculpture Garden is excellent. Check it out.  urlLink Walker Art Center  But watch out for the pollsters at the entrance accosting innocent bystanders with their Bush bashing. More tomorrow! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>