<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now ending discretely. Please hide away, I'm so lost. I drown and slumber, fall. And arise from the ashes of my former self. Now ending discretely. I am but a shadow of my former self. Again. Once more. And over, and over, and over, and over. And. Now ending discretely. Please make me invisible. I just want to stay in a closet, a void, a dark room. Eternally. Life is a dark hall.  One.  Long.  Dark.  Hall.  Now starting discretely. I'm down to just not me. A better person. Blankness. The night has taught me much. Please make me invincible. Now. And let me stay in this dark hall. And find another way out.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They are the one's I love to hate. They are the incompetent,  The ones that do not care, The ones that loves to hate. They have cheated, misguided. They have lied, evaded. They leave us wounded, to go through life with a scar. A scar that has taught us all a valuable lesson. In the pool of blood, a mirror image. Past, present, future? They are the ones I love to hate. Because They have done so little, and yet I have learned so much. To know is to be blessed. But. To know is to be scarred. I diminish, and wallow in a mirror image. And. Past? They are the ones I. *Silver*. They are the past and I.  *Silence*
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lie in the comfort, of sweet calamity, with nothing left to lose. Lie in the darkness, I'm slowly drowned to sleep, with nothing left to lose.  Three tears I've saved for you.  From AFI's Ever and a Day 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trapped inside, Oh my beautiful one. Trapped beyond, you cannot be reached. Someday, Someday I'll be more, More than you expect from the remains of a failing dream You cannot be reached. Beautiful one, Oh. The world fades. The enviroment, replaced. Replacements, noise. Fades to black. You can never be reached. What remains of this failing dream, Oh my beautiful one. As I fall, In my fall, Why I fall, Beautiful one.  You can never be reached.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Heartbreak, incarnate, I'm nothing if not your memories                       Heartbreak, please let me be enjoying your pain                         Someday, I will be...                       I'll be the common voice for community                       Because I am a man who'll forever be                       Where all remaining failed                         Please let me understand I'm your pillow                       Letters of past so distant and wrinkled                       Please let me understand I'm your pillow                       Letters of past so distant and wrinkled                         (Just say...) Say you will follow me (follow me)                       Invite me to your memory                       (Just sing...) Sing again for me (for me)                       That long forgotten song                         Heartbreak, incarnate, I'm nothing if not your memories                       Heartbreak, please let me be enjoying your pain                         Someday, I will be...                       I'll be that what you want from a failing dream                       Because I will, I may at best                       Be as low as you feel                         Please let me understand I'm your pillow                       Letters of past look distant and wrinkled                       Please let me understand I'm your pillow                       Letters of past look distant and wrinkled                         (Just say...) Say you will follow me (follow me)                       Invite me to your memory                       (Just sing...) Sing again for me (for me)                       That long forgotten song                         Let me be all the words                       Let me be all the words                       Let me be all the words                       Let me be all the words                         Let me feel the words echo in comfort                       Let me be all the words that you'd unsay                       Let me feel the words echo in comfort, comfort, comfort, comfort                       Let me be all the words that you'd unsay, unsay, unsay, unsay                       Let me feel the words echo in comfort                        Let me be all the words that you'd unsay                        Let me feel the words echo in comfort, comfort... comfort                        Let me be all the words that you'd unsay, unsay, unsay, unsay  AFI's Synesthesia 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can still regret the choices I've made. Sometimes the idea of meaning can simply fade. Sometimes I open the door, hoping to see you. Sometimes all that I see is nothing, and things that I should have been through.  Alas, alone I pray. A one-winged angel is what I am today. Indifference was my only crime. Waiting, for what seemed to be too distant to reach in a single lifetime.  Blind I was, at the hope of grand elation. From the inside and out, I was crying for salvation. This thing is slowly taking me apart. Sometimes people see me, only as a piece of art.  So tell me, have I completely shattered?  This thing is slowly taking me apart. I'm down to just one thing, and. Sometimes all that I see is nothing and things that I should have been through. A nightingale sings a lovely melody. Sometimes all that I see is me.  Alone I remain, afraid of nothing, frightening myself.  So come on tell me.  Why can't I just leave me. Sometimes all I see is you, everwhere I don't want you to be. A nightingale sings a lovely melody. Sometimes I simply don't see.  Alone I remain, afraid of nothing...  Don't forget the tears that was shed. When the memories start coming back all I want is to hide away under my bed. I thaught this love to be the perfect fit, but. I am smarter today. where I failed is where you'll forever sit.  All I see is my reflection in your tears. Scared of my own voice, of the echoes, ringing in my ears. A nightingale sings a dark symphony. As I sit alone, composing this sorrowful elegy. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>