<Blog>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So...I've entered this new mood that I've never really felt before. I'm aloof to everything pretty much (oddly enough this seems to make my driving better). BUT, I'm on the edge being set off easily. By set off I mean that if  anyone was to reprimand me then I'll go psycho on their tail. Maybe that's clear now.  Now for the big news. I know as I type this that no one out there is gonna believe me. I know I wouldn't. But I'm gonna continue and you can choose to believe it or to not believe it. When I logged off last night and was about to hop in the bed, I saw...[bum bum bum]...the THING. It was sitting beside my bed on the floor. Now, I know your thinking...wait...he said it died. Yes, it did die. I watched it. But there it was, on the floor, alive and meaner than ever. I didn't go into shock completely when I saw it and I decided I was gonna figure it out and study it (plus I wanted to see if its evil soul would spring out of it like it did last time). I ran past it and grabbed some tissues to pick it up with. Upon my arrival back to the bed, it was still there but it saw me coming to get it and it ran under my bed. I thought to myself...you fool. I knew I was gonna get it. I looked under the bed and what did I find right where it ran under? This weird looking kind of screw that I've never seen before in my life. Of course, at first, I just assumed it ran faster than I thought. So I placed the screw elsewhere and continued looking under my bed. I was almost completely under my bed looking for that thing. It wasn't there. I grabbed my cell phone to aid me with some light under the bed and it didn't help me find it either. I then proceeded to look under: my fouton, my nightstand, some clothes lying on the floor, my dresser, my desk, and even outside my room. Then I came back to my room and just started thinking about why this bug was harassing me so much. I then decided that the bug had turned into a screw. That's where you say "you're full of crap". But after seeing its evil soul pop out at our previous encounter, I don't put anything by the THING. Then I laid down to sleep and prayed and came up with the idea that perhaps this THING was a weird sign from God. He didn't answer me when I asked. He was probably too busy rolling around and laughing in heaven. I'm so confused about this dumb THING. There's not telling what may happen tonight or tomorrow but you can count on me keeping you updated. :) *Remember: If no one ever posts comments if gonna feel like a retard for putting all this on the web. Help a friend from feeling like a retard and leave a comment please.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One bit of randomness for the day before I start: on my way back from the movies, a man was waiting behind us in the drive-thru ATM machine line. He was walking through the drive-thru. He wasn't some random idiot either. He was wearing a nice suit and holding a briefcase. Thought I'd keep you informed... --- Hmmmmm... I've been thinking about the AGT for a little while now... I'm not quite sure what needs to be done to it... I believe drastic changes are not the solution... However, I believe termination will work best... To all you AGT members...trust me, this is for the best. Being AGT is irrelevant.  Being intelligent is highly sought after, highly overrated, and highly misunderstood. What really matters is the future and attempting to understand what your future holds. So, why don't you take the time from your busy life to ask Him what your future holds? Before you begin, you must understand that the future you have always pictured likely isn't what He wants you to picture. You don't want to end up in heaven only being able to say "I made it!" What you want to say is "Look what I've done! I did everything you wanted me to Father!" And then you want Him to take you in His arms and feel that nothing else that ever happened ever mattered. Now, so that you can achieve this, you must figure out what He wants you to do. Many people like to believe that they can just pick any career they want and they want to believe that's where they can do the most for Him. That's a load of crap. I've always wanted to be a corporate attorney. He doesn't want me to be a corporate attorney. So, as much as this stings, I need to figure out exactly what He wants me to be. I can examine my own talents. He will also examine the talents that He has given me. Then, His decision must pass to me. I'm yet to get a definitive decision but I know it will come. I've got all the time in the world. You hear many people telling you that your life is only justified by faith. But I will tell you, they are lying. These people are likely those haven't exactly succeeded in there spiritual life. They don't mean to be harming you by telling you this, but they are. James 2:24-"You see that a person is justified by what he does and not by faith alone." James taught it like this: First, you have the faith in Jesus Christ. Then, a sign of your faith is you wanting to go out and live righteously as He would have it for you. Faith and actions are a duel thing; your actions complete your faith and you cannot have one without the other. Hope you've enjoyed this rant. If you have then please leave me a comment and brighten my day! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There have been many things today which have brought me much emotional distress:  First, when I was brushing my teeth this morning (my bathroom is also a laundry room and resides in the basement) a cockroach went by the washing machine. This may be disturbing to some but I do not hesitate to smush bugs. So I kinda smushed it and at the same time slid it across the floor. I didn't really think this would have killed it, however, it was belly up and not moving at all. I didn't think that much about it so I went back to the sink and kept on brushing. A few seconds later I looked over at the bug (who knows why, but I surely wish I hadn't now). This is going to be difficult to describe so bear with my writing skills. Something black and kinda stringy was like moving over at the cockroach. For about maybe 3-4 seconds I just thought it was like antennae moving (you know how sometimes the muscles keep moving even though the body is dead). This was not antennae. The black thing started moving like a snake and it got longer and I found it was actually COMING OUT OF THE COCKROACH!! This thing moving like a baby snake (if you've ever seen one) when they are about 2-3 inches long. By now I've layed down my tooth brush a fixed my eyes and my open, scared mouth at the thing. Eventually it is completely out of the cockroach is moving like its own being. At this moment I am freaking scared to death. I yell for my mom to come here because I need some confirmation of my sanity. She sees the thing too and I tell her how it just came out of the cockroach. Mind you, this thing is still moving just like a worm. I suppose her mother instinct kicked in and she got a paper towel and tried to pick it up. She got the cockroach but it took her a few tries to get THE THING. Somehow, this has traumatized me beyond repair. I still get shivers. It was like something out of a sci-fi movie. [shivers again...]  For those of you keeping up with these blogs so far you know I had some psycho x-rays done on June 7th. Well the results are in: THEY FOUND ABSOLUTELY NOTHING. And I have no idea what kind of torture the doc will put me up to next. The fact they found nothing in the x-rays is kinda good since that rules out many, many bowel diseases.  Then, later in the day, I went with Kelly Hahn and her sister to Barnes and Noble to get some drinks and pick up a book. I ending up getting this neat book by C.S. Lewis ("Mere Christianity") instead of "Caesar" by Shakespeare as I had intended. But this is not the emotionally disturbing part. I traveled over to the religion section to browse. At B&N they have some sofas and tables set up randomly. In the religion section there was a table with a book on it. It was entitled "Friction" and two men were making out on the front. I was severely disturbed. Don't forget now: I found this book lying on a table in the RELIGION section...  Finally, my last disturbing moment came when Katie (Kelly's sister) was taking me home. This song came on the radio. I forget what it was but it sounded good. Yet, somehow my mind wondered completely off the song. I had this vision of the Rapture taking place. I was entering heaven with all the other Christians. It was great. And then I felt so sad for those who hadn't been ready. Then I pictured this scene with Jesus. If I was an artist I'd draw it, but, I am a writer so I will describe it. I saw a garden with a short dirt road leading to a wooden door that appeared as if from nowhere. The vantage point was from beside Jesus' leg and panning up at the door. His leg was in motion because He was walking closer to the door. When He gets to the door He is coming for His elect on earth. Wow-this emotionally disturbed me in a great way. Then, I finally calmed down and I heard the song ending. A very...different...experience.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Smile for the camera!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My current motto: Number two, no pickles.  I had a wonderful day today. Here's how it started out. I went to the doctor for x-rays to find out what in the heck is going wrong with my intestines. Well you have to drink this radioactive crap (barium sulfate for all you who really want to know lol) and then every 15-30 minutes they take pics of my guts (looks kinda neat watching how stuff goes through your stomach and intestines). The barium tastes like chewing up a tylenol-but 1000x worse. Its all gritty and sticks in your teeth. And then it made me burp (and it felt like it was going to come up...ugh...I know you're loving these details). I left-and I gulped down a #2 with no pickles. I burped and I tasted cheeseburger. Yum yum good. Better than barium sulfate.  I did some good arguing on www.secretmotive.com forums. Makes me proud. Harry Potter books are sinful. And that's that.  I bugged Ben til he would play some tennis. Not exactly fun playing someone who doesn't wanna be out there. But whatever I can get I will take. My parents made me mow. But that's not a big deal since I've got my iPod (aka Bill). Except for the fact that the lawn mower won't start unless you attach some jumper cables and about two dozen bugs flew up my nose, it was fine. Then I got Aaren to play some tennis and she whooped my butt (but this was expected lol). Then I got home and decided I'd make a blog. And obviously I did.  Song stuck on my mind at the moment: no clue, but its annoying and it needs to stop.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Death to squirrels. I certainly don't brake for them...especially the one's who just sit there and stare at you. Squish the squirrels!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    A new bumper sticker made by me.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a list of my top placed things "I'm tired of/disgusted with" (in no particular order). Enjoy. You may even be responsible for an item here or there.   -those who break the rules -those who can't understand losing -those who feign ignorance -Christians who can't read their Bible -those who can't accept critiquing when they ask for it -those who re-arrange my room -those who can't see beyond three dimensions -those who can't swim -those fueled by pride -those fueled by competition (pride's ugly cousin) -those who are immature -those who feign immaturity -those with words unusable -those who haven't the slightest idea of reality -those who claim Christendom  More are likely to come. There will be updates.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, I know you probably have no clue who Martin Guerre is, but I'm gonna tell you his story (he's quite an interesting man). It goes something like this:  Martin Guerre was born in Labourd, France. When he was very young his peasant father left the village quite suddenly and moved the family to a village called Artigat. Artigat was a good town to grow up in Martin seemed to like it. His family arranged for him to marry a very beautiful women, Bertrande de Rols, and he did. For the first ten years of marriage, they couldn't have a child. Then they suddenly did. And then Martin Guerre left when his son was about three months old. Its unknown for certain why he left, but he just up and did one day. Then, several years later (Bertrande refused to officially divorce him , although her parents were pushing her to) Martin Guerre returned. Out of the blue, he was there. However, it wasn't really Martin Guerre; it was a man named Arnaud du Tilh. He came claiming to be Martin Guerre and was received as him. Bertrande took him as her husband and they had children. And all was well for a time. Now, you must be thinking...how did they not know?!?! Well, bad memories I suppose and there were no pictures (the setting is 16th century France) and...Bertrande finally got the husband she had always wanted. They spoke together much and were in love; it was an "invented marriage". Now, Arnaud du Tilh ended up making his uncle very mad when he asked for his inheritance (the real Martin's father had died and Pierre Guerre, the uncle, was holding the inheritance). His uncle would not give it to him. That is when Pierre decided that this was not his nephew. Eventually, he forced Bertrande to take him to court over it. Before she did however, she worked with Arnaud du Tilh to make sure he could win the case and they could be back together. She did press the charges. And he ended up being found guilty. Arnaud was ticked off. He appealed to a higher court (like we do today). At the very end of the trial, when Arnaud had almost fooled everyone and was about to win his case...Martin Guerre Returned...the REAL Martin Guerre. The case was closed. Arnaud du Tilh was hung after he apologized to everyone. The End. And they didn't live happily ever after.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I slowly recognized that anger brings me perfection in driving the other day. My parents had completely ticked me off in the car and everyone was 100% silent as I drove us home in perfection. Isn't it weird that something that is a sin can bring perfection in driving? Perhaps it really isn't so odd. The car is perfectly fueled with anger and rage. It's man's creation after all, so it DOES make sense that it runs off of sin. However, when God creates something, it runs off of Him. Take ourselves for example; the human machine, man, was meant to run off of God; that is simply how He created us. Without God, man's soul is empty and he longs for comfort. He will fine no lasting comfort in a world destroyed by his fellow man. That's just a contrast at how messed up we are. Dang you Adam and Eve! (My preacher said once that they fell because they had no [this sermon was on Mother's Day, keep that in mind] mom. He said that if they did, you could count on her being there and saying "Get your hand off that apple!")  BTW-I'd like to congratulate the happy couple Rocky Sidden and Dalisa Fritts. Rocky is a step-cousin of mine and he's dating my ex. Makes me wonder if he even knows...? Thanks for the disturbance...it's working...don't count on any updates on this...I really don't want to know anymore...I think NC is turning into West Virginia...God save us all...
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm going to single-handedly disprove this idea of time travel with one, simple, rhetorical question based purely on logic and not on any scientific philosophy whatsoever. Here goes: If we were able to time travel, then why are we yet to be visited by anyone from the future?? According to scientists, there are multiple realities and multiple universes, so why are we yet to be visited? BECAUSE TIME TRAVEL IS IMPOSSIBLE. There you have it folks.   Emily, you better start leaving comments lol; I only typed this early because you asked me to :p
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I probably have too much free time to just wonder about these things...but I do and I think maybe you'll like to hear them.  I was sitting around outside the other day thinking about God and his physical make-up and appearance. It didn't take me too long to find out what He must look like, since we are told in Genesis that man is made in the "image" or "likeness" of God. Sorry girls, but God IS a man because men were made in His likeness, and women were in man's likeness. Anyways, that doesn't mean that we're made of the same stuff, just that we look alike. I wouldn't even venture to think that He has intestines or anything of that sort, for if you made an image of man, you wouldn't draw his insides. So, thus far we have man looking like God, but not necessarily having the bodily functions of man. I hope this breaks up any thought that some may have had that He was just this big, glowing light (since we look nothing as simple as a big, glowing light). Now, what is God made of? He can't be made of matter as we know it. God created every atom in the universe, so if He was made of matter like we know it, then He's made of His own creation. That means He'd be His own creation! That's a whole different religion called pantheism in case you were wondering. If you believed He was made of anything that He created then He'd also be subject to His own creation! Then He wouldn't even be God! So...now that that's outta the way...what's He made of?!?! He can't be made of anything we know of because we only know of His creation. So...He must be made out of something we cannot even fathom. It surely isn't something that you could just run your hand straight through, that would make Him seem almost non-existent. I like to think my God exists, don't you? So, in conclusion, I really don't know what He's made of and it likely doesn't matter as long as you don't think He's made of matter or something that's kinda non-existent...  I know its confusing...but its nice to think about...
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had something really great planned out to put here...and then it just left me. Did you know that every time you forget something, you lose brain cells? And brain cells cannot be replenished. Anyways...I'm gonna try to remember what I had to say:  I know there was something; something about...NOW I GOT IT!! So, ok, I figured out what I believe is my gift from God. Or maybe not. But I'm going to assume I have for now. I figured out that I can see that the small things that happen to us are God's ways of showing us His wisdom (its microcosmic). You might sometimes wonder why He can't just be apart of this world He has created since then His will for us would then be quite apparent. And that's a good question. Its like this: when an architect constructs a house, he cannot be the stairway or the hall; God created the universe, so He cannot actually be in it. Thus, He sends us little signs and messages; its kinda like when your mom leaves a note on the fridge saying that she loves you and that she'll be back soon. God tells us what's going on and what we should do next. Him sending us these messages expresses His love for His creation. Mom tells you she'll be back soon, so she wants you to get up and make your bed, take a shower, etc. Her saying that she'll be back soon is her way of instructing you on what to do next. Maybe, instead of a gift, its just a thing that believers have, that is, being able to understand His messages. This thing happened to me today and I can understand why and I can understand that there was supernatural involvement. I hope I've brightened your day :)  BTW-I updated twice today to make-up for my absent posts.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah I know you just can't call it a day without reading my blog...so now I'm here to update you.  Last night, as I went to go put my dog up, who was out terrorizing the neighborhood, I met this frog directly outside the door. He was just...there. I slowly walked around him and he tried to pretend he didn't see me...but I know he did...so after I put my dog up and was coming back to the door to go inside...he was there again...he was in a slightly different direction now...kinda like he had turned 90 degrees clockwise as he was previously facing the door...and I just stood there staring at him wondering if he was wondering about me...probably was...I'm just sexy like that :P...then I decided I wanted to make sure he was even alive because I was yet to see him move...so I got closer...and closer...and then I clapped my hands behind him...and through all this he didn't move...and then I lightly placed my foot on him...still didn't move...finally I gently kicked him in the butt and I'm pretty sure he said something nasty in the frog tongue as he bounced off...  Later, when I went to bed, I dreamt about the THING. This version of the thing was even more psycho than the real one. I got the other person in my dream (not going to say who) to kinda hit it like I had done (I don't learn lessons well). Well this person just like smushed it instead...or at least it should've smushed it. Instead it flipped on its back and its belly (like the hard part) just popped off. My dream promptly ended before the evil soul of the THING could come attack us. Thank goodness.  I'll try to stay more updated...sorry.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is the glorious sight to which I will wake up to every morning at the apartment. Bird crap in the morning-there's just nothing else quite like it.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Finally, I have returned. Forgive the absence of my updates, I've been doing A LOT of packing and moving.  I had a very intimate moment with God last night and I shared what I learned from His wisdom on secretmotive. Enjoy.  To Aaron and Emily: you both need to move on.  That's all for now, but next time I'll be speaking the infinite wisdom of old people...lol...[do I say this with sarcasm...?]
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    That's my current state.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    A new bumper sticker for my car!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just answered the phone and it was a call from Dental Care (the mean ppl who claim to be doctors). I didn't think I was due for an appointment, but when she started talking on the phone (we get pre-recorded messages reminding us of our appointments) I just involuntarily started yelling out "no! no! no!". My mom walked by my room and gave me an odd look. Turns out the appointment was for my dad. Whew. Close call.  I heard today that rinsing with Listerine twice a day, everyday, is just as helpful if not more so than flossing. These results have been confirmed by the ADA (American Dental Association). FEEL THE BURN! LISTERINE!  I seem to be spending hours in front of my computer each day reading about the Orthodox faith.  AND...the BIGGEST news of all is...I finished my AP Euro project!!! HOORAY!!! Now I have an English one to do...so depressing...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've recently been delving into the doctrines of the Orthodox Church. I can find virtually no holes in their logic. I really want to visit one of these churches, but there are none nearby which is really depressing to me. Reading about this Church makes me incredibly happy. I feel curiously open to these ideas when I am normally grounded in what I already believe. It's really weird if you know how close-minded I can usually be. I just pray that a path will be revealed to me. If you're interested in the Orthodox Church, then go  urlLink here .
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've finally discovered how to cure America of one of her plagues: cigarettes. You can no longer put people in jail for attempted suicide anymore; however, in all states excluding Oregon (in Oregon, doctors can prescribe you an overdose of med's to kill you) assisted  suicide is illegal. All people who sell cigarettes know that they cause cancer (see the surgeon general warning). Those people knowingly sell suicidal agents. Those people are committing the crime of assisted suicide in every state of the USA; even those in Oregon are guilty because they are not medical doctors that sell cigarettes.   That's my thought for the day.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lately, I've run into two religions head on. The first is what I call CCC-the Cultural Christianity Cult. The CCC doctrines can be discovered in multiple ways when determining if one person is CCC or not. 1) CCC members are determined to make amends with present-day science and Biblical History. When the two come in conflict, faith dwindles and today's pseudo-science takes precedence. 2) CCC members do not understand that growing in Christ means reading His word. 3) They cannot comprehend the idea that ALL truth lies in the Bible. 4) CCC members prefer to dismiss what they will not believe in the Bible by calling it "symbolism". The CCC is much simpler to define than this other religion since most so-called Christians fall into CCC. The reason CCC is so dangerous is the fact that most of its followers are going to Hell; that's the most blunt way to put it. Jesus Christ is the Word of God (see chapter 1 of the Gospel of John) and to ignore the Word of God (aka, the Bible) is to ignore Christ. The most obvious conclusion to be drawn from this is that one who ignores cannot can certainly not enter His kingdom. Now, onto the other religion. I'm not sure what to call it precisely-perhaps Neo-CCC or The Religion for the Blind. I've met fewer of its followers so it's much more difficult to generalize. For the sake of the conversation we'll call it  Chloe . Chloe members can differ in their beliefs but still rely on central doctrines. For example, some members make a large issue out of Biblical Versions when what they believe is threatened. Another example of Chloe followers is their way of taking large issues today and taking non-traditional, "Christian" stances on them. When the Bible disagrees with their beliefs, then Politics take precedence. You can almost view Chloe as being a step ahead of the CCC; given a few years, the CCC will be what Chloe is now and Chloe will be much more radical in a few years than it is now. The idea that ties the two religions together is the doctrine of putting your ideas ahead of the Bible and that's blasphemy against the Holy Son, Jesus Christ, the Logos, the Word of God, our Savior, the Messiah.  Be on the look out for Chloe and CCC; spot them where you can and don't make the mistake I have made of not thoroughly crushing them when I had the opportunity.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You know how it's so widely "known" that water has no taste? Well, that's a load of CRAP. Water does so have a taste. What right do these people have to declare that it has no taste? If I handed you water in a cup but you didn't know what it was you would tell me it tasted like water because water has a taste! We all know the taste of water. Certain types of alcohol are deemed tasteless, yet they do not taste like water because water has its own unique taste. Some people drink little water because it tastes bad. I don't like water either.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    If only Putt-Putt coins were really made out of gold...sigh...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was speaking to my grandmother a week or so ago (step grandmother to be precise, but she's def someone I'd want to be my grandma). She was just talking and in everything she said I saw wisdom, the wisdom of years. I just wanted to know everything that she did at that very moment. Well, that was until she told me I needed a refrigerator in my new room for drinks...and to keep my dip cold. I nervously smiled and laughed, hahaha...ha?...anyways, this is the wisdom that our parents don't have. Thought I'd put that in there lol. Anyways, my dad's been saying some strange things lately. For example, he just randomly walked into my room the other day when I had the news on and they were talking about who John Kerry's running mate would be and I said no one ever picks a good VP and he asked me, "Are you going to pick a good vice president?" "And how do you know I'll be president?" I retorted. "I just know", said he. It was kind of a psychotic moment if you ask me. But w/e trips his trigger. That's all for now but I'll be posting more signs and pics b/c I know that that is the biggest thing that tunes ppl in to my blog.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's fixed! My parents called and had someone fix it before we went to bed. I didn't think they'd come but thankfully they came out and now everything's great! As soon as it stopped, it seemed as if my headache just went away...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm an alien. Oh yeah...and that train crossing is still broken. It's gonna be a long night.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Our apartment is right outside train tracks and a train comes by at least once a night and always within 10 minutes of midnight. Right now the sign and lights by the track crossing are broken. They keep going off so we have to listen to a loud "DING! DING! DING! DING! DING!" all day long. Someone best be getting this fixed or off with their heads!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I would like to invite you to imagine, if you will, America being invaded by a coalition of 10 other countries. I'm going to leave you now to reflect on that.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      cheeriNshorTinNC: but thats how it starts cheeriNshorTinNC: once u say yall cheeriNshorTinNC: its starts goin down hill from there if u arent careful  [later]  De Facto 301: ur funny cheeriNshorTinNC: so ive been told  [later]  De Facto 301: [ding] you've been enlightened cheeriNshorTinNC: lol cheeriNshorTinNC: gees if there was a ding everytime i was enlightened ud be thinking that train crossing thingy was around  [later]  cheeriNshorTinNC: im goin 2 watch tv cheeriNshorTinNC: eww ahh  [later]  cheeriNshorTinNC: remind me not 2 talk 2 u
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Last Drop  She set down her glass And walked away; She saved the last drop for me.  I walked up to the glass, I glanced around To confirm my privacy.  I held up the glass; I found the aroma penetrating, Almost violating me.  I watched the glass Watch the drop Run smoothly like a sea.  I felt the glass As it sighed and gave up The last drop to me.  She stared at me with the glass And walked over, She took the glass from me.  She leaned over, Kissed me, And the glass shattered.  She stole the last drop from me.  [an explanation/analysis can be found in the comment section]
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Remember the last time when I quickly put to rest the idea of time travel? Well, I'm at it again with the very simple logic that makes you stop and say...dang.  Homosexuals like to complain. It's really that simple. They love to complain about how they are denied their rights because they aren't allowed to marry. What they need to realize is that they have the exact same rights as everyone else. They can marry someone of the opposite sex, just like heterosexuals. We all have that exact same right. And yeah, it's really that simple.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Bam!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    The Protestant religion is the egg layed by the Pope.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I really want to encourage everyone to look into the Orthodox Church. History reveals it to be the Church founded by Christ and carried through millenia to the current day. Just give this link a try at least:  &nbsp;   urlLink http://www.oca.org/pages/orth_chri/Orthodox-Faith/index.htm  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After viewing  urlLink this short documentary  on Kerry, I find that it would be most difficult for me to give my vote to him. Check it out. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was watching the DNC (that is, the Democratic National Convention for those of you not especially politically inclined) on FOX News which for me is channel 59. Well, I couldn't stand hearing the obviously scripted speeches by Kerry's kids, so I started flipping the channel a little bit to find something else on. I quickly landed on UNIVISION, channel 56. I quickly found Univision to be MUCH better than the DNC (if you didn't already know, Univision is the Spanish channel).  Univision is pretty much soap operas 24 hours a day-but they are hilarious. They're even more hilarious when you add your own words to what they're saying! So, I browsed the net and watched Univision in my room. I found it a little bit odd that my parents never said anything to me about it. Anyways, a little bit later when Kerry began his BIG address to the nation and nearly every channel was tuned into his face, Univision also changed to the stupid address! Univision, I thought I could count on you! So, over the voice of Kerry, I have to listen to his address in Spanish, which is much better than English I must say. I can sit here like I did during the soap operas and make-up stuff for him to say (yeah, I get a little bit bored sometimes).     One quick note: if you planning on commenting on my blog, please leave your name at the beginning of the comment. Thanks!  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I'm sitting here watching the Democratic National Convention on MSNBC and many thoughts are running through my mind that I would like to share:      1. I feel like I am watching old people's idea of a rave.      2. Some people need to practice their speeches more before standing up in front of millions of people and losing their place like 1458238569843200 times.      3.The host of Hardball has to have one of the most annoying voices I have ever heard in my life.      4. I don't think I can wait until November to get this election over with...I'm already tired of campaigns.      5. I wish I could vote...next presidential election!!        &nbsp;      &nbsp;      &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Ok everyone..here is the shocker of the century--me and Troy have decided to do this thing together (more like Troy asked me to and I figured it wouldn't hurt because I fill his with comments anyways).  To all of you that don't realize the irony of this, Troy and I hardly EVER agree on anything (from politics to ketchup). I'm not quite sure how this partnership will work out, but by no means am I going to change my opinions for you all--the audience (from what I have seen is pro-Troy's opinion, except for KittyK who seems aWeSoMe..but anyways). I am not like Troy and I'm not going to write like him either. My grammar can be total crap some days so you're gonna have to bear with me. I have no clue how this is going to work out and last night all I could think was--why in the world did I agree to do this so fast. Chances are that this won't work out but it wouldn't hurt to try.      My postings might not be too interesting either because I'm not about to sit here and talk about religion and politics all the live long day (just when I have something important to say about them). As a matter of fact, I have no clue what I will talk about for 3 or four times a week (how often Troy wants me to post). I'm tired of writing this now so I'll just leave at this--I am insane for doing this.        &nbsp;    Leave beautiful comments welcoming me and all that crap or telling me to go away because you don't care.        &nbsp;     PS-To troy-I'll do my font and style any way I please =)        
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Visit&nbsp;Nextels R Us&nbsp;for all your Nextel needs.&nbsp;They&nbsp;bring you the newest and coolest products to customize and accesorize your Nextel phone in a professional manner.&nbsp;They do modifications to Nextel phones including housing changes, and software modifications. Be sure to mention this blog when you make your purchase! Keep your phone up-to-date;  urlLink visit Nextels R Us today ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Behold! The throne of Ruby Tuesday!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is an ad I found online as I was surfing the web...does that guy actually make you want to click on the ad?????
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's a real quick update on apartment living for those of you deprived of this unique experience:       Our neighbor lives a rather suspicious life. She comes in at random times of the night and day and then leaves as quickly as she has come. She left for a whole week one time and seemed to be packing stuff up and out. Then, a police officer came and violently banged on her door when she was gone. He left. Then, two young girls came and went in the apartment and carried off a TV. But, within last week, she returned and has been back on semi-normal hours. My dad has talked to her and she's had a really rough life. My parents feel suspicous towards her but I feel really sorry for her-to me, she seems like a woman who's been through a whole lotta crap in her life and is just trying to get it all together.        Tonight, a major accident occurred right outside the apartment. When my mom and I were coming home from the movies after dropping Kelly off at her home, we found my dad standing outside on the cell phone. When I got out of the car, I noticed our neighbor standing out by the train tracks that are only about 50 yards from the apartment. She and my dad had been outside talking again when someone came flying down our road and got airborne going over the railroad tracks. The car had crashed down in the woods. I ran over to where she was and was looking around while she related to me what had happened. I was informed that I was not allowed to go down (because they believed the drivers to be insane/high/drunk) there (we couldn't see where the car was because it was too dark) to see the car. A car finally came up the road and we could see skid marks where they ran off the road. A little while later the ambulance my dad had called came and went down and found the car in the woods. The driver had fled. No one was left down there. They searched around for them but never found anyone to our knowledge. After we had gone back in, a wrecker came and took the car away.    Apartment living is quite an experience. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         yepp folks, i have returned to write an entry...          -there is something that has recently started to REALLY bug me: Random quoting. I mean this in the way that someone just shouts out something that doesnt make hardly any sense unless you have seen a particular movie/heard a particular song/played a particular video game (the latter being the upmost annoyingist)...I wish I had never admitted to seeing red vs. blue because now I am constantly subject to quotes that I can't even write here because I don't remember them..just the annoyingness of them...so folks:drop that terrible habit before I hurt someone.          Thanx dears*    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>