<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since last yr... June has been a month full of birthdays. Almost every single week we'll be celebrating someone's bday. Which also means, June is a month whereby my bank balance keeps decreasing. What's more I'll be going to Perth next wk, gotta pay for air tix, prepare some money for expenditure, as well as buy some stuff to 'defend' the cold weather over there, hahha.  Fri nite.. we went to Crystal Jade La Mian Xiao Long Bao to eat. Fang has been wanting to try out their la mian for quite some time already. Was us 'Wu Da Mei Nu' - Ci, Fel, Zhen, Fang & moi! Kekeke... Well, for me, the food was good as usual. I was the only one who finished the whole bowl of noodles, keke. Fel shared her US pix with us.. sigh, makes me crave so much to take a looonnggg overseas trip. But then, going to Aust for a week is also a consolation :) Long trip, hmmm, next time bah. Told Hendry if can, I'll go visit him in Madison. He said maybe by then, he'll have come back to SG already. KNS, see me no up! Anyway, aft dinner on Fri, went Checkers to drink n chat. WL n Kenny joined us some time later. Wahhh, Ci n WL was a humourous pair. Maybe coz both of them haven't seen each other for some time, both of them started bantering around, haha, buay tahan. Tat nite, coz we had 5 ppl, I decided to take cab home with Kenny, while the other gers shared another cab. Tat was the 1st time, I din take a cab home w Zhen, haha, so weird.. But then I tink I better get some getting use to.  Sat was off to JB. Yeap.. Fang has been craving for the butter crayfish, so we planned a trip there to satisfy her craving. This time round, we took bus in, wasn't so bad. Just tat when at the M'sian customs, they're pretty slow.. tsk tsk. Went shopping, but din see anything I like, sobz. In the end only bought some food stuff. off we went to have our feast during the evening.. Slurpp!! Everyone should have seen Fang, she was glowing with joy!! Hahaha~~ Now we know how to cheer her up if we ever see Fang feeling down. Just when we're abt to finish, it starting raining. Or shld I say pouring! Dampened our moods. So when it started to lighten up, we decided to go straight back to SG.   Called Kenny when I got back, n he said he was with his poly mates at One Fullerton, told me to go down n meet down. Haiz.. tinking tat he alwaz joins me when I'm with my frenz, I decided its time I do my part. Tired as I may be, I still went lar. Alvin was there with his gf too. Small grp, so wasn't tat bad. Coz I dun usually like to 'entertain' ppl when I'm tired. Wats more I'm also a pretty shy person (okok, u ppl, stop puking). 
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haven't been to church for the last 3-4 weeks I suppose. Been pretty troubled 'bout 2 weeks ago. N I very much wanted to attend service, thinking maybe God will help me find an ans for my troubled mind. Still remember having a conversation with Zhen some time back, and she enlightened me on certain stuff.. During then, we were still saying we guess God is using her to pass me the message. Thanks Zhen ;)  This week's service, PP happened to mention abt the same things Zhen told me then. I admit I was surprised, then I started thinking and then smiling to myself, haha. God works in many ways, and He ans your prayers in many ways. I'm really glad. This service has sorta encouraged and reinforced my decision. Told Kenny about it, and he was happy about this reassurance too, keke.  I found this service to be so totally relevant to me, even Zhen thinks so, haha. PP talked abt controlling your heart, do not always let yourself feel troubled. N that's totally me. I always got my mood swings, depressions, frustrations, troubles. So yes, I've learnt alot in this service.  Went shopping after service. We're planning to look for winter wear, footwear n jeans. But sadly, we still went home empty-handed, sobz! Was supposed to meet Kenny at 8.30pm or so. In the end, change of plans, drag drag drag. We met Kenny, FZ + gf, WL + gf and Tay at 10.15pm!! By the time they all arrived, Zhen and I were totally drained liao. So tired! Anyway, we went S11 to eat n have some drinks. First time meeting FZ n WL's gfs. Both lived up to their reputations, haha. Serene was quiet and pretty dao kind. Samantha was the chatty n friendly kind.   In the end Tay drove Zhen and I home. And as expected, after bathing, I'm awake again, keke. So came online to write blog lor :P Would like to end this entry by sharing this verse with you all:    Peace I leave with you; my peace I give you.   I do not give to you as the world gives.   Do not let your hearts be troubled and do not be afraid.   ~ John 14:27 ~  
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Was reading a fren's blog... n had some thoughts on certain stuff tat she wrote. How do ppl get into relationships, wat goes thru their minds b4 they decide to jump into the wagon. N upon doing so, should we commit fully, or just have a fling n see?  I wondered, when we chat amongst ourselves these days.. we'll say that some of our past relationships r puppy loves, infatuations or crushes. So does it mean that as we grow older, we become more commited? And is it due to that we think we've played enough? That we're mature and should get into something serious? That we're running outts time? And even when some are attach, yet they have flings outside.. what exactly are they looking for? Can we truly love more than one person at the same time?  I myself have just got into a r/s.. for me, I tend to consider the 4 C's which I've come up with - chemistry, communication, compatibility and being comfortable with each other. We need chemistry to have butterflies fluttering in our stomachs, haha. We must be able to communicate, if we don't convey our feelings, we won't know what the other party is thinking abt. Compatibility in terms of perspective and goals in life, etc. And lastly, being comfortable in each other's company. I came up with these 4 factors after going in and out of many failed r/s in the past yrs. Well, they may not be wat everyone else is looking for, but at least they r for me. Coz I know if any one factor is missing, the r/s I'm gonna have is not gonna be easy to maintain, problems will arise.  Some others are afraid or unable to get into another r/s.. you gotta ask yourself, why so? Is it because you're still harbouring hopes for an ex and refuse to let go and move on? Is it because the new person you are seeing right now juz doesnt fit the bill? For you already have a benchmark of that seemingly oh-so-perfect ex-bf? Is it because you've been hurt deeply in the past r/s and have grown tired? You think of all the time, money, and effort you've spent, and it has all gone down the drain. Thus, you start to think if the next time you meet someone, maybe you should be more rational, rather than go with your heart. N because of all these reasons, you may have refused a chance to begin a r/s with a considerable person who might have come by.  I guess we gotta learn to move on from our past r/s, especially one that we've envisaged a life-long journey. It may be really difficult, but life goes on, and hence, we must move on too. Or else, we may end up hurting new people who come into our lives. And at the end of the day, we'll be hurting ourselves the most by going through tonnes of emotional roller-coaster rides.  Just some thoughts ;)
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went Zouk on this Sat nite... after like 3-4 yrs. The last time I went was with the poly mates. Boy, doesn't time fly by in the wink of an eye. And not to mention, we're getting old really fast, lolz. Fang has finally finished her exams, haven't seen her for like a month or so. Hehee, miss u Fang!   Anyway, we 3, together with Zhen, went to Zouk to catch Marc's short film - The Day, or if we direct translate the chinese title, it'll be called 'Today you're me' hahaha... It's actually a Laselle event, screening some of their final students' works. Anyway, Marc's film was pretty ok. I guess among the clips that were shown tonite,  other than Marc's, I only understood another clip. I just dun really understand the rest of the other clips, haha. Maybe I'm not arty farty enough, tat's y :P  It was 1 for 1 tonite. So we order 3 glasses of red wine, and had another 3 free. I reckon I really need to quit drinking altogether. When I got home, I realised my whole body was red. And my arms n legs were especially itchy! Arrgghh!! Yes, from now on, I will not drink at all!! Note my words! Hahaha~  And so, yet again... when I drink and dun get drunk, I get insomnia and can't sleep. I've tossed and turned in bed for like hours. I've moved frm my bedroom to the living room, and back again, but it was no use. So I've decided to log on and just loiter ard till I get tired. I tink I'm gonna be a zombie for Sun. The sun is gonna rise soon, and I'll probably still be sitting here, staring at the monitor. Help!!!  Anyway, I'll like to end by wishing my dear Ling a HAPPY 24TH BIRTHDAY! Yay!! Hahahaa~ Though this yr can't celebrate too much coz of ur coming exams. Dun worry, u'll get to see Zhen and I in abt 3 wks time. Your presents will come along w us. Love you lots! Muarks!
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yup... coz of a new turn or start I should put it, in my life, I've decided to begin on yet another new blog, hahaha. Gonna keep this fuss free n simple. Pretty tiring to alwaz look for new templates. Anyway I got me own webbie now, so I can post stuff there instead. So shall post some interesting stuff in my life, and possibly some thoughts n reflections of life in general that's worth to ponder on now and then.  After more than a mth of pondering and being frustrated, I've finally decided. N yes, have broke my ans to him too. I couldn't help it... maybe coz I've been thru too many r/s, and some of us say, the more u go thru, the better u know urself, of wat kinda person suits u, on what criterias u're looking for. Maybe coz I'm also sorta a perfectionist, I hope tat my next bf wld fit into all criterias, n yes, I admit, tat is pretty greedy of me, hahaha.  So, I've finally said a yes... After thinking so much whether I should be more emotional or rational. Sorry for letting u wait so long, 'like years', tat's how u put it, hahaha. But by me thinking so long, shows tat I'm serious too rite? ;) Being a perfectionist doesn't mean I'm perfect either, I believe there r bound to be things abt me which u have to make do with as well. Been more than a yr since I was last attached, so I'll have to take some time to adapt to it. No more loitering ard n doing things on my own like nobody's business.   But as I've said b4, I'm not the 'sticky' kinda gf. I dun need to see or tok for long hrs on the phone w my bf every single day. I'm not expressive, I wun tell u 'I love u' or 'I miss u' every other time. But that doesn't mean I dun care abt u ok? I'm not the 'sai nai' kind either, haha. Gives me goose bumps :P Of coz there r my good qualities, lolz! I'm not the very possessive or easily jealous sort, so there aren't many limitations n u won't be too stress abt it. I'm pretty dependent on myself, so won't affect ur studies or anything. I also have a pretty mild temper, wun get angry so easily, but! dun test my limits, keke.  Anyway, I'm glad u tink u've made the right decision. N I believe I did too... So cheers to our future together, haha.  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The past week, has been a week of illness. I got a terrible bout of diarrhoea, which then led to headache and fever. I reckon it&nbsp;should be the cheesecake&nbsp;I ate at Borders Bistro... Fri, got better, and carried on with my plan to make dinner for Kenny at his place. Went Carrefour to buy all the stuff I needed. Walked out and woah!! the cab Q is so&nbsp;long,&nbsp;running late.. gotta call cab. Thankfully I met with a very&nbsp;polite and chatty driver, hahaha. Said he's jealous of Kenny, and&nbsp;unfortunately he don't like pasta, if not, he'll waive half of my cab fare and ask for permission to join us for dinner, haha.   So was rushing to prepare dinner... the end result was just ok. Din have enough time to simmer the sauce n ingredients of the spags, if not, would have been better. We rushed&nbsp;off immediately to catch our 9.30pm show of Brotherhood. Brilliant show... teary show... good! Jang Dong Gun & Won Bin, drool~~&nbsp;First time experience for Kenny to watch a show with me and have me crying *believe me dear, there's more to come, haha* What's worse was that I was really sobbing, instead of just the normal&nbsp;trikkling down of&nbsp;some tears.   After the show, walk around a little and its 12 mindnite. Ding Dong Ding Dong... happy birthday dear. Muarkz! Then we jus sat around, talked a little and then went home.&nbsp;   Sat.. woke up with a swollen left eye. Wonder if it's&nbsp;due to me wearing my contacts for too long the previous nite, or that I cried too much, or maybe both, haha.&nbsp; Kenny got sick too... throat infection, leding to fever, cough and headache. Haiz~ So much for spoiling his mood of celebrating his bday. We were planning for ktv, in the end.. only ended&nbsp;up with we 3 girls singing away in the room. Was only till dinner at Holland&nbsp;when everyone arrived. Kenny left to meet his pilot frenz aft dinner, while most of us&nbsp;left decided to head to West Coast Park.   Frankly,&nbsp;being a Singaporean turning 24 soon, I've never been to West Coast Park. So embarrassing, keke.&nbsp;Eventually, the place turned out to be pretty nice.&nbsp;The Mc and McCafe there was pretty nicely done up. And all the playgrounds and bstacles courses were pretty fun, keke. At least its much much nearer than Elias Park at the other end of the island. After chatting and&nbsp;enjoying the breeze by the sea we decided to go play, coz there were then lesser ppl liao. Wooo... we climbed the 'pyramid net' thingy.. and then spent most of the time at the flying fox ground, keke. Laughed till my&nbsp;jaws ached.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  Can't believe we were actually dorta exercising in the middle of the nite. Being all sweaty, we decided to go home. Waited for almost 30mins before we got a cab, duh!   Well, so that was how I spent the 2 days celebrating Kenny's bday. Seems to be more than the bday boy himself. Nvm dear, you enjoy more during my bday k? Keke... and I'll pray that you'll be healed very very soon ;)   
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Phew, after coming back for exactly a week.. I have finally finished all the work stuff I was flooded with. Man.. tiring! Been so long since I actually bring paperwork home to do. Which explains I've dragged till now to update my blog. After this, will have to go update my LS blog and&nbsp;webbie, sigh~  &nbsp;  So, how was the trip people asked. Fun? Nice? Well... I would say it&nbsp;depends on wats the purpose of your trip. N our purpose was to go visit Ling and relax. Jus as long as we dun end up like our Amara stay, even more tired when we went there, lolz! So yes, judging from our purpose, I would say it was a pretty good trip.  &nbsp;  The weather was brilliant... too cold at times, haha.. but no complains, compared to SG weather. An average of 12-17 degrees or so was good. Coldest it got was one morning, when it went all the way down to 1 degree. But then we 3 were ZZzzz in bed during then, so doesn't really matter, haha. A big part of the trip was spent driving during the first 3 days. The journey runs like this:  &nbsp;  Perth -> Albany -> Margaret River -> Bussleton, Bunbury, Mandurah -> Perth  &nbsp;  Most of the driving was done by Zhen. Hahaha, not that I din offer, but they dun dare to sit in a car speed-driven by me! So I only got to drive when we reached the towns, and in Perth. Haven't driven for 'bout a yr already.. great feeling. I love driving. But then, I hate parking, alwaz crooked wan, duh!  &nbsp;  As a summary... we watched lots of tv n vcd, coz the shops close as early as 5-6pm :S We watched Simpsons daily ('cept tat we missed it for a day), Neighbours, The New Block (or something lidat), Queer Eye for the Straight Guy, Taking Lives, Forest Gump... VCDs, we watched Koma, Mean Girls, Shrek 1 &amp; 2 and&nbsp;Zoolander. And I watched A Date with Tad Hamilton, Taking Lives (again), Twisted, One Love Last love (jap), and can't remember&nbsp;the last one, on the flights to n fro, kekeke. So&nbsp;this trip was like a flim fest too, keke.  &nbsp;  The scenery there was brilliant.. which led to ppl suan-ing me. Wahh.. so many pix, but so little of it with u gers in it. N esp from Ci... 'Ah-Jer&nbsp;msged tat she'll take lots n lots of pix to show me, in the end??'&nbsp;Haiz....... I like to take scenery shots mah, not&nbsp;nice meh? Nice rite?&nbsp;SG where got chance to see such sceneries? I help u ppl broaden ur horizons mah, never thank me still suan me.  &nbsp;  Food-wise... most delicious one would have to be the chilli mussels, haha. Of coz, not forgetting Ling personally cooked spags for us on our 1st day there... miracle! Hahaha~&nbsp;The chinese food there was pretty ex though. For a bowl of not-spicy laksa or prawn mee, it costs A$6. N its A$2.50 for a cup of kopi-peng... really pengz! N Ling's 2 german housemates, tsk tsk... Though one of them is quite cute, but haiz.. so slobbish. Eat liao throw everything in the basin dun wash wan.&nbsp;When we went there, they had clothes on the hangers in the kitchen, when we left, the clothes were still there! Must stink with smoke, coz we smoke there almost every nite, hahaa.&nbsp;   Ok, I tink the entry is getting a tad bit too long. Shall end here. Ling, next time we see u shall be yr end I suppose. So till then, take care. Love ya!    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep, its 1+am now, and in like 8 more hours or so, I'll be on a plane flying off to Perth. 1st time going overseas to visit a friend though, a nice feeling. Havent seen Ling for like wat? 6 mths or so I tink.. Told Hendry I'll go US to visit him when I've got the time and money. But he thinks too little of me, said that by that time, he'll probably have flown back to SG. Humph, kns!!  Its been so soo long since I last went on a vacation (not considering M'sia). I guess the last time I went on a holiday by plane was almost 4 yrs ago, when I went Korean and HK with SL. And if I was to count the last time I went to a western country, haha... tink I've lost count. Probably the last was my England trip during sec sch days. Personally, for relaxation purposes, I prefer going to western countries, because of the pace of life and the sceneries. Asian countries on the other hand are good for pigging out on food and shopping, keke.  I bought a digicam ytd.. Canon IXUS 430. Just launched in the market, reccomended by Mr. Effendy, his sis just got it this wk too. HGood recommendation I must say, what's more I've alwaz tot Canon to be the better brand for digicams anyway :) Before u can say I'm rich, please note, I actually borrowed $500 frm dad first, while paying the remainder by myself. Will slowly pay him back by installments I guess, probably ask him to deduct from my monthly pay, keke. So, will be ready to take lots of pix for this trip. Sadly, there'll only be us 3 Musketeers, the missing musketeer, Fang Fang has flown off to Japan last nite. Told her to remember to look out for Takeshi Kaneshiro n Takuya Kimura. Asked her if she sees them, bring them back to SG. But then she said she won't. She'll stay there in Japan and not come back if it happens, hahah. Buay tahan!  Went to church w Kenny today. Its funny really. We used to go Trinity together when we were in sec sch, and tdy, we went to New Creation together :) Nice feeling though. One thing I would have not tot of if he didn't mention, is tat I was his 1st christian gf, and hopefully now, the last. And on my side, he too is the only bf who's a christian. Maybe tis r/s will be our final one since we have God by our side, keke :) After service, we went to ktv with Ying, Roy, Jannis n Joelle. Though knowing each other for close to 10 yrs, Kenny n I have never heard each other sing b4, hehe.  Alrite, I guess I shall end here. Will write again when I'm back from Perth. Take care everyone! Muarks!
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Watched the 1st epi of SG Idol last nite.. asked mum to record it for me as I was out on Mon. Man... hugely disappointed, but still holding a 'lil hope. Watching the auditions, accepts n rejects, I feel the bar for SI is so much lower than AI. But I'm still holding a lil hope coz they usually improve as they absorb the experience thru every round.  The few memorable rejects. Steven Lim of coz, the so-called high profile freelance eyebrow plucker... totally  disgusting!!!  Dressed like a gladiator, stripped to his yellow speedos n sang the disaster song -  She Bangs.  Then there is the guy who came all the way from China. Given a 2nd chance, he still sang in his falsetto pitch. N kept saying he has the voice n that the judges will regret not accepting him. Then crying on Gurmit's shoulders when he finallly went out. Well, I guess if it was SG Opera Idol, he'll sure win. N then there was tis fella who carried on singing even when the judges asked him to stop. N his singing was so inaudible. I tink even the squeak of a mouse would be louder than his singing. Wat's more he asked for the judges comments on how he can improve. Ken Lim just told him,  'For us to be able to give u comments, we must first be able to hear what you are singing'.  Haha, good one. Of coz lastly, there was tis 'tut' guy, who said his purpose was to become the 'William Hung of SG'. Wat more can I say, DUH!  Well, as for the judges, they were not as critical as those we've seen in the foreign instalments. Though I can't really tink of better judges to take over the existing ones, but outta the 4, the only one I respect is Dick Lee. So lets just hope the contestants will raise the bar in the next epi tonite... 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got a new hp on Thurs, keke. Got a Motorola V600 frm an online seller. Was pretty sceptical abt getting it at first, coz I had bad past experiences with other Motorola phones. They used to have really slow systems n pretty user-unfriendly. But so far, so good :) Just gotta get some using to tat the function buttons r inverted unlike other hp brand models. Main feature I was attracted to for this phone was tat you can transfer and use mp3 files as ringtones on it. Haha, brilliant!  Fri was a lousy day at work with the recent release of Jay Chow's latest album. Expected 2 shipments to come in, but one was late, thus we had a shortage of stocks. Sales ppl complained abt shortage and tat other distributors r selling cheap. If u tink our items r ex, then dun get from us, farking getting on my nerves... Then had a dispute with dad at work as well. My mood was bad the whole day.  Went to Ci's place to help write out the wedding invitation cards ytd. But eventually, only Zhen wrote, haha. Aiyar.. my handwriting ugly mah. I go to give moral support :P We went to buy groceries n made dinner, keke. Everyone was playing w Ace, hehehe..  Later at nite, we went to Brewerkz. Had sorta a farewell gathering for Weilong who is gonna be flying back to England. First time interacting with this fella.. a somewhat irritating but yet, corny n funny guy at times, haha. Played pool, snapped picutres, drank.. n soon, it was 1+am already. The rest din feel like goin home, so decided to head on down to Labrador Park. Fang and I were tired, so we decided to go home.  Slept at close to 6am last nite, and Zhen got home late too. So, we din managed to go for service tdy. Tmr would be National Day, I'm not much of a patriotic person, so won't be celebrating. Will be meeting up the poly gers to celebrate Ying's bday at noon though.  Kenny is away at JB this wkend.. will be back tmr evening :) 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know I know... I seem to take ages just to post an entry in this blog. But well, too many entries, ans there's nothing new. So.. once in awhile, when u see a new entry, then more interesting mah :P Have changed the template. Nice eh? Yeah.. I guess black still suits me best. Mum and Kenny also comment I'm alwaz dressed in black. Oh well, what to do, I'm fat mah, so dressing in black will make me look not so fat, kekeke.  The last 2 weeks have been virus weeks. Alot of ppl falling sick. Maybe more so for people staying in Bt Batok n CCK. Haiz.. But I guess everyone is feeling better liaoz.  So last Thurs was Fang's first time joining Zhen &amp; I for hip-hop class. Hope she enjoyed herself. She kept laughing when she had no more strength to do the crunchers. Carol taught the class last wk, coz Bibiani wasn't ard. So as expected, the whole thing was  TIRING ! Wat's worse was that I attended the club jazz class b4 tat. So I was freaking tired aft everything. Can't make it in the club jazz class. So diff, cannot keep up. Guess I'll choose from the other classes.  Jim came to SG with his gf and grandma.. would be staying for abt 2.5 wks. Few of us met up with him on Sun. Not much change lar, though he's weighing 101kg now, thankfully he's tall, so dun look tat fat, keke. His gf oso pretty cute.. will suan him along with us wan, hahaha. Aft tat, watched yet another film fest show with Fang, Zhen n Kenny. It's call, Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter and... Spring. And again, it's yet another 'scratch-head' show. Hahaha~ Think Fang stress, this is the 2nd so-called arty show she've jio-ed us to go watch, first was Swimming Pool. Both oso turned out to be 'scratch-head' shows, kekeke....  We've just entered Aug.. one of my fav mths coz its the mth of my b'day, hahaha. But this and next mth wld be pretty bz I reckon. Other than a few b'days, Syl is gonna give birth soon (which means I'm gonna become a god-ma), and Ci's wedding is oso round the corner (which means I've not succeeded in my diet plan yet, so I'll look fat in watever I'm wearing for the wedding) :P
    
</post>


</Blog>