<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last night in scotland!! it's after 10 now, kinda late, but we are still going :-). today we just hung out, packed, cleaned...then after dinner we came to the church and played American football and ultimate frisbee with the mission team (or what's left of it...phil, debbie, jason and tricia left this morning).  inverness was wonderful...so nice, and lovely :-P i enjoyed it very much. although i must say i am perfectly ready to go home. scotland is nice, very nice, but i miss my family :-/ and i need a hug :-P. plus i have a ton to tell them, i'm about to BURST with all of it!!! 6:20 pm Eastern Time is too long to wait.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, we are now in inverness. We took the bus up from Glasgow at 11:15 and arrived here at 3:30. we are staying in a hostel, which is kinda like a dorm - there are lots of rooms with bunkbeds, and you share them with other people. it is a lot nicer than i thought it would be, but then, i haven't seen the other 3 girls who are in our room :-P.  friday went...alright. there was trouble with the bank not transfering the money for the loan, so the Quigley's couldn't move in until today. Thankfully, the owners of their new home still let  us move stuff in on friday, so that all there is to do today is move mattresses, clothes, and other things that they needed over the weekend.  on saturday we went up to Stirling. once again, it was rainy and cold, but we still got to visit the Castle and the Wallace Monument. we went to the top of the monument, but i only stayed there for - half a minute, because it was sooo windy it felt like i would be blown off! the mission team had a free day, so Joe (from Broomall RPC) came to Stirling with us. Then we met the rest of the mission team, Rob and Jess Edgar and Rob's parents at the Caledonian Brewrey in Edinburgh for a Caley. A Caley is Scottish dancing. It was sooo much fun! i have never had more fun dancing than i did then. i didnt know any of the dances, and neither did anyone else that i was with, but we went through them quickly before picking up the speed, and it was really really neat. ten times better than dancing at prom :-P there was one dance where there is 2 couples, and they are in a circle guy-girl-guy-girl, and the guys lift the girls up and spin them around!! :-P it's called the basket. it was very very fun. too bad we don't have Caley's in Pittsburgh.  well, we are about to head out to Loch Ness to search for the monster :-P. Christie figures now is about the time for it to appear, and that she will be the one to spot it.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well yesterday was rainy and dreary in Glasgow :-( we went shopping mostly, there isn't any castle there or anything to visit. when we came back we went to Mr. Kebab's with Karen for dinner. We were going to go to the Robertson's for MET, which would have been lots of fun, but Angie Robertson wasn't feeling very well,so it was cancelled. During dinner, Tricia and Ryan came to get us to practice some psalms. Andrew wants the mission team and us to sing some psalms for the congregation after evening service, b/c the psalter is different here. they are trying to move to ours, but they don't know them well at all so we are going to help them learn them :-). of course, we are singing 98A.  Their   psalter is a split-leaf (i think that's what it's called) with the music at the top, and then words on the bottom. actually, most of the psalters don't even have the music, so we have been winging it pretty much, trying to pick up the tune after the first verse.  today the Quigley's are moving. The mission team + people from the church are helping move, while Alicia, Bekah, Christie and Corinne watch the 3 youngest Quigley's, Calvin, Catherine and Caitlin. I am being sent to paint in the new house!! :-) it should be fun, at first it sounded like i would be the only one painting, but Jason (team leader) said that some of them would probably help.  tonight the mission team is having an ice cream social/bas ball game for the youth, that should be a lot of fun. well, i should go get to work now :-) oh, i'm terribly sorry, but the computer i'm on at the library won't let me onto my blog, it will only let me post stuff. soo that means i haven't been able to read any of your comments!! *sniff* lol you see, i'm assuming that some of you will have commmented. :-P well, i'll have lots to read when i get home, right?!!
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      not a lot of time...but the Covenanter Tour was GREAT!!! i really enjoyed it,even though we didn't get to go to Wigton to see where the 2 margaret's died...oh well, i guess i'll just have to come back sometime :-)i gtg, we are going to Glasgow today to shop, sightsee, etc. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whew! i have had an exhausting couple of days :-) on saturday karen took us into Edinburgh and, although it was wet and cold, we saw the castle, and shopped down the Royal Mile. it was very neat. on lord's day, after church the Robertson's, a family at ARPC had us, the mission team, and others from the church over all afternoon. we were fed twice, and other than that sat around and talked :-). Lord's Day evening, Pastor Blair from the Galway Mission work in Ireland came and did a presentation on their fellowship there. it was very interesting, as i had not heard much about it before then. after church, Andrew began our Covenanter Tour with an hour long lecture on the 2 reformations in Scotland, plus reformers and what they contributed. Yesterday we went to St. Andrews, a lovely town on the east coast, where we saw a different Covanenter's sites. we did the same today, only we were in Edinburgh. we saw the church where John Knox preached, and where the National Covenant was written and signed. we ate lunch at the Grass Market, a site where many Covenanters were martyred, after singing a few psalms and praying. it has all been very good to see the spots where our history was made, as well as inspiring and challenging to love the Lord and commit my life to Him as much as the Covenanters did, despite the threat of death. Andrew has been repeating over and over again a lot of the facts, which is good because it is hard to soak it in if you only hear it once. well, i'm off to a Church bonfire - according to Karen, anybody who's somebody is going, :-P so we have promised to be there. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow, very sorry i haven't posted this sooner, but i wasn't able to get online till now, which is fine, because i have been plenty busy!!! on monday, our plane was delayed 3 hrs due to a thunderstorm, thus we missed our Toronto - Glasgow flight. we were at the Toronto airport till 3 am, (fun fun) then went to a hotel for the night. we weren't able to fly out until 10 that evening, so we hung around the hotel all day. then, since we are just a special group of people (actually because there wasn't any more seats available) we got to fly 1st class!!!! from toronto to london. it was absolutely amazing... 4 course meal, huge seats that reclined, the works. i am now very spoiled :-D from london we took a plane to glasgow. so we FINALLY arrived in glasgow at 2:30 wednesday afternoon. since then we have been mostly hanging around our flat, getting over jet-lag. thursday we helped the mission team pass out Airdrie Word Today. at first i was a bit nervous about knocking on people's doors, but all we had to do was offer it to them, as well as a Gospel of John. it was a lot of fun. today we babysat the Quigley kids while Andrew and Heather shopped for new furniture (they are moving next friday) and went to M&D's, an amusement park. the roller coaster, the Tornado, was awful. i thought i was going to be dead at the end :-/ oh well, i can say i did it, right? hmm...well, i must go now, tomorrow we are going into Edinbourgh with Karen, and MOnday we start the Covenanter Tour. I'll hopefully write more later!!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      finally!no more grounded-ness  :) the reason, if you care to know, was that on friday night i didn't do the dishes (which i was supposed to do) before i went to bed, and thus - no internet for the weekend! let me tell you, that was a little annoying.  but i'm past that now, and - SCOTLAND to look forward to!! I'm so excited, this day is going to go soooo slowly, even though i have lots and lots of things to do before i have to be at the airport at 4:45. such as:  pack   (hehe), go to the grocery store to pick up some cool American foods/candy for the MET girls there, take michelle to a friends house, make chocolate chip cookies for the plane ride...ahh i can't sit still!! in less than 10 hours i will be seated on a plane, headed for Toronto, and then scotland. :-P The Lord is so good! it is absolutely unbelievable to me that all the money we needed to go on this trip - and more - was provided by our congregation and parents. the only fundraisers we did were 2 babysitting nights for the church. i am so blessed to be in the church that i am. looking at those people who eagerly poured out their love and prayers to us these past months - and in the past years! - it is so easy to see that we serve a God who is full of lovingkindess and grace. "No eye has seen, no ear has heard, no mind had conceived what God has prepared for those who love him" I Corinthians 2:9.  i'm going to try and get on the internet at the church often, and instead of emailing, i'll just post on my blog what's been going on...!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      grounded for the weekend...:-/ talk to you all monday, i guess. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have found it!!!! Finally, a club  perfect  for me! Absolutely perfect! JASNA - Jane Austen Society of North America!!!! " Founded in 1979 by Joan Austen-Leigh (1920-2001), Henry G. Burke (1902-89), and J. David Grey (1935-1993), JASNA has grown to 4,000 members. About 550 of us gather in October for our three-day-long Annual General Meeting, which is located alternately between east and west coast cities in the U.S. and every fourth year in Canada. Our members also participate in year-round meetings hosted by any one of our 60 regional groups, which you will find listed on this webpage, along with information about our dues. Meeting topics vary from literary discussions to Regency dancing, biographical and historical study of Austen and her times to the study and play of such Regency games as Whist and Speculation. Our interests in topics relative to Austen are as unlimited as Austen's interests.  ty of North America.  " If you want to join, which i know of course you do, simply visit the website:  urlLink http://www.jasna.org/  :-P
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're Element is Light. You are friendly, happy, social, bubbly, and can brighten up any one's day. You are very kind and a real people person because you have several friends (or atleast should). You're cheery nature makes you lovable and your stunning looks are sweet and stand out.     urlLink   What's Your Element(girls)? (PICTURES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, i've finally made up my mind, after much thinking and praying. I'm not going to try to play volleyball for Geneva, at least for my freshman year. The cons outweighed the pros, and much to my surprise (and relief) my dad was with me. I wasn't sure if he would be disappointed at my decision, but he said that actually he wasn't sure if it would be the best thing for me to play this year, but hadn't wanted to say anything to discourage me from trying. :-) so that is a tremendous weight off my mind, and i can safely say that i am content with my decision.  i finally finished  Crime and Punishment !!! and yes, i was very satisfied with it...but of course, i like Dostoevsky sooo :-P it is amazing to me how Raskalnikov could think for so long that there was nothing wrong in his murdering his landlady. He denied it all along, and yet the effects of it on his conscience - his illness, secluding himself from family/friends - were so clear! Well, I'm going to dive into  Anna Karenina  :-P
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, it's a pretty good day...:-)  "Is there a harder discipline than that of waiting, especially when one's desires seem as wild and uncontrollable as a prairie fire?  "Without real trust in who God is - trust in his never-failing love and wisdom, we set ourselves up for disappointment. Is He a good God? Will He give what is best? If the answer is yes to both questions, it follows that He will withhold many things that look attractive to us. It is His mercy to withhold them. Shall we accuse Him of failure to get "His act" together or shall we echo the psalmist's word, "I am still confident of this: I will see the goodness of the LORD in the land of the living. Wait for the LORD; be strong and take heart and wait for the LORD" (Ps. 27:13-14 NIV) "If we imagine that happiness is to be found by furious pursuit, we will end up in a rage at the unsatisfying results. If, on the other hand, we set ourselves to pursue the wise and loving and holy will of our Heavenly Father, we will find that happiness comes - quietly, in unexpected ways, and surprisingly often, as the by-product of  sacrifice . "Waiting is a form of suffering - the difficulty of self-restraint, the anguish of unfulfilled longing, the bewilderment of unanswered prayer,flesh and heart failing, soul breaking. These are indeed tribulations, and tribulation is the curriculum if we are to learn patience. We want answers  now , right  now , but we are required at times to walk in darkness.  "Nevertheless, God is in the darkness. "'My soul, wait thou only upon God; for my expectation is from Him' (Ps. 62:5 KJV). In Him alone lies our security, our confidence, our trust. A spirit of restlessness and resistance can never wait, but one who believes he is loved with an everlasting lvoe and knows that underneath are the everlasting arms will find strength and peace.  "God is in the waiting." ~Elisabeth Elliot  The Quest for Love 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whew!! i'm so dead tired that  i could...well, i'm tired. but don't you all feel special? i'm up just so i can write this :-P today was a ton of fun...working at the seminary brought back sweet memories *sniff* of TFYP, and even though i  still  think those flowers in the courtyard-thing don't look as nice as i would like them to be...everything else turned out nice. and then volleyball in the evening...it made me think more about the college-deal. coach smith emailed me back and said she'd look at my DVD, but that they already have 14 girls on the team -their ideal :-/. i was really disappointed at first, but after tonight i'm not to sure. i feel so decrepit (sp?) and my knee just  aches ! how can i play volleyball like this???? ok, enough of the pity party, laura. i'll end on another quote, this time one from haylee that i stole :-D:  "An attitude of contentment and hopefulness is one that recognizes Gods sovereignty in every situation. It is a faith-birthed optimism that looks to God--an attitude more aware of and grateful for the evidence of Gods grace than of problems needing correction."         - Joshua Harris "I Kissed Dating Goodbye goodnight!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hehe...i can conquer the world...i just had my hair done by 2 5 yr olds and 1 2 yr old - and it looks just beautiful, let me tell you :-P. i thought i had a lot more to write, but i'm drawing a blank here :-D sorry, you'll just have to be satisfied with a quote: "I long for such nearness to HIm that all other objects shall fade into comparative insignificance - so that to have a thought, a wish, a pleasure apart from Him shall be impossible" -Elizabeth Prentiss
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you know what really, really, makes a hot summer day all worthwhile? a bowl of cold, fresh cantalope (sp?). in fact, that is what i am enjoying right now while i type this. i just came back from babysitting in a cool, air-conditioned home to my house - where the AC is never turned on till the last absolute minute. yes, it's hot in here.  i am nervously waiting to hear back from the Geneva coach about the DVD i have for her. i check my mail...and there isn't an email from her, only spam :-/. right now there's a little conversation (actually, call it a debate/argument) going on in my brain btwn two little voices.  one says, you love volleyball! you can't stop playing after high school. what about all the things you've done to prepare? and the other says, what are you thinking?? you'll barely have time to get your work done, and have a job without playing a sport. plus...college is a totally different level than high school...especially trinity. YOU'LL BE SMASHED grr it makes me all so angry. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mm..summer is very nice :-). especially today - there is quite a bit of satisfaction in working very hard in my garden, pulling all those nasty weeds that just won't stay away. and tomorrow - mulch! more fun to look forward to :-).  two foster kids are here with us right now...poor dears, they both won't go to sleep because they miss their mommy. they are adorable - the girl is 5 and the boy is 2 1/2. as if our house isn't crazy enough, we have these two :-P plus another little girl named Delilah (who we've had before) coming on friday! sometimes i wonder if my mother is sane, thinking she can take in all these kids...and then i realize, no she isn't.  i'm so excited...the russells got me a book called Taking Flight by Elisabeth Elliott for graduation - it's wonderful! of course, anything by E.Elliott is wonderful, but this is especially so :-P. goodnight, adieu! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm, what shall i write about tonight? it's rather late (for me at least:-P) so i'm not sure what nonsense i might end up writing.  I am a graduate! no longer in high school, the doors of college are wide open before me! lol, it's a little scary...everything was just starting to get very familiar and comfortable at Trinity - i'm definately going to miss it! But college is looking very exciting right now, especially with all the Trinity ppl going! High school all over again, no? lol, no, i don't think so. But before this fall, there are many other things to look forwards to! I would appreciate very much prayer for my trip to Scotland with my MET group - for safe travel, that God would be preparing our hearts, and that He would use us to encourage the church in Airdrie.  VIRGINIA BEACH !!! Thank you, everyone, who made the trip such a great time - including "Vince", yes, that was definately a funny memory :-P ( i can't believe we even  named  him!) Well, it's very late, and i have promised someone to be up with the sun...lol 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hiya  i'm at calvin  it is cool  it is late  i should go  but i wanted to write something so no one can call me a loser for not updating  yay for me  yay for...green eggs and ham    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, i'm playing volleyball at Geneva! 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow, i just read this yesterday in Desiring God by John Piper and liked it a TON so i thought i'd share it... “while I was staying at Nailsworth, it pleased the Lord to teach me a truth, irrespective of human instrumentality, as far as I know, the benefit of which I have not lost, though now…more than forty years have since passed away.  The point is this: I saw more clearly than ever, that the first great and primary business to which I ought to attend every day was, to have my soul happy in the Lord. The first thing to be concerned about was not, how much I might serve the Lord, how I might glorify the Lord; but how I might get my soul into a happy state, and how my inner man might be nourished. For I might seek to set the truth before the unconverted, I might seek to benefit believers, I might seek to relieve the distressed, I might in other ways seek to behave myself as it becomes a child of God in this world; and yet, not being happy in the Lord, and not being nourished and strengthened in my inner man day by day, all this might not be attended to in a right spirit.   Before this time my practice had been, at least for ten years previously, as an habitual thing, to give myself to prayer, after having dressed in the morning. Now I saw, that the most important thing I had to do was give myself to the reading of the Word of God and to meditation on it, that thus my heart might be comforted, encouraged, warned, reproved, instructed; and that thus, whilst meditating, my heart might be brought into experimental, communion with the Lord. I began therefore, to meditate on the New Testament, from the beginning, early in the morning.  The first thing I did, after having asked in a few words the Lord’s blessing upon His precious Word, was to begin to meditate on the Word of God; searching, as it were, into every verse, to get blessing out of it; not for the sake of the public ministry of the Word; not for the sake of preaching on what I had meditated upon, but for the sake of obtaining food for my own soul. The result I have found to be almost invariably this, that after a very few minutes my soul has been led to confession, or to thanksgiving, or to supplication; so that though I did not, as it were, give myself to prayer, but to meditation, yet it turned almost immediately more or less into prayer.   When thus I have been for awhile making confession, or intercession, or supplication, or have given thanks, I go on to the next words or verse, turning all, as I go on, iknto prayer for myself or others, as the Word may lead to it; but still continually keeping before me, that food for my own soul is the object of my meditation. The result of this is, that there is always a good deal of confession, thanksgiving, supplication, or intercesssion mingled with my meditation, and that my inner man almost invariably is even sensibly nourished and strenghtend and that by breakfast time, with rare exceptions, I am in a peaceful if not happy state of heart. Thus also the Lord is pleased to communicate unto me that which, very soon after, I have found to become food for other believers, though it was not for the sake of the public ministry of the Word that I gave myself to meditation, but for the profit of my own inner man.   The difference between my former practice and my present one is this. Formerly, when I rose, I began to pray as soon as possible, and generally spent all my time till breakfast in prayer, or almost all the time. At all events I almost invariably began with prayer…But what was the result? I often spent a quarter of an hour, or half an hour, or even an hour on my knees, before being conscious to myself of having derived comfort, encouragement, humbling of soul, etc.; and often after having suffered much from wandering of mind for the first ten minutes, or a quarter of an hour, or even half an hour, I only then began really to pray.    I scarcely ever suffer now in this way. For my heart being nourished by the truth, being brought into experimental fellowship with god, I speak to my Father, and to my Friend (vile though I am, and unworthy of it!) about the things that He has brought before me in His precious Word.  It often now astonishes me that I did not sooner see this. In no book did I ever read about it. No public ministry ever brought the matter before me. No private intercourse with a brother stirred me up to this matter. And yet now, since God has taught me this point, it is as plain to me as anything, that the first thing the child of God has to do morning by morning is to obtain food of his inner man.   As the outward man is not fit for work for any length of time, except we tak efood, and as this is one of the first things we do in the morning, so it should be with the inner man. We should take food for that, as every one must allow. Now what is the food for the inner man; not prayer, but the Word of God; and here again not the simple reading of the Word of God, so that it only passes through our minds, just as water runs through a pipe, but considering what we read, pondering over it, and applying it to our hearts…  I dwell so particularly on this point because of the immense spiritual profit and refreshment I am conscious of having derived from it myself, and I affectionately and solemnly beseech all my fellow-believers to ponder this matter. By the blessing of God I ascribe to this mode the help and strength which I have had from god to pass in peace through deeper trials in various ways than I had ever had before; and after having now above forty years tried this way, I can most fully, in the fear of God, commend it. How different when the soul is refreshed and made happy early in the morning, from what it is when, without spiritual preparation, the service, the trials and the temptations of the day come upon one!” -George Mueller 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, i am finally home. it feels very very nice, even though i've been very busy getting ready for my graduation party...pray that that goes well, and no rain! i got my scotland pics back and am putting together a scrap book...hopefully it will look nice, we'll see :-P well my brain is fried so i can't write any more...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, i'm movinng on Sunday! yes, it's terribly soon and i'm definately not ready...all my clothing is still in my closet and my dresser...nothing is packed, except for the stuff i have bought. and i still need to get a few things. *sigh* last minute things!! but i'm excited...i'll be glad once next week is over, because i'm a little nervous about camp, but once beth gets there and i'm settled in and freshman orientation starts, life should be good. :-) especially since violet is coming to visit me!!! yay! haha, well she's going to visit other people, too, not just me, but...i'm going to steal a lot of her time. :-P i definately did not expect to see her so soon after calvin, but it is a welcome surprise.  niagara falls is a very very cool place, if ever you have the chance to go - i enjoyed our trip a lot. the falls are just - spectacular. well, i have plenty to do. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>