<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have a boyfriend who is kind and sweet and hard working. He's "good people" as some might say. He's faithful, dependable, giving, he does a lot for me. I care about him deeply. But I do not know if I love him. I want to. I say that I do. But do I mean it? Or do I only say it because I know that should? I should love him. I should throw myself at him. I should desire to fuck his brains out.  But I don't. I have sex with him because he wants to, not because I do. When I see him, I do not get goose bumps or butterflies in my stomach, I do not loose my ability to think straight. I think, "oh, it's him, my boyfriend.. ok."   This weekend we went out. With friends. To bars. I haven't done that in a long long time. I used to do it in college all the time. Go out with my friends, get wasted, try to hook up with some guy, usually S. I was passionate about S. Everytime I saw him I wanted to rip his clothes off. I wanted to be near him, to feel the heatradiate from his body, to touch him. Just holding his hand was electrifying. But he was not trustworthy, not faithful, not "good people."    This weekend I want my boyfriend's best friend.  That's bad.  I wanted to be near him, to touch him to feel him. I was happy and releived to see him. He brighten the party. He made me happy. He made me horny. In a way that my boyfriend has never done. Spark. Chemistry. Lust. Why oh why do I not feel these things for D? For the man that wants to spend to rest of his life with me. Why?  Now I'm worried. Will it always be there, that attraction to someone I shouldn't, I can't, be with? Will the tension be there on my wedding day? Everytime we have a barbecue? A party? Will I accidently call out his name in bed? Should I stay with Dan? I feel obligated to sometimes. Should you stay with someone out of obligation? Should I sleep with him out of obligation? Marry him? Have his children? He is offering me a life that every woman wnats.  A life of stability, a house a family, love. But what am I offering him? obligation?  

						
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok, so I work in a bookstore. Most of the time I work at the register. I'm the girl that begs you to join our program to get our discount to save you 10% on all your purchases for a year (at the low cost of $25 per membership). You decline, I tell you your total and let you know how much you would be saving if you had a member card, one more desperate attempt to convince you waste your money. You shake your head no, and hand me your money, or your card, or your check, whatever. I total it out, bag your merchandise and shoo you out the door.  But some of you do not play by the rules of retail. Some of you come to the store everyday, or most everyday, or maybe just once or twice a week, but you never buy anything.  You pull out a book (the one you've been reading here for a week) or a stack of magazines. You take your reading materials to the cafe or a big comfy chair and sit there and read for hours. Sometime you prop your nasty bare feet up on the table as if it were your own living room. And you sit there until the store closes at its ungodly hour. Then you get up and leave your stack or reading material on the table or on the floor or shoved unceremoniously on the wrong shelf and you walk out the door.  Sometime you buy a cup of coffee or tea. Sometimes not. If you do, you leave the cup on the table, or on the floor or shoved unceremoniously on a shelf. You never buy the reading material, even though you often damage it. You never put it back where you got from even though you are a grown person and I'm sure your mother taught you better manners than that.   Some of you don't even bother reading anything. Some of you come in, sit at a table in the cafe or a comfy chair and you play board games with your friends. Or you discuss politics as if you know what you are talking about (although we all know that you do not). Or you knit.  Or you sleep. Or you recover from you hangover. You make no pretense of buying anything. You are there to waste time, and while you are at it, you may as well take up space and waste my time and my coworkers time.   Because obviously we have nothing better to do than clean up your messes and remind you that the store is about to close so could you kindly gather your belongings and get the hell out.  A handful of you are what we might call eccentrics. Chicken Lady, for example. You are the smallest, thinnest little old lady I have ever seen. I hear you only eat onions, green peppers and egg whites. I hope you take a multivitamin supplement as well. Every night, you come in between 9:30 and 10, scurry over to the display of reading glasses, pick out a pair to wear tonight, and primp your hair in the mirror. Make sure you don't have any foundation lines. Then scurry over to magazines, pick out one or two that might have an interesting article. As if you are on an urgent mission, you rush to the reference section, or the bibles, or the children’s department. You pick out a book. Probably a dictionary or thesaurus or bible, pull a chair up and facing the shelf so that no one can see you, and you read out loud. Sometimes in a light, hurried whisper, sometimes in a deep, demonic voice.  You often will repeat one line again and again like a broken record. "He they were the most grotesque and disgusting women in all the world... the most grotesque and disgusting... grotesque and disgusting..." Again and again, committing it to memory the way I'd like to commit you to the asylum. You scare the other customers, you know.  Tim is another wacko. Every night you come in and pick out a book, go to the cafe and read. You will pick the same book tomorrow and the next day and the next until you have finished the book. A normal person might buy a book before they read it.  Not you. You are always the last to leave, five minutes after we have closed. Perhaps you can not tell time. Perhaps you do not understand the announcement, "...the store is now closed." Perhaps you just ignore it. You shake your head all the time, like it’s twitching. You talk to yourself incessantly. You can barely say a word to other people. You speak to a few employees. I hear that you are very knowledgeable on many subjects. I wouldn't know. I don't speak to you. Not because of your mental difficulties but because I don't want to encourage you to stay, continuing to read books that are not yours, until after the store has closed. Maybe you think that normal rules do not apply to you. Since you get away with all of this, perhaps they don't.  There is a particular type of you that we have labeled “stalkers.” You are creepy. You are annoying. You are the worst of the irritating customers. You come in the store frequently; not every day, but at least once a week. Enough to be noticed, not enough to be predictable. Like the others, you rarely buy anything. But you do not hide in a corner either; instead, you hover. Often you are a computer programmer who stares at a screen all day working numbers and letters and having very little human interaction. One day you stop by the bookstore to check the price on some large computer book, or to check the latest issue of a computer magazine, and while you are there you notice the check-out girl is smartly dressed and has a sweet smile and is probably the kind of girl you can take home to mom. But she intimidates you just as you are intimidated by most other people, especially females. So you can not just walk up to her and ask her out. Besides, you are inexperienced in these matters. You do not know what to look for. You do not notice the diamond ring, the matching earring and necklace set or the faint hickeys on her neck, all of which were given to her by a dotting, attentive boyfriend. You do not notice these things and can think only of how to get her attention. And so you become obsessed. You need to discover minute details of her life then slowly woo her. You begin to stalk.   Once or a few times a week you will come in to observe her. You walk into the store, go straight to the nearest display and pick up a book. Customers do not pick up the first book they see without ulterior motives. You look at the book too long. Much longer than anyone would need to read the book description. You glance around occasionally, searching for your target. You spy her. You put the book down, move in her direction but stop at the next display. Repeat: pick up book, look at it for too long, glance around, site, move closer, and stop. You continue this dance until you are at the display closest to your target. She is busy. She looks very busy. Moving things, shuffling paperwork, picking up the phone, dialing, talking, more shuffling, restocking, moving boxes. She is doing her best to look as busy as possible so you will not try to talk to her. Sometimes this works and you move on past her, to the next display, and on, eventually out of speaking distance, but not out of site. You continue to mark her, your target, ready for the invitation to pounce and annoy. Sometimes (particularly the first ten times you come in) you lose your nerve, wander off, perhaps in search of a new target, and eventually you go home without having accomplished your goal. But tomorrow is another day, and you will be back to try again. The dance will continue.   Sometimes you do not leave. Occasionally you work up the nerve to talk to her. But what to say? You talk about the weather. At least, you try to. But words elude you. You mutter, you stutter, you lose your train of thought, you say things that make no sense. You try to explain that you are tired, or that you have a lot on you mind. She is painfully aware of your motive. She only hopes you will not say it. She tries to wrap up the conversation, to move it to its point and its conclusion so that it can end and you will be at a loss for something else to discuss and move on. But you mistake this for interest. You think she is responding to you. You are having a conversation with her, she is replying, she must find you interesting. You try to ask more personal questions: what do you do during the day? Are you from this area? How long have you lived here? What do you do for fun? Would you like to get a cup of coffee sometime? She tries to let you down easy, give you subtle hints. She insists that she is a very busy person. She does not have time to go out, to get a cup of coffee. She will have to decline your offer. Sometimes (particularly the second ten times you come in) you lose your nerve, wander off, perhaps in search of a new target, and eventually you go home without having accomplished your goal. But tomorrow is another day, and you will be back to try again. The dance will continue.   Sometimes you do not leave. Sometimes you are a persistent stalker. You have finally work up the courage to speak to her, and after all, she seemed interested in your conversation about the weather. So you continue. Are you seeing anyone? You are. Is it a serious relationship? It is. Well, perhaps some other time then? No. Oh.   No, we will no date you, will not get a bite to eat with you, or a cup of coffee, or tea, or what ever. We are busy ladies with busy lives and busy boyfriends, partners, and husbands. Leave us alone. We are taken, spoken for, kept.  We are already in love.   You are a fly on the wall that is suddenly buzzing in our faces and we desire only to kill you. You and the rest of the wackos, weirdoes and stalkers that frequent the bookstore.  

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ugh.. I was taking a nice little nap and havingsome weird dream that had a group of chicks roofing a house for some odd reason, and ponies, there were ponies, brought by some old couple that were supposed to be distant relatives of mine. And someone told me they would take me to work, and I went over to their car as they were getting ready to leave and they were alittle confused about the whole thing, but took me nonetheless. Weird dream. Anyway, it was rudely interupted by the ringing phone, and I though maybe it was D calling, but why would he call right now? And I was confused. So now I'm awake and have an hour and 45 minutes before I have to go to work, and I'm still a little asleep. And despite being off of work for three days in row, and complaining about it because I won't have any money, I still don't want to go. Not that it's a horrible place - it's ok once you get their - but I would much rather sleep. And I would much rather get out of there at a reasonable hour like 10pm instead of 11:30pm. But there isn't a lot I can do about that. 

						
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hey there. This is Penguina.  Ok, that's not my real name, but that's all you're gonna know. This blog is 100% anonymous. No one I know knows it exists. I have another blog somewhere in the wild blue yonder of the internet but you'll never know which one among the billions it is. Why? Because this is where I write the real stuff. The personal stuff. The stuff about my family and friends and loved ones that isn't so pretty. Names have been changed to protect identities. Here my boyfriends name is D and his daughter is B and my best friend's name is A. That is all you need to know for now.  

						
</post>


</Blog>