<Blog>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know how I feel Lonely in the black of night There can be no love for me now Nobody listens when the words ain't right And you get into someone else It's hard for me to know Who's loving who  And where do I stand What did I do it all for There's no one I could love more I did it for your heart alone All that I try to be growing inside of me I can be strong if you're there  And there is someone belonging to someone And I got no one belonging to me I'm caught in a world where the face of an angel Is all that a fool can see You got the power to find me whenever I'm gone Where are you Who are we  I believe in time Can eat away a heart of stone And baby if I leave you too late It's just a feather and the bird has flown It's colder when the fire dies And all the trouble I'm in if I lose you too  Then what is my life If I don't wanna go through Anything without you Couldn't be a life at all I could be lying on You are the only one We didn't make it by chance  And there is someone belonging to someone And I got no one belonging to me I'm caught in the world on the edge of tomorrow Is all that a fool can find I don't belong in the arms of a love that is lost Nowhere to cry There must be something we can say, my love Something except goodbye  Then what is my life If I don't wanna go through Anything without you Couldn't be a life at all I could be lying on You are the only one We didn't make it by chance   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today is my fourth day of recovering from my appendectomy.  I don't regret having it, otherwise I'd be dead by now.  It's a painless procedure of removing the most useless part of our body--the appendix, which is a small pouch connected to the large intestines, and once it gets infected, the only way to cure it is to remove it.  It's just like shit; it happens (for no apparent reason)  Furthermore, appendicitis cannot be accurately detected through x-ray or ultrasound.  You first have to feel excruciating pain just above the right side of your pelvic bone.  And then, you consult a doctor and wait for a recommendation to be admitted to the hospital, while your bills start piling up.  Once admitted, several neophyte doctors would have to wake you up in the middle of your sleep just to perform a redundancy of physical check-up and interrogation that are completely exhausting for you.  Until, you've gotten full of it, then you tell them to operate you right away.  But no, they're still guessing whether it's gastro-enteritis, urinary tract infection, or appendicitis.  With all the conjectures you hear, you'd want to be diagnosed with gastro-enteritis or UTI to avoid being disected.  And then when you've dreamt that you won't have to be operated anymore, your main doctor wakes you up and tells you that you indeed have to be operated.  You think to yourself that the scar could be covered with a tattoo or be laser-removed later on, so the operation would be like brushing your teeth.  After having been sedated, which was great and not having felt the pain of slices and stitches, you wake up and notice that you're not wearing the same hospital gown that you wore when you were brought to the OR.  And then images of Uma Thurman in Kill Bill start haunting you.  You think to yourself that a handful of people have seen you stark naked or worse, have even raped you.  Then they bring you back to your expensive room and you doze back to sleep.  When you wake up, you feel nothing.  And then when the anaesthesia runs out, you feel dampness on your back and you realize that you had just peed on the bed.  You want to cry because you acted like a baby, when in fact if you cry, you'll actually transform into one.  So you rebel from that thought and laugh instead.   When you feel that you can walk again, you lie back on the bed and cry because the man that you love hasn't visited you yet.  And then he calls you up and tells you that he'll visit you the following morning.  Afterwards, you can't wait for nightfall to come so you could go back to sleep and wake up in the morning and find him sitting next to you with concern and relief in his eyes.  But then, you've already eaten your lunch and still no loved one came.  So you cry and tell yourself that he'll never come until he calls again and tells you that he was sorry that he wasn't able to visit you that morning.  Instead, he tells you that he'll definitely drop by between 9 to 10 p.m.  Your face sparkles again from the anticipation of his arrival and you try to amuse yourself by watching the TV to kill time.  And then 9 o'clock comes and he still hasn't arrived.  You wait for another hour and then another until you decide to dial his number and check if he's ever going to come.  He tells you that he's parking his car already.  Then you become excited and you remind yourself to be calm because it's not good for your condition.  Ten minutes later,you hear a knock on the door and you say "Come in", and then you see him entering through the door with a can of Pringles in his hand.  You hide your disappointment that he didn't bring you flowers so you put a big smile on your face.  Then when he comes near you, you yearn for him to kiss you on the lips but then he kisses you on the cheek.  He tells you how glad he is to see you looking well despite the operation.  And then his phone rings and you hear him tell his caller that he's in the hospital and that he'll only be staying for 20 minutes.  You become disappointed again because he made you wait for a long time and yet he'll be staying for a quickie.  But then you keep smiling at him and you and he talk as if nothing happened.  Then later he tells you that he has to go.  You tell him to give you a hug, which he does.  And then you ask for a kiss, which he doesn't give you right away, but when he does, he only gives you a quick smack on the lips and reminds you that he has to go because his cousin is waiting for him.  Then you let him go, but you couldn't resist him so you ask for one last hug.  After a few hesitations, he puts his arms around you and tells you not to be stubborn and to let him leave.  You ask for one more kiss, but then he tells you that you're a bad girl for tempting him.  What else could you do?  You love him and you missed him, eventually you'd be wanting a kiss.  Couldn't he see that it's all you could do since your doctor had told you that you can't perform any abdominal exercises for 2 months.  Then he kisses you on the cheek and you let him go.  When he left, you suddenly felt empty.  It's a kind of emptiness that has no end because you realize that you don't matter much to him as he does to you.  Then you tell yourself to forget about him for the mean time and let him miss you instead.  The following day you get discharged from the hospital.  You feel bad because your stomach is bloated from the operation.  And since, you're only allowed to move minimally, you put your full attention in writing your book, which needs to be finished by June 26.  As you progress in your book, you become confident that you could do without him because you could achieve a lot with your writing.  So you go on writing and find yourself laughing at the memory of yourself crying over him on your hospital bed.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>