<Blog>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks for everyone's support, feel free to leave me any great ideas or cool stuffs so we can share with others.  -979
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Leave me a msg or sign the guest book by leaving me the comments.  Thanks 979
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1)  urlLink Packetyzer   Packetyzer is a Windows user interface for the Ethereal packet analysis engine  2)  urlLink Winpcap  WinPcap is an architecture for packet capture and network analysis for the Win32 platforms. It includes a kernel-level packet filter, a low-level dynamic link library (packet.dll), and a high-level and system-independent library  3)  urlLink Ethereal  Ethereal is used by network professionals around the world for troubleshooting, analysis, software and protocol development, and education
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink AntiVir®Personal Edition  is a free Antivirus software that was created in Germany.  It's rather very good antivirus consider that it's free.  Here are the break down:  -detects and removes more than 80,000 viruses  -always among the winners of comparison test featured in computer journals  -the resident Virus Guard serves to monitor file movements automatically, e.g.  downloading of data from the internet  -scanning and repair of macro viruses  -protection against previously unknown macro viruses  -safeguard against cost generating dial-up program  -protection against trojaner, worms, backdoors, jokes and other harmful programs easy operation  -Internet-Update Wizard for easy updating  -Protection against previously unknown boot record viruses and master boot record virus -Quality "Made in Germany"  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink SoftEther Ver 1.0   Here is brief concept:  1)  PC to PC connections  Setting SoftEther as PC to PC connection is the most basic and simple connection method.  With this method, one computer has SoftEther Virtual HUB installed, which then allows 2 or more computers to be connected. Therefore, a Virtual Network or SoftEther Virtual LAN is formed.  This is similar to the physical Ethernet network to which multiple computers are connected to one switch, with the exception that those clients are based in different geographical locations, and it is also possible to communicate freely regardless of the existing firewall and treats all clients as if they are based locally in the same area behind the same switch.  2)  PC to LAN connection   Think of your office LAN and PCs that are behind the company firewall. Using SoftEther's Virtual HUB and Virtual Network Interface Card mechanism, we will be able to access Company's Intranet from our Home Computers or any outside computers.  First we install SoftEther Virtual Hub on the office computer, then at Home we install SoftEther Virtual LAN card. Then from home computers we are able to use the Virtual NIC that SoftEther installed to bridge across the Office computer that has SoftEther Virtual HUB installed, since its Virtual, it's as if you are behind the Company's LAN, which then will be able to access the Intranet.  With this concept in mind, you can do the same thing using your company's computer to access your Home Computer to surf the internet, without the restriction of company's firewall or restrictions.  3)  LAN to LAN connection   With the above method in mind, we are also able to merge two or multiple office's LAN users together. On the Head Office install SoftEther Virtual HUB, and on Branch Office install SoftEther Virtual NIC than join this two together and bingo, both office's LAN client will be able to access each other as if they were in the same segment. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here you'll find coupons, sales, rebates for the products you want.   urlLink BensBargains.net   urlLink FatWallet.com   urlLink GotApex.com   urlLink HotDealsClub.com   urlLink SlickDeals.net   urlLink Techbargains.com  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1)  urlLink Ad-aware  With its ability to comprehensively scan your memory, registry, hard, removable and optical drives for known datamining, aggressive advertising, and tracking components, Ad-aware will provide the user with the confidence to surf the Internet knowing that their privacy will remain intact  2)  urlLink Spybot Search & Destroy  Protect your internet privacy against, spywares, keyloggers, hijackers, trojans, etc..  3)  urlLink SpywareGuard and SpywareBlaster  Prevent the installation of ActiveX-based spyware, adware, browser hijackers, dialers, and other potentially unwanted pests Block spyware/tracking cookies in Internet Explorer and Mozilla/Firefox  Restrict the actions of potentially dangerous sites in Internet Explorer
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink AVG Antivirus Free Edition  is a complete Antivirus solution, and it's totally free. It also will automatically update itself, without expiring like all the pay ones do. Install and run it today!   AVG Resident Protection  AVG e-mail Scanner  AVG On-Demand Scanner  Basic Scheduled Tests  Free Virus Database Updates  Automatic Update feature  Easy-To-Use Interface  Automatic Healing of infected files  AVG Virus Vault for safe handling of infected files 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Nmap  is a free open source utility for network exploration or security auditing. It was designed to rapidly scan large networks, although it works fine against single hosts. Nmap uses raw IP packets in novel ways to determine what hosts are available on the network, what services (application name and version) those hosts are offering, what operating systems (and OS versions) they are running, what type of packet filters/firewalls are in use, and dozens of other characteristics. Nmap runs on most types of computers and both console and graphical versions are available. Nmap is free software, available with full source code under the terms of the GNU GPL.    Nmap featured in The Matrix Reloaded   We have all seen many hackers in the movies which pass off ridiculous and stupid 3D animated eye-candy screens as hacking. So I was surprised to find that Trinity does it correctly in The Matrix Reloaded.  She whips out Nmap version 2.54BETA25, uses it to find a vulnerable SSH server, and then proceeds to exploit it using the SSH1 CRC32 exploit   Click  urlLink Here 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink BlueOrbPC Matrix Kid Online   Basically, I don't know if this works or not, but for 25 dollars, even if i lose it, that's okay, but this guy is on ebay, and his rating is actually not that bad, so I figured, maybe ppl do get their CHEAP game console shipped, you can pay with PayPal or Credit, which is secure, after all, for $25 it wouldn't hurt.    Here is how it works:   If you have a Matrix Kits that says $25/8, what that breaks down to mean is that you have to pay $25 to enter that particular matrix and the 8 means that it is a matrix of 8 people.  The 1st person that enters a matrix will be at the top and everyone else who enters will be below the person before them up to the limit of the matrix.   As in a matrix of 8 people, once the matrix fills up and a 9th person enters the matrix the person at the top will get their product shipped to them for FREE and everyone in the matrix moves up 1 space. Then the process just keeps repeating.  That is pretty much the entire process behind Matrix Kit sites.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Click  urlLink Here  to acces the ultimate deals site, if you look at the left menu bar, it has Live Deals so you can check some of the greatest deals up to the minute.  Happy Dealing!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Sudeki  (XBOX)  Publisher: Microsoft Developer: Climax Genre: Role-Playing Release Date: 7/13/2004   urlLink Fable  (XBOX) Publisher: Microsoft Developer:  urlLink Big Blue Box  Genre: Role-Playing Release Date: 9/13/2004   urlLink Jade Empire  (XBOX)  Publisher: Microsoft Developer: BioWare Genre: Role-Playing Release Date: 12/7/2004   urlLink The Bard's Tale  (XBOX, PS2)  Publisher: InXile Entertainment Developer: InXile Entertainment Genre: Role-Playing Release Date: 10/19/2004   urlLink Forgotten Realms: Demon Stone  (XBOX, PS2)  Publisher: Atari Developer: Stormfront Studios Genre: Action Release Date: 11/16/2004(XBOX), 9/14/2004(ps2) Download Play Demo  urlLink  Here 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone, sign up for Yahoo Mail now if you haven't an Yahoo email account. Why, you may ask, because they are offereing 100MB for free, yes they've upgraded their services as of June, 15th 2004, that's today!! Act fast!!                   Before   After Free Yahoo Mail   2MB      100MB    FREE Yahoo Mail Plus   6MB      2GB     $19.99 per year       
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Are u looking for external enclosure to backing up your most valuable data when "blue screen of death" angel comes?  Don't know which is better? USB 2.0 or IEEE1394? well look no further, thanks to Highpoint, the e.SATA is born!  So what's e.SATA when it's at home? Fortunately it's all very simple and straight forward, the "e" prefix simply means "external" and is the name HighPoint have given to their method for taking the SATA standard and making it available on a bracket to external devices.   So why bother? Well, take a look at how SATA's data transfer rates compare to the already established USB and FireWire standards.  USB1.1&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;12 Mbps&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;1.5 MB/Sec  FireWire &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;400 Mbps&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;50 MB/Sec  USB 2.0&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;480 Mbps&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;60 MB/Sec  e.SATA&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;1.5 Gbps&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;187.5 MB/Sec   Clearly the overwhelming thing is eSATA's impressive data transfer rate. At over 185 MB/sec, which is over three times the performance of USB 2.0 which should make it ideally suited to go with the theoretical burst data speeds of current generation hard drives, far more so than either USB or Firewire neither of which on paper can handle an ATA66 hard drive at theoretical peak burst let alone ATA100 or ATA133   Click  urlLink Here  to know more
     

    
</post>


</Blog>