<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The Origins of "O.K."  There are many stories regarding the origins of the expression "O.K." One relates to the many apple orchards in the county. Back in the 1700s, apples from this area were packed in crates marked "Old Kinderhook." There is even one on display in one of the eateries on the village square. Apparently people started referring to them as "O.K." apples. Gradually the term was taken to mean a description of the apples' "good quality" rather than their location of origin!   According to John Ciardi in A Browser's Dictionary: A Compendium of Curious Expressions and Intriguing Facts the expression "O.K." was used in the 1820's when   "...Boston wits took to playing a waggish game of 'murdering the King's English,' and in that game O.K. became fixed as the abbreviation for Orl Korreck. The game had played itself out by 1840, but the [Democrats] remembered it."   "Martin Van Buren, a native of Kinderhook, NY, was popularly known as Old Kinderhook, or O.K. In support of Van Buren's 1840 campaign for reelection, the New York Equal Rights Democrats ... formed the O.K. Democratic Club. The cry "O.K.," indicating enthusiastic approval of Old Kinderhook, soon began to resound at rallies, and the letters O.K. became common on placards and in political cartoons."   "Foreign coverage of the campaign, which included reproductions of the cartoons, soon spread OK or O.K. through Europe and Latin America as a formula of approval. From that start, for reasons anyone is free to theorize, O.K. spread to become naturalized into practically every language on earth. O.K. is the most widely diffused word form in history, rivaled only by Coca-Cola. ...When Van Buren was crushingly defeated by William Henry Harrison, the [Democrats] let it be known that O.K. stood for Orful Kalamity and Orrible Katastrophe."      A great deal of additional material is available from the following sources:   Ralph Duck, "History of Kinderhook"  Piwonka and Blackburn, "Architectural History of Columbia County"  Donald S. Johnson, "Charting the Sea of Darkness: The Four Voyages of Henry Hudson" 1995  Collier's "A History of Old Kinderhook" 1914   (I found this info on http://www.kinderhookconnection.com/history.htm) 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was at my friend's house yesterday, and her brother was home from college. My friend and I were swimming in her pool and I was telling her my plans for this weekend, and how I might go see Farenhiet 911. Then her brother piped in. This is kind of how the conversation went.   (Friend's bro)"Yeah, you'd like that. You're the political type."  (Me)"What's THAT mean?"  "You're the Political Type. I dunno how to explain it"  "How would you know?" (I've never had a single real conversation with this guy besides where things are in his house)  "You just are."   Now, I definetly wouldn't consider myself the political type. I mean i have a slight interest in what's going on in the world, just so i'm not completely oblivious to the things around me, but not hardcore "fight for your rights" kinda person. I can't even say more than "yes sir" and "Okay" to a police officer. None of you really know me, but if anyone reading this is super good at analysis, do you think i am?   -Ali 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Due to a certain family member's interest in my life, i've been forced to post. Not that I don't like to post, i just don't really have anything to talk about. School is out. I just got back from Idaho. It was a long drive back, and very hot. I don't have AC in my car, so you can imagine. My birthday is in 2 days. I'm so excited. I can't believe that i'm going to be a senior, or that i am i guess i should say. I feel too young or something. I'm sure i'll adjust though.   Ok, so i've found something to talk about. I'm visiting my cousin in a few weeks over on the east coast. I planned it so that i'll spend 15 days w/ her, get back on the first and have a few days to get back in the swing of things before school started up again. However, i didn't plan on the school district changing their usual plan of when school starts. Turns out, school is gonna start on the first, a few days BEFORE labor day, instead of the day after. This presents a problem... my plane arrives at 11:09PM on the first. So, i'm gonna miss the first few days of my senior year. But there's not much i can do at this point... well i guess there is, but there's nothing that i really WANT to do about it. My teachers are just gonna have to deal i guess. I do feel bad about choir though. I made the Jazz Ensemble at school this year, so i really need to be there for it, i might just go in for that class and then go back home... i don't know, i'll figure it out when it gets closer to that time. anyway, i hope this is a good enough post for y'all (ahem! Joanna... ahem!) Love ya Cuz!   -Ali 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, I've had this friend, Brett, since freshmen year. He's a really cool guy, and a great friend. Recently, however, i've started to devlop a, for lack of a better word, crush on him. Apparently he's into me too, which would be totally awsome, except for this one little thing. He's got this thing where he told himself that he wouldn't date, cuz he doesn't see the point in it at our age. I totally can see his point of view, and respect that.... at the same time though, I'm sad, cuz i like him a lot. He's such a nice guy, and a good catch. The fact that he likes me too doesn't help my situation any, but there's not much i can do. So, any suggestions? My predicion: even though he says he doesn't date, something's gonna develop anyway, then that'll be real confusing!   -Ali  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, Obviously this was me, a VERY long time ago. I don't know why, but I had the biggest need to have a boyfriend, which i tried to fulfill last year, but i'll post that later. I was going through a rough time then. I had found out my friend had been raped, I was on the verge of depression myself. I had a poor family life, and I was starting to see how corrupted the world could be. It was a lot for my 14 year old mind to take in. But I've changed, boy have I changed. I no longer care if I have a boyfriend, Jennifer and I are no longer friends, and I've just grown up, to put it as simply as possible. The biggest worries of my life when I was 14 are now not even on my mind. Which is how it should be. I'm now almost 17. even the thoughts I had, and the things I did LAST YEAR make no sense to me. I have no idea why i felt the way i did about certain things, and why I acted the way I did. It's not who I am, and I know that now. I guess it's like they say, you learn from your experiences, and become a better person in the process. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is me&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Journal Entries:  (Freshmen Year) 6/2/02  I've tried to start a diary before, but I've never kept it up, hopefully i will this time.  I am getting so lonely! I can't find a boyfriend, and it's really starting to get to me!  All my friends are ditching me for thier boyfriends, and i just wish that i didn't feel like a 3rd wheel all the time.  Why do i still have to have feelings for Erik?  I keep on telling myself to get over it, but i can't.  Besides, he's taken to one of my friends (even worse).  I think i might like Johnathan, but i'm not sure.  I know i wouldn't want to go out w/ him though.  He's not really my type.  I wish and hope i can find a guy before the end of the school year, but I know it'll be harder cuz summer is comming up, and aswe know, guys like to be "free men" for the summer.  Well, better get to sleep!  6/3/02  Today I decided that I'm going to get my act to gether and shape up.  I acctually did my homework!  But anyway... Johnathan update: I still am not sure how i feel about him, but he notices me, which is always good.  I was walking to 6th period, and as i was heading into the building, he said,"Ali! How's the KKK going?" He always asks me that. [just to let everyone know, he was refering to the "Krazy Kortney Klan"].  I think i should try a REAL conversation with him one of these days.  I don't see him as much of a long term relationship kinda guy though, two-weeks tops!  But anyway... I'm gonna try to get a good night's rest.  That's all for now.  6/5/02  Okay!  MY week is NOT going well at all.  Yesterday, I found out that Mike, on of my "kids" got into a car chrash in Walla Walla on Sat.  at around Midnight.  Great hu?  He has a bruised lung and vertebre and cracked ribs.  His dad's shoulder is shattered and had surgury on it yesterday.  His mom, little sister, and brother all died instantly.  Mike and his dad were found concious at the scene.  It was a head on collision, with a drunk, illegal immigrant who rean from the scene.  I don't think the cops have found him yet.  And now on a less dramatic note- Johnathan likes Tasha.  Just my luck!  But i know she would just treat him like ----, like she does with all the other guys that she knows like her.  Maybe I can create a small deversion though... hmmmm.  Oh, at lunch, Tasha asked me if I liked johnathan.  I was sitting right next to him, so i didn't want to say anything.  I wanna find out if SHE likes him before I make a move.  I'm gonna write johnathan a letter now though, don't ask.  6/6/02  Today I had a migrane all day, and i still have one, grrr!  Jonathan was all, "your gonna walk with me." after 4th today I don't know what's up w/ him.  I dunno if he likes me or not, and Cortney doesn't want me to get involved with him because of the stuff he's into.  Anyway!  Erik stole me at lunch today again, and Cortney thought I got in trouble for skipping w/ johnathan or something (I didn't skip!), but anyway!  I really need to practice my piano.  I'm not doing the greatest at the moment and Holly can't go camping with me, so I called Jennifer to see if she could go, an she hasnt' called me back yet.  Her dad's (Step) sentancing hearing was today, so i don't know when she'll be home.  Well, i'm gonna go now. P.S.  I say DJ today and he came over and put his arm around me and i told him about my headeache and hen carrie said, "Oh, i thought you were going to kiss her forehead," so then he did.  DJ is such a flirt, and he has a girlfriend, weird, hu?  He calls me cutie or squirt and always flirts with me  I don't know what's with him, but I don't mind. :)  6/13/02  Sorry, it's been a while, but I'm determined to keep this diary up.  I'm sad!  Today was Johnathan's last day I was going to tell him today that I liked him, but that never happened.  I got distracted w/ something a little bit more important.  Jennifer told me earlier today that when she was 2, her real dad had raped her (supposedly).  She had told her mom, and it's not like she would lie about something like that.  But it didn't really seem to bother her, but at lunch she started to cry and later she dotl me, "I'm not even 15 and I've been raped 3 times."  And I just tried to comfort her, and tell her,"It's not your fault, that should have never happened to you.  You didn't deserve that, but you don't have to deal with it on your own, I'm there for you."  And then later in English I cried.  It's not fair, she didn't deserve this.  It should have never happened to her.  I've been trying to find the good out of all of this, the reason it happened, but i can't find it.  I've been praying about it, but i have yet for my prayers to be answered.  But I'm gonna move on 'cuz I'll start crying agian if i keep thinking about this.  So back to something a bit happier.  All my books are gone.  I don't have to worry about them anymore.  When we were walking back from the library Johnathan jumped on my back, so i ended up giving him a piggy back ride half the way.  He's really light though, like 100 pounds.  Today was the hottest day of the year, uggg! Well, gonna go to bed.  6/14/02  Today was such a weird day.  It started out really not good, and turned into a pretty good day, which is always good.  I woke up and my mom told me that I had to clean my room or cortney couldn't spend the night, so i had to get up and clean, first thing in the morning.  Then i started to let Holly and Jennifer get to me, so while I was walking to 1st period, I was blubbering like an idiot.  So i felt really stupid.  Then i found out that I still have a C+in PE w/ a 83.6%.  Which should be a B-, but no, Mrs. Abrams has to have a ----ed up grading scale just so she can ruin my life.  But by lunch, things turned around.  I found out tha ti was passing science, yes! I've got a D, but i'll get my credit.  Then Jennifer came w/ me and Cortney to -- ------ and we ate dinner and then went shopping.  I felt kinda bad cuz Jennifer didn't haave any money to buy anything,  but I think she had fun anyway.  Mom says we're gonna make me some summer shirts.  Cool, hu?  Well gonna get to bed.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So... This is my first official Blog.  I'm Basically turning my paper journal high tech.  I'll put entries from my old journal in, as they seem appropriate, and then new ones as well.  So, Hi.  Tell me what you think, I'll change and improve the blog as i fell is needed from your comments.  Enjoi!  -Ali
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Lately, I've been having really weird dreams.&nbsp; My most recent dream went down like this:  I was at a hotel somewhere, and it was pretty nice.&nbsp; All these people were there, from school, my family, my mom's co-workers... anyway, so yeah.&nbsp;&nbsp; I was getting married to Brett, and I was wearing a red dress, which was a little odd.&nbsp; But there never was a ceremony it was just like, i'm getting married, and now it's the reception, but at the reception, i was kind of ignored.&nbsp; So i got food, and sat down next to Brett, and he said something like, "well it's not like we're actually married, it's just a fashion show."&nbsp; and then i woke up.&nbsp; Weird hu?&nbsp; I think i need to start watching what i eat before i go to bed....   -Ali 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, I live next door to these people who used to basically RUN the Miss America Pagents, or something like that, so they know all these people.&nbsp; I was over at their house a few days ago, and Val gave me the card for an executive chairperson or something for the Snohomish County pagent.&nbsp; If i called her, and even just helped out at the pagent, apparently I'd get to know these top people, for like theater and stuff.&nbsp; Part of me says, oh my gosh! that's awsome, if you know these people, you can do what you REALLY want to do- but the other part of me says, this is too good to be true, it's weird, i'm not a pagent person.&nbsp; So... now i'm faced w/ the dellema. Do I call, or not?&nbsp; I can't make up my mind, help, please!  -Ali 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've thought a lot about college; where to go, what to study, but I haven't really thought about the work, what I'd actually do when I got there.&nbsp; Will I really be able to do it? The classwork, the papers, the research?&nbsp; Can I handle it?&nbsp; What if I can't?&nbsp; Then what will I do?&nbsp; My dreams, my plans, they's all be ruined, finished, and then there would be nothing I could do about it.&nbsp; I'm worried and a little scared.&nbsp; What'll I do? 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, I know all it seems I've been writing about is Brett. Sorry folks, but he's just on my mind. A part of me feels like I should just really leave him alone, so I don't mess up his no dating rule. Another part of me really wants him to forget about that. I just don't know what to do. I want to be able to support him and his decisions, but at the same time, if I were to do that, I'd be doing exacly opposite of what I want. What to do, what to do?   -Ali 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      On the 4th of July, Brett asked me if I wanted to meet him to see the fireworks show in town. I obviously said yes. Erik was with me at the time, cuz his family was out of town and he had helped out w/ the races, which by the way raised over 700 dollars from my guild for children's hospital.... anyway.... so the park was really crowded, and i couldn't find Brett anywhere when i got there, so I was a little frustrated, meanwhile, the whole time Erik was making fun of me because I like Brett. So anywho, i tried calling him, and he never picked up, so I ended up just watching the fireworks with Erik and his friends.   When I got back to my car, I had a message on my phone- Brett. He had called to tell me where he'd be, and sounded all disapointed. He said, "So.... I hope i get to see you tonight..." and then I felt so bad, cuz I could tell that he really was looking foreward to hanging out w/ me. I told Erik that, and he just said,"Oh my God Ali! He likes you." and I said, "Yeah, i know, and I like him, but he 'doesn't date'". That's when I think Erik realized that it was more than just a crush or something, and he stopped teasing me.   So, I headed on back to Brett's house, so he'd know that I hadn't just not come, but that I couldn't find him. You should've seen his face when he saw me at the door. We hadn't even talked to eachother in almost 3 weeks, so it was great to see him agian. Erik had said he wanted to stay in the car, so I was talking to Brett, while erik was doin whatever in my car, and then I realized that i'd been in there for more than half an hour. I said I needed to get going, so Brett started to walk me to my car. It was nice, cuz it was the first time we'd been alone (his parents were inside). He started to get a llittle close to me, and then Erik stuck his head out the window, and screamed, "COME ON ALI, LETS GO BLOW UP STUFF!" Well, of course, then Brett stepped back about five feet, and said i should probably get going. I could tell he was thinking, "oh, she's with  Erik"  I didn't know what to say, but i was just thinking it's not like that, i swear! I was soooo mad at Erik. But, i can't really blame him, I did leave him in the car for forty minutes. However, i was very frustrated, now i don't know if i'll even see him for the rest of the summer, but i'll certainly hope i do.   -Ali 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, i don't know if this is a common fact or not, but it's new news to me. Did you know that the Moulin Rouge was ,and still is (to my knowledge), a real place?  Most importantly for our story, the Belle Epoque gave birth to a new culture of entertainments immediately recognisable as modern. To mark the centenary of the French Revolution, a revolution against privilege and inequity, Paris staged the Universal Exhibition of 1889. Here, a variety of amusements and new technologies serviced wondrous worker and bourgeois alike. This 'levelling of enjoyments' as one contemporary called it, marked a democratisation of leisure that heralded the 20th Century's invention of mass culture.  As Paris raced toward the end of the century, automation and mass production brought heady rewards. There was more bread, wine, books, textiles, fashionable garments and new concept Parisian department stores to buy them in. Above all, the populace made a dizzying start on the twentieth century's love affair with new technologies. The invention of the telegraph, the telephone, the elevator, the bicycle, hand-held cameras, the first automobiles, the electric light and the first mass produced typewriters - not to mention advances in both public hygiene and in surgery, spawned an optimism at once practical and utopian. For the Bohemians of Montmartre, who in our story called themselves 'the Children of the Revolution,' the promise of 'Truth, Beauty, Freedom and Love!' of a better world, seemed germane in these unprecedented new technologies.  But it wasn't all unalloyed progress and joy. Along with the benefits of the machine age came bitter social dilemmas. Paris drank as never before, increasingly as a social past-time, spawning a new social disease: alcoholism. Tuberculosis, organised prostitution, the spread of syphilis, and overcrowding as the promise of regular income beckoned those from farming communities to the ever-swelling cities, abounded. Still, evidence of a new mood afoot is wittily immortalised in a contemporary pamphlet attacking the work ethic and the misery of workers in capitalist industry - and entitled 'The Right to be Lazy.' Here, author Lafarge condemns the 'dogma of work,' chastises French workers for 'vegetating in abstinence' and recommends work be confined by law to three hours a day in favour of a new healthful 'regime of laziness.  With the rise of organised mass labour came the new concept of 'leisure hours' and a demand for mass entertainments. A booming middle class found more time for distraction - and more money to spend on it. An ever-growing new demand for popular entertainment, for race tracks, circuses, opera, brothels, cabarets and balls, was voiced. Indeed, turn of the century Paris hosted some 27,000 cafes which, in tandem with the wine bars and cabarets gave it more drinking places than any other city in the world. By century's end, 264 cafe-concerts or 'theatres of the poor,' many of which evolved into their grander relation the music and dance halls, also flourished. Here, bourgeois, worker and Bohemian alike could enjoy a song or a theatrical act for the price of a drink. All kind of distractions were in vogue, and the low life, in particular the amorous low life, was suddenly hot. Located right in the heart of artistic Bohemia and Paris' criminal underworld, the establishments of the Montmartre district were perfectly equipped to serve it up...and to fulfill that yen which the French even coined a phrase for, that is 'la nostalgie de la boue' (lit: longing for mud).  Crowning the Montmartre-based world of commercial entertainment was Joseph Oller and Charles Zidler's landmark music hall, the Moulin Rouge. When the Moulin Rouge opened its doors on the Place Blanche at the foot of Montmartre on the 6th of October 1889, all Paris turned out. Highbrow and lowbrow society alike mobbed the 'Palace of Women' before the paintwork was dry on its extravagantly decorated interior. The Moulin Rouge's decor, by Montmartre painter Adolphe Willette, its exotic colour, form and themeing became an overnight legend. Besides the immense dance hall complete with galleries to watch the dance floor and an orchestra mounted above the stage, there was a garden with another stage, cafe tables, cavorting monkeys and unstockinged prostitutes riding donkeys. Also in the garden, a giant elephant (gleaned when the Universal Exhibition of 1889 terminated) housed an Arabian-themed club inside its body. Male clients entered via the elephant's leg where a spiral staircase opened onto belly dancing performances, an orchestra and an opium den. Making a radical break with the century's relentless class divisions, a microcosm of Parisian society rubbed shoulders in scandalous proximity. European royalty (including the Prince of Wales), ambassadors, politicians, industrialists and magistrates slummed it with celebrity courtesans, can-can girls and workers. The local Montmartre Bohemians and the cocottes and noctambules (prostitutes), pimps, madams and thieves who were their neighbours were also out in force. Within the Moulin's velvet draped walls, the aromas of women's scent, face powder, tobacco, and beer mingled as promiscuously as the audience. In a class of their own were the courtesans, a social phenomena that all but died out with the end of the Belle Epoque and the beginning of World War I. Though springing from the same working class as the prostitutes, the more celebrated courtesans were distinguished by the length and high-style of the relationships they formed (with, near exclusively, the elite of Europe). Like today's film stars and super-models, they were also cultishly observed by press and public. But if the Moulin Rouge quickly established its reputation as the most exotic sex market in Paris, it also represented a kind of cultural and social revolution. Think of it as a can-can-besotted version of Steve Rubell's disco-crazed Studio 54 crossed with Bangkok's sex market meets Mardi Gras' carnival.  The Bohemian's anti-establishment mores thrived in Montmartre, whose Butte district was honeycombed with the studios of struggling, long-haired poets, painters, sculptors, musicians and students. Shunning the bourgeois world of their parents generation, the Bohemians plunged into cafe society, leftist ideologies and a drug and alcohol culture that many - notably the legendary poet Rimbaud and his lover Verlaine - saw as the gateway to artistic inspiration and transcendence. With characteristically anarchistic verve, Bohemian artists broke with the ultra conservative Academies and took art to the streets with their posters, overnight magazines, satiric cabarets, costume balls and the democratised theatre of the cafe-concerts. Painters began to observe the demimonde - the streetwalkers, beggars, drunks and petty crims they cohabited amongst - with a frankness and an observational wit that challenged establishment mores. Artist Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec, reluctant scion of one of France's oldest aristocratic houses, became one of the most notorious Bohemians of fin de siecle Montmartre. (At 4'11" - a genetic bone condition had stunted his growth - he was also one of the shortest). Lautrec immortalised the inhabitants of bar, brothel and dance hall in his paintings, prints and posters with a stylishly simplified perspective that is now credited as one of the earliest forms of visual Modernism. Lautrec, whom a contemporary described as 'a queer top-heavy little man, swaying on his stunted legs like a ship at sea,' was a favourite at the Moulin Rouge with management and dancers alike. Armed with his legendary wit and drafting skills, and a fashionably fatal alcoholic habit, the diminutive Frenchman partied and observed the world from his regular table, often till dawn.   Entertainments at the Moulin Rouge included roaming performers and side show freaks; witty social comedy and stand-up; an opportunity to listen to the latest Edison phonograph from New York; a view of Paris from the howdah atop the Elephant or somewhere deep in its belly, a quiet shot of morphine; pseudo-exotic dancers; every sexual favour or deviance imaginable for a price, and most famously, the can-can dancers. Evolved in Paris' ragingly popular cafe-concerts and music halls, and identified with the lower classes, the can-can's violent abandonment and erotic acrobatics were the sensation of the day. Considered especially provocative was the height and violence of the dancers' leg kicks which were literally policed via the safety pinning of their split knickers. Legendary can-can practitioners at the Moulin Rouge included Jane Avril, La Goulue (lit: the Glutton, named for her habit of draining abandoned glasses at the bar) and the male dancer Valentin Le Desosse (the Boneless)...all of whom were favoured by Toulouse Lautrec. There was also Nini Belle-en-Cuisse (of the Beautiful Thighs) and Mome Fromage, a plump lesbian red-head. Inspiring further characters in the film were the North African cabaret artist Le Chocolat and the curious Le Petomane, a musical flatulator whose 'aspiratory anus' caused corseted ladies to be carried out in breathless hilarity.   The cocktail of choice among cabaret and musical hall goers was a bitter green alcohol called absinth that had something of a cult following amongst the Bohemians. With a high spirit content, absinth also contained elements of the poisonous herb wormwood and had rumoured hallucinogenic qualities. Its popularity in late nineteenth century Paris inspired a renaming of the city's beloved cocktail hour to l'heure verte, or 'green hour.' Taken either with or without sugar, absinth inspired one Parisian poet to shout "I take it with sugar" as a rapturous form of greeting that sorted fellow users from non.  (All of this info and pictures were gathered from  urlLink http://www.clubmoulinrouge.com/html/member/background_sin.htm )                                          
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, as soon as I clicked the "publish" button, I remembered some more stuff to write about....  1. I have a weird uncle (no offense Joanna). I was talking to my aunt and she said that my Uncle Jack had called her and asked her how many social functions she thought i would want to go to. She told him that i probably was going to DC more so to sight see and visit Joanna than anything else, so no more than two, IF ANY. So he apparently called her back and told her to tell me to bring one long and one short formal dress (this is of course without talking to me or getting my input at all, but whatever) So I went out and had to buy a formal long dress, i have a short one, but not a long one, so yeah.... It's neat, it's simple, but rather elagant. I like it, and i'll be able to use it for a school dance, so it works out. (I wish i knew what it was for though....)  2. I am now afraid to drive with my window rolled down I was driving on the highway a few days ago, and they had just put down a bunch of gravel, so the speed limit was 20mph, of course no one was doing even close to that, since it's normally a 50mph road. This car drove by me, superfast, and kicked up a bunch of rocks that flew into the window and hit me in the head. It hurt, and even cut the side of my face a little. Not fun.... Then, today, i was driving to Brett's house, and i was talking to my mom on the phone, and i felt something kinda hit me in the head, so my first thought was, "oh great! I just got crapped on by a bird, so i feel my head, and there was nothing there, so i let out a sigh of releif, and then i looked down at my shoulder, and there was a yellow jacket there, just hanging out on my shoulder, and i SCREAMED! My mom started freaking out cuz she thought i had just gotten in an accident, and then i started screaming "THERE'S A BEE ON ME! THERE'S A BEE ON ME!!!" and so she told me to pull the car over, and get out, and i pulled the car over, but said, "I don't want to move, it's gonna sting me!!!" and then after a few minutes of this I finally got out and tried to get it off by moving my shirt, but it was haging on good, so i brushed it off, screamed again, ran into my car and rolled up the window.  I swear, i was all jittery all the way to Brett's house.  FYI: I hate bees.  -Ali 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Mo called me, from "Footloose" and said, "we were all standing around, and i asked Carrissa 'did you call ali yet?' and she said 'no, didn't you?' so i'm calling you! How are ya!" and he asked me if i would still like to help and i said that i had a pretty busy schedule so it looked like i couldn't.  However, right after i hung up the phone i was like "man! i really do want to do it!" so i searched everywhere for mo's number and frantically called him back leaving him a message someting like " I really can't make up my mind, and i'd like to help, so PLEASE call me back asap."  So he did, and i'm working as a costume change helper :P  Its really rediculous, cuz i don't do anything, but whatever, it gives me something to do.  Another interesting thing about this is there's this guy that works over on stage left with me, and he's an interesting fellow.  I could tell right away that he was all "hey, how you doin!"  and so I decided to stay away from him.  However, he had to go to stage right to do a scene change, and he came up to me, and said something along the lines of "I've gotta go to the other side of the stage" paused for a moment, then gave me a hug.  "....ooookay!" I thought.  "this guy is a little odd" anywho.... oh and later he asked me if i would "do" the male lead in the play.  I've decided i don't like him.  Okay, now to how it becomes the play from hell..... The second night of the performances, i got to the theater and was setting up stuff, getting ready for the show to start, and us crew people were just standing around about 10 min. before the show was suppose to start, when the fire alarms went off, which meant we had to go around and evacuate the building; cast, audiance, crew... then two firetrucks show up, checked it out, and told us it was just  hairspray that had gotten on the lightbulbs and made the fire alarms go off (which we warned the cast about, by the way...) Then, once the show finally started, one of the cast members flew off stage in a hurry and knocked over one of the set peices,which landed on one of the legs, which landed on the syke (a very expensive screen). Translation: not good.  So, i had to rush to the other side of the stage and try to help this ONE other girl move this huge wooden bench that whieghed a ton.  But that's not all... no, no.  After the intermission, we were just about to start act II when, one of the cast members starts to hyperventalate, and almost fainted, so we rushed her off stage, and were trying to get her to breathe and calm down, and we couldn't, so we had to call the medics, and for the remainder of the show, she was in the back room w/ an oxygen tank and 3 medics around her untill her parents could get there to pick her up.  WOW, was that a show or what?!  On a much better note, Brett and I hung out today.  I'm never letting him pick the movie again.  We saw colladeral, and there was way too much "GUNSHOT! SPLAT!" for me.  :P  It was R for a reason i guess.... all throughout the movie i was curled up in my seat all grossed out and Brett just kept on laughing at me, and saying "Ali, you're so cute!"  Which under other circumstances, it would've been just fine, but it wasn't.  anyway.... I think that's all for now... i'll post again later if i think of anything more, it's been a while since i've posted, hu?  -Ali 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>