<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Devon used to be a fairly athletic guy, always running around, doing sports. He wasn't the best, but, he definitely wasn't the worst. But in time, he matured and became somewhat of a nerd. He was always on his computer, his brother gave it to him once he moved out and got a better one, so it wasn't a great computer. His friends, few friends, described it as 'ancient.' His life wasn't all that boring until one day...so he thought.  Devon was at his little computer, typing away for a research project for his college history class. He was writing a 10 page essay over the Revolutionary War. It was due tomorrow  and he was only on the 7th page. To make matters worse, he was really stressing out and when he looked at the clock it read: 2:16 AM.  "Crap, why did I wait so long to do this! Prof. Neits assigned it a week ago, and I blew it off until three days before." He sighed. He finished the sentence he was typing and leaned back in his comfy chair, his only escape from the major pressure, with his arms behind his head. The screen flashed black then a greenish blue screen popped up.   "Oh my God! What happened to my report!!" he screamed as he slapped the computer hoping it might help.  It flashed white then blue again and typed out the message:  "m-th-r k-dn-pp-d. -ddr-ss = time, r-ck p-th."  "What is that supposed to mean? It's in some sort of code, or something...Wait a minute, there aren't any vowels! Except in time. I wonder why.." Devon questioned. "Hmm...maybe the dashes took place of certain vowels?? M-_-T-H-_-R..Hmmm, M-A, nah. M-E? nope...M-I!...no..M-O! M-O-T-H-E-R...Mother?! What about her!!" He screamed, as if it were a living person.  Devon spent hours, it seemed, trying to crack the rest of the message. So far he had Mother kidnapped. Address = time rock path. He still was unsure what the time was for. Eventually, the remembered it was 2:16 when this message came up.  "216 Rock Path? That's not an address anywhere near here." wondered Devon. "What addresses do I know of that have a 216 in their address.."  After about 10 minutes of thinking, he finally had it.  "216 Rock Path stands for 216 Stoney Road! It's only a few blocks from here!" he shouted "But why would my mom be at the library? Oh well, I better go look for her."  For some unknown reason, he got up, tossed his bag over his shoulder, and headed out the door.  "What the-!" exclaimed Devon as he peered around outside. It was daylight. "How is this possible?! My computer said 2:16!"  He decided it didn't matter seeing as he had to get to his mother's aid. Then, he realized that his mom was here, in New York. When she lived in Kansas.  "Wait a minute. How can she be here?" asked Devon, as if there was some all-knowing guru right next to him. "No time though, I must get to her."  He trekked on and eventually reached the library. It seemed to be standing unusually taller than normal but he ignored it.  "216 Stoney Road. This is it" he said. As he walked into the library.   There was a spiral staircase. He walked up to it, looked upwards, only to see it going up very high. Too high He saw the ceiling and figured his mother might be there seeing as she wasn't on the first floor. He started hiking up the staircase getting nearer to the ceiling, and to his mom. He was looking up the whole time but, when he looked down, he appeared to be on the third step still. This threw his equilibruim off and he stumbled. But, the ceiling wasn't any further away than when it was a second ago. He got up and started up the stairs once again. After hours, it seemed, he finally go to the top. He peered over the edge of the floor and saw his mother tied to a chair at the end of a hallway of bookcases. He hurried up the rest of the way and dashed to his mother. As he neared her, her heard her screaming something.  "G-- -p!!! W-k- u- D---n!!" she screamed.  Slowly, the message became clear. She was screaming 'Get up! Wake up Devon!' Devon, realizing he was in a dream, he suddenly awoke to find himself in his room. But, it wasn't his room as it had been in the dream. Not his sheetless bed, cluttered desk and shelves. But, it was his twin bed, with dinosaur sheets and pillow, his rug with a street and town imprinted on it. The rug had toys scattered everywhere on it.  "Devon! Get up! It's time for school!!"
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "LANCE! WAKE UP! NOW!!" A large man with a deep voice was banging on the door to Lance's bedroom.  It was six o'clock in the morning, and Lance rolled over with a sigh.  He opened his eyes to look at his clock.  "Ugh, I hate this... especially on a Monday..." he shut his eyes and went back to sleep.    Twenty minutes later Lance's father came into the room, dressed for work in a black business suit and a tie.  "Lance," he started "It looks like I'll have to get you out of bed again." he walked over to the side of the bed and pulled back Lance's warm covers.  Lance's legs shot up to his chest the moment the cold morning air touched him; he shivered a little.  His dad then lifted the matress off on one side, sending Lance rolling over onto the floor with a thud.  "DAD! I told you not to do that anymore!" he said, shooting up.  His dad replied with a small devlish smile on his face, "maybe next time I should pour cold water on your head instead?"  Lance shouted back "NO!  Come on dad, I'm never late for school." "Only because I get you up." his dad replied.  Two minutes later they left the house, Lance was chewing on a cereal bar and trying to flatten his messy brown hair which he had no time to comb.  "Got everything?" his dad asked.  "Yeah, everything except a good night's sleep." Lance said with a small yawn.  He saw his dad get into his car and drive off to work.  Lance lived in a small community just outside of the city, so his house just across the street from school.    In Twenty minutes the first period bell rang.  Lance was practially falling asleep, he stayed up too late doing homework, only because he chatted over AIM too long.  His dad didn't get home until very late, so it's not like his dad would really care on the way home from work.  First period was Geometry, and he wondered why this class had to be first period of the day.  "Class." a blonde haired teacher addresed the class, "pull out your homework.  Problems 1-65 please." Lance's heart sank... he didn't do his homework!  "Oh, what am I going to tell hi-" he stopped mid-thought, walking across the room, her blonde hair flowing in the air behind her, was Alexa. She walked past the window which overlooked the flowers in front of the school, her glowing blue eyes flashed in Lance's direction, and for a moment, both eyes met, and the-  "Looking at the beauty of God's work, Lance?" the teacher asked. "Uh, y-y-yes, sir.  I mean, no sir, I mean-" Lance replied, wondered if the teacher saw him looking at Alexa. The teacher replied sarcastically "I know how beautiful the flowers in the garden are, but please try and pay attention.  Now, you're homework?"  The last bell rang, and Lance picked up his bag and headed for his locker. Behind him walked Alexa and some of her friends.  He wondered if he'd ever get to make a move, she was always hanging around with her friends, and it's not like he could just pull up in some nice expensive car and drive away alone with her, impressing both Alexa and her friends.  He headed outside, going home, but stopped at a tree to think.  After banging his head against the tree several times, he saw Alexa come out for tennis practice.  Several rounds went by, when all of a sudden a voice popped up from behind Lance.  "Painful, isn't it.  You're whole world standing just beyond that fence, just out of reach."  Lance seemed not to notice too much "it's only a fence..." he replied back.  The guy behind him answered that, "a very big fence, can't have stray tennis balls flying out... or flying in for that matter."  "No.. we wouldn't want tha-  HEY!" Lance jumped back.  Standing behind him was a shrimpy kid with red hair and brown eyes, he was obviously a freshman.  "What are you sneaking up on people for?"  After several minutes of talking, Lance really only found out the guys name was Mike, and he skipped all of middle school because of his intelligence, but knew how he could help Lance get Alexa.  "Um, but if you skipped all of middle school... wouldn't that mean, you know... you're a nerd?  And uh, incapeable of getting a date?"  Mike looked stunned, "well, if you don't want my help, you're doing a greeeeaaat job already with getting your date.  So I'll be out of your way."  as Mike walked away, Lance realized how good off he WASN'T in getting Alexa.    The next day after school, Lance was in his position.  Mike had reset the electronic message board in front of the school to read "ALEXA, I LOVE YOU", and then Mike would set off some fireworks or something.  Lance could care less about fireworks, he just wanted the message to be seen.  Alexa would soon come out from tennis practice, but one of the last ones to leave so all of her friends wouldn't be there.  He waited, and waited, and waited.  Until at last, after what seemed like an hour (but was really only five minutes) Lance got up the courage to go find her himself.  He walked around the corner, only to see Alexa making out with some other guy!  How could this happen?!   Lance quickly tured around and headed home.  Moments later he heard the fireworks go off, so he suspected that Mike sent them off, and also wondered if he turned on the sign.  If Mike DID turn on the sign, it was probably in the other guy's favor.  He gave a big sigh as he fell backwards onto his bead.  "Oh well, life moves on I guess." he said to himself.  "but I really did like her..."
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The contributors to "Pirate's Gold" have all agreed that the current story, "Pirate's Gold" has gotten to the point where nobody wants to continue it.   Our next activity should be better. Each member will be asked to write a short story. Each story will only have one author, and will start and end in the same post. The due date is June 25, next Friday. Participating in this activity is optional.. but if you care at all for making this blog succeed than I suggest you participate. *ahem*  So, Begin! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Dimitri! Wake up!" yelled Drew, one of Dimitri's crew buddies.  "Huh? Aaaaaah!" screamed Dimitri, still thinking he was falling toward the deep turquoise waters of the ocean.   "Whoah buddy, calm down, you are safe inside the ship on a nice cot now, don't worry" reassured Winters.   "Ouch! Ughh...what h-happened? Where am i-I?" mumbled Dimitri as he flinched the moment he felt a shock of pain run through his battered leg.  "You were hanging on the anchor after being hit by that cannon ball. You fainted, but, you still hung on. You saved my life." said Winters. Dimitri noticed the faintest trace of sympathy within his gaze. "Thank you. And, thank God we managed to get you up. Drew here had to go down there with a rope around his waist. He carried you up to safety!"   "Heh, th-thanks Drew. But, d-did we win the battle?" said Dimitri, shivering from loss of blood.  "Yes we did. It was a close one though. They got us pretty badly. I have some of the crew working on those dents below deck. It's a good thing we built her sturdy!" chuckled Winters.  As Dimitri looked around the room from the soft cot they had lain him on, he saw Drew, Winters and a few other crew mates he sometimes talked to including Jake, Gavin, and Hector. He started to smile, knowing that all these people were here because they cared for him, just as everything started spinning and became fuzzy, he blacked out yet again.  His peaceful sleep was broken by another dream. It started just as the other one ended.   It was a trap... 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Dimitri hung from the anchor hole as best he could, the shock still held him in its numbing grip. He could see Cptn. Winters yelling, but the noise was shier void, as if audio has seized. Dimitri held fast for a time into the battle, but has only the strength of a man, and finally his grip faltered, and he plunged into the turquoise water.      The following few minutes were a total blur of blue and white foam, but by a godsend chance, he ended up on a plank, 100 or more yards out, it was all he could do to hold to the board as he drifted farther, and again, passed into darkness...     Again awaken, this time, to the lumbering shadow of a Royal Battle Ship. Then he noticed a life raft headed in his direction, with fully armored gaurdsmen ready to escourt him to the abyss. He made a feble attempt to flee, but it was only an aimless paddle outward, and he soon stood before the Admiral of the Royal Navy Fleet.     It was a trap...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      His happy thought was soon interrupted by a loud *CRACK*. Across the room, there was a large, splintered dent in the hull of the ship. He jumped, dropping Wesley to the floor. Wesley hurriedly scurried off to his same little cove in the flour, but, Dimitri had nowhere to go.  "We are surrounded!" said a crew member, shortly followed my another loud crack directly behind Dimitri. He was thrown forward by the sheer force of the blow to the hull. Dimitri decided to run up on deck to see what the heck was happening.  When he saw Winters standing there, calm and fierce, at the same time, he too was clam for a second. A very short second. Out of the corner of his eye, he saw a huge steel ball flying through the air straight for the captain's back.  "CAPTAIN! WATCH OUT!" scream Dimitri as he dove to protect the captain. The ball thankfully misses Winters, but, Dimitri wasn't so lucky. The cannon ball had bashed his right leg from the knee down to no return. It's force carried Dimitri, away from the captain toward the edge of the deck. He fell down the side of the ship. The captain was sure, he would never see that young, intellegent Dimitri again.  He slowly walked to the edge of the ship to see the fate of his young hero. Everything around him seemed to go in slow motion as he peered over the edge to see young Dimitri hanging from the anchor hole.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      He walked carefully accross the slightly flour covered floor, taking special care of where he placed each foot. Upon reaching the wall he slid down onto the floor, his knees bent into his stomach. He surveyed the floor around him, looking for something. His face lit up at the sight of his partner. A large fat, grey haired rat, was laying, almost squished, between two bags of flour. Dimitri greeted his furry companion, and gave him a little scratch on the nose. "Hello there, Wesley." The rat instantly began grinding it's teeth, making the clicking noise all rats make when overjoyed.  Dimitri reached into his vest pocket, and pulled out a shimmering gold coin. The rat's eyes burst with joy at the sight of it. It began scraping away at the floor with it's paws, slowly, but surely pulling itself out of it's little cave. (How it got in there in the first place, is another mystery of the universe.) Then, like a bullet out of a rifle, Wesley the Rat came rocketing out of his hole. His head slammed into Dimitri's outstreched hand, and bounced back. Taking a second to regain his thoughts, he than grabbed the coin in his paws, gave it a snif, and than a bite. He looked up once more at Dimitri's face, to show his gratification, and scampered off, down a hole in the floor.   Wesley returned from his home in the floor, skipping greetings and immediatley searching Dimitri's hands for another shiny prize. Dimitri handed about 20 coins to the large greedy rat, untill he came back to an empty hand. Dimitri patted him on the head, and scratched him behind the ears, and said, "Don't worry Wes, I'll bring you more another day."  Dimitri had been practicing this ritual for quite awhile now. He's probably stored atleast 300 coins down there. Dimitri smiled to himself. He picked up Wesley and cradled him in his arms, tickling his white belly.   From above, a loud commotion broke out. Dimitri sat nervously, petting the rat to sooth his fear. He'd been through this many times, but it always worried him. The panic in his mind has calmed down a little since his first time in an attack, but never completely. To erase the fear completely would be to erase the human in him, it is impossible. The yelling got louder, Dimitri became more uneasy. He imagined the fight taking place above him. He saw the enemy ship, 4 times as large as his own. He saw a cannonball lodge itself in the side of the ship, and the entire room filling with water. He then saw Captian Winters, fighting to his very last breath, and suddenly, remarkably, most of his worry was soothed. He pictured him and Winters, fighting together, side by side. He smiled to himself again, and waited.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After seeing the captain's steady gaze, he calmly went back to his room to read. He was reading a very good book. It was an action scene, much like the one he was experiencing at this very moment. The only variation was that it wasn't between two pirate vessels. It was between two small countries a ways south and east of where they were. It was a fiction book so, it never  really  happened. But, it was really interesting. So interesting, he didn't even notice the captain standing in the doorway, giving him that same, comforting, yet forceful green stare.  "We are approaching the enemy ship." explained Winters. "We are just out of firing range so I need you to take cover below deck, on the starboard side."  "Yes sir." said Dimitri as he snapped his book shut and stood up straight.  The captain then turned on his heel, and walked, almost marching, down below deck with Dimitri following. Once below the upper deck, Dimitri once again saw this familiar place. Barrels of ale, bags of curry and flower. There was a different arrangement in the corner with some flower bags. One could tell that Dimitri has been here before and these small battles are no new thing. Little did he know, this was not any ordinary 'small battle.'
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It still amazed Dimitri how organized the crew was. Drunken fools only hours before, they now worked with an ease and grace like no other. Another mystery of the universe, thought Dimitri. Perhaps though, it wasn't all that much of a mystery at all. Dimitri glanced at the captian, and they caught eachothers eyes, and for a split second, Dimitri knew exactly why the Pirates worked so well. The sharp green eyes smiled at Dimitri, and seemed to tell him, "Everything will be alright." 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         "Sir! You must awaken! The pirateship Sailbeam has been spotted only half a mile out!" Fumbiling about for his trousers and coat, the news is delivered quickly. "The Captain requests your prescence on the bridge, sir!" Out of the cabin, it was utter pandamonium, men hurried for their cloths and ran to their battle stations, some half nude.    Once on the bridge, he realized that only half the officers were in uniform. "How long till were in range?" asked Captain Winters. "Twenty minuets, if the winds hold", said the navigator  "What are we up against?", the Captain asked  "Armorment unknown," said the weapons specalist," but our range isn't enough to strike first" Dimitri sighed, this was the kind of thing right out of the text book, but he still worried. Would this day end for him at the bottom of the sea?
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         As owner and operator of The Mental Motel, I'll do my best to add my part to the tales of now. (stop by http://thementalmotel.blogspot.com/, our rates are competitive)
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In the warm lamplight Dimitri fumbled dizzily around the swaying, creaking, snoring room. Dimly lit all around him were the faces and beards of stinky old men, half asleep, half unconcious. The smell of ale wafted steadily in front of Dimitri's nose, poisoning his every breath. He carefully made his way through a maze of bodies, trying hard not to step on anyone, and then halted in the corner, shining his lamp on a large chest nested next to the wall, bolted to the floor. He exhales, sending dust in swirling patterns in front of his eyes. His attention is temporarily lost in the swirling patterns of light rays through dust. Quickly he snaps back into reality, and reaches into his pocket. His hand emerges from the pocket of his sleeveless white vest, revealing a rather large, rusty key. Hey presses the key into it's rightful hole on the chest, and turns it. Quickly but carefully he opens the large metal framed lid of the chest, and the light from his lamp is reflected back at him, from thousands of golden coins. Hastily, he shuffles a couple handfuls of coins into a small bag, closes the lid, locks the chest, and creeps back through the maze of smelly old men. He climbs up a ladder, breathes a sigh of releif, and retreats to his cabin.   The creaking of the ship continues steadily as Dimitri lay on his back, staring up at the ceiling of his private room. He closes his eyes and has a short moment of peace. Sadly to be soon interupted by tomorrow's duties.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi, my name is Travis and my other blog is  urlLink here.   I hope that this group story blog will turn out well and I will do my best to contribute. I am not much of a writer. But, I think it will be fun to practice writing, especially for school. I want to develop my writing skills, not because I want to be a writer, but, because they need developing. :)  -Travis-
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And with his mighty hand, Buddy created A bowl, and in this bowl, letters and tomato soup. Then with a grace like no other, Buddy called forth the soup crafters, who formed the letters into sentences, and then into paragraphs, and finally into stories.   This will hopefully be a fun group blog in which those who wish to join, and have decent writing ability, can come together to create collaborated stories. Eh, I give it a couple weeks before we give up on it.  So, we'll start a new story every month, and maybe take a break for short one member stories, weekly stories, and any other new interesting things we can think of.  I'll begin by inviting some friends to come join in on the fun. Then we'll attempt to start some sort of story out of our little brains. 
     
    
</post>


<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The earlier post by okiejory that has a quote at the ending saying "winning a race with a Honda is like winning the Special Olympics, even if you win you're still retarded" is wrong, it goes "Winning an argument is like winning the Special Olympics, even if you win you're still retarded." The way he changed the quote I do not like, mostly because I like Hondas, they are good cars for regular people, and my step dad drives a Honda Civic.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         ah, the wonder of the video game. Behold, one of mankinds many vices. fav's include Halo, Diablo 2, and Starcraft. My 1337 Necromancer skillz own (i wish). Im cursed with a dibilitating disease, PNS, perminent noob syndrome. No matter how long i play, i suck. period. if anybody has a cure, plz let me know, its bothering my friends.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Can you install a supercharger in an hour? can you lay custom fiber glass? Can you even change the oil on that p.o.s.? if you answered no to all or any of these questions, your a chick (and its ok) or your an idiot who needs a hobby outside your computer. I love cars, classic muscle baby! every once in a wile ill write on my obsession and see what i get back from it. I love cars, i love ladies, i love to hate every minuet of my existence and yet have it so good.          Racing in a Honda is like racing in the special Olympics, even if you win, your still retarded!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey all, this is Haybusa, for anybody who knows me, I have a Blog called Orc Fort...Go check it out! Anyways, I have become a member on okiejory's site, yeah so, um, I'll be randomly posting here telling you about... Stuff. So, cya next this is Hayabusa, out.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A skeptic by nature, I at first assumed a blog was for those who lack the means for a social life and geeks, but now I've come to a chilling realization... I AM ONE! I may be stupid, but at least I'm smart...If that makes any sense.       If I may borrow a quote form an old friend, "if the world didn't suck, we'd all fall off." I must say, of all the suck in the world, it seems to congregate around my little microcosm. My family isn't much help either.         (not bad for a desperate attempt for attention) 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I love to meet new people. I enjoy the different personalitys, I take them as a new challenge. Because I realize finally how i am, I've decided to embrace it. Each new person is a challenge, to see what their personality causes me to be. Sort of like, testing chemicles togather, and seeing the reaction. Its like evolution, on a one on one scale. Anybody who is disgusted by my new attitude can lodge a complaintin our department.  http://www.candytower.com/link/1296.jpg
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I dont know how I'll get along from now on, but I'll try to throw this in the air. My agony is a realization, I'm fake...There is no Jory. Jory Frick is an empty body. Useful as a sack of beef. I realize my personality isn't my own. My persona raps itself around whoever I'm around for extended periods, and if I ever sound like someone else, I'm just reseting my personality and readying myself for my next thought process. In essence, I become what others want me to be, and if its not possible for me to be like that, I revert to an old personality.  This is why I like being along for extended periods, I seem to almost catch a fleeting glimpse of who I might actually be, but as soon as I'm around people again, all hope of me is lost, because I become that which is wanted around.    There are a few possible culprets. One, maybe I have a sub-conscience want to be excepted. Its possible that I want to be wanted. A second, more likely idea is, I see the other persons personality as superior, because I see them interacting with others in the way they do, and become jelous. You know, the grass is always greener. Finally, it might just be possible that none of us have a true personality, perhaps we all, weather we realize it or not, we all just imprint and combine the best and worst into a collective that is yourself. A mental copy and paste. Perhaps were all just collages of other people, endlessly changing and evolving.    wow, that felt good...there I, the real me, the thinker is, and there I go...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         to whom it may concern:      Anybody who thinks they know or knew me. That was then, this is now. I've decided to make a change, and it only took 2 weeks of suspension. I'm going back to the way I once was. To BTR, I'm sorry, now shut up about what was. To Hayabusa, I'm sorry, now shut up about what was. To musashi, I'm sorry, now shut up about what was. to anyone who has beef with me, SHUT UP!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I was reading Buddy the Rat's (who I'll call BTR) posts when i came upon this Blurrpi person, and apparently they have something to share.    "Blurrpi: Heh. All you can do is have the people that you care about/care about you understand your taste, and you understand theirs, and live comfortably without hoping to change one another. If you try to change other people because of your choices, then we have a problem. Blurrpi: But if you simply discuss and enjoy and such, don't worry."    *SLAP IN THE FACE* this is what BTR has been trying to tell me! We (BTR and I) have been friends for quite some time and as long as I can remember the only time we ever fought, it was because I was trying to change him or impress my opinions on him.                                Quote for the log books    "Dont try to change the people around yourself. Remember,  people often change because of the people around them, so change yourself, and you'll notice a change in them."  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         To my friend and fellow blogger Hayabusa, I feel I must express an opinion, or more strait forwardly, a request. Even though you've been a favored guest in the mental motel, I must ask you to leave your keys at the front desk. Hayabusa, what's mine is mine and what's yours is yours. No longer shall you post, but do please comment (as I enjoy them so)as often as you'd like.     sorry...    fine, I'll stop bashing Honda and I revoke my previous statement that people without car knowhow are idiots. Upon re-reading that post, i realize that sounds like someone else wrote it, i hope that doesn't send out wierd vibes. I'll break down my apology:    "if you answered no to all or any of these questions, your a chick (and its ok) or your an idiot who needs a hobby outside your computer."  women, not chicks, thats demeaning if you dont have car skillz, who cares, only idiots who write things like that even notice. "I love cars, i love ladies, i love to hate every minuet of my existence and yet have it so good." I do enjoy working with metal, and motors are interresting, I do enjoy female company, but I try not to say it like that, and I do have a fairly good life, and sadly, I do take it for granted.    im sad to say that depending on my mood, I have a very different personality, In all of 40 minuets between posts, I became something I wish I could say I wasn't. If I'm like that again, slap me through the computer screen.          peace, love, and crabs (eat at Joe's Crab Shack)                        
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I feel bad having not written in my blog, but not as i did feel a short time ago. something i cant even see put me out of commission temporarily, but im back, and just as sarcastic as ever. its funny a virus, an assorted collection of proteins and self replicating DNA can reek such havoc on the human form. the only bigger irony than the dominent form of life on this planet being brought down by the smallest known (though non-living) thing, is that we cant kill it. virus 1, me 0    but anyway, life goes on and the sun will rise and there will always be a broken down honda somewhere on the interstate :)!        Semper fi, carry on!    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        As my previous post states, I'm leaving. I'll be back posting Friday. The camp I'm going to is a church camp (Life Church to be exact) and were going to texas...(oh boy...) So, i recommend different blogs for your enjoyment: http://ratnest.blogspot.com/ http://alphasoup.blogspot.com/ http://shogunsfortress.blogspot.com/ http://orcfort.blogspot.com/
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       to the regular readers of Room for Rent:      Guess what? I'll be leaving for camp Monday morning. Try to contain your utter sadness, as I'll be back late thursday and post again on Friday. but anyway...      Looking at my half bottle of IBC root beer, I thought about optimism and pessimism. I pity the people who call it half full. Deluded into being happy with where the glass is filled to. The same goes for the people who whine about it being half empty. To me, it is half of a glass. The glass isn't to be looked upon as it is, but as it could. Don't think about the amount in the glass, think how you can get more in the glass. Think, "how could I put myself in a position to fill it further?" And once you've filled your glass, help others fill their glasses too. Eventually, we will all be filling each others glasses, and this pain-in-the-butt world of ours will be that much fuller. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          I find myself at a crossroads between people i care deeply about. I like two different ladies,  but im the classic can't-choose-between-them situation we all end up in. Used to i'd just be good friends with all of them, but now, I fell I need to go exclusive, just because i havent in forever.     "If it is true that a man who finds himself in a situation to choose between to two evils should go with the lesser, does the same apply with the greater of two goods?"     What if my heart feels i should go with the lesser of two goods? If I go with the lesser of two goods it would be the greater of two evils, thus my delema. Both are amazing people neither of whom I diserve, but they both share my mutual feelings. Anyone in the same poisition, do feel free to give advice on the comment section (I do read them).
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey, im back...finally! I've been in Texas at the YMCA camp called Camp Grady Spruce. I went with my church youth group, and I im truely changed through the expirence.      I have many friends, who ill not name, who dont actively seek a religion. I personally believe in a God above and the lord Jesus Christ, but for those who have a difference in opinion, I accept it. I cant change some ones opinion by willing it, but i can show them my beliefs, and if they choose to act on that experience, more power to them! At camp, me and my piers grew in our walk with christ in ways not possible without the loving support of the YMCA and our councilers. Thanks guys...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      just when I thought I had my life set, another girl comes along...(but I'm sure u don't want to here about that)    one thing I've realized in my fourteen years is, life is too long. Now only matters now and tomorrow, come a week of month or year, on one will care. Consequences are only temporary, and relationships are temperamental, and u can always move on. Decision is a false sence of control. But, don't mince my words, if you dont take care of now, there will be a very sour later. Don't take my post as a call to lazyness, it is true that it won't matter later, but the time between now and later can kill you if your too reckless. Be careful, but live alittle.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've decided to not decide. Because of the advice from friend, I've decided to wait. I can give them both time to grow on me.     My friends parents don't even think dating at this age is appropriate. Well, I agree, but i dont agree. Dating at this age isn't necessary, but it is a good tool for devoloping the skills you need in later life to get married. Anybody who takes it too serious should realize this is just a time of learning; for anybody who doesn't date, you'll have a disadvantage in later life. (why did I post this?)
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The Triarchic theory of Intelligence states that intelligence manifests itself in three facets: the Analytical, Creative, and Practical facets. The Analytical Facet is basically a measure of academic-based problem solving,  thats how it started...and i soon became bored, i guess im not in the 'intelligence' mood. i just feel like being plain. I feel lonely, but I've got friends all around...  oh well
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The idea of genetic predisposition is based on the idea that your genetic maps and code have more to do with your personality and I.Q. than your environment. This theory is backed by the story of two twins, separated at birth. The twins each grew up under different circumstances, one lived in a small town with good schools, where a good education was readily available. The other, grew up in the inner city, where a good education wasn't so available. Despite the difference in life styles, when the twins met each other, they had very similar personality and intelligence level, even though they grew up in totally different places with totally different learning opportunities, yet both twins act very much alike. This can only be explained by the theory of genetic predisposition.  (if this bores u, scroll down and find the location of our complaint department)
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      back from florida finally!! &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; When i was in the airport, I got a tase of the true melting pot that the world it. Here where I live, everybody is white. The airport has so many races and religions, its kind of a shock. Id say i have a new apperication for others. kind of... &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; i have a problem, or should i say a weakness. Im a loser when it comes to ladies. Every other aspect of my life im fine with, except my relationships with ladie friends. I never know what to say. Anybody who doesnt know me would say im doing fine, those who do know better.  ...i, of anybody, can live with it... 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
           Never think that there is a secret saying or strategy that will give you the leg up on the people around you. There is no one ideaology that can guarantee success with the tempermental humans we interact with everyday. They change in mood faster than you can devolope a plan, therefore, im just gonna limit myself on me's, that way, It'll be less likely for me to slip up and say something stupid. Life is a game of chess, War, and poker (person to person strategy, group to group strategy, and luck). THE NEXT PERSON TO SAY SOMETHING ABOUT MY SPELLING SHORT-COMMINGS WILL HAVE THEIR ARMS TORN OUT AND WILL BE BEATEN TO DEATH WITH THEIR OWN APPENDAGE!!! (taste, kigami, not tase)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      because i hate everybody, and everybody hates me. I can never be the same person around anybody, so i quit... i need to take a break from people for a wile... 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>