<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know that in life we must do unto others as they would do unto you. Today I helped the NVCPlayhouse get donations so that we can open a new playhouse. After that we all went to the Phoenix Rescue Mission to help feed the homeless and thoes who are just not fourtunate to have food on the table to share with their children. I believe that this experience helped me realize that all of man kind or equal but there are thoes of us who are delt a horrible hand in life. I think i'm going to go back and help out more. Maybe i'll even get my friends to come too. I'll write to you guys later. ttyl &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      la la la ok iknow something you don't know I'M A DORK...no wait.....that's common knowledge. So I don't know something you don't know i know something we all know bye bye &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if your stressed heres a way to relieve it. 1.)go egging and run around like a maniac  2.)make plans to just hang out with a bunch of friends from grade school ppl u haven't seen in awhile. 3.)ignor your parents  4.)sleep till 3pm  5.)Do w/e you want and dorn't care what ppl think of you 6.)steal a lawn gnome 7.)ask your parents for a couple bucks and go get a king size slurpee!  8.)dress like a freak and go around the mall for 2 bucks 9.)blast up your stereo at three in the morning  10.)go skini dipping inyour grandparents pool when their out with your bf/gf and take pics and send them to your gp's in the mail j/k just take pics &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      random but i'm on the phone w/ jim at 1:30AM!!!!!!! holy crap and he's all like CALL ME &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      GOD I HATE DATING! do u know that dating leads to having a social life? wow i so don't need one of thoes...i'm like just BLAH over alix and jay like they even care they know i like them but like uh dude i'm not ur dream girl really i'm not! Jay and Alix prolly already have gf's and i'll be looking in on their happy lives from the "outside" maybe if i had developed social skills when i was little i'd be like normal. Ha not instead my k-8th grade years were spent crying in the girls bathroom at the end of the field..the farthest from all the kids and it smelled so no one went in it. My life looks so awsome because i put on an act woohoo ya for all u guys who thought i had the COOLEST life ur mistaken i didn't really even have friends until freshman yr, my first real relationship was this yr and now i'm spilling my guts over the internet Smoothe move caci!  bye &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      her teeth look really funny! lol lol lol rofl&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok my sister tally her two front teeth broke in half and like she doesn't brush her teeth or go to the dentist! GROSS!! Talk about ewe and she has 2 kids but like she blames her not going to the dentist on her husband and shit it's like dude he has insurance go to the fucking dentist well i g2g.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok my friend mike is soooo stupid! he's like "you will feel pain the next time i see you" and i'm all "i'm taking that as a threat!" so ya he's dumb im WeridkideDK or Mrono7 to tell him he's a dumbass and needs to fuck off &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey guys i'm super bored GO FIGURE but anyways we went bowling last night (me kiley shawna dustin and debby) and kiley and i were dancing with dudes from other lanes and these guys and their girlfreinds came pu and were all "uh excuse me but thats MY MAN" and i was all oh ok w/e so we stole the bowling shoes and left! mu wahahahaha&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      boo boo boo boo booo i'm doing karaoke tomorrow! yay&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok today wasn't a good day really...Kee punched me in the back then i threw the oxy clean at him and hit him in the head. His only comment was "when did u learn to throw?" so ya now the babies are at the ER because they have really high fevers well thats it&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    i may be a dork but i'm really a nerd on the inside! (friends b-day party @ the bowling alley)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In my life span there have been many journals, diaries ,things of that sort but never an online blogg. Finally after many years of this life I'm ready to come out and let people see the real acacia, for once my mom and dad will see I have a voice and that I like to speak it when everyone else isn't around. Now for simple background information. I was born into a family of 6 counting myself, during this past year a lot of things have happened my family no longer accepts who I am or that my dad is always spending time with me. I've sat there time after time being ridiculed by my eldest sister tally and my other sister kira. They just never leave me alone and then kee is brought in by the fact that he is abusive and since I'm the smallest, weakest, and wont tell he has to beat up on me. My mom resents me saying I was an accident and if she hadn't been stubborn I wouldn't be around she thinks that I'm am the root of our family's problems! And yet she is a hypocondriac. Well this is me get used to it  acacia 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ok so i was on the phone with dave last night grr idk y i was but i was welk g2g    lovecaci  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      important new info I MIGHT JOIN A BAND muwahaha and i have more incommon with my crush than I thought well g2g  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ya fish r fun I miss ppl but still can't get over crushes &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ppl bug me but i still hang out with them anyways...Jim and Liz came over last night. Sometimes I question why they are friends with me because I was talking about Val and My ideas and they were like "she's weird" so I was like "you guys just like people like you and sometimes I wonder why your even friends with me" I mean if you don't like people who are weird or strange then get over it they exist and I love them! muwahaha bye lov caci! &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wish that I could tell you how I feel                               But deep inside I can't finde anything real           Because I'm all alone & there's no one home     I'm just thinking of you                                      I wish that I could yell this out                         Scream into the clouds that....I like you oh ya..I like you                                                 More than anything I've ever wanted more...I want you....oooo i want you                                   ....................................................................................Ok thats my song &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is my first song for a long ass writters block i still don't have the title so bare with me.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so anyone who would like to donate any hawaiian stuff for my sweet 16 feel free! i love you all!! love caci!!! &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ooooo crap i told zayra who i liked! &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey got my class schedule! FIRST SEMESTER: marching band, algebra 1, french 1-2, lunch, & American History 1-2. SEMESTER TWO:algebra 2, concert band, intro to chem1-2, lunch, & english 5-6. Teachers: Hoeber, Eeles (math 1&2), Stark, leighty, comer, kelman, and mowahed! yay good teachers i guess all but mr. comer i hate him! grr and eelse is a weird-o cross country but mrs. kelman is awsome!!! g2g                                             love caci! &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG i can't believe i'm writting this but i like a friend of mine who just broke up with his gf!!! WHAT IS WRONG WITH ME? tell me plz! &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey we went tubbing yesterday and i hurt my arm it sucks big time but it was really fun. Even when we went through the really rough rapids and a kid fell out of his tube and my dad grabbed him, to think if he hadn't then the kid would be dead! but it was a hoot and i got a tan...tans r cool well g2g &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is jason he's my very nice friend he plays baseball and thats amanda she introduced us! but amanda moved ::cry cry:: I miss her but i'm happy i got to meet jason this is me most recent and i look really pretty!! god i'm so stupid yet so conceded j/k i'm not stupid...well g2g love you all &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ok here is my pic of jason and amanda&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        heheh it's funny for me to be writting about love when i'm the last person who should because of my tendencys to be an ass after i find out a friend likes me.....I love this song called something unspoken and it reminds me so much of rich....like when we talk and then I want to say something and I don't. It just remains "unspoken" it's funny but ya know how it is! Last night my dreams came true Rich finaly said he'd love to date me but then there was a BUT he said But I'm inexperienced I kinda just laughed at him.....Idk if he realizes i'm the same as he is and how much I acctualy like him...welk i g2g ttyl      leiben caci   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok i've gone pink......Latley I've been going through some bull shit with dave over some stupid thing me and his brother were talking about....i mean fuck were over and i like rich so he needs to get over it! Seriously his brother is like my little brother and for him to call me up with this are u gonna hook up with my brother NO o god no i mean come on i've never even been kissed WTF.....well i cried over losing him once and that's never going to happen again g2g i'm talking to Z ttyl    caci   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ya sure life is complicated but sometimes you get thoes few min. where everything is great! I've just spent the last week at band camp and ya i know everyone will be going "this one time at band camp...." well band camp isn't like that infact we use that phrase as a big joke sure ppl do hook up and it makes me sick that some of the girls that were freshmen last year we shall just go by their initials NB and JG are total sluts.....But this past week I felt so much power and we were so together i don't think i've ever been this phsyced about band! Well I hope thoes girls change their disposition on being the band sluts and to let it be known NB is a bitch aswell and i personaly don't like the name she's giving to our band....well g2g bye 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>