<Blog>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had my BCG injection today and all I can say is OUCH! anyway my pain soon turned into laughter when I got home and checked my mail to find one of those daft e-mails from a king of some third world countrys offering you millions just to take some money, always good for a laugh. :-)  Not much else to say today, apart from I have started writing a story for my english coursework and wrote over 3,700 words in less than 10 hours *shock*  anyway, time to get back to work. :-P
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The e-mails have stopped! BioRUST isn't being flooded with messages and I've re-written the tutorial that I accidently ripped, yes, accidently, i didnt know I couldnt take it and change it, shows how much I know :-P  Anywho... I'm happy becuase of that :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, as if things wernt bad enough already I'm now getting accused of ripping a tutorial from someones site and uploading it to BioRUST.  http://forums.biorust.com/showthread.php?&t=720  This guy needs to try the two tutorials himself before throwing accusations around, there completly different!  Anywho apart from that I'm going to a collage in a few hours so I'm please about that, might make some friends for once :-P  I'm still lacking ideas for my site *sigh* looks like version seven will be around for a few more months at least...  Time to shush up again me thinks.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so I got up at half seven on a sunday and I cant get back to sleep, it sucks! I've got nothing to do today so that makes it worse... :-( Just downloading a few songs right now, I found a great one by the white stripes its called fell in love with a girl, i highley recommened getting it, its great!  Anywayz time to shush up yet again... :-D
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just got back from visiting the client I made the leaflet for and I was amazed how well it turned out again for my first attempt at an A4 size print! it was printed on A4 glossy paper, yummy, looked great :-)  Anyway enough boasting... :-P  Not much else to say apart from I'm working on my site... again, adding my tutorials, some rollover images and a new links etc... someone tell me I have to life...  Anywayz time to shush up again.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok... so I've been working on a new version of my site for about 5 weeks now and I cant make a decent one, everything I want to do goes wrong, I guess I'm not getting enough fresh air...  On an upside to all this I've just had my second tutorial put on BioRUST :-) so I'm quite pleased about that.  Boring day as normal, dull, dark, cold, just the way I like it :-P  Hmm.. I'm going to see a client tomorrow about a leaflet I made for him, I guess I'll get enough fresh air then so I might actually be able to think stright, I'll let you know how it goes on, not that you'll really care. :-)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nothing to do again... sat here bored :-( I need a life...  Downloading some songs right now so hopefully if they work this time i'll be a bit happier (yes, it is possible for me to be happy :-|)  Not much to say today, apart from I'm still fed up...  Guess thats all so I'll shush up again.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dosent life just suck? I'm completly fed up, nothing to do, no one to talk to, sat in the house 24\7 to shy you go out, yep life sucks... Guess I shouldnt really complain becuase there people worse off than me but everything is just annoying me so much! I need a life and friends... :-(  Besides that, I got my letter from collage today, I have to go for a meeting at 1PM on the 13th July, hopefully I'll get in, if I do that will make me alot more confident becuase people will actually trust me to do stuff for once, if I get in I'll be doing the website design course, should be fun :-)  Hopefully this weekend I'll see my girlfriend, she moved but were still going out so we dont see each other much :-( her friends are coming with her though so thats worrying me alot, they wont like me!!  Hmm... Guess you people who are reading this and havent got here via my site are wondering who the hell I am...  Well if you want to find out, which I highly doubt you do, visit my website...  www.meltedgfx.tk  I know, I know the design is crappy but I'm working on a better one, it will be finished soon hopefully :-)  anywayz... I guess I'll shush up now becuase I'm probibly putting you to sleep with my endless moaning!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>