<Blog>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      at the end of the tunnel.. or just some mean ass prick with a friggin flashlight. Cause I swear by all that is holy and un-holy that I am going to tear it from his hands and beat the piss out of the bastard when I get there.  I keep thinking, and maybe that is my problem, that I can see the end of the current wrong turn/path I am on. But then BAM- sorry Emeril- something else happens. Why? Dont know. fate? life? the karma frieght train? Still paying back for a previous lifes screw ups? Honestly I figured I would be earning money on an escrow account by now. Seriously. Havent I been though enough? Wasnt being married to the cheating rat bastard and being away from my family for so long enough? Wasnt being in NC when my dad needed me enough? Losing my horses- who were my best friends... enough? Having my dad die within a month of me getting home? Having lied to him that I was "alright" when I really wasnt.. and the guilt. Wasnt enough?  How about losing my self respect for years? my self esteem??  How about not calling my best friend on Sept 10th and telling her that I got "one of those feelings" and had "one of those dreams" Knowing she was going to be in the WTC the next day. She would have listened, taken me seriously, not gone in early to prepare for her presentation. not been there.   How about losing my Tahle'? My gelding, because i didnt make the right choice there either. I should have gone back to work.. to a job I hated. Left my baby girl with a day care provider and prayed I choose the right one. Then THEN!!! My life would be sooooooooo much better.   Or would it.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Or handed to me by fate? Or, better still... given to me as a penance for a previous lifes screw ups?   I cant decide which way I would prefer it be anymore. I mean, there is alot in my life that I LOVE. Alot. But then again I cant figure out exactly how I got here. Although I am sure if I put "some" time and thought into it I would.  I remember sitting on the wall at Nantasket Beach with a friend years ago- like when we first got our licences and didnt "need" our parents so much anymore. LOL! I still need my mom!  We were discussing where we would "be" in our late 20's early 30's I am no where near the place I thought I wanted to be back then. Pretty sure my friend isnt either. Gone are the careers, the fabulous lifestyles and the hot bodies we thought we would have forever. Ahhh youth!   Dinner parties? Sure, pizza anyone? A burger perhaps? Wine?? Try a beer from the fridge. Jaguar in the driveway? I think she is still driving the 1988 Escort she got after our car accident killed the minivan her folks gave her.  I am currently sharing a 99 Accent with my husband (Sean). Gone is the pickup truck (was told a boyfriends mom didnt think it was feminine) and gone is also the 1969 Camaro I rebuilt, with help from a over sexed ex boyfriend. Ahhhh sex. I have a daughter now, I dont have sex. She is nearly 2.. going on 15. Smashed was the career I wanted. Changed my mind mid highschool.  Made a "career" out of customer service.. might be why I generally dislike people on the whole now. I give everyone the same starting point though.. I am fair. I dislike and distrust you til you PROVE to me you are not a absolute moron. Alot of people never rise in rank. Alot fall back after pissing me off. Gone are the horses- albeit temporary as it may be. I am currently horseless, which is more painful than most people can ever think it would be. But that is because most people suck.(see above) I am starting to look for another horse now though.. makes me happy to even be looking right now. Although I am sure the one I am currently day dreaming about will be gone when I get the money to purchase. But there are sure to be others. Looking at an off the track Thoroughbred. Very good cause. very nice horses.   I still have my sense of humour though. Damn all those for trying to break my spirit!!! A pox on you all!!!!! And I a not joking either. I need my sense of humour to make it through my hours,days,weeks, months, years. Really need it at 5 am. I am a mom. I need to be able to laugh.  Anyway, welcome to my blog.. welcome to my world.. welcome to my path.   
       
    
    
</post>


<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink TheStar.com - Baby girl for Courtney Cox Arquette   Coco Cox Arquette.   Why? Are they hoping the girl will grow up to be "really" good looking?  Talented???  Why not a nice "traditional" name like - ohhhh I dont know.... Sarah? Katherine?? Any number of  the names in those baby books. What seems to be the "Hollywood" name book must be on bookshelfs only in that  part of the country.  Rumour, Scout, Apple    Now Coco  Please Brad and Jen. When you start your family please ask your parents for the names they had on the list for you. Dont ask your colleagues.   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink CNN.com - Video shows 9/11?hijackers at airport? - Jul 21, 2004   The meer fact that the US government... and ANY agency within, knew that these men were ( and still know that members of this group of murderers ) were (are) in this country. Is simply unacceptable. And is a crime on its own.  I heard a news report a few days after 9/11, that the FBI or CIA knew that there was a terrorist cell IN MASSACHUSETTS!!!   Funny that it was quickly squashed and never mentioned again. I wonder how many people caught it. And subsequent reports that were just as quickly dropped from the news wire.  I wonder how many people (Republicans) heard this and still think that "our" President didnt know what was going on.  I wonder how many are still walking around free in this country that they hate so much that they murdered thousands of innocent people. Men, women and children.   I wonder how the officials in our country IN OUR GOVERNMENT can sleep at night knowing that they allowed this to happen and that they spewed lies to get us into a war that had nothing to do with the men that murdered those people. tore apart our country and destroyed families.  Kerry may not be much better. But atleast he isnt Bush.   Myself.. I wouldnt want the job. Clean up the royal mess that Bush/Cheney and his zealots have made of this country and our standing in the worldwide community.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink News   "the pit bull, which had no history of aggressive behavior had been tussling with another pet, a smaller terrier, when it attacked the boy, Kerss said.   The dog had been playing with another "smaller" dog in the same area that there was a 8 MONTH OLD BABY!?!?!  Hmmmm baby was most likely near the same size as "a smaller terrier"  Common sense just doesnt come into play alot now does it. The baby was on the floor around two dogs. Yes, if the terrier had been the one to get caught up in the playing and snap at the child the boy would still be alive and this wouldnt even be in the news. But the fact that this grandmother was negligent- YES NEGLIGENT!!! in allowing her grandson to be on the floor with two dogs in the same room pisses me off.  Atleast Sheriff Thomas Kerss has some brain in his head to see what may have "provoked" ( and I am using the term very lightly) this attack.  " Perhas the child either reached up and grabbed he hair of the dogs neck or the ear, or anything that the dog may have taken as being an attack from the other dog" the sheriff said  Yes, perhaps that is what happened.. OR the dog was still runnning on adrenaline from "tussling" with the smaller terrier that was also in the house. that he had just been sperated from.   A child is dead. A family pet is dead. The Anti Pit Bull people have more fodder for their "Pit Bulls are Evil and Should all be Destroyed" campaign.  I am just hoping that maybe. MAYBE!!! this time other families with ANY BREED of dog learns from this.   DONT LEAVE ANY DOG ( no matter how trusted) WITH A BABY IN THE ROOM.  never mind with the child on the floor with TWO dogs in the room.   For Cripes Sake THIS IS why safety gates are made too people. To keep your children out of potential dangerous areas or situations.   Maybe I am blaming this tragic event on the grandmother.. on the parents. But we -as adults- are responsible for the health and safety of ALL other living things. Our children foremost.  This little boy was let down. As was the family dog.    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink CNN.com - Report slams CIA for Iraq intelligence failures - Jul 9, 2004   Not shocking, after all. All the lies that are coming out now and the way the current adminstration is unraveling.   A few months after he was elected- using that term very lightly- I noticed military movements at two decommissioned bases. TWO decommissioned bases!  I mentioned this to my husband, my mother and my friends (one of whom was murdered on 9/11)  I told them he was  "poking at a lion through the bars with a stick" and sure enough.  This was before 9/11 - which I am still convinced "he" knew was coming. Before the war on terrorism, before the war in Iraq to "help the people there" Whatever it is about the oil, anyone that thinks otherwise should get thier head out of thier ass.  I can only hope that as this hits the media. And as more information comes out that the collective American head gets pulled out of the asses feeding us lies all this time and we vote Bush and his cronies out.  I honestly feel bad for Kerry and Edwards. They are going to be the ones cleaning up this mess. Fixing international relations. Getting the faith- what little there was, in the office of the President back.   Clinton Lied, but NO ONE DIED  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>