<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday the program "The Ketelson institute " went on a feildtrip to the aquarium. It was really fun. I got to touch a sting ray.They are actually very friendly and came right up to the side of the tank. They feel like ...um...a pussy....The shark ride (train ride) was superdeduperly corny.  It was a big mechanical shark popping out of the water.  I couldn't help but think about that movie A.I (Artificial Intelligence)and how Manhattan was all underwater and if that happened here in houston all the little fishes and stuff would get out and the aqaurium would look so freakin creepy to "scuba divers".  And if you were to pass by the corny train ride shark you'd crap yur pants thinking this huge mechanical head is a huge ass shark.  Actually to think about that happening to a person is kind of funny... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A happy person onse was I  Lonley now I have been  Only solitude is my friend No one knows the pain I feel The memories are hard to forget  My love for you I can't erase  Sarrow has now come over me  as I remember hugs and kisses  Right or wrong am I  I don't not care,victious things we say and share  Erecting the past  Unearthing lies re-opening profound wounds and re-crying the tears   Always must you hurt me  Always you  make me cry  Always am I in darkness
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It surounds me  an evil darkness wells up inside me  and swallows me whole  With a slur of words  profound wounds are opened  Memories of the past spill forth a blood to easily bled You whip me with my wrong doings  and thrash my conciene with my mistakes Yo fill my eyes wit  hate  and my heart wuth remorse  I'm falling now  deeper into the darkness  Into my anger
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      empty tears fall from my eyes  Empty tears roll down my cheeks  Empty tears  blur my perception Empty tears bring forth the pain  Empty tears fall from my once bright eyes Empty tears help ease the sarrow  Empty tears take the happiness that I barrow I'm going beneath the surface, drowning you beneath  my empty tears 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Iam alone  Iwonder when I'll see you again  I hear yoour voice  I see your smile  I want you here with me I am alone  I pretend your near  I feel your breath  I touch your skin I worry about when I'll see you again  I cry from the pain of being without you I am alone I understand our love will only grow I say together we'll grow old and grey I dream of your arms holding me tight  I try to imagine you here with me  but it's not the same  I hope you understand that  I am alone 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As we sit here talking I realize yur eyes so deep and full of lies. we continue talking& i continue to fall  into yur eyes so deep and full of lies I know longer hear yur voice but alow crackling sound it grows louder & louder until it stops And then I hear a all the lies you've told I feel anger rising and patiece falling I remember all the broken promises you made and suddenly my mouth tastes dry and the air smells sour As I look into your brown lyeing eyes Ive cried and cried often like babies do for your eyes speak to me as you can not do  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I'm still over at my aunt's house and it's really boring so I decided to get a tan (to correct the horrid tan lines I accidentaly got at a car wash.)&nbsp; Well naturally my little cousin who is somewhat a pain in the ass had to go out there with me. I took the sun tan lotion crap that's supposed to help you get a tan and a towel and she changed into her swim suit.&nbsp; &nbsp;.N.E. ways, we were out there and I was rubbing&nbsp;the lotion crap on my legs and every where I hoped to get a tan and since I couldn't get all my back she helped to make sure I got my tan.&nbsp; Well I was laying there in all&nbsp;my glory basking in the sun and it's time to turn over and give my backside a little time in the sun so I undo the strap to my bra thingy.&nbsp; (She's such a pain in the ass sometimes; it's like she's trying to fit in and be what in her mind is cool.)Well any ways I&nbsp;undo the strap thingy and Miss Thang decides to turn the very cold water hose on me.&nbsp; I'm like ha ha ; okay you got jokes funny.&nbsp;&nbsp; And she persists and I 'm there trying get my damp tan.&nbsp; N.E. ways after a while I get really fuckin pissed off and I tell I 'm going inside and it's a lost cause trying to get my skin to tan evenly.&nbsp; I totally forgot that I had unhooked the strap and I was walking past her ( I have all this crap to carry back in the house and I carry it all to my chest to protect it from getting wet)and she thinks it would be funny to spray me with the hose again.&nbsp; Well her bright idea caused me to drop everything I was carrying not to mention my top.&nbsp; Now you have to understand I have 36FF size boobs and I was standing there topless.&nbsp; My boobies fell out of the damn top and my grandma yells through the window " Toni Marie the nieborhs can see you through the fence and so can the people in the street.&nbsp;" I &nbsp;only stood there for like a second till I realized my boob fell out before I rushed into a corner to try and hide and replace my top.&nbsp; Now all the while my 11 year pain in the ass cousin is laughing her ass off and poking jokes at the size of my boobs.( She has boobie issues because she...um...wants boobs.)     
       
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Do you remember the show Daria or whatever that used to come on MTV?&nbsp; Does that come on any more?&nbsp; I remember the intro song "La La La La La La..."&nbsp; SickSadWorld was what she read.&nbsp; Um yeah.... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Today was so fucking boring.&nbsp; &nbsp;I think I would've had more fun at church.&nbsp; Now you know there's something horriblly wrong when a gurl&nbsp;my age actually wants to go to church.&nbsp; I think it's safe to say I can scratch my eyes out now.&nbsp;&nbsp;Someone pray for Toni.&nbsp; She (meaning me)&nbsp;is stuck in&nbsp;the house with an eleven year old who is um well ...eleven .&nbsp; (Oh and Jay if yur reading this she isn't fond of you because she didn't know&nbsp;what STFU is.&nbsp;So if you could like um tell hr next time you decide to comment on me?)&nbsp; N.E ways back to my crappy day;&nbsp;yeah um... I found this web site for poetry. It's kind of like a blog but only for poetry and everything is copywrited under your username.&nbsp; Then I started watching music videos and um yeah it was crap.&nbsp; Today I think I died of bordum and went to Hell.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dude the other day I went to cash my stupid check and the stupid lady would't cash it for me... That was ... stupid!!! Any ways dude these fuckers think I'm um... depresed (well who isn't now adays) and that I cry and write poetry! HA HA HA!!I wonder where they got that idea from. I bet they pulled it out of their ass!Well um... yeah. Man, Tony left for Miami.  That ass is probably visiting the damb hookers. HORNEY BASTARD!!! N.E ways I just got off the phone with my cousin Chris and we are leaving to go eat or do whutever she said she wanted to do. We didn't talk long because she was at work.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Cry my tears for me  and let there be revelation Cry my tears for me  I feel like I've been sentenced to condemnation Cry my tears for me and tell me of your sarraow Cry my tears for me  knowing that my happiness, I barrow Cry my tears for me  and feel my pain Cry my tears for me and let them fall like the rain Cry my tears for me  and know everything I said was true Cry my tears for me because I've already cried them for you
       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>