<Blog>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is colourless with nothing but problems & ideas. boring.
     
    
</post>


<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is me!! :) Primary 2. Sports day. with my "boyfriend" cute sia? haha..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is my best friend, Sharon.. She's no longer in CHIJ STC. but we all still love her as much.. :) YEAH..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is 2004, Mission day! Look at all the chio bus.. A day filled with tears (of joy & laughter), and also lots of smiles! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    happy times with kyla.. haha.. this is when i'm not angry.. YEAH.. :) haha.. erm.. mayb i'll take pics of mi when i'm angry with her!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My (2003) sec 3 class! cool sia? haha.. YEAH! not everyone is cool though.. haha :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My ex nerdy boyfriend.. haha.. :) cute huh? haha.. he's damn smart.. Got 12 for his L1R5!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    DeeDee faking sleep with one eye open and one eye close.. cute!!! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is DeeDee. My ex boyfriend's Dog. I love her lots.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is my new blog webbie. nice? will update again.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this pic is so sweet.. i onli haf one copy.. and i reali dun wish to ever lose it.. I miss this old matt, who loves mi so much.. even though i was ugly.. even though i had so much weakness.. and the matt who stood by mi even when my mind/heart is not right with God.. but too bad.. things haf change so much since the India trip.. mayb i've been a veri bad gf.. but sure.. He had set a veri high standard for all those who are interested in mi.. haha.. :) mizz my naughty baby polar bear..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Mingtian & Matt.. taken before matt changed..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is the cute Jun Seng i used to know.. he's still with Michelle right? the Bible guru.. haha.. i find him veri veri cute.. cuter then any other guys in region B.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi & teresa.. :) cute right? we were so close last time.. :(&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    sharon and mi.. haha.. when we were veri close and i had my hair.. haha&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi in short hair and taken with jasmine..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    do you know where is this? make a good guess? haha.. matt knows i htink.. if he doesn't i'll chop of his head.. haha.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    serene took this pic, she's trying to take kyla lah.. haha..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    shron.. chio right?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    deb & trina.. playful..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the teddy bear i hug to sleep every night.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    sharon and mi when i still had my long hair.. but no worries, my hair is growing.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    young eric, kyla loves him to bits.. haha.. think he's mr nice.. well, i still dun like young guys.. that's too bad.. haha.. she flirts with him damn lots even though she has more then one bf and also she is interested in playing girls too.. ugly bimbo.. slut..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this was taken veri long ago..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my best friend Deb!!! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is Jasmine, my classmate.. :) chio right? :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    kyla shocked look and chee hui concerned look. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is sharon.. still my best friend.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is ban ban.. :) my neighbourhood dog.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    trina and kyla, the current best friends group.. haha..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is my dad&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    these are my 3 veri naughty brothers.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is after g12.. haha&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi & trina! :) cute? haha.. deb took this pic.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my tatoo&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi & deb my current best friend! :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is my mum&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is taken way before g12&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my burnt back&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi and a ghost&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    matt & mi&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my hand.. hee.. see the tiny silvery thing? haha.. it's called a ring. haha.. okay.. if you're wondering who gif that tiny silvery thing to mi i can onli say it's not my old baby.. haha.. it's not a from a male.. haha.. go make ur wild gueses, i wun tell you haha.. :p&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is my hockey ball haha.. not in a veri good shape i know.. but u should take a look at DeeDee's pink hockey ball..&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is the new book that that i bought today.. haha.. :) i hope i'll enjoy it.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi.. haha.. cute right? bleah.. i know i know.. veri ugly.. haiz.. sianz..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is my mp3 player.. cute? haha.. love it to bits.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my pictures all veri funi looking (with mi inside how can it look nice?), but at least sharon look perfect in here.. :)&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi and Sharon.. haha.. cute? I look like shit.. :p  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Bryan trying to stop mi from taking his pic haha.. so funi looking.. Sharon says he changed alot.. i wonder if it's the doing of Kyla..&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is sharon after i tried to straighten her hair.. haha.. but it was better untill the wind damaged it..&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    all eyes closed.. haha.. well mi and chee haf reali small eyes u see.. haha.. okok.. veri crap.. my photography skills sux.. honest i can't believe i haf such a big mouth.. haha.. big teeth.. :'(&nbsp;man.. i wonder how can i ever get a bf with such ugly features..&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    chee_jas_mi.. haha cute? well.. i look veri ugly i know.. haha.. Jas and Chee&nbsp;rawks!&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    still eating her chicken wing.. haha.. cute right? reminds mi of my old hamster hyper.. :'(&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Chee eating chicken wing.. haha.. it's really nice u know.. haha.. I love chicken wings.. :)&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    i tied my hair up and this is wat i get.. haha.. a funi looking mi.. haha.. but some ppl says it's sexy.. oh well.. mayb they haf eye problems.. time to get those ard mi to go for eye check upz.. &nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is my keychain.. haha.. this is mi.. haha.. okok.. BE HAPPY is a great message isn't it? haha.. yupz.. this is mi trying to tell myself to be HAPPY. haha.. this is lame i know.. but i still mizz my polar bear.. haha.. okok.. brb with more pics of my life.. :)&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    cool.. i like this one.. :) haha..  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    i juz dun like my eyes.. and nose and face and .... ... but no matter wat, i love my bear!  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     i think this is so cool.. haha.. Yes the shades may seems big to you, but it's suposed to cover my whole face.. :P&nbsp; urlLink      
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    do i look veri funi here? you bet.. haha.. look kinda blur.. haha.. a interesting pic.. :P&nbsp; urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    haha..i know veri blur lah.. but haf to make do with it loh.. :P haha.. I will rmb the 6th YEP camp! :)  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    nice? I did it on my own okay.. :p  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this rose.. i will nvr forget.. given by my classmates.. it is my first rose... now, a couple of months haf passes, my friends haf becomed my enermy.. they are all strating to dislike mi.. but i will still kip this rose.. if i haf to die, i wish to be buried or burned with this magical rose.. *tears*  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this pic is taken at the shop.. :) by the lady lah.. she's quite nice.. haha.. well, all three of us love this pic so much that we all put as display pic in our wallets.. :) yeash!!! we can't stop looking at it.. :P sun1 will be so jealous sia.. haha.. :)  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    haha.. nice shot? gwen took this i think.. :P we look like there is not much height difference but actually the both of them are bending down.. :P  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Gwen, mi and jas.. :) haha.. i feel like i've destroied the pic.. haha.. :P  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    jas, mi and gwen.. :) took this at harbour front toilet.. haha.. afte we ate a fantasic late lunch at PASTAMANIA.. :P I haf this pic somewhere in my wallet.. :P yeah!!! :)  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the much talk abt bag.. haha.. yeah.. this is my new sch bag.. but dun think i'll contiune to use it for sch that often.. it's heavy!! i love it.. the attention it gets its wow.. haha.. well, i love it's bright orange colour.. ez to look for it in a crowded place with lots of bags.. haha.. :)  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    may i, Mike Wee, have you.. christina... as my beloved gf... so as to love you whole heartedly... share ya sadness.. and happiness.. ? (I will remember this for life..)  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    all sleepy and nice little boiz.. :)  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    dun you think they learned it from someone? hmm.. i wonder who?? :)  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha... this is funi and cute.. :)&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi and him again.. haha.. i think i perfer him with specs.. next time i show you.. haha.. :P yesh.. my love.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    mi and my love.. he named mi a little princess in his blog.. (haha) okok.. I'm not a princess lah.. this is the first pic we took together.. nice? :) i think i look ugly..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    this is the best i can get of this cute little thing.. :) he's so nice to hug.. veri cute.. he's amazed by many things ard him and loves to follow his brother.. :) He's reali special in my sight. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my little nephew.. love him to bits.. his brother was the cutest but since he is born, he took over the place. :) yeah..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my grandad's birthday durian cake. :) it was fantastic.. *yum*&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the takeshi cousin.. haha.. ain't he cute? haha.. he's quite a shy boi.. duno if he's attached.. haha.. :) yeah..&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    2 of my cousins and 2 of my brothers.. :) haha love them all.. :)&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>