<Blog>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm at work and doing what I do best....procrastinating!  My life in a nutshell is pretty simple....well, maybe not.  I'm a dork and LOVE things like classical music, Queer Eye, American Idol (I love Ruben!), and a bunch of other equally dorky things.  That's about it for now.  Although in the weeks to come, I will write plenty more....especially when I'm bored and wanna pretend like I'm working!!  =)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today is the day that my roommie, Ron, and I are quitting "the smoking"!  I'm only about 4 hours into it, and so far, so good!  Thank God for  urlLink Quit Net !  I've joined 2 clubs...the DC Area one and one for musicians!  I should be okay with this!  As long as things don't get too stressful within the next 2 weeks!  I think if I can survive the next 2 weeks, then I'll be okay.  Ron and I are both on the patch, so we're not going "cold turkey"!  Leave a message of love and/or support b/c I'm gonna need it all!  In a few weeks, I'll be driving to Michigan with my Mom for the  urlLink Harbor Choral Festival .  That will be so much fun (except the fact that we're singing the Faure Requiem....and I am extremely tired of that piece!!  Anyway, it'll still be fun.  AND it'll be the first big test of my not-smoking and I won't have to be sneaking out of the hotel to go smoke...!! =)  Let's see....there is a certain person who was a big part of my college life (and if you know me AT ALL, you'll know who I'm talking about)!  Well, I found out about a month ago that he's going to be a father....and that just scares the shit out of me!  But people need to be proud of me b/c I kept it to myself (except for Anya who doesn't know anybody in Radford to tell!) until I got the OK from Josh.....Oops....I mean.....my friend....! =)  Anyway, I could go on and on and on and on.....but you can probably figure out my feelings on the subject, so I'll stop!  Work is going very well.  We just launched our new  urlLink Web Site , so check it out!  Pay close attention to the Women's Health Section and the Position Papers b/c I transferred all of them over from the old site and formatted them so they would fit right.  I know it sounds easy, but it is! =)  ....it's just time consuming!  But if you see it, let me know what you think! =)  Man, today's a big day....I'm quitting the smoking, Rent was due (lord help me with that one!), and Mom and I are officially members of the  urlLink Alexandria Singers  Board as Co-VP of Performance!  This is HUGE for me b/c this will be my first time on the Board AND I've been in the group since BEFORE...yes, before.....I was born! I have literally NOT known a life without the Alexandra Singers and now I'll be on the Board! The first meeting is going to be really interesting  Here's a great web site with a bunch of the Fab 5's best  urlLink quotes  (especially Carson's...but he's just hysterical anyway!!)  Check back every week b/c new ones get added after each new episode!  But if you're a purist and JUST want the  urlLink Bravo QE website , now you've got that, too!  =)  Well folks, I'm about to wrap this up, but I can't not mention summer music camp!  Yes, it's that time again....when the end of June comes around and I'm not at Camp, something in me says "You've got somewhere you should be right now!"  But alas, I just can't anymore! =( From counting down the hours, to 6-7 weeks of pure HS drama, to hundreds of performances (good AND bad) over the years, to best friends, to enemies, to life experiences....to camp!  I hope the kids who are at  urlLink PAI  this summer have a phenomenal time!  I think I'm done....and now I'll have nothing to say for another month!  =)  Love to you all!!  -L-
     
    
</post>


</Blog>