<Blog>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Made this photo at Photoshop by taking photos from my hamsters in a blue scene,then duplicate them on this landscape photo & completed it with adding few effects to make it more acceptable. &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink     * Name:Hamster's Gathering * Software:Photoshop version 7 * Resolution:500*375 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       This is my own wrist watch that my father gave me as a present;I made it to keep this watch in my mind for ever.You can see two different render of it below;At the second render I added lights & a camera to the scene to get a better result from it. &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink     * Name:A Present * Software:3ds max version 5 * Resolution:1024*768 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       In the way of increasing my knowledge about materials,I started to make this short animation project.But unfortunatly it has never completed. &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink     * Name:The Mouse * Software:3ds max version 5 * Resolution:1024*768 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I made this flowerpot with its flowers & also my next project "The mouse" to gain more experience about making different kinds of materials.Maybe it seems easy but took a long time from me to arrange everything & made these roses with their leaves naturally (atleast close to it) & also the material of flowerpot was made by compositing few materials together;We call this kind of valuable stone Firoozeh in our language. &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink     * Name:A Flowerpot of Roses * Software:3ds max version 5 * Resolution:1024*768 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Another instrument of mine which I created it in 3ds max.I used only from edit spline tools to create this object. "&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink     * Name:Telephone * Software:3ds max version 5 * Resolution:1024*768 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       This is my first serious 3D modeling with 3ds max which contains my name with a wooden figure who is standing behind it.I didn't use any kind of skeleton to form this figure that time;The only thing that I used,was:executing "Inverse Kinematic" tool on linked body parts.So you can see it was not a simple job for a beginner. &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink     * Name:Woody & My Name * Software:3ds max version 5 * Resolution:1024*768 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink      Hi everybody & welcome to "My Imaginations" site:This site is about all different kind of my computer graphic arts;From Photoshop to 3ds max & Maya 3D world.  You could enter your comments about each of my art works at the "Comment" section that is shown under each article in this site.I will appreciate your honest opinions about my works.Also it would be great if you send your ideas & imaginations to my email address (mahdismn@yahoo.co.uk) & help me in this way to design new things.Sometimes even a simple & small idea can lead me to a unique art work.  So please be in touch with me;I'm sure you can help.                                                       Goodluck                                                       ...Mahdi 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>