<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy! Yay, my first journal entry ever! Woo. But it's seriously amazing, my computer to actually do it's job today and WORK. Amazing. So today I got up around 11 and started reading my new book "Lucky". My cousin and I are supposed to do something today, but she hasn't called yet, so I'm just chillin around here which is nice because I've been busy all week. I'll update you haha.  Monday: Kristen and I went to see The Stepford Wives down at the one and only Waterfront. We went to Bravo! across from Loews and got some lunch. That food is freaking awesome! We couldn't finish the pizza so the waitress put it in a box for us. So then we walk back over to Loews with me carrying this big-ass pizza box. They let us take it in, surprisingly. The Stepford Wives was pretty good I suppose, I dunno what I'd say about it. Then after that she came over to mi casa and we rented Gothika. That was fairly scary. No volleyball either because of gym reconstruction or something.   Tuesday: Went to my Grandma's and got a little tan. I watched The Lizzie McGurie movie too. Then I went home, got ready, then my mom picked up Bill. Bill and I went to Eat 'n' Park and then over to Blockbuster Video in the grand Edgewood area. We rented  Robin Hood: Men in Tights(which I still haven't watched), Vacation, and S.I.C.K(Serial Insane Clown Killer). I rented SICK on DVD b/c I wanted to watch it on the computer, but OF COURSE, the piece of shit decided not to work. So that was a waste of money! Bill left around 11 and then we talked on the phone later...haha.  Wed: Went to Kennywood w/ Kristen. We waited in line for like a freaking hour for the Garfield ride and then it SUCKED. Seriously, no one ever ride that ride, its a waste of your precious time. I dunno, Kennywood just isn't fun for me anymore. Those rides are all freaking lame. They need some big rollercoasters!! Well yeah, basically all we did was walk around looking for a good ride and also wasting money on food. Haha typical.  Thur: Went to the Wave Pool and got extremely burnt on my legs. Came home and went to Barnes and Noble. I also finished my book, "Shes Come Undone."  So I dunno what's going on for today, it's currently almost 4 and I still have no freaking clue as to what I'm doing. Haha fun. Degrassi's a repeat tonight, but My So-Called Life is new. Haha, indulging myself in some Friday night teen soap operas is so fun.   Ok whatever, this is already wayyy too long, soooo  PEACE OUT... sike I'm not that ghetto...
     
    
</post>


</Blog>