<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I know i'm not alone but i've never met another person of my kind  to always be the bottom of the top or the top of the bottom i can never be ahead ov everyone for some strange reason. i'll always be the worst of the best or the best of the worste and i can never explain why. but if another of those people stumble upon this blog they'll know what its like when every one you know always better then you or your better then everyone you hang with but everyone in your category is better then you.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've been searching for you I heard a cry within my soul I've never had a yearning quite like this before Know that you are walking right through my door  All of my life Where have you been I wonder if I'll ever see you again And if that day comes I know we could win I wonder if I'll ever see you again  A sacred gift of heaven For better worse, wherever And I would never let somebody break you down Until you cried, never  All of my life Where have you been I wonder if I'll ever see you again And if that day comes I know we could win I wonder if I'll ever see you again  At every time I've always known That you where there, upon your throne A lonely queen without her king I longed for you, my love forever ------------------------------------------------------------------------------ All of my life Where have you been I wonder if I'll ever see you again And if that day comes I know we could win I wonder if I'll ever see you again   ~ Lenny Kravitz
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dance Dance Revolution ???  further into the nothingness of the drift i have 2.5 weeks till summer school starts for me but i forgot how to use it. 4 hours of DDRing every day probably isn't the best way to waste time.  *a good game is $.75 for 6 min so thats like $7 a hour*
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i'm on a drift. i'm at that point where i just move with time. nothings in my way but nothing is stoping or pushing me. i'm just in the drift. but what do i do while i'm in the drift. whats at the end of the drift. what will happen in the drift. Time to drift
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      noa moa finals : no more finals woooohooooo  i still have school tomorrow but i don't have any finals woohoooo how many woooohoooooos can i woooohooooo in one woooooohoooooooing sentance, wooooohooo.  4 hours of nothingness. would it be wrong if i brought a playstation to class
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      e'h no finals today wohoooooooo! just 4 hours of nothingness.  and i got the senior gift for that someone as i wish her good luck at colorado state.  now to deal with all the other summer premaths
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      upon return i realize. all of my classes were near completley seniors. all the seniors no longer have to show up and i'm one of 5 students in almost all of my classes that isn't a senior. i now understand why people always confused me for a senior since freshman year, i always acted and surrounded myself by them.  though there are a few things i sorta forgot about senior graduation! like a graduation gift for
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      the best generation of seniors graduated today and now it's up to my generation to replace them.  great i didn't really get to say goodbye to all of them especially the one i have a crush on.  !!! i mean i never said i had a crush on!!! i never said a thing a thousand arrows in my heart for my stupidity. (and shyness, it's complicated)
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      wow someone is reading my blog.  well not to much special bout me, though so far i've dealt with everything from crooked cops to prom problems. seriously.  if you discovered this site i probably told you about it so you should no the rest from there.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      3 weeks in and like just about every year thus far summer is mostly wasted with exception of those things to good to mention to the public.  e'h what now
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      6 weeks into summer and things never really change much. though it looks like week 9, the week i'll be out of state, happens to be the registration week.  ughh of all weeks of the summer to have vacation it just happens to be the week that i'll gone and how am i gonna get a parking permit now.  Crap! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>