<Blog>


<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You are..  My power  When I'm lost Down to earthbound Torn and tortured A savior of the soul in my deepest darkest hour  You are..  My Pleasure  Grand love fantasy Your T.L.C - my ecstasy Like a soft summer breeze Flower, rainbow and sunshine Angel of peace to my heart  You are..  My pain  The tears I shed every night Hurt, despair and misery Helplessly addicted My confusion and sorrow
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I lay here on a river Listening to its cold quiet flow The splendid sun warms me Peace, caressed endlessly Graceful  Heavenly angel
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Could you be the light so bright Touch my soul And turn it into a rainbow scent vanilla Relishing the abuse of despair and sorrow In my dark forest of pain  Would you be the strength of romance Mend my torned heart And silken it with love and hope Transform the vulnerable dreams Into born free reality In your everlasting care  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s You. It’s every part of you. Your tenderness, your sweetness, your affection, your passions, your darkness, your brightness, all of you. You are part of me. You are the king. The lighthouse. The Grave. You are the heartbeat within me. When you are busy. When you’re far from me. When I miss you. God, how can I reach you? Silvery moon and velvet sky failed to entertain me. They are misery, and you are my angelstar. My only angelstar.  Memories of you. They want to stay in my heart, forever. You. Now my heart knows how to keep you. Now my heart knows what to do. If you only knew.I need you.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In each of an end, there’s a beginning of something. Khrisnamurti is so right. I’m not talking about a Matrix reloaded, or Lord of The Rings, Two Towers! Whatever ends, it’s somehow show a start of a new thing. A beginning. Endings is usually sad, and beginning is usually scary. But middle part is the best. Are you afraid of a new beginning? I am. Well, sometimes. I’m usually excited of a new start. Worry what’s gonna happen next, worry if it’s gonna be okay or not. Is this a good decision? Where is this going to lead me to? Am I blessed? Will I survive? The truth is, the list of question will go on and on. We tend to think much of something way beyond the future (now how far is that?) but when we do it, when we made our choices and live with it, we’re actually are faced with new choices, new decisions- a beginning. What clothes am I going to wear to the movie? Which movie I will see tonight? Is he going to call me tonight? Is anything gonna happen to us us tonight? Will I gonna die on my way to the movie? And options are always there. I can choose to wear black t-shirt or black shirt (hey, I have many black outfits, ok), I can choose to see Troy or Harry Potter, or both of them, and I can choose to NOT to think that I’m gonna die young. Have you ever notice that life is actually full of choices? And why we always say to ourselves that we don’t have a choice? Maybe because we choose NOT to have an option? That’s an option too right? Now did I just make you confused? Maybe Life is really a cycle like they said. The end will lead us to a new beginning, and what starts must have an end. Where is my life gonna lead me to? What will happened to me in the end? Maybe it doesn’t even matter like Linkin Park sang. Because choices are always there to spice up the beginning, the middle part and the end. And choices are made of yourself. You are the master of your own story. To be or not to be, that’s the question. Oh, I wish Watson was here! 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Do you know that every word you said has a flavor of its own? it could be sweet, sour, salty or even taste like wine! Every word can have different taste everytime you say it.You would be the one who decide the flavor. What's your flavor? I've got lots.  How would you say these words?Come Back Here! Come Back Here? Come Back Here...  You would be the one who decide the flavor. What's your flavor? I've got lots. Welcome to my world, my door has transparent locks. It will only visible to those who refuse to understand me. Open minds, Free spirits are the key to get inside my chamber. Some of u might bump into my invisible walls, but they only appears when the gates needs to be fixed. My tip is, do look into it, instead of the surface, only then you can find the truth. Somethings are not mend to be changed, but to live with. Cheers to you all!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>