<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Can't get into the work mode yet today. Man, that whole Genesis 3 Fall of Man thing is such a drag! Way to go Adam and Eve; becuase of you I've gotta be cursed to work the ground! hahaha Actually, sometimes work is good but it sure isn't what I'd really like to be doing. Reality strikes however and you've gotta be able to pay the bills.  Training for a 12 hour race in August. Just lost a teammate this morning due to prior obligations with his wife. Although I understand, I'm still bummed. Gotta do better on the next race. I got a heat stroke on the last one and almost didn't finish. Almost. Finishing is definitely the fun part. Playing through the pain. Proving to yourself that you can stick it out when you're gasping for air and your legs are burning. You ain't gonna quit for nothing! That's what its all about in my opinion.   Well, gonna try this work thing today. Later.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Never even read a blog, much less wrote one. Well, you've gotta change your tactics in this race or you'll get left behind, right? What race? you may ask...more on that later. Suffice it so say its not the rat race. After all, even if you win the rat race, you're still a rat.   How about Reagan's mourning week? I saw the funeral procession for a moment yesterday on tv and was literally "wow" struck. I've never seen anything like that in my lifetime. I do remember the assassination attempt though-I'm that old enough. I feel like I would have liked to be there though to see history unfolding. I feel like I missed out. Do you know what I mean? I remember as a kid being afraid of nuclear war with the Soviets-does anyone else remember The Day After or Alas, Babylon? I do. At it scared me to death. I was so glad when the USSR crumbled; it was the beginning of a new era. Not that Ronnie was primarily responsible for that but from what I can tell he played a big part.   This morning I met a friend and we prayed to God together. Ever try that? Do you even believe that there might be a 'higher power' or a 'creator'? Heady stuff, huh? Deep down, I think we all hope for it. C'mon admit it, even if you aren't 'religious', which I would not describe myself as, you've got a brain and you've got an intellect, soul, spirit, id, etc....call it what you will. But you've got one. I know you think about it.  More on that topic later.   In this life you've got to work-and I'm heading back to the land of responsibility as we speak. Till then,   gh
     

    
</post>


</Blog>