<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       My left arm feels absolutely numb cuz my doctor drew ridiculously a lot of blood out of my vein. (6 tubes!) Watch me, I'm starting a brand new life, enjoying the present time, not retreating into the past. Because in the end, you only realize you've wasted your best years suffering and hoping for something that is not even worthwhile.    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Canon PowerShot A80! This better be good cuz I'm completely broke! 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So it seems I'll briefly see Arturo in Vigo. Nils complains that I'm telling the whole world about my personal life... But the truth is only my close friends have access to these blogs.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Florida was hot as hell. I guess the best time to travel to Florida is sometime in March as I remember from a few years back. The temperature there last weekend was always above 90F and it was such a pain to get on a car after parking outdoor even for a few minutes.    Oh boy, Demarre got a new "steel blue metalic" BMW but he didn't let me drive. Oh well, maybe he'll let me drive when I get my driver's license. He totally underestimated my ability to drive in those video games.       I got to Tampa at around 9pm, 6/11/04. The first night, we just went out for late dinner in some Italian restaurant in downtown Tampa, updating our stories since we hadn't seen each other for a long time. Then, we went to some bar where a live band was playing old rock music. Although we only stayed there for one beer mainly because it was too loud to talk, I must say, it was truly entertaining and refreshing. At least, people at the bar seemed much less pretentious than those from New York. Also, it was unbelivable how much fun they can have with this lame rock band! Demarre and I came home in St. Petersberg at around midnight and talked until 6am. Wanted to see the sunrise since the home was almost right by the beach but I passed out in a second...   The next day, Sat 6/12/04, I got up at around noon. Our mission was to go to the beach near by. We drove around for a while and finally found a decent place to do sunbath. But the sun was too strong and I got the wrong suntan cream and so by the time I got home, I realized my skin color resembled that of a corpse. Anyways... Because we hadn't eaten breakfast, we were feeling exhausted on the beach. I think the main conversation we had while lying on the beach was what to eat for dinner. We had a few plans for the Saturday night; going to Karaoke, movies, having dinner and drinking wine with Juli and her husband, who is a wine connoisseur, or hang out with his friends from the orchestra. However, we couldn't hold it until 7:30 so we decided to go to a Sushi place. I've never had so much Sushi in my entire life. They were really big and fat! --I know what Dave has to say about this. :)   There is something about sunbathing that makes me feel very exhausted. When the dinner was over, we decided to stay in. We rented two movies; legally blone 2 (yeah yeah) and the mystic river. Yet, Demarre fell asleep within 5 minutes. I came out to the garden by myself and stayed there for hours. I don't know what I was thinking at that time. My mind was filled with a bundle of complications.    6/13/04:  Demarre got up awfully early the next morning since he went to bed at 8pm! (he denies he went to bed that early, though) We went to a shopping mall to buy a laptop. I knew not so much would happen that day since he had to set up his computer. It was pathetic, though. We both are PC persons so it looked like two computer illiterates struggling with the new Mac computer. Then, we went to the Sunday Mass together. It was kind of a funky/secular Roman catholic church unlike the church I go to in New York. I was very grateful to Demarre for coming to the church with me since I have many friends that are either atheists or anti-christians and unhappy about me going to church. After the Mass, we came home and watched The Mystic River. We were being total dorks analyzing the movie for hours. That evening, we cooked Salmon, potatos and onions and drank tons of beer. At 11:40pm though, we realized we didn't have any more beer. It was sunday night and stores close at midnight. As if we were able to telepathize with each other, we immediately hopped in the car and drove like maniacs to get the last minute beer. Oh boy, we must have drunk at least 8 bottles of beer each.    6/14/04:  I woke up with a terrible headache. Demarre and I have a personal terminology when it comes to party. We say one party is never enough so there should be pre-party, party and the post party. I think we completed the mission last night. After 4 hours of sleep, Demarre had to go to work in the morning. I slept through 11:00am until he came back during his lunch break. Since we didn't have enough time to eat, we went to McDonald's to get fatty lunch. He dropped me off at the beach and went back to work. Now, I had the right suntan cream. I was lying on the beach until 2pm, now my skin golden and shiny! There were mostly kids and mothers on the beach. However, I saw many old men sitting on the benches by themselves and looking into the void. There was this old man trying to talk to me while I was walking around the shore. First, he asked me a favor; since he couldn't go into the water, he asked if I could collect some water into his container. I thought he might be an environmental scientist of some sort who tries to analyze the sea water. But then he said he had been in the navy for 20 years and that he learned to clean his nose with the sea water. ew... he goes on and on about his life in the navy. I don't think it's his best interest at the moment but maybe he misses talking to someone. He showed interest in the book by Haruki Murakami in my hand. I briefly told him about the book but he probably felt that I wanted to be left alone. He turned around, wished me happiness and all, then disapeared. For a minute or two, I felt deeply sorry for him and wondered what this brief meeting with a stranger must mean in the Karmic cycle.    Demarre came back from work. We went to eat at some Chinese restaurant before heading to the airport. As usual, we ordered ridiculously a lot of food. After lunch, we looked at the sky and predicted the rain would pour after I leave. Good guess, the flight was delayed forever due to the thurnder storm.    I hate airport, it's such a sad place to be. I guess my long distant relationship with Nils, me in New York and him in Duesseldorf, for years kind of turned me into the "airport phobic". I remember even randomly when I heard a sound of plane taking off, tear rolled down my face. Even though Demarre was coming to New York next month, I still felt sharp pain in my chest.    Overall, I had a great time, rediscovering Demarre as my truly good friend despite the fact that he drives me nuts sometimes. He's a person that I can talk just about everything with, without worrying that he might judge me, a friend that is so selfless to his friends. Yeah yeah, he's a drama queen, so what? I love his artistic nature and restless passion. I have this feeling that we'll be very good friends for a very long time... 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, I need to get out of the city, I don't think I can wait until I go to Spain. My mind still wanders everywhere, it feels as if I'm going to explode if I stayed here for few more minutes... My trip to Tampa is from 6/11/04 (Fri) through 6/14/04 (Mon). I'm visiting a friend, Demarre, who also has a relationship crisis just like myself although my crisis has been ongoing for more than a year. pathetic...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What a pain. I would have never decided to go to Spain if it wasn't for someone else. Now, without knowing anyone, even the language or any background information of the city and/or the country as a whole, I'm on my own. The ticket I purchased is restricted so I could not change my flight itinerary. I felt completely betrayed, abandoned and lost and had absolutely no desire to go... I even thought about giving up the tix previously but no, I changed my mind; this might be an opportunity to break the patterns of my passivity and dependency. Let's explore the country I have not previously had any interests in. It should be fun to explore new culture and meet new people!    Here is the tentative plan for my trip to Spain.   7/14/04 [Wed]	4pm (JFK)- 	                New York 7/15/04 [Thu]	9:35am (BCN)-                 10:30am(BCN)-  12:05pm(VGO)	Vigo 7/16/04 [Fri]	Train to	                Santiago de Compostela 7/17/04 [Sat]	7:30am (SCQ)- 8:35am (MAD)	Madrid 7/18/04 [Sun]	Maybe train to either Segovia or Toledo	                         7/19/04 [Mon]	4:40pm (MAD) -5:45pm (BCN)	Madrid/Barcelona 7/20/04 [Tue]		                        Barcelona 7/21/04 [Wed]	7:00pm (BCN)- 8:10pm(MAD)-                 9:35pm(MAD)-10:45pm(VGO) 	                                                                                                    Barcelona/Vigo 7/22/04 [Thu]	7:30am (VGO)-9am (BCN)-                 9:55am (BCN)-3:00pm (JFK)	Vigo/ NY    It'll be a rather tough journey but I'm going to keep myself busy and sightsee the cities as much as I can. I even got myself fairly decent hotel rooms which means, by the time I come back to New York, I'll be completely broke. At least though, it might as well be a relaxing vacation... Whew, I've spent a few thousand dollars in a few days. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>