<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      to partake in Pride, debauchery, and inebriation.... Not necessarily in that order.  I'll be back Sunday evening. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While a defendant might   figuratively   be caught with his or her pants down in court, this is nothing compared to an Oklahoma judge   literally   caught in the same situation.    urlLink  Check this out!  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      though I worry that Michael Moore may just be preaching to the choir.... I don't think it will convert any Bush-lovers.  Though I don't believe that was ever the purpose.  I do hope however that many undecided voters go see it.  Perhaps this will act as a motivation for the 50% of eligible Americans that don't vote to get out there in November.    Yeah, I said I was going to have a review of the documentary here, but I never said I was going to write it! Ha! Yeah... I'm lazy.   urlLink  Read all about it here  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks goes out to Mike for getting his hands on tickets for the Wednesday sneak preview of the film.  I will post a review on Thursday.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      thanks to James from Toronto for, once again this year, making sure I had too much fun at our summer cocktail reception.....  I'm hurting this morning.  But I was in the office by 8:30.... hopefully I can keep my head up all day.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      read more:   urlLink  http://www.tompaine.com/articles/consequential_lies.php  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeap, you guessed it, Cleveland, Ohio takes this award.  read more and find out why:   urlLink  http://www.kidfriendlycities.org/2004/   Let's keep adding to the list of Cleveland's unfriendly qualities! UGH!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm glad someone wrote about it.  Are we going to be a Republican-lite party or are we going to stand for real progressive values?  This McCain courting has gotten out of hand.  Sure, the polls indicate that a Kerry/McCain ticket would beat Bush/Cheney, but this is fundamentally the wrong approach to winning.  We cannot as progressives allow the Democratic party to move more to the right.  Clinton, through the DLC, moved the party to center.  This allowed the Republicans to move even more to the right.  This is dangerous for two reasons: Number One: the obvious reason being the right-wing Republicans in power. Number Two (and not so obvious): this leaves a vacuum on the progressive left.  My hope is that the Clintonesque/DLC style of the Democratic party was an aberration of the 1990s.  The only way to win back the White House (and the Senate and House) is to have a party that stands for real progressive values again.  We know McCain is out, and that is a good thing.  If Kerry picks a DINO like Evan Bayh and loses, don't say I didn't tell you so.  We know what the Republican party stands for, but what do Democrats really stand for these days?  The Democrats come November are going to be real sorry they sandbagged Howard Dean.   more views here:  urlLink  http://www.commondreams.org/views04/0615-04.htm   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't you hate it when you have added people to your buddy list and then they all of a sudden pop up and you have no recollection of who they are?  Did I flirt with this person online one evening when I was drunk?  Did I like this person's photo and profile and want to talk to them at a later date and never did?  I have 168 people on my buddy list... perhaps it's time to clean house!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    down 75 on the Dow..... down 30 on the NASDAQ.......&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every month I get a newsletter from a firm in Chicago we have a business relationship with.  It is usually full of random funnies and the like.  It is simply sent out to remind us to call them once and awhile and perhaps do a little business....that's quite noble :)  Enclosed with this newsletter is usually a toy or a trinket of some kind.  As Independence Day approaches they felt it appropriate to send an American flag button.  A nice gesture indeed.  The pin says "Made in China" on the front of it below the flag, no joke.  Don't you think it would have been more appropriate to stamp the "Made in China" on the back of this piece of cheap plastic with a small metal clasp attached to it?  I am so amused by this because normally I wouldnt display an American flag.  In this political climate displaying the flag reeks of a blind nationalism associated with the Iraq War and the Bushes....I think of the large American flags on the back of Chevy Tahoes and other highway leviathans.  You know the type of people that love to drive these vehicles, the overweight middle-aged NASCAR-loving homophobes...  The same men who flip me the bird and try to run me off the road after seeing my anti-Bush bumper sticker and HRC window decal on my Honda.  These are the good Americans that love to display the American flag so prominently.  However with this little pin, "Made in China" has earned a place on my desk.  Perhaps this could be a good slogan going forward.... bumper stickers with the American Flag on them and "MADE IN CHINA" in very large lettering below, and with a website address....  some sort of website discussing free trade, globalization, and the like.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    thank my friend Brian in Columbus for finding this one..... this is absolutely a riot, and frightening nonetheless.  We wonder why the American public is so morbidly obese and unhealthy.... Read more:  urlLink  http://x-entertainment.com/articles/0744  &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Looks like Bill and Hillary enjoyed the State Funeral as much as I did... *snooze*&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On this day of national mourning, let us remember some of the glorious achievements of the 1980s that we can attribute to the 40th President of the United States.   Read more:  urlLink  http://www.commondreams.org/views04/0607-10.htm  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Washington Post reported today that people visiting Reagan's body at the Capitol Rotunda wore clothing that was "Not Quite Reaganesque." While Reagan was always known for his formal attire, "The same can't be said for many of his mourners, some of whom trundled past his flag-draped coffin yesterday wearing flip-flops, cargo shorts and T-shirts, their flabby midsections exposed. Some young women wore ultra-mini skirts and halter tops."  This image above was taken near the Washington Monument, on the grassy area between it and the new WWII memorial.  They appear to be extremely grief-stricken.  The bereavement process is difficult for all of us. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>