<Blog>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      its 7:16 pm and i'm wasted.  had sammy's party today, rush rush rush till about 11:30, and then drink drink drink, relax, drink some more.  saw family and relatives, a good time was had by all.,  lost $0.50 in sheephead for about 30 hands played, so all in all not bad, basucally broke even.  ate tons of awesome food, including home-made macaroni and chesse, which is the best food ever.  drank lots, ate lots, talked lots, played cards lots.  good time.  bro-in-law scott and i discussed the beastie boys albums, and then plaanned a future drunken foray into appleton stadium for a baseball game on $1 beer night.  dates are tentative.  tonights plan is (since i'm not going to drive now) stay home and return a call to corey and liz, maybe play some gamey games on the internet, maybe give heckman a call and watch spiderman in the nateplex.  i'm pretty undecided.  pardon the spelling if its bad, too much of the drinky. i am OUT!
      
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, it works!  Now all who visit my website can check out my ramblings on a semi-regular basis. I'm hoping to post a couple times a week, I won't lie to myself and plan on every day.  So, I'll get right into it.  This Saturday is my sister Sammy's graduation party so everyone at my parents' place has been running around trying to make it look like we are not slobs.  The party will be held in my dad's giant shop, so basically the floor area and big bench get cleaned, but most things get a large roll of paper rolled over to conceal their existence.  Game 3 of the Finals, Detroit whupped up on L.A., which ruled.  Should be up 3-0, but blew game 2.  Still, next 2 at still in Detroit, so they have a good chance to set up a seven game series, maybe an upset.  I got this gut feeling that fat-boy Shaq is gonna explode in game 4 and take it away.  We shall see.  Talked to Corey and Liz about coming up to visit them sometime on July here, I'll have to see what my weekend look like once it gets a little closer to then.  Always a bangin time up in tha Ro-C, as I likes to call it (or Rochester, MN, for those not in the know).  Two of the most gracious hosts ever, and always fun.  This time, I will be determined to actually pay for something while I'm there, anything, even a pizza or something.  Corey seems to have an innate sense of when to stick his credit card into the waiter/hostess's mug and pay for all my meals and drinks.  Bastard!  Otherwise, highly looking forward to Dave & Stacy's Fourth of July party coming up in a couple weeks.  I look forward to it more than Clintonville's fireworks now.  And the dance at the Rustic, although that has been fun the last couple years.  Always makes the evening memorable when you see your 18-year old brother show up at the bar you're drinking at.  And then, of course, to buy he and his pals beers.  Quality.  Anyway, that's enough for now, will post more soon.  I'm out!  -Nate
      
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Testing to see if my text will appear on my blog page.  Yay.
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This morning I woke up early with a very painful muscle pull (I think) on my right calf, I literally rolled onto the floor in pain and it stayed for like 2 minutes.  Nothing seemed to help.  Then, the pain gradually subsisted until it was at least not overwhelming.  I've never had this happen before, but I talked to Dave and Corey and they said its not uncommon, and they both have had this happen before.  So that was an auspicious start to the day, but dammit, it hurt.  Still hurts.  Well I'm staying home this Saturday, since I am flat broke and just deciding to go all out next weekend to make up for it.  Still, I'm staying home on a Saturday and that makes me a loser.  So, I at least cleaned my room and went grocery shopping.  Then I came home and watched a show I've never watched before.  Its on ESPN classic, and its called "Cheap Seats".  I can't believe I never saw this before.  It rules.  If you have cable and don't watch it at least once, then you suck.  Speaking of not watching TV, anybody who has cable needs to get HBO.  The three best shows (non-comedy) on all of TV are Deadwood, Six Feet Under, and The Sopranos.  Okay, actually, just watch these shows.   Comedy Central  - Chappelle's Show - The Daily Show - South Park   HBO  - Deadwood - The Sopranos - Six Feet Under - Curb Your Enthusiasm - On The Record with Bob Costas - Real Sports with Bryant Gumble   ESPN  - Around the Horn - PTI - Sportcenter - Cheap Seats   CBS, NBC, or ABC  - Late Nite with Conan O'Brien   Well, now that I've made that list, I'm sure advertising execs the world round are giving high-fives to each other because an 18-34 year old male just listed every show targeted for him.  So, yeah, mock me if you must, at least I don't watch the Man Show.  In fact, who does watch that, besides poser frat-dudes and racist, ignorant, white males?  Party on.
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am proud to announce the addition of Nick to my friends list.  It already had such fine and outstanding members as Corey McGlone and Andy Lagatta, and now I've completed a tri-fecta of talent, a tertiary of tenacity, a trio of titillation.  You can read Nick's innermost dark secrets, see Corey's shocking examples of java functions (heh heh), and see visual evidence of the SPAM factory in Andy's pics.  Oh, and Corey has a blog too, it rules.   urlLink Here is the address , since he doesn't link to it from his main site, most likely because he is lazy.  In other news, I've finally completed the DVD version of camping trips 1999 & 2000.  Took me a long time to find the time and to get it to work right, but now they're done and I can send them out to nick, Andy, and Kyle.  Dave has one already.  The link on the bottom of the main page gives a 2-minute trailer, in essence, of what transpired.  I should really call Andy and make sure its ok to leave it up there before I send out the announcement letter of naterohan.com to everybody I know.  There is a certain phrase Andy says that he may have had no issues about saying to us, but that may be different for other people visiting my site.  Andy used the phrase multiple times on the trip, and I felt the need to include them all in the 2-minute video, mostly because its hilarious.  Otherwise, not drinking soda sucks, running more than 100 feet sucks, 270/270 on my exam rules, as do fresh Dupont cheese curds on Thursday mornings.  This is my weekend on, so not much on the planner, sound like I might help my dad haul some haylage, which will blow.  Plus I have heifer chores. TGIF!
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, the Pistons put the  smack down  on the Lakers.  That just rules.  SO gratifying.  Big Ben throwing down that rebound for a slam dunk was the most satisfying dunk I've seen in a long time.  So nice.  So what else? Not much new.  Today I made the final decision that I am too fat.  You know its bad when you get winded walking up your stairs.  I'm gonna cut out soda again, any smoking I do on the side, and all eating (+ beer) after 5pm.  I think my knee is well enough to start jogging again, and maybe I can fit in some other exercises as well.  So mark it down, I'm hoping to lose 50lbs by December 31st of 2004.  This will be like the 325th diet I've done, but oh well.  Getting too fat.  in more depressing news, my hair is turning grey.  I'm not sure what is causing this, although I have relation that have had grey hair in their 20's before and even one who had his hair turn completely grey in high school.  For the big finish, war scotto-baggins bringing tha funny, war an in-shape naterohan in 2005, war 159/160 on my micro-apps so far, and war the Global Link commercials with the seriously depressed pitchman reciting the phrase "Global Link" like 10 times in a row.  I am out!  -Nate
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Aced the test I think.  No murders, fortunately for those in my company.  I actually finished the test before almost the whole class, and most of the uber-nerds, so that's either really gratifying or foolishly optimistic.  Signed up for 19 credits this fall the that school.  But its almost all on two days, Tuesday and Thursday.  So it shouldn't be too bad.  Not much else new, caught up with the N-playah himself, Nick.  He's doing good.  Ah, my peeps beckon.  Gotta run, I am out!
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ah yes.  I knew it was only a matter of time.  Well, at least the inappropriate language is now a thing of the past and we can move on.  Apologies to those under the impression I had some semblance of class, those visions have now been rightly erased.  To paraphrase the immortal Rick James,  Alcohol  is a hell of a drug.  Sunday was crappy weather all day.  It rained from dawn until about 2pm, and then was incredibly hot and muggy until about 7, and then a severe storm to cap off the night.  I stayed in my air-conditioned room and played computer games.   Have school tonight, 1st exam of the year in my Data Communications class, worth 1/3 of my grade.  I'm taking bets on what will happen first...  A) I finally lose my cool with the uber-nerds and murder them with CAT5 Network Cable B) I take the test, but am so filled with rage at the uber-nerds that I cannot concentrate and fail the exam. C) The instructor decides to fail the entire class on principle, since everyone is a smartass-know-it-all D) I ace it and then murder the uber-nerds with CAT5 Network Cable.  Oh yeah, I was also looking at gauging some interest from people about a potential trip to Cancun in January of 2005.  I will write more for people to look at and maybe even just write a new page for it and throw it on the main site. This much I know, it will be 4 nights and cost about $1200 all inclusive.  My uncle Dave went and highly recommended it.  I saw pictures.  Its a giant, beautiful hotel right on the Caribbean, with plenty of wet-bar seats and a balcony in every room. Like I said, keep an eye open on the site, I'll throw up some details and see what people think.   urlLink http://www.funjet.com/cgi-bin/hotelcontrol/IFJHotelF.asp?code=CUNGRAI^^^&OAC=   Maybe that will show you pics, I dunno.  Later -Nate
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, i just walked in from a nice 15 hour day.  that was so awesome.  you know, if i could think of one thing i would love to do on the two days i have off work every two weeks, it would be to put in 15 hour work days.  goddamnitmotherfuckersonofabitch.  yep, bright and early at 6:30, i was covering bunker silo and right after that, hauled feed all day until now.  and you know what the even more awesome part is?  i get to do the same damn thing tomorrow, probably even longer! sweet!  and then, monday, when i go to school and take that second test that is worth a third of my grade, i will have not studied one bit!  AWESOME!!  damn it, this week has sucked so goddam bad.  i haven't even listed half of it.  i hate every part of this goddam week and goddamnit i'm gonna do shitty on my exam now.  such bullshit.  i'm sick of it.  pardon the language, but i am pissed off.  fuckin huzzah, bitch.
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, sorry for the delay in posts.  Had a couple crappy days to start the week off, as you can see by my last post.  So, this week has flown by.  Tuesday I had school and did well, Wednesday I drove truck for my dad for 16.5 hours strait, and then almost had to again on Thursday, but I had school.  Today I paid bills, did some computer work, and did chores, so now I'm done until tomorrow morning, when I have to help my dad cover the bunker silo for probably another 6 hours.  Think of the worst job in the world, and then double it, that's what covering the bunker is like.  I know it sounds I'm just bitching a lot lately, but trust me, if you had to do it, you would bitch about it too.  Not much else new.  Bought "To The Five Boroughs" by the Beastie Boys, after purchasing "Ill Communication" and "Hello Nasty" about a month ago (*ahem, Nick).  I like it so far, only listened to it all the way through maybe once or twice .  Devin Harris went to the Mavs, which as of now is really cool--he'll fit into that system well.  I say as of now because people talk like Dallas might but the only team to put up a legitimate trade for Shaq.  Now, I think Shaq is giant and powerful and gets every single call in the world.  So he is awesome that way.  Of course, you have to consider the fact that I hate him.  He's a big giant offensive tackle that bullies his way over guys a la tackle football and not basketball.  He is old, slow, lazy, selfish, and narcissistic.  People say "Well, he's only 32." Well, he's had to carry around like 400 pounds since he was 20, so I doubt his knees will last longer than 2 more years, let alone his waist size.  Anyway, getting back to Dallas, they might have a totally different team by the end of the summer, if they are stupid anyway.  So, hopefully Devin Harris will get to represent tha UW with Mike Finley dynamic duo style in big D.  Tonight, I"m probably gonna play games with Corey and Liz, since I have to be up tomorrow early, which sucks.  Might see if my brother wants to switch weekends for chores around so that I could have off next weekend instead for Dave's 4th of July party, which means I would have to do chores this weekend.  We'll see.  Anyway, Enough typing, I need some grub before 5 and then relax tonight.  I am out!
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate group projects.  I think they are ill-conceived, arbitrary busywork that an instructor uses to take a break and make me suffer.  Its the same thing every time, I have to push and pry my group to even talk because they are 'too cool to do anything constructive in a group project.'  So what happens every time is I start typing and doing the projects, asking for ideas, when really I just do all the work, because no one talks.  It doesn't bother these people to let me do all the work (even though I make it obvious I am bothered), because they know I am concerned enough about my own grade that I will complete it myself for a good grade, with them coasting along for the ride.  God damn it.  What is this supposed to teach us, how to work with others?  Fuck that.  There is no 'group project' in the business world; there is  a bunch of people, of which, one person is appointed task leader and thusly assigns personally-specified tasks to the others and then meets afterward to combine results and finalize the project.  There is no equal sharing of responsibility.  If they try to do that, what happens is one guy get frustrated and tells the other people to shut the hell up and just does it himself.  Others take credit, dude is annoyed.  Sound familiar?  Its the same types of people I get every time too, even since high school and at Platteville: prep athlete guy who is too dumb or not concerned enough to do anything and basically just scoffs at me working for his A-; quiet short stocky girl who probably has ideas but doesn't voice them in order to not look dorky in front of prep dude; good looking girl who will not talk to me because I am not; and a person of varying ethnicity, who doesn't speak English well, thereby taking himself out of getting anything done, although his presence provides the jock the go-ahead to tell racist jokes about him to me.  Now if you'll excuse me, I have to write a multi-page report tonight and stick about 5 names on it.  God Damn It.
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I sent out the letter of informing people about the new site.  I've actually had the site going for a couple weeks, so if people want to see what's been going on with me over that span (uber-nerds, 4th of July party, jogging, and rolling on the ground at 6am), then scroll down to read my blog.  The most recent entries are at the top.  Also,  urlLink Nick's blog and Corey's blog are good, and Andy has some pictures  from trips that are amazing, some not so amazing, yet amusing, such as Mandy in spam-making attire.  Going over to visit nephew's Brady and Tyler.  Everyone calls Tyler "tippy" instead of his real name, probably because whenever he sits in a chair or swing, he always leans over the side and gets stuck.  Brady will want rides on the gator, of which I will undoubtedly oblidge.  One last thing, I've come up with my new signature catchphrase-- "Huzzah!"  Look for it soon.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Its Saturday and I just got out of the movie theater where I saw Spider Man 2.  Very, very good movie.  I really enjoyed it.  The dialogue was smart and in perfect proportion to the action, which was not a special effects spectacle but more a tool of storytelling.   urlLink Roger Ebert  can articulate it better than I can, but his review contains a lot of spoilers.  I didn't read it until after I watched.  Very good movie.  Today is kinda rainy, which sucks because tonight is the Clintonville Fireworks show(hopefully).  Last night was the celebration at the Clover Leaf Lakes, but I didn't go.  I was too tired and I didn't know anybody that would be there this year.  Instead, Heckman and I watched the first Spider-Man movie at my place since he's never seen it.  Today, I went to a 12:30 matinee with Heckman, Corey and Liz for SM2 after we went to lunch at Half-Nelsons. A good time was had by all.  It sounds like it might rain on Sunday here, which sucks beyond belief.  I have such high hopes for the party, it would be a shame if we had to move it inside and lose out on what could possibly be a very cool fireworks show.  Rap at ya's latah
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just a quick post today.  Been a busy week so far, I wont go into detail, but basically more of the same from early this week and some of last.  Lots of driving truck into late hours.  But, lots of paycheck too.  Sunday is Dave's party and I am super-psyched.  I ordered a 1/4 barrel of Michelob and the fireworks themselves will be awesome, as usual.  I am bringing meat too for hamburgers, and Dave talked like we should grill them on the tripod over an open fire, which I'm all for, but I hope I don't have to cook them all.  That always seems to end up being my job.  Usually I don't mind, but this is going to be a very "relaxing" weekend, and I may not be able to effectively cook when I've had some "relaxing" juice, probably a half dozen glasses or so by cooking time.  We are clear that by relaxing juice I am referring to beer, right?  And by relaxed, I mean hammered?  Ok, cool.  Gotta run for now, I need to do chores, then I guess we're covering  another  bunker later tonight.  Its moved past annoying, infuriating, ridiculous, and strait into mind-numbinlgy frustrating.  I've had enough.  I think for every load of feed I hauled these past couple weeks, I will drink a beer for.  That seems to be a good idea.  I am out!
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The above is a recent quote from Shaquille O'Neal, whom I hate,  urlLink but said something really funny .  So what's up?  Not too much.  I hauled hay for my parents at the grand hour of 5:30 this morning until about half an hour ago.  I have to go to class soon, plus we finally finished the field, so I'm done.  Monday I stayed home and studied, I took the test, once again I finished early, only two people beat me, but I wasn't trying at all to race anyone.  I didn't go over some difficult questions that I probably should have.  I took the time to write the question numbers down, so I could check again before handing it in, but once I was done, I was like "Fuck it", and just handed it in.  It was 9pm and I was anxious to get home and relax.  Last night I printed out 6-month, 12-month, and 24-month goals that I've actually typed up.  I know, its lame.  I never set goals in high school because I really and honestly didn't care.  I knew I was smart enough to get into college and I could carry a decent enough GPA for that.  I mean really, who hangs their hat on what they accomplished in high school?  Its all about what you do after that.  Well, after bowing out from college a couple times, I now have nothing to show that I'm remotely intelligent or that I should know what I'm talking about.  Eight-year-old ACT scores and potential don't mean jack in job interviews and promotion evaluations.  I've also set weight loss goals, some other personal stuff.  Even though I think this is a good idea, I still know that its hella-lame.  Anyone's mocking will not only be valid, but encouraged.  On a final note, one of these days I'm going to go into a rant about W, because even though I consider myself a democrat, I think there are a  few  good people in the republican party that would be excellent presidents.  John McCain, for example.  But, seriously, what the hell is wrong with people that they would vote for someone with such a hillbilly, ignorant demeanor as that guy?  So watch for that, it isn't every day you hear somebody rip on Bush, I know.  Huzzah!
      
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I'm going to try to turn this blog back from a bitching and moaning outlet to something actually interesting again. (if that's possible)  Today went better, a lot better, than I thought.  I didn't get a call until 10am as opposed to 6am, and only worked until about 4:45.  Rain ended the work day short, so that was fine with me.  During the driving day, I spent some time debating Coldplay (yet again, this has gone on for over a year), drank some pop (which I haven't done for a while), beeped at girls, yelled at dumb drivers, and drove past an art fair many times.  At first I was like "aw, cool, art fair."  But, after trying to squeeze between parked cars on both sides of the street for hours on end, I soon turned into Cartman and was saying things like "Screw you, hippies!" and "You will respect my authori-tie!".  So, that was exciting.  My sister Laura is due with her first baby this week.  So, soon Scott and her will be parents.  I think the names are like "Kaleb" for a boy and either "Suzannah" or "Carly" if its a girl.  I could be wrong.  I will post pics of baby Busse when its born, so stay tuned for that, if you're into that kind of thing.  SO, I'm very excited about that, especially for the long term; in the short term, I am very exited about this upcoming weekend for Dave's Fourth of July Party.  It will rule.  Corey and I alone are splurging for $200 worth of fireworks.    I am going to be drunk.  There will be burgers, brats, and beer, all provided for hunger-quenching...Wait, when did this turn into a Smoove B. article?  Anyway, now that I'm in for the night, I'm gonna call some friends and then shower and relax for tonight, tomorrow I have to study hardcore for my data comm class exam.  After that, simply await the arrival of baby Busse.  :-)   I am out!
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yep, its a girl!  7 lbs, 20 inches.  Lots of beautiful brown hair.   Giant  eyes.  Mom went through quite a difficult, painful, and long labor.  Eventually, the had to do an emergency c-section because Ella's heart rate was dropping from being so tired of trying to come out.  But, no worries, as Laura is fine, just in some pain, and baby is in great health.  Proud daddy Scott looks more ready for a beer than I've ever seen him. ;-)  Pictures will be coming probably in the next day or so, I'm sure.  I'll post them up on the picture page when I get them.  Picture page, picture page...hey, wasn't that an education children's show hosted by Bill Cosby about 15 years ago?  Today I'm just watching the dog again, probably till tonight or tomorrow, whenever Scott comes through to go back to Sheboygan.  Laura is staying until Monday or Tuesday in the hospital because she had surgery, but Scott can't take off any more work, so he's gotta be back Monday.  I think Laura delivered Friday at like 5:40 p.m. or so.  Poor Wau-wa was in more pain than I've ever seen here, even hours after the surgery.  She was finally starting to feel somewhat better  by the time we left the hospital around 9:15 last night.  Tonight I have no plans, but I'm really damn broke after last weekend.  Payday is 5 days away, and I should really be saving up money for next semester anyway.  Books are probably going to kill me this fall.  Anyway, that's it for now, I will post a blog entry informing people when I get those pictures, so watch for that.   Uncle Nate is out!
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Fourth of July party was awesome.  I joined my pals in many beers, and watched some great fireworks.  Needless to say, there was much debauchery and much rejoicing.  The food was fantastic, and even though I cooked most of the burgers, no one seemed to get food poisoning, which was a plus.  I made old-fashionds for Dave, Liz, and I after dinner, while relaxing over the firepit.  Then, switched to the 1/4 barrel of Michelob and drank to my liver's content.  Everything went well, except some people brought lots of crappy fireworks instead of a few nice fireworks, so the show kinda dragged on with some not-so-impressive stuff.  At least Corey saved the day be not following me down the path of drunkenness; thereby giving us 1 person who could safely fire off the fireworks.  It was really fun, but I think next year, less fireworks, more beer.  Today I talked to my sister Laura and she told me that this Friday she is being induced into labor (if she doesn't have her baby by then) because she is already overdue and definitely ready to have that kid.  So, she asked if I could watch Rabby-Roo-Hoo (their dog) on Thursday night until I don't know.  So, for all my friends who loved having Abby relentlessly push mucus-encrusted chew-toys into their laps for hours on end, come on over.  Otherwise, not much new.  No school this weekend because of the holiday, and then this weekend I have off of chores, so I'm trying to figure out what to do.  Probably be down in Sheboygan seeing baby Busse, which is cool.  Huzzah!
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey, hey! I'm back with a vengeance. Back to rock your world. So whats new with tha N-Dog, you ask? Well, let me tell you. Wednesday I drove myself, my mom, and my sister Sammy down to Sheboygan to give Laura some relief from watching little Ella (who's pictures I have still not procured). I brought down my new copy of NCAA Football 2005, Scotty and I played. I ruled. We also broght Pizza Hut for them and let Laura catch up on some sleep. I think more than anything my mom just wanted to go hold her grandaughter for a good while. So, that was exciting. Thursday I had class, went well. And today I managed to get done with my work very early, as its not even 2:30 yet. This weekend I am on for chores, so my options are limited to what I can do.      My parents went left to go camping this morning and asked me to come visit, but I think I will tomorrow, as its kinda raining and I'd only be up there for a couple hours and have to come back. Sounds like Shannon will do chores on Saturday night if I do them Sunday, so that will give me the option to stay up there and sleep over, although that doesn appeal to me, as everyone goes to sleep at 9pm and wakes up at 6am. Not my regualr sleeping hours, especially on a weekend.      Tonight I am gonna game it up with Corey and Liz, and probably download the Modest Mouse album off ITunes and just burn it myself. I know I'll miss out on the packaged goodness of the actual album, but so what. Actually, I could propbably just go to Appleton now since its so early. I think I'm gonna do that.      Oh, and check it out,   Corey is an internet god now  . Millions of nerds `round the globe are hailing him as thier new king, and rightfully so. Huzzah to you, King Corey. Good job, bud.      I am out!  
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      BTW, is there anything worse than The Polyphonic Spree?  Maybe Jay Leno, but that's about all I can think of.  Somebody let me know if they think of anything more obnoxious.  In fact, I'm gonna start a thread on my message boards, go there and share your thoughts on the things that are annoying as hell.  Records I should, and will, buy:  John Coltrane : The Olatunji Concert  Modest Mouse : Good News for People Who Love Bad News  The Clash : The Essential Clash  The Flaming Lips : The Soft Bulletin (the second time for me)  Grandaddy : Under The Western Freeway  Franz Ferdinand ....I dunno.  I think I'm gonna go buy it, even though I've only heard one song, the "Take Me Out" song.  I've listened to some samples of others, and they seem ok, plus its only 11 songs, so if it sucks at least it wont last that long.  I guess in cases like these, I find it best to follow the advice of Mike Myers: "If its not Scottish, its crap!!"
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Word.  An interesting this happened in class today.  Well, first of all I got another 95 on my exam so that was good.  But, more interestingly, our instructor gave us some inside information on some developments at FVTC.  It seems that they administrative board is either being pressured through state funding or enticed through state kickbacks to shift the focus away from the technical aspect of its teaching core to more of a preparatory education for transfers to 4-year colleges.  It seems thats what the UW colleges are looking for.  Changes for the new year include the addition of more "general education" courses, and the elimination of the specialized, more program-specific courses.  Now, does it seem odd that a technical college is trying to remove the  technical  part of its name?  I mean, the main reason people come to a tech college is because: 1) It will offer program-specific courses more readily, hence,  technical . 2) The programs take 2 years, thereby allowing graduates to enter the workforce sooner.  Do people really need a place in Appleton to study general education courses before they transfer to a 4-year college?  I mean, they have UW-Fox Valley  for that reason .  I dunno, this whole thing pisses me off.  Just when I thought I could get some education while I worked and lived near my family, this has to start happening.  Our instructor is one of the few that are campaigning against this "generalization", so that's good, but its still unnerving.  It might not impact me right now, but what if a year from now they eliminate my program (which has happened to at least 2 people in my class in previous years, I learned)?  Sucks.  I have class again Tuesday and Thursday, but I'm hoping Wednesday to travel down to Sheboygan and visit Laura, Ella, and Scott.  Thursday I also have the farm's quarterly meeting, which I'll have to send in a bunch of reports in for, but because of class, I can't make the meeting.  Awwww.  So sad.  I heard from Dave that a guy who does his job on second shift at his plant tested positive for the reefer, so the guy got quickly canned.  And, they have offered Dave the position, which he has taken.  Tonight, Monday, is his first day on that shift, so that's cool.  It kinda sucks he's on second shift because I won't see him during the week as much, but now the weekends should be much more easy to hang out.  I think his shift is like 4pm to 1:30am.   Well, that's it for now, the pictures will probably be up Wednesday night.  I am out! 
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, after watching the trailer and doing a little internet reading, I am officially pumped for "coffee and cigarettes."  urlLink You can watch the trailer here , if you haven't heard about it and are at least interested.  I'd write more about it but I have to go now.  Huzzah!  
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hooray for you, announcer-guy. You, as you well know, have lately been referring to the Tour de France, of which Lance Armstrong is all but assured a victory with his dominant effort, as the Tour de  Lance.   What a witty, clever and original thing to say. How you ever uncovered that gem of literary genius will forever escape me. I mean, what mammoth level of brainpower and wisdom did you have to utilize to create a pun so goddamn hilarious? Dammit, why do people in the media assume everyone is an idiot?     Gah.   
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         I always tell people that they shouldn't buy stuff like firewall and anti-virus software because you can get it for free. Then, they ask "where?" and I say "I'll send you a link." I never do.      So I decided to make a list of some software that gets the NateRohan.com seal of approval. What criteria does it have to meet, you ask?      1)  Free    2)  intuitive interface    3)  Spy/Adware free    4)  Effective      So here you go.  Enjoy the goodness of free shit.          urlLink AdAware  - adware and spyware remover, free updates           urlLink Sygate Personal Firewall  - a firewall, you will need one on a broadband connection           urlLink Skype  - voice-over-ip program that also functions well as an IM           urlLink AVG Antivirus  - very good, unobtrusive anti-virus program, free updates           urlLink LeechGet  - an accelerated downloader program      urlLink LeechFTP  - simple but effective FTP client      urlLink OpenOffice  - office software suite made by Sun, very stable, useful, and, most importantly, free            urlLink Firefox  - a good web browser.  Much more secure than IE.  tabbed browsing will change your life     
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         urlLink I knew it.  
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Aaawwwweee yeeeeah, boyeeee. Fantasy Football is up and running. You know what that means? That's right, get ready for 7 months of constant bitching and griping in this blog about how my players suck, how other guys got so lucky, and over-analyzed stats.  God, I love football.  Anyway, if I know you, and you want to join Corey's league (he might have an opening or two, I'm not sure), let me know. We do a live draft, like in person, but last year I couldn't make it so they let me draft over an IM client, worked fine. I can hardly wait. To quote the immortal Andy L, I am pumped "as a motherfuck."  Tonight is my last exam in one class, Data Comm, so I am studying for that. Not much else new. Although, last night Corey and Liz and I went apeshit with all those South Park characters and  urlLink put them up on the message boards(forums).  Like I said, it was surprisingly amusing and stupid. I think there are like 12 or so caricatures of my friends and others that we did in like 10 minutes. So, if you want one of your own, check yesterdays blog and find the link to the character creator. Make one. You have to do a screen cap to save it, which sucks. Plus, you have to host the image somewhere and link to it in the message boards, so that sucks too. If you can't host, send it to me, I will do it. It sounds complicated, but once you do like 5 or 10, its pretty easy. Ah, its the simple things.  Rap at ya's latah, I MUST PROTECT THIS HOUSE!!
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       WORD. I have pictures of Ella.  urlLink Here they are.  Thanks to Lowa and Scotty for sending me those. The guy who is not Scott is his dad, Brian. SO, thats cool. I have finally come though with my promise, which, if you know me at all, is something of a rarity.   Today, besides doing chores, was very uneventful and boring. Here is what I accomplished today.     Yep, its me drawn in the South Park universe.  You can try yourself  at the  South Park website . Its suprisingly amusing and stupid, which in my book are the best ingrediants for success. Yeah.   I am out!!   
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha, well it seems Nick's company (or at least its website censor)deems my site too hot for the web. That's amusing. I'm guessing the censor didn't like my goddamit rampages, which I can understand.    Not much else new with me. I've had some long days lately that have been going on into the late hours of the night because of things breaking down in the heifer barn, but otherwise not too eventful. The big news for me was buying a pizza maker, which is nice because the "open-style" one that I had was only very good at cooking the outer 3 inches of pizza. The middle was nice and frozen, usually.    Yesterday one of the guys who works for my dad (incidently, --Andy, Nick, and Monica-- he was one of the guys you met when you visited the barn) told me that he had to talk to me about an exciting place to go on the internet. At first, I figured this must be a place where I can either... a) see some naked girls  b) consolidate debt  c) gamble    I was wrong, as this guy proceeded to tell me he is part of a company now called the "Team of Destiny". In the "Team of Destiny", members can apparently  go on the internet  and  buy stuff , just like if you were at Wal-Mart-- except you stay right at home!  I'm serious, that's exactly what he said. All I could say was. "Wow." Stupidly, I feigned interest as he proceeded to ramble on some rehearsed sales pitch that he got from his kit he bought off an infomercial, no doubt. All I could think of was "WTF, are you this stupid that you can't realize that what you're doing is a scam? Or, at the very least, simply a way for people to rip off people they know, making them buy into a two-bit pyramid scheme?" It sucks, because he's a decent kid, and I know he's not the brightest star in the sky, but he should know about these kinds of things. Part of me wanted to interrupt him and just scream into his ear, "Are you a fucking retard? Do you not understand how stupid that is?!" But, I couldn't just destroy the kid's visibly ambiguous self-esteem right over something as trivial as the "Team of Destiny", so I just politely declined and changed the subject, leaving soon after.    I dunno, it bothered me.    This weekend is my cousin's graduation party from high school, and while many people I know are glad to be done with graduation parties, I actually can't wait. It isn't often I get to tear it up, beer style, so close to home where I can really let loose and not have to worry about driving home. Scotto baggins promises to not stand me up this time, so it will probably be good times with drunken attempts at learning sheepshead and discussing ill-fated trips to various stadiums on various $1 beer nights in various cities.    Tonight, I'm gonna play my $20 football game that I finally understand (they have a cap system used in the franchise mode that is apparently the same as the cap in the real NFL, and now that I understand it, I am finally prepared to take my destined job as director of finances for the NY Jets). Also, I might buy some more albums off of iTunes, to which I have become a buying monster. I think in the last 2 weeks I bought four albums. So nice for super lazy people like me. Oh, and this weekend I have the dog, so look for me to post pictures of her eating my socks, wallets, and maybe even some bottles.    I am out!
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Aw man, I must have spent 20 minutes just listening to  urlLink sound clips from Chappelle's Show .  The best one is the Sam Jackson clips, but really there are no bad ones.  Check it out if you are bored, good for a chuckle.
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Nick commented to me when he started his blog that the assault on my word count was about to commence.  At the time, I held a sizable lead, with about two weeks worth of posts and literally thousands of words.  Well, he has now chipped and chiseled his way to within 300 words exactly of my word count, as of before this posting, and it seems all but inevitable he will surpass me in a week.  Much like Jan Ullrich, I seemed doomed to fail against an American hero, in this case, Nick Lucht.  My brother left for a week-long camping trip yesterday with about 12 of his buddies.  They stay in a cabin that is about 15 from the Minnesota-Canada border, and from what I understand, the purpose of this trip is to:  A) Drink B) Fish C) Drink, eat the fish D) Sleep  Which sounds ok, even though I don't really fish.  Regardless, since he's gone, I've had to pick up his workload.  So therefore over the course of 21 days, I will have had one day off.  Nice.  But, since his birthday is tomorrow, I gave him a giant bottle of Bacardi rum.  Good times.  This morning I received an email from someone I see exactly once a year, at Andy & Mandy's new year's party.  I would say she is a friend of Mandy's, but that makes it sound like i hate her guts, which i don't, so I'll say she's a friend of mine too.  Anyway, she was quite amused at the inclusion of a NateRohan.com thong at the store, and thusly purchased it.  Equally amused, I told her she must send me an action shot, much like Corey and Liz did.  Well, she did today.  And, as she put it, is not a "money shot", just an action shot.  It rules.   urlLink Check it out .  This week is going to be hella-nasty, with exams and extra chores gallore.  Oh, hey, not that anybody I know owns an X-box, but if you do, go buy the new ESPN NFL 2K5, because it just came out and instead of charging the standard $50, they are charging $20.  I had to ask the store clerk if it was correct and it wasn't just some sort of upgrade thing for last years game.  Needless to say, I bought it, and its pretty good.  Its pretty different from Madden, which is the standard, but its visuals are  much  more realistic.  So, anyway that's about it.  I'm off to get ready for the Steenbock family reunion, which is usually really damn boring for me.  I'll probably end up chilling with scotto baggins (my brother-in-law Scott)over many beers.   And wtf is up with Ricky Williams?  I know he's defiantly not your typical football player, but still.  As I write this, ESPN is comparing his early retirement to others, like Gale Sayers, Jim Brown and Barry Sanders.  Uh, no.  They ruled, he was just ok.  This is more like the Robert Smith retirement.  Oh, and way to go out on a limb and  urlLink predict Lance Armstrong's victory  after he had like a 3 day lead with one to go, Bush.  Thats amazing.  Dumbass.  I am out!
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      BTW, I've been listening to a lot of Mase lately.  Question - Does this damage or enhance my street cred?  Please comment.
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, the tell-all video about my true nature seems to have brought out an interesting reaction in people, mostly a strange mix of humor, mockery, pity, and sorrow.  That, my friends, is just a recipe for success in my book.  For now, I'll put the video hidden away where it can no longer incriminate me, back in the archives of NateRohan.com.  And, eventually, I'm gonna do a little more tinkering with the menu layout so I can include a link to all present and future videos.  This week has gone very fast for me.  I finally finished my MicroApps course with my group project.  Our presentation went well until I stopped talking, giving way to others in the group to explain their portion of the presentation.  I know that makes me sounds like a elitist prick, but its the sad truth.  I still think we did well, and I'm hoping to get an A- in that class.  I have a feeling its a B+ though.  Only because of the group projects.  I asked Teach what my homework and test grade was before I left the last day and she said 97%, so here's hoping I can offset our crap groupwork.  Lately I've been thinking a lot about what it means to be a democrat or a republican, and trying to figure out why people vote the way they do.  A lot of the people I know through the farm are republican, I would say about 90% (just guessing) of the people in my local farming industry vote republican.  Farmer themselves, salesmen, contractors, and nutritionists all seem to have these sorts of ideals.  I've found when I bring up the war in Iraq being started without any resolve to the insurgence into Afghanistan, I'm often meet with silence or a scowl, which makes me think they're republican, because I'm second-guessing our republican president's actions.  Conversely, when its comes to that subject in another setting, most recently in one of my classes with some mates of mine, the conversation is usually interesting and well-informed.  Now, I don't mean to say republicans are dumb and democrats are smart.  That's really what bothers me, is because a lot of these guys around my area are good, decent people with common sense.  They work long, hard days and provide good homes for their kids.  They probably also like to hunt, and they go to church on Sundays.  And after working almost all day, they don't want to hear serious, dull speeches about the environment or why some pot-smoking lazy teenagers should be free to do so--they'd rather be entertained for a little bit and go to bed.  Unfortunately, for the middle and lower classes that these men actually compose, I think that's why they vote republican.  People are constantly told, mostly by their own friends who heard from their friends, that democrats are going to take away their rifles and shotguns, and deny them their second amendment rights.  IF you vote for Joe Republican, that won't happen.  Also, I've sat through countless church services where I'm told, basically, that this democratic candidate is only help committing murder by allowing right to choice for women, and so we should all vote for the republican candidate.  Now, personally, I happen to support the right to life here.  Its something I've formed of my own thought, experiences, and religious beliefs.  But I don't believe any congressman/woman is aiding murder by allowing the right to choose.  Frankly, I see that as the mother's transgression.  But I think this issue hugely, hugely determines the average person's political leanings.  Lastly, I think one thing that makes average people vote republican are the attitudes of the party's most notable figures.  Bush, Cheney, Limbaugh, Gingrich, Rumsfeld, hell even Charleton Heston..These are guys that  are great for one-lined, short and direct replies to questions.  "Finish the job", "Never quit", "Working hard for you", these types of slogans relate to somebody who works tirelessly with a strong work ethic.  Now, unfortunately, the thing people are just not understanding is that, if you nevermind the potheads and hippies, and you actually DO read those lengthy investigation reports and you DO listen to those dry speeches and testimonials, you will realize that most of our republicans leaders are lying to you.  They don't look out for the average working citizen, they tax the hell out of you.  The ones who get tax breaks?  Yeah, its your company's boss and that prick millionaire down the road.  Its congressman, its corporations, it aint you.  I could go on for pages, but that's just my opinion.  I understand that some people want to vote, and are, republican.  That's cool with me.  I got no beef if that's what you believe.  But I do have a beef with Bush.  I don't need to explain why he should go or why he's a horrible president and person, that's been done and redone, with good reason.  I've said before I think their is good leadership in the republican party.  If, miraculously, John McCain had won the republican ticket, I would have voted for him over John Kerry.  That's just one example.  So I'm not against republicans, just Bush.  I just wish people would think about Bush and who they're electing for another four years of their life before they do it so easily.  And I'm frustrated that almost all these guys I see on the road, in the fields, busting their humps every day, just to pay for some millionaires tax break, are gonna end up voting to keep on doing it.
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      If you looked at all at the main page, you might have watched my very first attempt at making a special effects shot.  I made it using the program AlamDV, which seems to be a popular program on the web for doing those kinds of things.  It isn't all just lightsabers, infact, thats  a small percentage of what can be done, but it seems to be what everybody likes about it.  Two film students from Maryland used this program with a digital video camera to shoot a 5 minute short that is basically one giant lightsaber duel, and its so fucking cool.  Two actors, who may or may not be the students, obviously knew some martial arts and used that in conjuction with a lot of choreographed fights to make this movie, and then edited it and used AlamDV to add in the sounds and light effects.  It turned out fricken sweet.   urlLink Go watch it here , click on the "play" button halfway down the page.  Or, if you'd rather download it to your desktop to watch it again, right click and hit "Save Target as", and then pick where.  Maybe its not for everyone, but I got as much of a kick out of it from the sounds and effects as the actual fight itself.
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm not sure what it was, but something about this weekend made it great and relaxing, fun. Scotty got hella-wasted on Friday night, after he and Laura came home early from their friends' wedding (because Lowa missed little Ella), and then brought Sammy and her friend Jolie over, we all watched "School of Rock" for the first time in the Nateplex. His proceeding move to pass out/"fall asleep" during the movie was amusing, as was his subsequent crashing/pass out onto my couch. I'm guessing it just looked too comfortable to someone so wasted and ready to fall down for the night, plus, he knows that if he went back to my parents house, where Laura and Ella were staying, everyone there would wake up at 6:30am and start banging pans, listening to pastor Arnold Murray on TV at an unreasonably high volume, or even just start talking at their normal-talking voice level, which for my dad makes it sound like screaming to the normal human ear. So, maybe it was that too.  Saturday started of with finding out Scott had been dry-heaving and feeling awful for the better part of the day, whilst I went about getting chores done early so I didn't have to leave the upcoming graduation party that night. It went well, went home and showered, went to the par-tay and started off that time of the week I affectionately call, "beer time". Unfortunately, Scotty was not able to join me in beer time, as it would have made him vomit. Plus, they had to drive back to Sheboygan that night. In any case, after eating some delicious food, I proceeded to yak it up with some relatives, played a little with Brady and Tyler (my two nephews), and inevitably got to that point where I around the place for people who might be down with playin some cards: select uncles, Scott, my sister Sam, and so on. Turns out, we thought instead of sheepshead to play some Texas Hold `Em, which, I agree is the "hot new thing", but oh well. It's fun.  Brothah, I dominated.  Started out slow, probably down a buck or two (playing for pennies, Canadian pennies no less), but then throughout the next several hours I wiped the table clean. I was in a zone, a "poker zone", if you will. The poker zone is a happy, fun place, where all your bluffs work, where that pair of 8's your banking a huge raise on actually win you the hand, and where you fold early when the winning hand was a strait aces to 10's. When I finally left, I had so much change that my pocket was dragging my right side of my body down. It was rad. Came back to my place and proceeded to play gamey games with Corey and Liz for several quality hours, and then slept last night like a baby.  So I'm in a good mood, this weekend has gone well. I was gonna go on a rant today about W, especially after reading the last several  urlLink Reasons to dispatch Bush  that Nick tipped me off to, but I don't wanna get pissed off. So, off for more relaxation today before this upcoming week of insanity. I am out!
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A lot went on this past week, much that is blog-worthy, eventful, and cool.  However, I am not going to write about it, because at the moment, Madden 2005 has been out for over 24 hours and I have not acquired it.  This demands serious attention.  I hope to write about what is going on and other musings as soon as I stop playing.  So, here's hoping for September 1st!
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      dude, i got an A in my micro-apps course, which means combining that with my from data comm, my gpa is a sterling 4.0, biotch.  Luckily, my group project did not drag me down.  ah, so nice.  had to gloat about it.
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I should have worded my little rant from yesterday a little better, because I don't mean to make it sound like Christians are bad or they are one-dimensional in their political direction.  God's cool.  And so are a lot of people that worship God, such as myself.  My point was that its more common to find an instance where the church sides with a republican stance rather than a democrat stance because of the right to life issue, and that was a major reason for a large number of people I know siding republican.  So, my apologies, I realize that came off the wrong way and used a bad example.  But, it was just an off the cuff rant.  I would have been more tact and rational if it were a persuasive essay or something.  Also, I don't hate republicans.  I hope we cool.  Well, today was a good time.  I went down to Sheboygan with my family to see Ella get confirmed.  The service was held outdoors in an open shelter, with picnic tables and everything.  When I sat down and felt the familiar board-seat feel, my ass told me "Ah, picnic tables, that means soon I will have many beers and be playing cards."  I was wrong, but the service was very good.  I suppose until that glorious day when I got to church and am surprised with beer and cards (and the back of the cards would have to have the  "Buddy Christ" on them, for sure), I will keep a silent vigil.  Also, the church was kind enough put up a very big banner that had a picture of the Christ-dove or whatever that thing is, along with "Ella Sue, you are mine."  Something about that phrase just made me laugh, like it was some evil villain proclamation.  This amused me for a while, and after the service I stole the camcorder away from my brother and narrated a sinister "You are mine" during a shot of the banner.  So thanks, heartfelt strangers, I turned your genuine kindness into mocking humor.  After that, we all came back to Lowa and Scotty's place for beers and cards, and some delicious food.  Scott's cousin Phil was there, so I got to catch up with him a little.  He's a good guy, very bright and has a sense of humor that is in line with mine, as is Scott's.  Discussed cancer kazoos and Kentucky basketball, along with some sports radio rappin'.  We played some Texas Hold-Em, but after going up by a buck or so I ended up down $1...All-in-all not bad.  Later, a bunch of us went down to that giant beach in Sheboygan and yucked it up with some frisbee and sun-soaking.  Should have brought shorts, an oversight that will not be missed in the future.  Then, said goodbyes and came back here.  Had a good time.  Tonight I plays gamey games with good friends Corey and Liz way over in Minnesota thanks to the magic of Internet.  Then, its Adult Swim on Cartoon Network, where tonight they play my favorite episode of "Family Guy" ever, where Peter becomes president of a Tobacco Company.  Hilarity now, hilarity now...  Oh yeah, and Friday night, I went out for a delicious chicken sandwich, and on the drive home decided I should buy a pack of Lucky Strikes, because cool people smoke them.  So, I went in and asked the girl if she had any, she said they have 1 pack that's been there for over a year, and I was like "Awesome, I'll take `em."  Later, I found out Lucky Strikes don't have filters on them, so I guess they are for hard core smokers, not posers like me who smoke a pack a month, usually after a good meal or a late-night drive with the windows down and the blues turned up.  Regardless, I'm determined to smoke the pack, just to prove my cool.  I've tried proving my cool before, but it never works.  I'll let you know if it works.  For now, time to play some video games!  HUZZAH!
      
</post>


</Blog>