<Blog>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Serenity doesn't last...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I recently noticed (while watching the horrorshow video for This is the New Shit) that Marilyn Manson is so good at using his hands. It's hard to explain but he just seems to know exactly what to do with those things!  "don't forget the violence"
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Those days were pissing me off. But I found them to be (infuriatingly) inspirational. The swaying green: my applauding audience. Not quite enough. So I used and I discarded. Without remorse nor regret, and I find myself here.  This day.  This now.  This moment.  Surrounded by authenticated darkness. Serenity.  “In Theaters April 22, 2005” – (not contextual) 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "If you choose to pull the trigger, (should your drama prove sincere): Do it somewhere far away from here."
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My computer, after trials and other bad stuff that starts with "t", is back in fully working order. Which means i'll be blogging more often (unless i get bored and stop). It's taken me a while to re-download all the stuff i need (quicktime, winamp, flash player, updated versions of MSN and windows media player etc) but now at 12:20am i have finished, and i can get back to my normal life. I recently downloaded a  urlLink trailer  for  urlLink The Grudge . It was extra high resolution, so it took about 3 hours but it was worth every second. It looks like the best movie ever,it looks really scary and more importantly, it stars the coolest person in the world,  urlLink Sarah Michelle Gellar !! *sigh* She is so beautiful and talented. She's the most amazing actress I've ever seen. So go watch the  urlLink trailer !! On another Sarah related note, on friday i went to town with my friend  urlLink Campbell  who bought  urlLink Buffy the Vampire Slayer  season 7 part 1, and  urlLink Child's Play 2  on dvd. Some impressive purchases if i do say so myself. Christ! I'm boring myself! So i should probably stop typing for the sake of anyone who reads this post.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My computer (which has been fucked for at least a month now) has been fixed. Unfortunately, the internet still doesn't work and all of my files have been deleted. Ha. It's funny how that box of crap can bring me so much pain...End of Post.  "All that glitters is cold"
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My computer is fucked. None of the posts i have done (before and including this one) have been posted from my computer (I either did them at work or at  urlLink Taeghan 's house). Anyway, I have been so bored without my computer. In fact, last Sunday, I was so bored i tidied my room. I spend the whole day sorting out every single thing!! If it weren't for my CD collection that helped to keep me sane for the whole terrible ordeal, I would have some dead people on my hands. I listened to most of my CD's which include:  urlLink Marilyn Manson ,  urlLink Placebo  (by the way, I LOVE Brian Molko),  urlLink A Perfect Circle  &  urlLink Tool . Now i am afraid to live in my room because i don't want to mess it up again. Bored Now. See you all in death valley. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm at work and one of my work mates came in and gave me a passionfruit candy stick. Trying to open it proved to be a difficult task. It wasn't opening so i threatened to murder it. Luckily no one heard me... My psychotic nature remains a secret...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, I'm at work now, i've been putting videos away and puting stickers on videos and returning videos and letting people borrow videos for an agreeable sum of money. Can you guess where i work?? I'll be finished in 12 minutes. I'm getting out a movie (for free) called  urlLink Lost Highway , staring my two most favourite artists in the world  urlLink Marilyn Manson  and  urlLink Twiggy Ramirez  (aka, Jeordie White) (as Porno Star no.1 and Porno Star no.2). (seriously).
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello, today I am creating a blog. I'm actually meant to be at school today. I'm not. Oh the controversy.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate people so much. Sometimes I feel such seething hatred for people, I don't know what to do with myself. So how do I feel now? I feel like snapping necks until everyone's dead.  Isn't that right Ripper?  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I sit on a throne before&nbsp;my  subjects .  Hardly able to draw a breath. Any of them. The obesity of their nature takes care of that.  The skin is&nbsp;crushed and rolled out of shape by the heavy dark they call their home. While they weep and bleed and whither and wait for the earth to retract it's relentless apple peelers.  pity.  pity them.  I pity the&nbsp;lived ones.  Sometimes I wonder why before I remember my eyes. The thorn on the road of rosemary sweet tickles. When will the cut become real? Bleed me dry?   Tomorrow always comes.    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Who do  I  see? No one. No one at all. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It fucks you up. Me, in this particular case and yes I'm quite&nbsp;surprised I've given in so quickly. The endless progression of minute-long minutes continue to bore into my empty soul (and&nbsp;I don't mean&nbsp;that&nbsp;in a Trent Reznor&nbsp;sort of way).  I just laughed at my little performance of strictly script based theatre. And that's really, really pathetic.   "Don't think about it. Don't think about it"   A&nbsp;tourniquet of&nbsp;words that seem so, so very empty, leave me feeling betrayed and unwanted.  -He claps me his sword upon the table- and it looks like there IS infact, a need of thee.  &nbsp;But&nbsp;being so weak, my  feelings  don't deserve to be (attractive or even)... noticed.  None of them do.&nbsp;That's why they never laugh. But I do.   "Don't think about it. Don't&nbsp;fucking think about it"   Why am&nbsp;I doing this? angerenvybordemrevengeprofitbleedingart*hitprideendingaches  *It's looks more and more like it every day. Does anyone else&nbsp;see it?  Revenge?? That's a fucking joke. He doesn't even see me when&nbsp;I claw at him from the inside. I only do it because&nbsp;I don't care and neither does he.  And what of those who&nbsp;do care? The nothing that can, and constantly does, cause so many somethings.&nbsp;&nbsp;I don't even want to be there for that. Not even if I thought I could.   "Don't think about it. Don't think about it"   If I could, maybe I'd want to. But that's doubtful.  /what I really do want isn't there. When it&nbsp;gets here&nbsp;(if ever), I'll get tired of it and leave it in a box.  I AM HAPPY.     "You can kill me, you can kill them, you can let everyone die  
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't realise that sun came back out. I  guess I forgot what it looked like. looked like[.]  a sphere of gas fuelling the fires of hell.  “************”? (you ask). Of course --  heaven’s hell is far from mine.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First of all: Angel, episode 4.20: Sacrifice: Amazing (as always).  There was this one scene that really touched me. There was something about it. It was just the most horrific, beautiful, disturbing image. So i suggest you see it. Watch it on TV, buy the DVDs. Do what you must.  Second: My new stuff. I got a plain, black, long sleeved t-shirt, a spikey leather wrist thing and a pair of shades (Not Twiggy's shades but what are you gonna do?). I also discovered the coolest hat in the world. A black velvety thing. I just want lots of people to take pictures of me and show my hat to the world!!  Thrid: This blog is getting boring so if i stop posting soon, that's why.     
     
    
</post>


</Blog>