<Blog>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If your computer needs a make-over,  Pixelgirl Presents  is a great place to start!!  This is THE best webpage for computer desktops, icon and anything computer-y!! With anything from the CUTEST icons, to the GRUNGIEST desktops, this website has everything.   It has categories such as:   3D   Anime   Cute   Girlie   Holidays   Urban  And MANY more.    Pixelgirl Presents  works with many talented artists that all display their work here.  I PROMISE you, you can not go wrong at this website!!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       White Ninja comics  if  SUCH  a funny site, following the adventures of an (obviously) white ninja. White ninja is...not all that bright, to say the least. With over 150 comics to date, you are guaranteed hours of fun, for the whole family (well, perhaps not the grandparents. Or the parents. Actually, keep it to yourself)   I was first directed to the site by  tIMMY  and haven't stopped going back ever since. It is updated every Tuesday and Saturday so, go on, you  know  you want to!!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       The Spin Starts Here  is a great website that takes what is on the new, on the internet or just in society and puts a funny spin on it. With regular writers such as 'Caz', 'The Hack' and 'Atari' you know that everyday you will be startled with the topics that they talk about, but at the same time, generally amused.   Check out this website if you are looking for something to do on the web!
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is the website that I always visit when I get on the net. If you don't know who Tripod are - shame on you!! Tripod are only the best musical comedy to hit the world since....well, forever.

Check out their webpage and their forum. The forum always has nice people waiting to talk about Tripod, or simply just chat.

Their diary gets updated reguarly by each of the boys, giving an insight into their lives. Check out the archives of that as well.

The songs haven't been updated for AGES, so I wouldn't worry about that too much. If anything happens, the forum'll be sure to tell you about it!

Thats about it. Did I tell you Tripod are the best??
     
    
</post>


<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       skitHOUSE  is a great show that has many great comedians....including Tripod. And most of us would know my opinion on Tripod, if you have seen my other sites. I THINK THEY ROCK!!   Anywho,  skitHOUSE   is a random sketch comedy show. It has a couple of skit's which are....less amusing than others, but that can't be help now, can it??  Tripod are also featured doing a song at the end. WOOHOO!! lol. What else can you ask for??  Check out  skitHOUSE . Usually aired on Wednesday nights at 8:00pm, at least in Adelaide, on channel 10. Check your local listings to be certain!!
     
    
</post>


</Blog>