<Blog>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Friends  What is a friend ? is a friend who backstabs you ? a friend who lies to you ? or a friend who used you for his own will ?  A friend is a person who you can really trust no matter good or bad times a friend is always there a person who will be next to you  when there is a need of care. What more can a friend be ?  In life we needs friends. We can't live our life all by ourselves. If we do why bother living anyway ? Trust is not can't be bought but it is earn. So if you want your friends to trust you, you got to earn it from them and they will earn your trust too. Love your neighbours as yourself and love your enemies more. If your love people who loves you only, what is the reward ? Remember life on earth is uncertain, is there any of your friends that you want to tell them that you care for them ? Nonetheless, choose your friends wisely because friends are people who influence you or you influencing them. Well keep this is in mind and take care.  -Kevin- 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Inner Sins   The guilty feelings that dash across my mind losing myself and there's nothing to that can define severe to a mindless thought and nothing can be find the serene feelngs are lost in despair In my life there's nothing to share but the inner sins that I can't suppress drench in guilt and soon to be condemn all of these no one can comprehend filling myself with torment and hatred soon to found out I'm desperate nothing seems better than death but it never happen to take its steps My inner sins that control my mind finding a way to forget the past behind.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Lying on the bed of sorrow spent sleepless nights with shattered tears my life is such low and hollow my heart hurts just like it was pierce.  Shattered pieces of my life are missing lack of worth deserve nothing captured and hold in a dimless hole awaiting for someone to take my soul.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Turning away from the darkness, putting the past all behind you, escaping the loneliness a time to change but it all up to you.  Into the depth of the sea, facing a problem that is unforseen. looking for the answer that I cannot see, wishing nothing for what have been.  Regretting the past without any change, taking you nowhere but deeper into your guilt. only you can make the step to renew, and to open up your life rather than to rebuke.     The Sorrow Of My Heart  Sorrow brought me here I am why won't the dorr just close and slam so my wrecked life won't be like this fallen into a deep and dark pit for this I don't want to live rather than live in the dark and lonely pit.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You know what !! I got tons of homework to do and I am so lazy to do all of it !! I think I will just finish my econs and accounts and maybe my add maths tonight if I can last la.. den maths..dunno la see how ler...me eyes are totally tired..no nescafe blewk...tomorrow got tuition but no youth maybe got time to do my other homework ekekeeke...lazy la me..now nobody online only a few folks online. Dey I wanna get my new guitar leh....darn it...today learn Behind Blue Eyes yahooo !! soo cool..but need to practice more for the timing eyh...wah this is my new blog ehehe my other one is www.xanga.com/kev88in check it out la wei.. hehe..til den see ya  -kev-
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Life may seems miserable to you but have you ever seen life from a positive angle ? If you haven't I challenge you to do so. It will help you a lot.   As for me, I felt my life was miserable and I really hated myself for the past and for what I am .The past is the past no one can change it. It took me hard to accept it .Well if there were a time machine I don't mind going back to the past and change it.. hehehe    Well my advice to you is to look at life in a different view a positive view and enjoy life take care !!  -kev-
     
    
</post>


</Blog>