<Blog>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, I went to a social with Jenny and her stupid ass boyfriend aaron who both did coke before we went. An ill omen I thought. We didnt go to the social until just after 11, when Celine finally showed up. Anyways we got there, and I knew 90% of the people. They were pretty psyched to see me, which made my day better. Jen, Aaron and Celine went and sat at a table with some people that I didn't know. So I made my way slowly to the table, and noticed a decent looking guy checking me out. S'all good, I smiled and made eye contact. Left to go get a drink and dance. Came back and he introduced himself to me... Wes Goodon. His brother had went out with Jen's sister Allison quite a few years ago. He seemed really interested and bought me a drink. We danced and he asked me if we wanted to go back to his sister's after the social. We decided we would go to the bar before we went there but that we would make an appearance after that. Jen told me that he was single, but that he had 2 kids and broke up with his ex about 3 months ago. I was a little apprehensive, but he seemed like a really nice guy so I said whatever.Jen, Aaron and I went to Gravity. Wes's sister Amy met us there, while Wes and her bf, Brian went back to their place. After the bar we headed over to Amy's me being my klutzy self tripping over the sidewalk and my feet... Aaron and Jen "had to go get something" so Amy and I went in by ourselves. Wes came and kissed me which was pretty good and we cuddled in a cool chair. He let me know about his situation - his ex, the fact they had 2 kids, and had given 1 up for adoption. He seemed really sweet and sincere and I asked him if he was sure that he wanted to get into something, if he was ready. He said yes. Jen and Aaron came and left, and Wes told me that if I stayed there that night I could get a ride in the morning. So I stayed there (nothing happend), and got a ride in the morning. we exchanged phone numbers, and he said he'd call. Which he did, that night. Seemed nice, but I told him I'd call him on the Monday, as I was busy tonight and Sunday. Going to Houston's tonight with Marnie... should be fun!!
     
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bar last night was kinda lame, we went and everyone that we didn't want to see appeared there. The only good people who were there were J Chum and Amy, and Wes's brother's gf Jayme. Apparently Wes must've been talking about me, bc she knew who I was and said Lisa from last night Lisa? SO we chatted a bit, and Marnie and I ended up leavign early - around 12:30, which was ok, since I had forgotten that I had told my mom I was going to go to her CPR class this morning. We drove around, got soem Tim Hortons and called it a night. Got up and went to the class, didnt seem too hard, except my mom laughed at me casue I didnt know how to hold a baby. After that, I went to my father's for supper. Marnie and I decided to go to the lake tomorrow, to open up her cabin, and get away form the city. Decided to call Wes tonight, since tomorrow, it will be long distance. He was surprised to hear from me, as he thoguht that I didn't seem interested on the phone. Told him, Id call him when I got back from the lake and that wed difinatly make plans for then. I am really starting to like this guy!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, umm... the saloon last night was pretty good. Jen and I went there, and just as we were going in, Amy, Jayme and some of their friends came up. That was cool so we got soome drinks($4 each!!!) and sat down and chatted. I drank some of the little bottles in my purse so that i would get drunk, and we danced. At around 10:30, we decided to go to the bathroom, and while I was in there, I get this call... from Wes!! I was like Wes I never thought I'd hear from you again, and he was like why, and I said that the last time i talked to him, he made it sound like that and he was like no. He asked me where I was and I said at the saloon... with your sister! He was like wha??? so i asked him to come to the saloon and he said ok, jayme and amy were like whats going on? and said i dunno. they both talked to wes and then we agreed to meet him at the top of the ramp to the keystone. so he came and evertything was good. we talked -he's been living at his mom's the past few days... he never even told jayme and dallas, he just moved out, casue he needed time away. He held my hand everywhere, even though he says its for 10 yr olds. It made me happy so he did it. Yay!!! After the saloon him and Amy and I walked home, he stayed here again, and amy lives like 4 blocks away. Then we woke up this morning and he got a call from his stepdad to go do some work, so he left. Jill and Kevin saw him leaving, as they were upstairs in the kitchen when we came up, but i dont think theyll say anything...Going to the saloon tonight, with jen cause last night she couldnt drink and bailed on me by 11. Id rather hang out with wes but oh well, i promised, plus his kids are going there for a sleep over.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was pretty fun - went to Jen's and got there just as her sister and her youngest Chloe were getting there too. Told her the whole Wes story, she knows him bc of Dallas... thought it was shitty. neways, went to go to artistic, and it was closed until later, so we decided to go to the mall for a bit. well chloe was being so funny, she was wandering around the stores while jen and allison were looking at clothes and we had to keep rescuing her. then we went to mcdonalds in walmart and chloe was the meesiest kid ever. she had caramel and ketchup everywhere. We were so loud at our table - Allison was talking about the goonies, and said HEY YOU GUYS!! so loud I think all of walmart could hear and jen was talking about pads... it was quite funny. We were going to leave and Allison couldnt get any water and tried to clean Chloe off with just a napkin... didnt work so swell. she had pieces of napkin all over her face. she looked like an orphan :) So we went back to Artistic and Jen was told that they couldnt do her tattoo until next Wednesday. so we just decided to walk form there to the fair, as Allison had left us to go and pick up Holly. So we walked and eventualy got there. I was happy casue it only cost $2 to get in. Yeah!!! Aaron and Jen went and got their passes and started going on the rides. I was their designated holder of shit. We ran into soem of Aarons freinds who were carnies and they said that during their breaks they would take me on some of the rides since they can get on for free. So I ended up going on the Inverter, the bumper cars and the fun house. They were ok, but Aaron's friend was stiny and I didnt really like being around him. Then we ran into Amy, and she was like what happened??? I told her the story and she was amazed. She said that she hadnt talked to her brother yetm and had just heard that we werent together. Ran into her a few more times and she told us that seh is going to the saloon all weekend. i told her to get my number off wes and to give me a call and we could go together. Jen adn I tried to get hypnotized, but it was too loud and noisy and I couldnt hear the guy, so that didnt work out. We went home shortly thereafter, as Jen and Aaron were getting cold and so we didnt see the fireworks, but all in all, not a bad day. Not doing too much today, just hangng otu as far as I know...
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So last night, I went with Jen to work at McDick's and saw everett there. Asked him if he wanted to go the mall with me after he got off work at 5. so while I was waiting for him to get off, Mark came up to me and asked if there was any hard feelings, I said no. So ev and I walked through the mall and sat in the food court. he listened to my sob story and then, since Wes and I were supposed to go and see Harry Potter that night, but we obviously werent, that he would take me. I decided that I wanted to go get my nose pierced too, since I was mad at Wes. So I did and we made it back to the theatre just in time. It was pretty good, and Ev was really nice to me... afterwards, we went for a walk around, and we ran into Cam at Sev. Cam said that he was thinking about phoning me that night to hang out. I said if he wanted, he could call later. So then ev walked me halfway home and gave me a hug. It was nice to have my mind taken off the whole jodie/wes saga. came home, and went to bed early, talked to cam on msn around 1215 (i woke up to the noise of him writing to me) and we decided not to hang out. Today Im going to go over to Jens and go with her to get her tattoo fixed up, and maybe go with her and aaron to the fair. We'll see how things shape up
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a difference 24 hours can make... Wes finally told his mom and Jodie about me, Jodie wasnt too happy, but whatever... Last night I finally let Wes stay over. So I had a shitty night, cause I kept on worriying, thinking that my mom was going to come down - which she doesnt usually - and find Wes in my bed. So a barely slept from 6 - 8, then got back to sleep for a few hours - loved sleeping with Wes, he was always holding me, and didnt want to let me go. Around 10, I got up, told him to just relax, adn I went upstairs to do some cleaning. I finished everything I was going to do and was just walking into the kitchen and heard my phone beep - which meant I had a message. I went downstairs and saw Wes with his head under my pillow. I said whats going on and he said my phone wouldnt stop ringing. So I listened to the message - It was Jodie, saying that she wanted to talk to her  boyfrined  Wes, that she knew he was here and that they needed to talk  now !! Needless to say I was speechless and said its for you, played the message for him said, wtf? why does it say that your her bf? Are you? he was like no, and then my phone started ringing again. It was her, i didnt answerm but she kept calling. I told Wes to answer it, that I wasnt putting up with the phone ringing nonstop. He said hed phone her on my landline, that he was just going to go to the bathroom. So while he was in the bathroom, I answered the phone, just so that she would know he was going to call her. She was like is WEs there? I said is this Jodie? Shes liek let me speak to Wes, I said again, is this Jodie? She said let me speak to Wes. I said he's in the bathroom, he will call you back on my landline, she said no, I want to speak with him now. I said no, you cant he will phone you back. she said ill wait then, i said no, hell phone you back. she said well whats the number, ill call him, i said no, hell call you, then she said dont hang up, and i had had quite enough, so i hung up, and she called back and I didnt answer. When Wes got out of the bathroom, I thrust the phone in his face and said here you deal with it, I cant take it. So he answered it, and told her to fuck off and hung up. She called back and he agreed to meet her. So he left my house, gave me a kiss and said hed call me later. About 2 min after he left I got another call, this one from Jayme - she was apologizing becasue Jodie had calle dthe night before, and Wes hadnt been home, and so she called at like 830, and at 9... Jayme finally answered at like 930, and said shed go get Wes, thinkin he was back, but then she said that he wasnt there, so jodie freaked out and said seh was coming over right away. then when jodie got there with the kids, she started going through the called id on the phone to find my number. she called every cell phone on there until she got my answering machine. like who the fuck does that? so jayme was really sorry, and seh said that they always fight like this and its one of the reasons that they arent togehter and shouldnt be, as its bad for the kids. She said Lexa was on the couch when jodie and wes were yelling on the phone and that she said mommy and daddy always fight. thats so sad!! I feel so bad for the kids. She also said that they had gotten noise complaints about Jodie na dWes fighting, but that they hadnt told Wes cause he would get mad and feel bad. Neways, she and I talked soem more, then she let me go, as they were both coming in to her place and that she would get Wes to phone when Jodie was gone. SO I got a call from Wes and he said sorry, I cant involve you in this, you shouldnt have to put up with this. I told him that if he liked me, that we could get through it together, he just said he needed time, adn that he would call me. So I said are you going to call me and he said yes so I said ok and goodbye. So pretty much I am never goning to hear from him again. This is so shitty. Grrr.... Im going to go to Jens and tell her.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today - Kinda weird. Wes phoned and said that he didnt really want to go to the movie, I said just come over and we'll figure it out, as Aaron and Jen were supposed to come with and I hadnt heard from them yet. So he came over and I had since heard from Jen and Aaron and they still wanted to go, so Wes and I started walking there. He finally told me why he didnt want to go - Jodie was taking his kids there and he didnt want her to freak out. He thought that she was taking them to the show at 7 though, so that we should be ok. So were sitting in the theatre, and hes made me paranoid, bc i dont want some chick to start blacking on me. so im checking over my shoulder, worried that Jodie will appear. She didnt, movie was pretty good. We went out the back door though, to avoid confrontation. I told him it was stupid and that he had to tell her, cause I didnt want to have to go through it nemore. I got a call from Marnie saying that apparently Chris Milne is saying him and I are dating!! Ahhh!!! He called me twice and both times I was busy with Wes, so we had never even hung out! I dont think Wes was impressed with that news either. The movie was over at 630, and the game started at 7, so Wes left and said he'd talk to me later. He was kinda grouchy and I was all wtf? but whatever. So I went home and started watching the game with my mom. During the third period, Wes phoned and apologized for beign grouchy and came over. He missed part of the first overtime, just to get over here, so that a good sign, that he would rather see me then the game. so he came over we watched the rest of the game (stupid Tampa!!!), then watched a movie. He keeps on wanting to stay over but im afraid my mom will black on me, so I keep saying no.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lake was aight, kinda rainy though, we went for a walk on the Marsh trail - didn't see nething and found ourselves a new friend - Notty the gnome. Had some drinks and the like and played some vids and watched some movies. Seen Wes quite a few times, seems really into me and Im excited that he could be a great boyfriend. Went over to his place and watched Return of the King. Hes living with his brother Dallas and Jayme right now. We went for ice cream and he has spent quite a bit of time at my place too. So far, so good!! Tomorrow we are going to go and see Shrek 2. Yay!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went out for Jens birthday yesterday. Drank at Scully's house first, then to Gravity. Was ok, but I ended up hitting on Chris Milnes friend Marty, who I was supposed to talk to about being a secretary, and is married/or has a girlfriend. So i felt like a loser. Then we went to Scully's after the bar, and walked home at 6. Celene was mad cause when i left, chris decided that he was going to walk a couple of blocks with me, and so he left with me, instead of being with her. so she phoned me and i told her that he had just left me and was walking back to the party. i guess he mustve ended up going home, casue he never showed back up there. Then today has been pretty crappy. I felt like crap all day and ive been grouchy. i skinned my knee and broke some nails. we were supposed to go to houstons 2nite, but everyone bailed, which made me happy cause i didnt really wanna go. Then, Jodie phoned me up, asking if id talked to wes. i said no, and she asked me a few more times and i said no. she thanked me for beign honest and said that they are moving back in toghter, and that she is paranoid, cause he was supposed to be home from golfing and he still wasnt there. i told her that i was pretending that id never met wes, that he didnt exist. she said that she was apologizing for the whole situation and that i was caught up in it. and that she knows what i look like and that if she ever saw me out, she would be nice, that she has nothing against me, and neither does wes. hopefully amy feels the same... neways, going to go to sleep and then to the lake tomorrow for fathers day... job interview on monday, hopefully will go awesome and then i wont be looking for any more jobs... yay!!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was not too bad... woke up in the middle of the night casue i ripped my nose ring out again, and this time i sure felt it. i found it though and put it back in. then just lazed around for most of the day, applied for a job at westman communications group, then went to jens so that i could go with her to get her tattoo touched up. She ended up getting her nose ring changed out and they gave her shit for not ever taking it out before to clean it. Then went to pizza express and had lasagna which wasnt very yummy. got home and then talked to marnie for a bit then cam called me up and asked if i wanted to go see a movie. we went and saw chronicles of riddick, which was aight, but you can tell they want to do another movie in the series, bc the ending was a little weird, but whatever. cam told me that he found out danielle was pregnant, and that she is getting an abortion. not good, poor girl. he also told me that rose has a new bf, so i guess shes out of the picture. him and reece and soem other buddies are going to gravity on friday so ill probably see them again then. going to bed now, ill keep you posted...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate Tuesdays!!! I phoned Wes's this morning because he never phoned me back yesterday... Jodie answered. She asked if there was a message and i said no, id call back later. she asked who it was and i said lisa. she said oh... ok i will tell him you called. then she phoned back like 5 min later and asked whats going on. i said we were dating (even though friday wes said he was my bf), and i said why... she said that she is wes girlfriend and that they have never broke up!!! I was like thats not what i heard and was told... then she proceeded to ask me questions about our relationship and i was totally honest with her... she was like thats it, and you can have him. then she called back later and said that she still wants to be with wes and that he doesnt want to have nething to do with me. i was like whatever, as he lied to me and i said the only thing i wanted was to talk to him cause i wanted to know why he brought me into the situation and why he got his family to lie to me. it fuckin pissed me off!!! she then started to get mad and said that if they break up and he is with me that i would never see the kids and that he wouldnt see them if i was around, and i was all like wtf? so there it goes again. Then went over to jens to talk and fill her in on the new developments. and jeff comes along, pissing me off. we all ended up going to see day after tomorrow, and we were standing in line behind some guys jen knew and one was really cute. i told her later that she shouldve told him to go to the bar on fri or sat for her bday, but she didnt. oh well the movie was aight. then marnie called, and i told her what went down and she asked if i had confirmed with wes what jodie had said. i said no, but that he hadnt phoned me, so to me thats an admission of guilt. shed better not have lied thoguh or ill be really pissed off. ttyl ps boys suck!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to the Saloon Sat night, it was okay, ran into Amy again, ended up drinking a mickey of Amaretto, and only spent $8. There was a really hot cop... yummy!! WEnt through mcdonalds afterwards and got me a mcchicken, which wasnt well liked in my stomach, so i went right to bed as soon as i got home. i was happy that Wes had wanted a big glass of water that morning because i sure needed some water and didnt want to get up. Then Sunday didnt do too much all day, Wes called in the evening and Jill drove me up to his moms. Met his little sister and Amy an d Brian were there with Dustin. They left, and Wes and I ended up having sex for like 3 hours. it was interesting to say the least. I ended up losing my nosering somewhere in the process - i think my hair got caught in it, and i pulled it out. we searched everywhere for it, but never found it. i ended up having to put a hoop in it from my ear until i can get back to warlock to get another one. stupid lisa... so im going to warlock at 1 when it opens to get a new ring... ttyl
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I finally got a job!! I had received a call from Giselle at Behlens on Tues, asking if I was still interested in working there, and if I wanted to do a phone interview on Wed. I said sure, and then on Wed afternoon, she left me a message asking if I could come in there for a interview. So, I did. She was really nice and really seemed to like me!! I did a data entry test, which was pretty easy and then found out this morning I had the job and will start on Monday!! Last night, I was grouchy, and Jen wanted me to go out and go over to Scully's. I didnt want to and then around 10, I figured why not? So I got mom to drive me over to Scully's, where everyone was plastered. Jeff phoned and said there was no lineup at 12, so Jen and I decided to go out, hey it would be free... so we went, and at first we didnt know anyone, and then we saw piggy!!! He said he hadnt been out since we saw him Easter weekend, but he cant come out for my bday thing on the 3rd... and then next thing I know I see something blond flying at me, it was Amy giving me a huge hug, so I guess that answers the questions about whether shell be nice to me. so we hung out with her and her friends, and went upstairs. Larry and Dave were there. Jen works with Dave and Larry is Bobby-Jos ex, and Jens friend. So we hung around with Dave too the rest of the night. Hes a hottie and single... yeah i might have a crush :) He knows carey gould though, and is standing up for mike blacks wedding on the 3rd. So hell definatly be at the bar on the 3rd! yay!!! So after the bar, Jen decided to go back to scullys, and dave and I went to bp to wait for larry, and to get something to eat. We walked to his house and he showed me his pool, which i was excitede about, as i want to go swimming lots this year and he gave me a ride home and a kiss!! :):) But stupid me didnt give him my phone number, although he technically has it, as he phoned my cell for me so that i could find it in my purse. Well see, but he definatly seems like a great guy, so heres hoping ill see more of him. Oh yeah, and were almost for surely moving to Durum Place, Aug 1st, Im excited!! So this weekend Im painting up a storm. and maybe going to celebrate my new job, by going for supper or something!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, my birthday bash at Houston's didnt goat all how I planned... Jen was too sick from partying Friday night that she had to go and get her stomach pumped, so she didnt come, Amy didnt show up, Jeff and Jay were being fuckers, Gavin didnt show, Cam and Reece showed up but were too fucked to doanything but sit there, and they didnt show up until 1, and then there was Dave... He came in, I went over said hi, introduced Marnie, and then he was like Ill see you later, and took off. Not impressed at being blown off by him, considering how he treated me everyothertime we were together. Fuck him. I think he took Chera back to his hotel room and screwed her, so screw him. As part of Jens apology for fucking up my bday plans, she is going to bitch him out. So all said, I had the shittiest bday ever. Friday night was ok though. I decided to go over to Scully's. Aaron phoned Dave to come over, which he did. He hung out with me all night and we made out quite a bit. We all went to the decker, then went back to scullys. so scary guys showed up, guys that dave was calling pedophiles, and they creeped me out cause they were watching me dance and trying to dance with me. ick. dave and i left at 430 and he took me home, because he had mikes wedding. jen phoned me at 9 in the morning - at which time she was fine - whatever- telling me that scully and his brother dave got into a fist fight and the cops came and threw them in the drunk tank. scullys are cut up and jamies bruised from trying to break it up. so im glad that we werent there, cause dave hubbard probably wouldve tried to fight dave horkey before his brother. so that was my weekend. jobs going good... more later
     
    
</post>


</Blog>