<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, well, well.  Now the summer of sin really is turning out quit as expected.  A guppy in question has backslided a bit in his "vow."  Hmmm, I wonder which guppy that is?  Another guppy is doing his damndest to finish every drop of JD out there.  Another prediction fulfilled.  Senor Jurado though is embracing his roots and not working as previously expected.  A nice twist I must say.  Just remember, when American dollars run out, businesses will not accept pesos or centavos or any other forms of payment.  Sorry sir, "favors" will not get you 2 chalupas and a soda at Taco Bell.  Keep it up men!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Al's birthday is coming up on Thursday, July 1st and Gerrit's is on August 6th.  Hmmm, I wonder which one will be more decadent?  Could we have a drink off?  Somebody might get served.  It's Jack Daniels vs. Wild Turkey in the championship match.  Good luck fellas and remember, I'll be the one with the camera while you're praying to the porcelein gods.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry friends and family, i've been slacking as of late on posting new info.  My hard drive decided to go all nutty on me.  Low and behold, Computer Man (aka Joe) came to the rescue and saved my computer.  Many thanks go to Mr. Scoffinger. Pity that the man isn't using these valuable skills more.  Just a thought.  Much has gone on since the last post.  I'll try to parcel it out as to not overwhelm anyone.  So, here's a starter:  As rumour has it, a certain Filipino bartender we all know and love is going to be going to the river with a certain young Monrovia police officer.  Now, I don't know nothing about nothing, but word on the street says that perhaps a marriage proposal is in the works.  We shall wait and see.  Oh, imagine the children....what a site that will be......
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello friends.  An interesting idea's been proposed from the Sensei himself.  Luke suggested creating a Guppy fight team, with shirts and everything.  If we could come up with a cool logo or somethings, perhaps we could create something cool to wear.  That's step one.  The second step, and surprisingly a big one, we have to learn how to fight! Now of course Luke and Edgar are way ahead of the curve, but it's time for the rest of us to step it up and start learning the goods.  Joe and I are gonna be at class on Saturday.  Gerrit is talking about returning.  Ruben's got the whole kickboxing thing working in Pasadena.  Adrian and Al....it's time to decide.  Are you with us?  Come on buddies...come on buddies....
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ladies and gentlemen, children of all ages....I am pleased to say that a miracle has happened in our lifetime.  Yes folks, that's right...Joe didn't flake on something!  Hold the phone and put the children to bed, Joe kept his word.  He actually went Luke's class like he said he would...and on time to boot!  Is this the new Joe we're seeing?  One could only dream.  Next up...Al  Keep it up Guppies...you're doing great!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today is movie day for the old Guppy Bowl posse.  Vince Vaughn, Ben Stiller, and "a little bit of throw-up in my mouth," should make a pretty nice combo, wouldn't you say?  Let's see if the whole group actually makes it out today.  Hopefully nobody has to "go running," or "pick up his sister," or "do this thing."  Hopefully everyone's cell phone is functional and doesn't go to their mailbox after two and a half rings.  Hopefully everyone actually has there cell phones and doesn't "forget" them, even though they go nowhere without them.  See a trend here?  Anyway, the movie should be dope, especially if everyone heads on out.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As the summer begins, many questions loom in the minds of the collective Guppies.  1.) Will Gerrit finally falter this summer in his vow of celebacy?  Will the whiley ways of Ms. Tanya Ferguson corrupt the ever so strong will of Mr. Kovach?  Or will a dark horse come in from the flank and win over the "heart" of Gerrit?  Only time will tell.  2.) Will Al consume every last drop of Jack Daniels that he can find?  All signs are pointing to yes, an emphatic yes.  Will Al be arrested for public drunkeness in Huntington Beach?  Will Al propose to Kevin?  Will Al drink away ALL of his money this summer, or will he actually have enough to move out by year's end?  3.)  Will Edgar return the oh-so-enticing restaurant business?  Will the professor lower himself enough to return to, say, Coco's Bakery Restaurant?  Edgar, i'm sure Farzana, Manny and Mike would love to have you back, selling food items that we don't have.  Remember the fun of going back to a table four times on the same visit to tell them we were out of stuff?  Remember that......oh the memories.   ***More questions to come.......*****
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys.  This is my first post on the ol' guppy world blog, so I thought it'd be only appropriate to respond to Joe's haircut jibe.  Joe, people tend to flock to their own kind, so it's almost like the Salmon swimming up stream, you going to a gay hairdresser.  Just one question....did he actually use "shaving lotion" when he trimmed you up, or did he use the "house special?"
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys, dont know if you heard yet but Luke and I's complex caught on fire early sinday mornig. Apparently 36 units were destroyed and parts of the third floor collapsed onto the second and over 100 people were left homeless. Dont worry about me and luke we are currently staying at my sisters house until we can get back in. Im hoping to&nbsp;be back in monday night with the&nbsp; comfort of my own toilet. If&nbsp;any of you feel like making a donation to either of us it would be appreciated. Please call. We will be willing to take anything, even lisa.&nbsp;Anyway guys, ill talk to you later. &nbsp; Also, If either of you are not gonna make it to class anymnore, please let luke know, the not callin, not showing&nbsp;has really&nbsp;built on him. Just letting you guys know. Looks like we have another pirhana recruit! &nbsp; G-Unit&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys....  Sorry I've been Missing In Action.  I've been extremely busy at work, where I'm now training to be a bartender.  Open invitation to anyone who wants to come in and see me craft a Strawberry Lemonade or Pepsi on the Rocks!  I haven't talked to anyone in a while, except Gerrit, who came in yesterday afternoon to say hi.  Hope everyone is doing well.  Gerrit- We will roll, soon! Luke- Sensei, Sifu, Master- I will be back on Saturday, my next day off Edgar - Yo quiero Taco Bell Joe - I have a Kiwi Drink with your name on it Al - Jack Daniels spells T-R-O-U-B-L-E.  And p.s., knowing a police officer doesn't mean your above the law. Adrian - Where are you little buddy? Ruben - Read any good magazines lately?  Anwyay....I hope to see you all soon  The Irish Bomber aka Applebee's Newest Drink Slinger, Danny 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First and foremost, weve got Lisa birthday comin up on July 24th people. Lets show her how to celebrate guppy style. Now, im telling everyone a month early. That means Joe and AL listen up. I wanted to decide what to do early so flaking will not be tolerated! Let us not forget Joes mishap of last year where he chose filly and courtney over his homie. This may also be the summer of redemption. Im letting everyone know, A MONTH IN ADVANCE, that i would love to do this thing on august 4th. Yes august 4th so Lisa can join us. Newport again calls us as i would love the GuppyZ to do some kayaking which means early moning. Then after another deep sea adventure, well end the night at hooters or something. So this is mainly for Al and Joe to see that you have a months heads up cause id really love for you guys to be there. So again, Wednesday august 4th. Edgar, lets me and you show lisa how we celebrate birthdays!!!!!!! Luke if theres a way to finagle a day off that would be sweet. If not we can hang on friday the 6th.  G-Unit
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      With all of the talk about rebel cells within the group, we all should take account what lessons we learned form theat great movie "You Got Served." Two groups were formed and tried to take on the world, but only with each other were they strong!!! It seems this group may be heading to that path. All i have to say is practive your dance moves cause ITS ON!!!! If only Mr. Rad were here to fix everyting for us.  Also, on another note, it seems that not only does al flake because he stays up until the wee hours of the morning, but it seems that maybe were just not fun enough for him. A conversation was overheard today with Tim about going to vegas saturday to sunday, and Al was all for it right away!!!! So when the Gupps wanna hang out, its if he feels like it, but when a friend wants to go to vegas you cant stop him. Is it us Al????
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys....  Been a little while between my posts.  We got the ol' matinee this afternoon with Will Ferrell's Anchorman.  Can't wait, it should be hilarious.  I wonder whose turn it is to buy Rubio's?  Maybe I'll shine up my wooden nickle and splurge this time.  Luke's class also is coming up tomorrow morning.  We'll see if Joe comes back with a vengeance or sits on the DL again with Montezuma's Revenge.  I know I'm waiting at the edge of my seat.  Ok guys, that's all for now.  And by the way, and rebel factions within the Guppies WILL be dealt with accordingly.  Certain Guppy members need to realize that they're not Che Guevara or Pancho Villa or any other radical leader.  Some people need to just shut up and trim the edges and pluck the fruit, metaphorically speaking.  So, quash those feelings gentlemen and deal with it.  I believe "Flaking" is stated on you contracts on page one along with getting drunk and inappropriately touching one's sister.  Read your contracts!  Later!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well the day started off as usual. The guys were to get together at 9 AM and take off to newport for some kayaking fun. Well it was answering machines all morning as edgar and gerrit got flaked on again. Well they missed out. A group of venomous man eating sharks that spit bees attacked carrie! Who should come to the rescue but edgar jurado. As edgar grappled and ripped his way through many a shark, gerrit quicky used his chemical knowledge and combined gum, saltwater, and beer ala macgyver to creat a smokescreen and get him outta there. The ocean was now clear again.  OK, that may or may not happened, but the machines have gotta stop! Danny is off the hook due to school responsibilites which he forgot to mention the day before. Al and joe need to not commit to something then flake out. Although it is expected, how late do you guys have to stay up! Al and Joe up late.......Hmmmmmmmmm I wonder......  G-Unit
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well gupps, we are about halfway through our summer of sin and all i can say is so far so good. We all know that last summer was characterized by late nights at dennys and a lot of flaking of certain members, and the enlightening that drinking syrup is so unhealthy. Well this year promised much more with new addition lisa and the reintroduction of Al to the gang. This seems to be al's summer of sin more than anyones due to the shortage of jack daniels in the san gabriel valley! Joe looked as if he was gonna committ to some grapplin then came up with a case of "the runs" that seemed to have all gone away now. Sr. crippler (edgar) may have a hairline fracture in his forearm area, from what may i ask? The Forearm is used for many a task, and i still have paris so rest up my friend. Keep it up guppyz. We all know of certain members slip ups but has another guppy slipped? A certain birthday boy was supposed to go with parents to dinner, but did he really????? Another shout out to guppy member luke who has on more than one occasion sprung for a good meal and has made several apperances this summer. Also, adrian has also made several apperances from the hard work of orange selling (JK dude). So props to the crew for a great summer so far. Lets keep it goin this friday with a matinee viewing of Anchorman, and a newport trip on wednesday to do some gool ol kayacking. Lisa better wear a 2 piece!  On another note, we have regained contact with minnow liz voshall. Liz has been on hiatus in australia doin good person work. She has returned to the area, well i guess the united states is the area, but will be spending probably the rest of the summer in Maine. Ya i dont know whats in maine either. Anyway, she says whats up to everyone and still has sweet sweet dreams of joes sweet touch........  --Phantom Hands (g-Unit)
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Whats up boys of summer. Well summer 2004 is winding down and things have been gettin interesting. It seems that Al now has a new drinking hole, so feel free to call him trifecta, and YES Al, it is a dive bar. Wednesday is the celebatory day for the birth of G-Unit, all eyes will be mainly on Al and Joe. Can they actually be up and somewhere before noon? We shall see. Its all about guppy bonding in newport harbor and capping it off most likley at the yardhouse in pasadena. Also, there are new developments surrounding the possible guppy house. The target date seems to be january 2005. Can Joe, Al, Danny and Gerrit co-exist under the same household? Looks like it would be a great reality show. No big panties allowed! Stay tuned for updates and future developments, but until then lets all get together and have some fun wednesday with the whole crew, Danny, Al, Joe, Adrian, Ruben, Veronica, Edgar, Me, and of course Luke and Lisa. Lookin forward to some good ol scratchin and burping with the guys and lets see who tosses his cookies first, Gerrit or Al?Later, G-Unit 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>