<Blog>

<date>30,Juni,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Excuse me for living, don't mind if I do! I hope all is forgiven, you know I'd do the same for you. If it's true what they say, someone must pay. I'll bear my share of the pain, but I won't take all the blame, if it's all the same to you. I used to like to choose my poison, but now I wouldn't dare make a choice between the water and whatever's in the air. I'd like the buy the world an aspirin and slip it in their coke. If it'd do any good, I'd like to tell the world a joke. LIGHTEN UP EVERYONE. The weather's not that bad, and even if we can't use Skow field, we can still have fun!!!!!! >:|
     
    
</post>

<date>26,Juni,2004</date>
<post>

     
      “My friend must be a bird,  Because it flies!  Mortal my friend must be, Because it dies! Ah, curious friend, Thou puzzelst me.”  Am I delusional enough to have imagined that these people were ignoring me? Am I delusional enough to have imagined this so well that I did not realize until last night that I was the one ignoring them? I really do not  think so, but that is basically what happened. All this week, I have had this idea in my head that a few of my friends do not want to talk to me anymore, or that there is something going on that is making them act differently around me. I still do not know what is going on, but now I am almost completely sure that no one was ignoring me, and that I was imagining that. Of course, if that is possible, then is it not also possible that I have been imagining everything?   “For each ecstatic instant,  We must an anguish pay In keen and quivering ratio To the ecstasy. For each beloved hour Sharp pittances of years, Bitter contested farthings, And coffers heaped with tears.”  “If I can stop one heart from breaking, I shall not live in vain.  If I can ease one life the aching, Or cool one pain, Or help one fainting robin Unto his nest again, I shall not live in vain.”  “Much madness is divinest sense,  To a discerning eye; Much sense the starkest madness.  ‘T is the majority in this, as all, prevails. Assent, and you are sane;” Demur,- and you’re straightaway dangerous, And handled with a chain."  
     
    
</post>

<date>22,Juni,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In her book, "Reading Lolita in Tehran," Azar Nafisi uses an interesting phrase..."Gnostic Turpitude." She later goes on to describe that the crime of gnostic turpitude as committed by Cinncinatus C. was punished by death. Seems pretty harsh when you consider that all he was guilty of was wanting a little privacy in his life, wanting time to himself without the government standing over his shoulder and dictating his every word and movement. Everyone is guilty of this to some extent, but what do you do if a friend is hiding some very important things from you? I mean, no one's going to die over this, but I guess what I'm trying to say is that you don't need to keep secrets about me. If there's something on your mind that you want to say, it's alright, I'm not going to get mad at anyone for sharing their opinions. Thanks for listening, if you did. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,Juni,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "I've been swimming in a sea of anarchy, I've been living on coffee and nicotine and I've been wondering if all the things I've seen were ever rea-were ever really happening."  "Politicians on a mission, build them up, bring them down for the good of the "system," well we don't like the way you live your life and I got one thing I must express: we try our criminals in the press, justice is a fading light."  "Mary, Mary, quite contrary close the door now it's too scary, you might see something you wish you hadn't seen."    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,Juni,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Mockingbirds don't do one thing but make music for us to enjoy. They don't eat up people's gardens, don't nest in corncribs, they don't do one thing but sing their hearts out for us. That's why it's a sin to kill a mockingbird."  Yet people still go after the mockingbird, rather than shooting down the bluejay. Why is that? Is it perhaps because they know the mockingbird won't be as quick to fight back? I think so. Just wait, though. If you push that poor innocent little bird hard enough, he'll do something about it, and it'll more'n likely be something that you're not ready for. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,Juni,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's hard to lose a friend because of a mistake you made, and then turn around and make the same mistake with someone else. "Hear the sound of my tears, falling down and falling down like the rain, oh that sound, that lonely sound." 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,Juni,2004</date>
<post>

     
      After the blackbird sings, what is left for me? That's exactly what I'm going to figure out, with your help. A friend of mine is a very talented writer, and it was his blog that inspired me to "remodel" mine the way I have. I'd like to be able to write about important things, but it's easier done than said. I've never really been good at expressing my feelings, whether because I just didn't want to share them, or because I didn't think that anyone would care or understand. Anyway, I'm going to try harder this time around and hopefully this will make for a more interesting read than Die Kartoffeln. :P
     
    
</post>

<date>06,Juli,2004</date>
<post>

     
      HEY! It's been a while since I've written anything up here, so I'll bring you up to date on all that's been happening. As it turns out, I am keeping the kitten, who is now officially named Marlena. [pronounced MAR-LAY-NUH  for those of you who do not know the song.] The day my dad found her was fun. Sean, Chloe, Angela, Andy, Austin, Alex, Lizz and I walked around the woodlands and posted "found kitten" signs...but that got boring so we ditched the signs and started "lizard hunting." That was pretty fun, Andy caught a very interesting lizard that was dark brownish and a little bit goldish, and he kept that for almost the entire time we were out. We caught a few of those little green ones too, and someone-not saying any names-accidentally let one of them loose in Chik-Fil-A!!!! That was crazy. After that, it started raining... Since then we haven't done much except eat popsicles, swim, play homerun derby [Congratulations to Andy who beat me yesterday :) *or maybe the day before.......*] OH and of course there was movie night at Anthony's house. REALLY fun, we watched the Count of Monte Cristo. Der Film war sehr spannend! Anyway, Jaci's been hanging out at my house almost every day-VERY fun, lol ABS and BEES! And today...today Lizz, Andy, and Sean woke me up! They were standing on my driveway throwing tennis balls at my window and talking very loudly. I just went back to sleep, though. ;) hehe. Oh, and I've been missing Justin because even though he's back from his cruise, I still haven't seen him yet! He's coming over on Thursday, though, so it's all good!!! Love you Justin! Ooooooooh and more good news-Timmy's moving back and coming to visit from Alaska next week!!!!!!!! Alex is coming up from Trinidad either tomorrow or Thursday, and THE SKOWS ARE COMING ON THURSDAY! Yay!!! Then I get to see Justin again on Saturday *huge smile* and my very cool cousin Sarah is coming to visit on Sunday, and she's staying for a week!! And after that, Sarah, Lizz, and I are going on a three-week vacation to Missouri and Arkansas-possibly Oklahoma-to visit family. I can't wait!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!      Ok so now that you've been filled in on everything going on here, leave a comment!   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,Juli,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Anyone want a cat? No, great! I get to keep her! (I wish)   This morning, my dad found a kitten over near Bush Elementary. She's calico, with white paws that look like socks, huge ears, and no tail. :) Very cute. I really, really wish I could keep her because she's so sweet and seems to really like me and like my house (tons of places to explore and get stuck in.) Unfortunately, my sweet kitty Nutmeg doesn't really like having the kitten around, although both of my dogs seem to have already adopted her. I'd really really like to find a nice home for Marlena (Marley) but so far no one's been able to take her. :( I will keep her if I have to, but I don't want to make the cat I have now mad. Anyway, besides having a new kitten in my house for a while, lots of interesting things have happened today. The weather's been absolutely crazy. For the entire time that Lizz, Chloe, Angela, Andy, Austin, Alex, Sean and I were outside walking all over the Woodlands and putting up "Found Kitten" posters, it was VERY hot and humid. Basically terrible. As soon as we got home, though, it started pouring. We ran around in the rain for a few minutes, and then some of us went inside to put our swimsuits on so we wouldn't ruin our clothes out in the rain. We came back out to sunshine just like it had been before-and no rain at all. :( A little disappointing, but another good thing happened! Anthony and I finished the Tolle Katze!! (the "go-cart" that almost never was....and still isn't quite.) I pulled Anthony around the neighborhood for the first run, and then he pulled me on it. I flew off into somebody's yard, so then it was Lizz's turn, and then Andy's. It was VERY fun. Oh yeah, great fun!!   Call me about the cat if you want her and can give her a good home.   :)
     
    
</post>



</Blog>