<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is my second time writing and i think i am getting the hang of it. i couldn't update yesterday cuz i was out the whole day. let me brief you in to what had happend: i wanted to spend the whole day at home, lazing around while playing my PS2. but it just so happend that i had to go to this class "picnic" at the beach. why did i put "   " you ask?? well, it didin't felt like a picnic nor even look like one!! i had to meet 2 of my other friends first at the bus interchange. after we met, we set off on our most exciting and the most fun journey we ever had!! (ya right!!) then we took a 30 min bus ride. after that, we walk through an underpass and we reach the beach. then we ask for direction from a fat officer who works there at the beach as a patroler. he was riding a golf cart. we ask him for direction where the mcdonalds were, which was the meeting point for the "picnic". he said it was that side (the right side). so we took his advise as we thought he ws a dedicated, honourable, and honest officer. but like always, the person that you think is the person you can trust, is the person you shouldn't trust. we walk and walk and walk all the way to the other side; but the macdonalds wasn't there!! so do you know what that means?? the officer had given the wrong directions for crying out loud!!! so we took a taxi. fork out 5 bucks and reach the mcdonalds. to our surprise, only 13 people came. 13!! 13!! only 13 freaking people came! out of 40, only 13 came!(including me and the other two guys i had came with)i shouldn't had went. but i already made a promise to the "captain" of that party. so we sat at the beach. sat on newspapers. a quater of the food had already been eaten by the early comers. what a picnic!! so there it was: the sun, the sand, the wind and the party which i don't know why on earth i had gone to! after the party, we went home. we wanted to ride a bus because it was cheap and it was the only transport home (unless you want to fork out 8 bucks for a taxi ride!!) after i reach home, i lie down my body on my bed, knowing that my misery had ended. but!!! my dad, ask me to go to this wedding wif him. i tried to find an excuse but to no avail. the wedding was at night. strange huh?? a malay wedding at night?? but it wasn't a malay wedding. as you people know, i'm an arab; a good looking male arab!!(just kidding!! But not about the male part!! just kidding about the good looking part!!) so we went there riding my dads motorcycle. reach there; ate, saw all my cousins, relatives, aunts and uncles, grand-daddies and grand-mamas!! all arabs, BUT!!! all not as good-looking like you know who!!hahaha! please ignore when i say that sort of stuff!! its the other bad but good-looking side of me trying to get out off this nice and good-looking side of me! its hard to be me! handsome, sexy, cool, macho and on and on and...aiya!! what a hard life!!! (just kidding!!) and so i spend 3 hours there, messing with my phone and my cousins. and so night went, dull and dry. dull as the word dull itself and dry as the sahara desert with hamizan doing the funky chicken dance!!( for those who don't know him, he's hot!wow!) finally! it ended with a guy giving a long speech (which till now i have know idea what he was talking about!!) then i went home; home bitter home. as bitter as it was, it was till my home! so it ended there after i watch braveheart on the tele. ( that movie rocks!! but the ending was sad!! like wanted to cry! BUT! i did not! so don't come up to me saying that i cried watching a movie showing a bunch of guys wearing skirts!)-kilts; wore by scottish men which looks like a chequred skirt- so that day ended there after i closed my eyes. so there you have it; just another day in my life. till next time...  ~Peace Out~    Crash
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm...what to write. This is my first blog posting and I don't know what to write. I thought that it was kinda fun writing a blog when i heard it from a couple of my friends. I read theirs and it was kinda neat! Now, I wish I didn't met them in the first place cuz now I'm stuck here with nothing or what so ever to write about. Me- what about me?? I dun noe what to write about me. There isn't anything interesting about me. I’m a boring person. There isn’t any good about me except for my school shoes(trust me, they aren’t a pretty sight!!) I’m not the richest of guys nor the most handsome of guys (that’s for sure) sexy? Maybe, just maybe! (just kidding!) Smart? Not so. But I can’t count to ten! Talented; beats me! Dun noe what I am good at. If I have given u this blog page website, it’s for sure that u noe me quite well. But if u dun, I have nothing further to say. There’s a lot of people that dislike me, if you are one of them, thanx! Thanx for making my life an exciting one. Cuz if there weren’t any person who hates me, then my life will be as dumb and boring as yours!  Myself. What about myself?? . I dun like talking about myself. I hate this sort of things where you have to describe yourself. It stinks! If there’s one word to describe myself, u noe what it is?? Well, I definitely noe what it is. No lah, just kidding. I dun noe what the word it. Juz writing all this juz so it will fill up this part of the writing column. I live a simple life. The simple of the most simplest. I dun own neither a condo nor a small cute little pony in my backyard (I don’t even have a backyard!). I am the usual suspect. I have everything what the everyday person has. Nothing fancy. Just the things I require. Life- Forest Gump says that life’s like a box of chocolate, you never know what you’ll get. Well, don’t listen to a single word he said. He is a moron! Life’s not like a box of chocolate if you noe what I mean. For those who don’t, let me tell you what it is. Honestly, I dun have a dam clue. Juz writing any sort of crap that comes into my mind juz so that my blog will be 5 sentences longer! (smart aren’t I??) Family- Well, I dun noe. Sometimes their fun, most of the time their boring. Friends- its juz another 6 letter word. Eh, wait a tick, another 7 letter word. Sorry, I stink at maths! I have a lot of friends, but I only trust 2 or 3. Others are all the same; Hypocrites. When you need them at the most crucial time, they aren’t around. Busy with their  new hip, cool  friends. They forget about you by then. Being oblivious to the fact that you were the person that had stuck by their side when they needed the help. Then when their new friends ditch them at the reception, they’ll come crawling back to you like a stray puppy asking for help and trying to make it seem as though they had done nothing to you. That is what always happened to me. Maybe you dun. If you dun, then all the best with your friendship in the futre. School- The only thing that separates me from the word fun. But sometimes it can be fun. The only thing good about school is to meet my friends. Other then that, teachers screaming their hearts out at me doesn’t create any sense of fun for me. Well, that’s life! No matter how much you hate it, you still have to go through it. Just move with the flow. Like they always say: if you can’t beat them, join them and create some serious havoc while you’re at it!( now where on earth I heard that from??) Whoah!! My, my, my. I have really written a lot! Never thought I would write this much! Hmm… u noe what? This is kinda fun! writing stuff that doesn’t make sense for half an hour is rather fun!! To the person who gave me that idea to write a blog, Thanx! K lah, that’s all I want to say. Till next time. Hope I dun forget my password and the address to this webby!!  ~Peace out!~      Crash 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok, it has been a very long time since i have updated my blog. reason: my computer was usually used by my siblings and i am very occupied with schoolwork, frenz, Euro 2004 and house chores. ok, this is a recap of anything exciting or new which had happend to me for the past few weeks: my school holiday was boring. filled with boredom, boredom and more boredom. how do u describe this sort of boredom?? hmm...ya! the word best describe this sort of boredom is BORING!!. did not do aynthing much. just t.v, homework, going out and sleep. (not to mention watching the Euro 2004!!) i went to K.L. it was kinda fun. it was suppose to be a family thing but my sis had to get ready for her first day teaching and my bro had to go to work. so it was only me, my mum and my dad. my mum wasn't really into travelling. she was reluctant to go. i think my dad was also reluctant. maybe because the fact that it was just a few days before work and school reopens or maybe because of the fact that the whole family wasn't going. i have no idea. but in the end we went. went shopping, theme park, went up the petronas tower and more shopping!!most of the time my mum does all of the shopping BUT like always, i have to tag a long. luckily now i have my own freedom. i don't always have to hold her hands like when i was 5 or 6. i can go somewhere else while she's scampering among the mountains of clothes. i remembered when i was around 6 i think. i was following my mum shopping at the nearby mall. it was kinda tiring but it was all worth it when i could go to the toy's department.(although my mum doesn't allow me to buy anything) that was the best part about going shopping. BUT! like always, if theres the best part, there must be always be the bad part. the worst is yet to come!! when i have already indulge myself on the sight of all the toys, my mum will grab my hand and walk to this area. at first, i thought that my mum was buying a new blouse or a skirt. but then, when i walk around this shelf, when i got the first glimpse of it, i got the shock of my life! you know what it was?? the worst thing that can happend to a 6 year old kid. UNDERWEAR!! lots and lots of them! she had taken me to the ladies underwear section! it was like 'what the hell am i doing here??' dam!can't a 6 year boy get some space around here?? it was like stepping into no-man's land. a smaller version of the bermuda triangle. the last place a 6 year old kid wants to go. so i have entered the so called 'AREA 51'.so i tag along with my mum as i entered Area 51. so there it was; me, my mum and lots and lots of underwear. it was hanging everywhere! here, there, everywhere, underwear!! red colur, blue colur, black colour... i never knew that there were so many colours in entire life! i always try not to look at any one of them. i close my eyes. sometimes there will be some ladies there buying them(the undies). they will stare at me for a few seconds. my god! shame! so shameful! i was facing death head-on. i lost my honour, pride and dignity. so from then onwards, i went there like once a week for the next few years. it as like my fourth house. those were the days... hahaha. when it think back of what had happend, its kinda funny. hahaha. ok then. thats all for today. til next time...   ~Peace Out~    Crash
     

    
</post>


</Blog>