<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, now I know I shouldn't have done "all those drugs" back in the '70s!  I inadvertently typed in the wrong user name on the "Dashboard," and ended up at an old blog I created in November of '02 (  Guy Librarian  no less!)...and had completely forgotten about! I was momentarily befuddled and exclaimed (to no one in particular), "Hey! There's another Librarian with my name!"   I felt a little like  urlLink Alice just after she emerged from the Rabbit Hole  or after  urlLink Lucy has stepped through the back of the Wardrobe  and surprised Mr. Tumnus hurrying home.  And then, after looking squint and wary-eyed at the monitor, "Oh. Wait. That's me!!"      ;)  More Gingko Biloba, please! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Seven years in one branch is a long time. Seven years in one branch is long enough to leave your mark. The past seven years at Widener Branch have seen the building go from a dark, cluttered, unfriendly place to a place of more open space, an updated collection, a staff willing and ready to help. Programming has gone from maybe one or two programs per quarter to four or five programs a month; variety of programs has gone from almost exclusively african-american children's events to a whole range of children, teen, and adult programs in any number of cultures (african-american, to be sure, but also asian, latino, and european flavored).  And, surely the acme of the past seven years: moving into a brand-new, state-of-the-art work-of-art library this coming November.  But now an opportunity has come: a chance to be department head in the children's department at a regional library; the chance to work with two to four colleagues, to have a much bigger programming budget, to work in a lovely children's room, to pick and choose the books for the collection; the chance to focus more on professionalism.  The timing of all this is what makes this less of a clear-cut choice. Some would say,"of course, you should move on. The department head job is a step-up, it definitely moves your career along." Some would say,"With all the effort and work you've put in over the last seven years, you've earned the privilege of enjoying the new building."  So, here is the crossroads in my career. In the end, the administration will make the final decision and I'm sure I'll have an opportunity to have my say. Considering these choices will occupy a lot of my time over the next several days.   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ahhh, a quiet day in the branch. The temperature is just right (high 70s), the humidity is very low, the sun is shining bright, and there is a street festival going on about four blocks away.   A few people have come in since we've opened: a young woman with her child in a stroller; someone I used to help as a teenager. Then two young men came in, one is from Colorado visiting Philadelphia for the summer and every time I see him his greeting is "I just LOVE to read!"  And he does, too!  He especially likes Manga and Anime graphic novels and takes out 4 or 5 at a time.    Old Mr Cook is here with his chess set, waiting for someone to join him in an epic battle of wits, skill, and strategy. Dozing quietly, lines of chess moves dancing in his head.  And all these books, waiting patiently, as they always have, to be discovered just at the right time, by just the right person, right when they need that information most. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      After reading Blogs for so long (and posting once or twice), I'm taking the plunge. Also, 'cause my good friend, Vanessa, just created her own, I HAD to follow.  :)  Guess I'm a "butterfly" chaser!  More later...
     
    
</post>


</Blog>