<Blog>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am post-graduate of Fine Arts. I play guitar, sing, dance (not any more), and have written a few songs. I have not been able to find a job in that field since I graduated. I taught a dance class to some young kids for a short time for $9 an hour and it was only a few hours a week. I don't feel like giving guitar lessons or painting lessons, it just not worth the small amount of money. Some art work has sold and no telling where it will all end up. I only paint a painting when things are going really well. It's been a while. My guitar is in hock. Now that I've cheered everyone up....I got a job at a computer help desk where they train you on the job. I passed a computer test to get the job because I did take enough computer classes to know a few things. That job lasted for two years then I got married had a baby and my husband and I both ended up laved off from the same company we met in and it closed down after 9/11. No computer tech jobs in Dallas made us move to Houston where he got a job as computer tech in the school.   Ever since the Genome project began in 1990, I have wanted to go into Biotechnology and Genetic engineering. To show you the importance of the genomics research, here is the latest on the Humane Chromosome 19 just completed as of April 2004:  The DOE Joint Genome Institute (JGI) and Stanford University completed the sequencing of the 55.8 million bases of human chromosome 19, the most gene-rich of all human chromosomes. The achievement is described in the April 1, 2004, issue of Nature. Although it represents only 2% of the genome, chromosome 19 features some 1500 genes, including those responsible for controlling the repair of DNA damage caused by exposure to radiation and other environmental pollutants. Among other genes identified are those involved in such diseases as insulin-dependent diabetes, myotonic dystrophy, migraines, and familial hypercholesterolemia.  So the knowledge of these genes allows us to manipulate them by removing cancer, diabetes, and really horrible torturous genes from our species. Obviously this raises some moral questions and I really would like to here from people to see what is thought about taking our destiny into our own hands. What do you think? There is more information at http://www.ornl.gov/sci/techresources/Human_Genome/home.shtml  I am trying so hard to get a scholarship to go back to school. As fate would have it, I am glad I ended up in Houston because there is going to be a huge Biotechnology Research Park which will be my second home. Here is the information for those interested in the future of mankind: http://www.uth.tmc.edu/biotechnology/  I also like environmental issues "save the planet!" and astronomy "find another just in case!" oh and I'm crazy about plants and animals. I am a real down to earth barefoot in the wood type of city chic.   Screening Embryos for Disease: Preimplantation genetic diagnosis (PGD) is a test that screens for genetic flaws among embryos used in vitro fertilization. With PGD, DNA samples from embryos created in-vitro by the combination of a mother's egg and a father's sperm are analyzed for gene abnormalities that can cause disorders. Fertility specialists can use the results of this analysis to select only mutation-free embryos for implantation into the mother's uterus.   Before PGD, couples at higher risks for conceiving a child with a particular disorder would have to initiate the pregnancy and then undergo chorionic villus sampling in the first trimester or amniocentesis in the second trimester to test the fetus for the presence of disease. If the fetus tested positive for the disorder, the couple would be faced with the dilemma of whether or not to terminate the pregnancy. With PGD, couples are much more likely to have healthy babies; Although PGD has been practiced for years, only a few specialized centers worldwide offer this procedure.  Gene therapy: Gene therapy is a technique for correcting defective genes responsible for disease development. Researchers may use one of several approaches for correcting faulty genes: A normal gene may be inserted into a nonspecific location within the genome to replace a nonfunctional gene. This approach is most common. An abnormal gene could be swapped for a normal gene through homologous recombination. The abnormal gene could be repaired through selective reverse mutation, which returns the gene to its normal function. The regulation (the degree to which a gene is turned on or off) of a particular gene could be altered.    What do you think about these new studies? I think it’s like when everyone thought that computers were from the devil and they would take over the world, then people thought that the Y2K glitch would be the end of the world as we know it. I worked as a computer tech at the help desk that night and you guys kept me up all night! The inevitable fact is that it's going to happen whether you like it or not! You can not stop progress; you can only slow it down so get used to it. The future is here and I want to be right on top of it. I just need to take the first step and get into the first Biotechnology Program at Houston Community College, and then transfer to University of Houston for a Bachelor degree then, hopefully on to UTH for my Masters while working in the Biology Research Center. I plan to dedicate the rest of my life to the new field of Biotechnology and Genetic Engineering.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Science Forum @ www.ezboard.com 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I AM
</post>


</Blog>