<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, summer is off to a good start. Tomorrow, I am leaving for Soul Survivor until Sunday. Things have been going pretty smoothly... Me and Lindsay went shopping and I bought this AWESOME skirt and jacket and a scarf..YAY!! Kyle, Sebastian, Quinn and I went and saw The Terminal on Sunday night. The movie was horrible but Quinn and Sebastian are into each other...YAY!! I make a great matchmaker. Then last night, I spent the night at Lindsay's and helped her pack. She's moving to Hunnington Beach and she might not come to Mesa next year. *tear*. She's my best friend...I don't want to lose her... Today I babysat Emma, cut Tyler Legg's hair into a MOWHAWK!! WOOHOO!! and talked to Herbosa. I miss him so much. He's the greatest...really. He gives me butterflies in my tummy...like a little elementary school crush. Man, I miss him....
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hullo Guys! Well, I went to Graduation last night. My beloved seniors have become Big Kids that get to play on the Big Kid Playground called THE REAL WORLD. I didn't cry like I thought I would, but I'm not worried about the Class of 2004. They are stupendous people with REAL potential. They're gonna do awesomely wonderful. It was so powerful seeing them all up there. Allie Wimmer, Matt Mendez, Erin Costelloe, Angelica Sinajon, and Marc Daniels..people I idolize are finally growing up. They are are going to make a huge impact on the world just like they did in my life and my heart. I Love You All... At graduation, Ms. Hayes gave the most amazing speech on life..and related it to none other than QUILTING. In order to make your beautiful quilt (your life) you have to select a pattern to follow, pick the right fabrics (make the right decisions), and stitch it all together (these "stitches" include family, friends, etc.). And in the end, you have created a beautiful quilt.  It really made me think about my stitches. I want real good ones...that won't break. :)  Thanks for listening to incessant ramblings yet again.  Buh bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I feel like Rockin' out...Hell Yea!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sexy!! Me and Herbosa!! ;)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whaddup guys?! Well, I hope things are goin' good for y'all. LOL. I'm doing pretty good...except I think I'm getting sick..RIGHT BEFORE SUMMER!  Today was so exciting. First of all...I took my finals...SO EASY! I actually knew the crap on the Chem final and History was easy too. The rest of the day was cool...I asked Lindsay to marry me (inside joke). I helped Mrs. Brude grade papers after school with Lindsay, Adeline and Emily Cotton.  Afterwards, Luis Herbosa asked me out and I said YES. YAY. You cannot imagine my excitement. I'm all smiles... Well, other than that, my day was AWESOME. Summer is off to a great start. Valerie, Lindsay, Adeline, and I are having a movie night/slumber party at Val's house on Friday. WOOT WOOT! Hmmm, that's it.  Chow for now!  Later Days, Sexy.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    MeEeEeeEoOoOoOWwwWwW!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whaddup dogs? Well, today was very interesting. I had a pretty good school day...lots of people signed my yearbook. It made me feel loved. After school, I hung out with the buddies and went to get Boba and who should show up, but VICTOR. (Hot (?) guy I met at the carnival.) Well, the dude got my number, and showed up at my school, followed me to Boba, AND asked me if I would take him to my house. What a friggen' weirdo! So, Angel, Herbosa, Jimmy, Christina, Reesa, Robbie and Adeline stayed with me because Victor was being a furreak! I mean, he was just asting like a fuckin' retard. Well, everyone had to leave, so I called Shawn, his arc enemy, and had him come rescue me. So, he distracted Victor and me and Adeline ran and hid in Stater Bros. and ditched the poor bastard. Dude, I was fricken' scared. Thank God for Shawn and my good buddies that stayed with me. Thanks dudes.  So, I talked to Herbosa and I couldn't be more delighted. He LIKES me...he REALLY likes me. Damn...I wanted it so bad. I prayed about it, and God blessed me. I get along with him so well it's scary. Oh man... Well, things are going pretty well so I'm excited. MY FINAL SCHEDULE: Tuesday: 1st Period- History, 4th Period- Chemistry Wednesday: 2nd Period- Geometry, 5th Period- Madrigals Thursday: 6th Period- English, 3rd Period- P.E LAST DAY! After that, I'm going to Mrs. Brude's End-of-the-Year BBQ and then I'm singing at Graduation with the Mads. One final goodbye to my seniors. I couldn't be more proud. They are all going to be SO successful. They are in my thoughts and in my prayers. Class of 2004, We Love You. Congratulations.  Well, Peace Out Boy Scout. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me and Kylie, for his photo project. Man, I love this kid...&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Look, it's Tu and Me!! YAY!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Dude, this is me as a little kid. Can someone say CUTE?! Yea, I know...WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is my baby sister Emma! AwwW!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OH MY GOSH! Summer is almost here! I'm so excited, but kinda bummed. It's gonna be so fun, but my seniors are kickin' it elsewhere. They sayings are true...'you never know how much you love someone until they are gone.' I feel like I've taken advantage of all this time...GrRrR. Well, I trust that the seniors will find their way. They are too cool for high school anyway! :)  Well, things are a little rocky with Kyle and stuff. I Love Him so much..he's the best guy friends I've ever had...but he doesn't see that. I wish he would. I found the coolest quote today. I got it a long time ago, but I just found it. Ladies, listen up! 'You know, you used to be really big in my eyes, but your dick and your brain has shrunk to the size of my pinky fingernail and I cut it off and flu shed it down the toilet where it belongs.' HAHAHAHA. Oh wait, here's a better one. 'The psychic once said, if you swallowed your tongue every time you lied, it would be hanging 25 miles out of your ass--and maybe then you would get a taste of the trail of shit you leave behind for everyone else.' It's so gross, and funny, but oh so true.  Anyway, things shall get better. Hoopefully!! Hey, call me up, we'll hit the beach!  See ya on the flip side   PUNK!  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>