<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so i know this is extremely ... well, we can say ironic. or just hypocritical. let's just say i'm providing an example of what i am describing as i am describing it.   I've been reading so many blogs lately and feeling so extremely overwhelmed with stumbling through other people's jumbled ramblings, it feels like there are way too many voices intruding in my head. shut up!  i'm not crazy (debateable, of course). just the blogs don't edit. and so in that tradition, i will not edit this. hah.    (no, i am not drunk. all i had to drink tonight is water. tyler, becky, yoshie, and jasmine can all testify to that.)
      
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so after looking around the apartment, car and office for about a week (sadly resigned to my not finding my cds of photos of europe), i went to sleep and woke up knowing exactly where to look for them. got out of bed. and found them in that spot. amazing. why does that always happen? i've learned to believe it will happen every time.
      
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I picked up Jonathan Franzen's "How to be alone" from the shelf at the apartment I'm temporarily occupying. Lot's of essays about his personal life. His father's death, his unhappiness with the response his novels got, etc. etc.   I haven't gotten very far but in the middle of the essay "Why bother," as he talks about how increasingly unhappy he gets the more tv he watches, I started to wonder if he blogs. If he reads blogs. On the surface, they seem just another Internet distraction. Keeping people from interaction, face to face discussion and so on. But at the same time, I've learned more about a lot of my friends and feel more connected to some out of town friends than I have in a long time. And they don't even know I'm reading their blogs.   Maybe it's making me more alone. Maybe it's making me more connected. I say it's all in how it makes me feel... and right now, I feel more connected even though I haven't actually interacted personally with anyone today other than the checker at Circuit City. And she DID NOT SAY A WORD to me, nor I to her. I thought it was odd at the time, but then I started wondering what she was thinking and if this was some grand experiment to see how many people she can not talk to at work? And why say anything anyway? It's just a bunch of mindless pleasantries that you don't really mean. I bet she really just wanted to say, "screw you. why do you have money to buy this cd and dvd when you you should be at work on a monday?!"  I lied. I shared mini-pleasantries with my family. "hey" "how are you" "can i try some of your macaroni and cheese?" "thanks" "have you seen my photo cds?" "later" ... briefly. but I could have easily not interacted with anyone until I go to work later.  so. definitely alone. all day. it was a good day though. monday. time for work. bleh.
      
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Pretty sure that nobody cares, but I've enjoyed reading friends' blogs so here goes...   About seven months ago, I needed a big change. As big as dropping my job, heading to grad school, moving to a new city... So instead of doing that, I decided to move out of my apartment and live in my parents' house again. This made sense (then). I could save money for all those other things. They had space since my younger sisters were both away at school. I would barely see them since they work normal hours and I work evenings. I could even hop onto their YMCA membership. Perfect right? Of course not.   You all know how parents are. You have your own.   Mine were surprisingly better than I expected, except when I arrived home at 5 a.m., or fell asleep at a friend's place and couldn't hear the phone ringing for six hours of their frantic calling. Of course, this didn't happen often but these two events were way too much for them.  This lasted five months. Then I left for a three-week trip to visit friends in Europe. When I got back, my sisters were back from school, the spring rains had seeped into the basement bedroom I was living in and the house was CRAMPED with all of our STUFF. Too much stuff. Having a garage sale didn't help. My parents wanted to rip out the basement walls and get them fixed. I had to leave. Which was the plan all along, but I only had two weeks to find an apartment. (The apartment search is another story that I am too frustrated with to write about yet. It might take another seven months.)  Now I'm (luckily) subleasing from a friend who is in New York for a month. But I have to be out at the end of June. So I settled on an apartment where the messed up hardwood floors (appears to be a refinishing accident that produced long black streaks) might make me crazy. Maybe I should adopt a zebra theme in the whole apartment. Oh wait, that would clash with the mustard yellow in the kitchen and bathroom.   Definitely could be worse: I could be living with my parents again.   
      
</post>


</Blog>