<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shame on me for not posting, I cant see my blog either so thats another minor detail. Page wont load. Huh. Anyone comment? Last day of work today.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I'm in awe of Bush. Yes, I never thought I'd hear myself say that but I'm in awe. of his stupidity and how, hm, dont know the right word for it. Just read this article.*    Hitler Image Used in Bush Campaign Web Ad By JENNIFER C. KERR, AP  WASHINGTON (June 27) - Adolf Hitler's image has surfaced again in the White House race. President Bush's campaign contains online video, removed from a liberal group's Web site months ago and disavowed, that features the Nazi dictator.     The Bush Internet video, which was sent electronically to 6 million supporters, intersperses clips of speeches by Democrats John Kerry, Al Gore and Howard Dean with the footage of Hitler.  Democrats want the video pulled from the site. Campaign aides said it would remain.  Republicans had criticized the group MoveOn.org in January because it briefly posted an ad contest entry that linked Hitler and Bush. It showed images of Bush with text saying, "God told me to strike at al-Qaida," before turning to images of Hitler with the words, "And then He instructed me to strike at Saddam." The submission ended with the words, "Sound familiar?" on a black and white screen.     The group later said the entry was in "poor taste" and pulled it from its site.  The 77-second video on the Bush-Cheney re-election site splices footage of Kerry, the presumptive nominee, and his 2004 rival Dean along with 2000 nominee Gore and film director Michael Moore. The spot calls them Kerry's "Coalition of the Wild-eyed." Clips of Hitler's image are seen throughout the spot.  "The use of Adolf Hitler by any campaign, politician or party is simply wrong," said Kerry's campaign manager, Mary Beth Cahill, who called on the GOP campaign to remove the Web video from its site.  "We're using the video from MoveOn.org to show our supporters the type of vitriolic rhetoric being used by the president's opponents and John Kerry's surrogates," said Scott Stanzel, a spokesman for the Bush-Cheney re-election campaign.  The online spot begins with clips of Gore assailing the Bush administration. "How dare they drag the good name of the United States of America through the mud of Saddam Hussein's torture prison," Gore shouts during a public speech.     It then cuts to an image of Hitler, followed Dean, Moore and Rep. Dick Gephardt, D-Mo., all bashing Bush. There are more clips of Hitler, Gore and then Kerry, before the screen cuts to the words, "This is not a time for pessimism and rage." Video images of Bush follow.  A disclaimer was added to the beginning of the Web spot on Saturday afternoon to explain that the video contains "remarks made by and images from ads sponsored by Kerry supporters." The disclaimer also accuses Kerry of failing to denounce those who have compared Hitler to Bush.   *Note:I dont ususally post articles, but this one is an exception.    This is wrong.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Michael Moore:  Bravo
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Look out! So today I took off work cause Rockapella is coming to town tonight. Whos Rockapella you ask? well, remember that show  Where in the World is Carmen Sandiego ? they were the people that did all the singing on that. So when we figured I'd have the whole day off we schedualed my drivers test. It twas this morning at 10:30. I passed. I have my license. How fuckin cool is that eh? 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So my dad and I just got back from a 3 mile hike. Good hike even better day. We were in the CVNRA (national park) which was kinda cool and we say this big falls thingy neither of us had seen before. Fun times eh.  Yesterday had to work becuase I'm taking wednesday off. We worked the PRIDE parade and event and it was actually alot of fun. Got to hang out with one of the directers and some of the crew that I wanted to get to know more. I think we were there for a little under 6 hours but it was fun anyway, plus it didnt really seem like it. So, there ya go. Oh yeah. I saw alot of people from school there. Just thought I'd mention it. Car.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once again this would just be a post about work, but I figured I'd go for a happier post. So I was sitting in my living room after work (I mean) and I hear this large thing coming down the street. now the only reason this is so unusual is because it was at 11:30 at night. So it turns out it was an ambulance. Great. So the pulled up almost right across the street from me to an elderly couples house (89+) and I figure, "alright, maybe they just fell, they do that alot" so I watch and then they pull out that stretcher thingamajig "shit" goes gideons mind. so they took one of em away, and while the ambulance was there the other was just staning in the doorway...watching. I felt so bad for em, I donno, just kinda sad watching your loved one getting loaded and taken away in an ambulance.  Right, hows that for a happy post? G
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So last night I had a stellar night, as well as living thro this terrific storm out office also started a campaign with Ohio PIRG, I am one of the people working on it. So anyway, last night I raised 290, second highest of the night which is way cool. Supposedly I'm a field manager now, which means I get 50 extra bucks in my pay check but I have to be there at 11:14, instead of 1. Hmmmm. I don't see much of my family anymore, especially my papa, which is kinda weird actually. O! Yesterday we ordered a bunch of stuff that I still need for camping, like a sleeping bag, rain gear, and other whatnot that eludes my memory at the moment.  Cheers
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I already created one blog here, the realized I left off the e in management. Crappè, so hopefully this'll work.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you can see it all again. Huh. Strange. I dont know what I'm doing, yeah, I'm moving back to blogdrive.    urlLink Home again.   And yes, please rechange your links.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sence I cant see my own blog I'm moving back to blogdrive. Cheers.
     

    
</post>



</Blog>