<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Blogspot? I had come across this name before. But I didn't sign up because of ebloggy. Out of curiosity, I've signed up just for fun.   I've edited the prologue for The Marauders Four. It's a much more pleasant introduction than the previous one. Gulp. Still writing, wonders if I'll do a revised version of the Marauders Four after I completed the whole chunk of story. Oh my, that'll be a lot of work to do! But still, I enjoyed reading. I like Darkness Dying by Iniga. Forever Alive by Shaye/Mordred. Confusing matter, I don't know which one to trust.   Godric's Hollow was still in the change of server. Everything went on fine, doing a bit of stuff and homework. 
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Really! The next week was so full with tests and remedials and enrichments! Finally, it was the last lesson of the English Enrichment! Thank god! But  he  is coming back!!!  OH NO !!! God. What am I going to do!? There is the IPW [inter-disciplinery Project Work] presentation, which I absolutely hate, the napha test, which I'm absolutely afraid about. I know I can't pass this time round! How can I? I've never ever passed my napha test! and I know I can't...I've been working like mad and crazy to brush up my standing board jump but to no avail. It's no use, do you see that!? Sometimes, there is a glint of hope which disappeared soon after I jumped and I know I haven't met the target. Two common tests next week, English and History - my poorest subjects. Sigh. Then there was the Geography test on tuesday, I think.The Napha test will be on Tuesday too. On that day is also the national day parade rehersal, which probably will be until 6pm...sigh. On friday is a half day, which will be the national day parade of the school. Our band will of course be participating in this upcoming event with much much more and higher confidence than ever. But my clarinet is still under repair, meanwhile, I can use my old clarinet... which is a lot better than the current one, apart from the fact that it is not shining, and I cannot borrow it back... Gee. Life is going downhill for me. 
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I got a lot better when I reached home yesterday...It was a terrible feeling...your head was spinning and your fingers went numb. You couldn't feel a thing - and you were out of breath. That was like...hell.    Today was much much much more better! [but my legs are still aching like hell] I set up an instrument, my previous clarinet and used Jaslyn's unused reed [after fall in of course]. Haha. When I reached school around 6.45am and almost everywhere was in darkness. It felt so cold... I went straight to the direction of the bandroom and saw no source of light. So I strolled over to the canteen. My eyes immediately lit up with the encouraging smile of Nizam... Trust me! He's so shuai!! =). haha. Such a pity that he is a malay...haiz. It's so difficult to find a guy with good looks, good grades, good behavoir and character, and humour most importantly! He fitted the conditions exactly, but too bad, he's a malay...haiz haiz haiz...    The sec1s had 2.4km run today so they all went off. Good luck! And they all passed...yay. So we had sectionals afterwards when Mr Ong realised there's not going to be a rehersal today. So nizam took over as usual and he was torturing us! Majulah Singapura! We are Singapore! One people, one nation, one Singapore! Wah...haiz. And Andre came back today! Omg. He looked  so  different! he's no longer that duckling! When the sec1s came back, they looked as if they were going to faint right on that moment. Napha was such a torture.    AHH! [Before I actually forgot it. You know what!? Qiuming sat with Jaslyn today! With no juniors in between...hahaha....memorable day eh??]    During Sectionals, Peggy was very strict with us. I could actually see her eyes burning with fire... Oh no. What I like about Peggy is the force which Elaine can never give. The force, those kind of force that push us forward and very on going. Huilin and Vivian came back sia... Ooops. That was  so....scary .   When it was finally full band, we threw all the songs aside and played made in Singapore!! YAHHOOOO! LOL. It's the nicest song I ever heard...and I remembered the first time when I ever heard it during the encore...    On that day, Jaslyn actually called me to inform that there was a open air philharmonic winds concert at yew tee and Elaine encouraged us to go for it. Since it was senior's orders, I had no choice. Till the end of the whole programme, the audience was very attentive. Mr Ong is the mc [in-charge]!! Woohoo! So we yelled for encore and this was the song they had played.    and so we played. The mood was jumpy and bouncy, happy and bright! Lively! Nizam was actually skipping with the instructions of Mr Ong, which made us all laugh like madness....haha. It was a great sight to see. After that, was the end of band. I wanted to borrow the instrument, but I couldn't. It was not  my  instrument now...Fall in and then...a lot of people pump. I didn't know why, but there was so many people, flutes, trumpets, admins, french horns... It was a terrible sight to see our dear student conductor pump, especially when we had seen him before, about to faint and he couldn't support himself and had to be supported in between amin and farhan...omg.   Went to lot 1 with Jaslyn, bought long john silver and  disappeared  right after that.....................  
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's the 2.4 day. I thought it would be nothing and just like any other normal days... but how wrong I am. Early in the morning, I walked a short distance to school after a sleepless night. I've slept from 6.20 to 10.55, that's why I didn't blog yesterday! 'Cos I'm too tired to do it. Now I've&nbsp; the 2.4. Though not so worried as the others, I'm so excited about it. So we changed and went to the foyer to get ready. We stretched and then got ready for this very big challenge.  I was waiting with anticipation near the front line. We cheered and wished each other good luck and do our very best to cross over this huge barrier for 2.4km run. The whistle sounded and the boys shot off in a fast pace. My heart was beating faster and faster every second. I can do this! I knew I can! We wait for two minutes, each time trying to take a step forward and the time came, the countdown... 10...9...8...7...6....5.........4.......3........2......................... 1!!!  We ran off as if there was a dog chasing behind us. I ran, each step I tried to make it as bouncy and as quick as possible and I ran and ran and....I stopped. I took a few deep breaths and told myself I CAN DO THIS! and continue with a slow jog all the way even though I did stop a few times on the way there and back. I ran...all the way near the mosque, thn huiqian about to overtake me. Nooooooo!!! I can't let this happen!( haha. I doesn't really mean it all right?)&nbsp; I CAN DO IT!!!  (I can!!  Or else I will be failing ) So I ran all the way non stop with a faster pace until I reached the school foyer and finally took the card and sat down, my mind twirling... the image was blur. The breathing was quick and raspy. It was like the end of the world. But  I managed to pass!!  We went back to classroom, and straight away was a Geography assignment in 30min time. God. I cannot even think properly. I actually copied the whole chunk of information in the textbook. Then near the end, I was scribbling the points and then filled in everything and handed it in. Phew.  After that, thank god, was recess, which is the time that I can grab something to eat. It feel so weird after all the energy lost, I actually do not feel hungry. Instead, I bought a drink and it was enough. Next was two hours of lessons and finally was band time.  I felt the headache getting more and more painful each step I took. I really felt sick. A lot of people wanted to skip band practice because of this reason. This is the first ever time when there is a situation like this. Yingjie,&nbsp;qiuliang&nbsp;skipped band practice..What will happen to Jasreel!?&nbsp;Gee! Even&nbsp; that guy &nbsp;doesn't want to come because of napha,&nbsp;which I doubt is a lie (he got his napha on thur!!) and he got so many homework to complete...ahh.&nbsp;(During fall in time, Jaslyn got samula [back to the previous position] 6-7 times...haha) So I had no instrument since my clarinet is not working and I feel so out of place. When it's sectionals time, I finally got to lend Elaine's and Peggy's clarinet so that I can practise.  However, I feel myself getting more and more giddy. The energy was lost. My fingers felt so numb...I draw raspy breaths, as if I was going to vomit any second. I totally lost the will to strive on. Everything was twirling...spinning...like craziness. I stumped my way through the bathroom. I can't think at all. and I vomitted all my lunch out. I was sickening. But it was feeling better. I staggered back to the sectionals ground and peggy forbidden me to play...gee. Jaslyn said I looked very pale. Am I? I rarely felt this weak before... even after a run, I should not get sick!  The energy boosted through me as I smiled encouragingly. This is not the end of the world afterall. After that, I can only watch the conductor and spend my time glaring at the score...Ahh. Nizam. My way of thinking was getting stranger...he is so shuai (handsome) and so cute but so  childish .  And it's duty. All of them hurried me to do the duty sooner. Hey, what's the hurry!? Are they afraid to fall in!? Ahh. it's&nbsp;so easy...hehe. I've been longing to fall in. haha. Falling in isn't that&nbsp;bad afterall, you see? They sabotage me! In the end, Peggy and elaine kept me back to clean the instrument room!!!!! *groans* now I REALLY have to fall in. I ran through the way slowly, but my head is still aching. I came to a halt right infront of the Mr Ong and Miss Lim. *gulp*.&nbsp;I cut my way through them...=P. Then fall in! ha! (so shuang sia..) Then after falling in, I paid $15 and my wallet is like...empty.  Then on my way out of the gate, I accompanied Jaslyn to wait for her mother even though I really don't need to. I just wanted company...haha. So I waited and it was great fun to communicate along.   I bet tomorrow will be a better day!  *grins*  
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Wednesday. God. Time had passed really fast in an alarming speed. Before I knew it, it was already the individual speech presentation for the English enrichment. I was damn scared and nervous even though deep down in my heart, I know I can do this. I've done this for so many times. Who couldn't!? But turning around, I saw that many people had prepared well for this special test. Big pictures, scripts, a great amount of cue cards, decorations, everything. Panicking, I thought I should get something done. Well. At least I can paste my pictures on a vanguard sheet... I made my decison and bought a vanguard sheet shared with Haina and glue. Then I went to get the form for the computer lab and dashed upstairs to get a pen, come down, search for teachers and found someone I wanted to see. Miss Yani.    I looked around and Miss Yani is my only hope. I went up to her and asked her to sign the form for me. She agreed, I was in joy! so much in joy that I asked her about the t shirt, since mine is so large, I simply can't fit in. She agreed! I was filled with joy and happiness. Then I ran off.    I headed to the bookshop to get one piece of paper. Then I met Ying Ge with Qiying together with Xue Yi over there. What an unlikely trio. I saw them holding the form and thus asked whether they wanted to go with me, since I already got it signed.    So we went to Com lab1, which refered us to com lab4. After we reached com lab4 with running and panting as if we had run for miles, we sat down, worked for 15min before a teacher stop us. Hell! She told us she booked the lab for remedial! But there're so many computers! Can't she spare us some!? gee. I ran back down to com lab 1 again and saw somebody there. (But of cos on the way, I met somebody...) Nizam, talking to mrs low. Maybe I'm really that easy to be influenced, Nizam is somehow more smugly and more shuai than usual..haha. We headed in and mrs low had given us the left side of the room. I was grateful for that. We start to work, when I was all ready, I found that the printer had NO INK!!! But with the help of Ng Li, Junyi helped me to print. hehe. (He was the someone whom I met along, afterall) Thanks, kor! Haha. But I simply couldn't speak it out of my mouth during that time. Seeing his cheeky face simply reminds me of that time...    Then I dashed up to the fourth level again. Gee... why couldn't our class be on the first level!? I was about to faint when I held on and ran into the classroom only to see the entire class in disaster state. I sat down, grabbed the glue and ruler and started to tear and paste. After thirty minutes of pasting and decorating, finally, it looked like I had done some work...    So we went down to the Drama room even though we knew that we were late. But the class was not dismissed yet. After 2/10 came out of the dance room, Daphne came to me. Her visual aids was really well done but she hadn't gotten the chance to present it this week. I was impressed. So we went in to the usual smelly dance room and sat down waiting with excitement for our turn. Somehow, time passed and my turn still hadn't come. I was about to die from waiting! That kind of nervousness... And the day ended with the last, Qiying's presentation. My heart sank with disappointment. After so much preparing, after running like hell from level to level, is this what I 'll get in the end!?I was so...frustrated. I did not want to wait until the next week! I didn't want to have more fears hanging in my heart! So I, with amira, "begged" the teacher to let us present for the day, so that I could be relief. She agreed! YAY!! So I waited again for amira's speech to end, it was really great, it was a kind of important presentation she had given. I stood to my feet once more, the script clenched in my hand and the visual aid in another. I spoke and I looked up to have eye contact with the audience. I stuttered though and I paused for a few moments. But it was great. It is great afterall...    The desperation&nbsp;died after the speech...   On my way out of the school, I saw michelle and grinned my broadest smile ever with the most content feeling... She returned me the smile and I had the urge to tell her "It's over! It's finally over!" but I couldn't. lol. I came to a halt at the bus stop station and met Grace over there. We talked for a while and she got onto 307. I had the urge to go home too but I was held back by the downpour of rain. Afterwards, Amira came by. So we talked again ad 175 arrived. I boarded the bus and tapped my ezlink card and walked on...   The bus drove away as I saw a familiar figure...    The figure of a pale boy carrying a tortoise bag...     And I just can't avoid looking back...............................    
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tuesday was once again here and over just as fast as expected. Somehow, time seemed to be passing at the double speed and now I  finally  knew why. Because the Napha test was soon to be here again. And  VERY  soon to be here, it was starting for the sec1s tomorrow, which was probably a surprise for them, but for us, we had one week for the preparation. It was such a "pleasant" surprise. Sigh. I'm really scared that I might fail for this upcoming physical test, just like the passed years. I haven't passed for a single time in my life! It was such a misery... I'm really really scared! The urge. The feeling. No one can understand those kind of pain being behind and the slowest at speed everywhere. It was so scary. It is a nightmare. It had always been my greatest fear, the Napha test... I can do well almost for everything with practice but napha? I simply can't... I can never... It will be a miracle if there is.  Sigh.  Sometimes I really wished I can do everything if I had the will. But this is too much to be true. It's not about your thinking, it's about your real strength and weakness...   
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Monday again! Time is sure slipping away fast and I can't imagine the Napha test here the very next week! It's my greatest fear, the napha test. It's not that I'm scared of failing the test but scared of the teacher pulling me away during band practices in order to pass my Napha, or train, or something similar. Last year, I had not been able to go back for band rehersal due to Napha. I just simply can't jump far! Gee. I can never pass my Napha.    Next, there's common test today and my mind doesn't seem to work just as well as usual. I can't think. I just stared at the poem and read along the lines. This poem seemed oddly familiar as if I had read it&nbsp;somewhere before... But I can't think! I read the question, then I stared at it and picked up my pen and scribbled something in my script. I refered back to the question again and started to pick up evidence and something... But! It's so less! There's only two pages! I've got an instinct that says I'm going to fail this literature common test just like before! It's streaming! I can't afford to fail! But my mind simply can't think! What can I do!?    And then there is the IPW presentation to worry about. We haven't done the third instruments and that is the string! It's Victor job to do it but none of us will believe that he will be doing it on his own motivation. You believe that!? Gee.    I just can't stop worrying about troubles and problems heading towards me in a few weeks or days time. Can somebody please help me!? Ahhhhhhhhhh!    
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Finally saturday had arrived! And it's Daniel Radcliffe's birthday yesterday! Happy birthday! I'm in such a great mood! lol. Well, I'm cheerful enough to stop thinking about negative thoughts. It started the day with a wet rainy morning. I just couldn't fall asleep. I kept waking up in between my dreams...oh dear. I woke up and of course cleaned up, ate breakfast and dashed off to school. I can't be late! But it was raining...and the car was travelling in such a slow speed. I finally reached there. But I'm late. Sigh. I want the bubble gum!!!  Then we fall in at 7.45 sharp. Did a little tiny bit of drills but it's enough for me. Set up the instrument and headed&nbsp;for sectionals. But after about half an hour, we went back, because the tutor was not able to be here. So we went back and then we sat down at the trombone's seat. It's extremely bizarre to be sitting way behind from the front sit, but comfortable enough. We played and I noticed the good thing about sitting behind is that we can do things without the conductor or other people noticing. Ha.  I exchanged instrument with Peggy because Jaslyn suspect I AM THE ONE who is producing the airy sound. But hey! It's not me, all right!? I may be airy sometimes but not that airy. IT IS REGINA who is the culprit! Seeing her just makes me faint. The band needs more potential player even like shiqi but none of us will be sad to see her go, that's the truth. She's been sticking out during the blending in tuning and she can't read notes, dynamics, rhythm. I AM LOSING MY PATIENCE! OK, I admit I'm once like that but I can't imagine myself smiling infront of huiling or kokting when I can't play the notes! I can't really be fierce because the atmosphere won't be either. Gee. I'm really wondering how I'm going to survive like that. Regina is a hopeless case and Yina is slacking away! What kind of juniors are that? Last time, we don't dare to voice to things because seniors are fierce. But now, they're taking the chance to slack!    We're being reprimanded by the conductor because of our gleeful look, our heck care faces, mainly because of our attitude. Our band's fame had been completely being thrown away and we had the notorious reputation of being the cca nobody wanted to join (except those who come from musical backgrounds). This problem had been going on for a long time and it was being focused even harder than usual lately because the sec4s had left! We cannot even play the national anthem properly! The marches don't even sound firm! I've got a feeling that if we exclude the sec1s, we can play even better. There are players with potential in the sec1s but not all. But then again, we didn't have enough players. We can play better! We  can  do it! C'mon! But is everybody willing to strive for the best!?  No!  Surely there's someone who did not want to practise and didn't want to come for band at all! Gee. How I hope this band will be filled with people who want to play! But it's impossible...    Just when I am about to practise as hard as I can for this weekend, now, my instrument was sent for repair! GEE! I'm just about to be hardworking and now they're taking my instrument away! I guess that's how life is. It's great that now someone can send it for repair because this clarinet had not been working for ages. Furthermore, it's  new !! It's hardly a year old! And if those rusty clarinets can work and function properly, why can't this newer one be the same!? *groans*. But then again, when I don't have the instrument, I can teach the sec1s more accurately than usual. But I'm surely going to miss the clarinet. Sigh.    After keeping my instrument and giving the clarinet to the quartermaster, I hurried downstairs to fall in. Who knows there's going to be drills again!? It seems like Peggy is in a  very  good mood today. We had a mini competition to compete among the levels. It seems that we're the winner if I'm not wrong, but Peggy&nbsp;had clean&nbsp;forgotten about it. Sigh.    Then Mr Ong came down. We compete again. And we had the most solid bang without a timer!  *grins*!  That's our proudest achievement ever. Then later accompany both of them to lot 1 and then went to buy long john silver myself and headed home.     What a great day!  =) (Well, it's satisfactory for me!)   
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Everything indeed had been going downhill since Monday. It's like climbing a mountain or a hill...the higher you get, the tougher it is. I guess, that's the way of life...    Head to school, everything went on quite OK. Except during english, I spent 1 1/2 hour trying to complete 10 points of 100 words summary. It was such a difficult task. Gee. I had to say thank you to Janice, she helped me to hand it in. hehe. Then no PE again, which is such a waste. It's been two weeks! I haven't run for two whole weeks! Sigh. Time indeed is passing very fast like seconds...    Following next after geography, which was being held by one teacher and one investigator, was recess. Finally, I could stretch my limbs and walk about, only that...I couldn't. After recess was maths, which was very challenging and just as enjoyable as usual (only that miss chan wasn't here, it was such a disappointment for the boys! ha). Right after that was science which was slightly more fun than usual...   Then was band. I somehow did not feel like going. I feel like skipping band practice, which was something unsual. Band was something that uplifted my spirits at the end of the day. Almost everyone skipped today, novan and kian yong. Those were ones of the best players in band. The trombone section would not survive when kian yong was not there and the same goes to the french horn section. It was such a discouraging band practice. Reprimanded by Mr Ong because I don't know the rhythm. It's my first time ever reprimanded and insulted directly! :'(! Hello, who would not feel nervous!? It was my worst day ever for the week... And everything won't go any better for tomorrow...    I just wished, tomorrow would be all right.   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Before you know anything, time is slipping away above anything else. Time is seconds, passing right under your nose...From&nbsp;Monday onwards, everything started to go downhill. Monday is all right, Tuesday quite ok, Wednesday completely alone, Thursday&nbsp;was so lousy. Tomorrow can't be any better.    I found myself once and&nbsp;once again influenced by comments of&nbsp;all different sorts. Negative comments mainly. There were all kinds of comments from classmates which I sometimes found really very true. Some of the few like:&nbsp;huiqian dun care about anybody&nbsp;else other than jaslyn, jaslyn is not really friendly except to huiqian they all... All kinds. All sorts. All so true. All which I found was so depressing. Whenever I seek company, I first go to yuhui, who is already taken by szehui. Then I go find huiqian, then she went off with jaslyn. Ying ge is with Qiying and her constanting staring and growing wide eyes are always warning me off. Pamela went with Fanqin, then janice they all...Sigh.&nbsp;No&nbsp;matter how hard I try, I eventually will always end up alone. I stared at them, unnoticed by anyone who ever cares. Because there's nobody. In&nbsp;this class of 2/7, there's nobody at all. Nobody who cares to&nbsp;open their eyes wide to&nbsp;see the situation.&nbsp;Nobody... &nbsp;   Then I realised I am doing a wrong thing, I'm reading Jaslyn's blog. Whenever I read it, I only sank more into depression. Because I'm never existant in her eyes other than some days, I'm never mentioned. I'm only forgotten. Had she ever observed her surroundings? Only once in a while. Once in a while she will remember me and in the next moment, I'm forgotten again. There was a news going on in the class which everybody is keen on. That is that on national celebrations, we're baking cookies to sell! Something very fun for everybody else. Something very depressing for me. Baking cookies, it requires help more than anything else. I turned around and saw that everybody was so excited. I asked. But my question was ignored. I really wonder how I will pass that day trying to help, but to no avail.    I really don't know what to do, how to survive in this world...    
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I heard his hand flapping my bedsheets and I stirred to see a blurry figure. "Hey, wake up, it's nearly eight o'clock," he said. I could recognise that voice anywhere. It belongs to my big brother whom I always respect, whom I always seek whenever I had trouble with homework, whom is my greatest childhood playmate, whom&nbsp;always accompany me.    I had never expect him to do this thing of sort. It was nothing.&nbsp;It was a bit childish to me but it's too much! Imagine! Waking up, walking up to the dinner table expect to&nbsp;see a plate&nbsp;full of fried chicken. Within&nbsp;two hours, so many things happened. I dunno why but he consumed them all except for&nbsp;2 pathetic pieces left at a plate.&nbsp;   I broke into tears. I couldn't resist it. He was so- so...sigh. It was a bit childish, yes. No, it was so childish. But I couldn't help it. Your stomach empty, you expect your mum to whipped up something delicious specially for your family,  AND YOUR BROTHER ATE IT ALL!  Too much, don't you agree?    I insisted that I'd rather skip dinner. I just can't think while eating how your brother had eaten them all without caring about you for a bit! Then I came up with a solution, it happened everywhere. It could also happened in home. That is that my existance was gone in his eyes...    It was a terrible truth to accept but it was my only suspect...     &nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I had no idea why but the days seemed to be getting worse day by day... Monday is all right. Tuesday is okok. Wednesday is total loneliness...     &nbsp;   I had to go wandering by myself again. There are so many tests that I have to put my mind on. There was no time to relax or to think anything else. I don't know why but I seemed to be be avoiding them every single day whenever I can. Or they were avoiding me. Either one. I don't feel too happy about it either. It's never joy to not have any company at all. It's utterly pain and depression. Leave you one year by yourself all alone and the next year, you will go mad.     &nbsp;   Loneliness.     &nbsp;   I've seen this word countless of times. It is something which many people fear, which I fear, loneliness. I've sighted this somewhere in a place where it doesn't even fit at all. In someone's blog... Yet I know her. She doesn't know what's called lonely, what's called a loner. It was misery. It was beyond hell. She can never know and appreciate what's called occupied.     &nbsp;     There are so many friends you can have but not one of them can accompany you when you need them. That's called lonely...        
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's tuesday once again! Time is passing so fast as if the clock is set to work doubled the speed. I remembered this day a week ago. He didn't care. I was so mad! Enough about him. Tuesday well. passed like normally. Go bp, thn the scene flashed through. I remembered that day so well. I can never forget it. I can NEVER take insults from anybody, whether it's about me or my school or something else. Since then, I had never step in bp ever again. It's been like...half a year? Well. I can't get rid of my fears. Those pairs of staring eyes... I had done so much wrong in my life and I told myself again and again never ever to repeat the same mistake. I kept looking around and stayed in silence. Everything had changed so much within half a year. They didn't know what I'm thinking. Well, at least one of them dunno what I'm thinking. But everything had passed fine and well.  Then I'm thinking again. I had no idea why. But I had so many thoughts. Words had naturally formed in my mind. But I never exactly did recall the words anymore...Thoughts can be so complicated but thoughts are always silent and personal...
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's monday! Yeah! Monday! HEhe. It's so good to start a week with a monday! Of course, there is still monday blues... Of course! Who want sunday to pass so quickly and welcome monday when work to starting again!? I want more holidays!! hehe. :D. In such a great mood. It's always great to be back in school even though a whole lot of examinations are waiting for us yet again... Monday! The energy booster of the week! LOL. Well. It's so bad to start a fresh day like this, sitting in the parade square under the sunshine, listening to the principal talking like eternity. Well. After that, we headed back to our classes, sit down and started the day. One good thing is that ray chua is not here! Two bad things is that there're going to be history test on wednesday and the chinese spelling afterwards. But it's music after reccess! so it's time to cheer up! Music, is my passion. But it's really not my thing...I passed the four levels and thus headed to the fifth. However, I almost passed with a 47%. "Bravo".  For the entire day, I felt so sick. I'm down with flu and had no idea why I got it. I just woke up and found my nose blocked and kept on sneezing like madness.  After common test, I packed my bag and followed them out of the school gate. At first I thought I am going back home, but I was thinking and then I dun feel like going home afterall. Thus, the six of us boarded the bus to west mail, I as the outcast. =P. Whatever. It's quite an enjoyable time, really, with the exception from those who sat beside the old lady who criticised about our school and bragged about her own children. I really felt like bashing up the lady after I heard it from my friend. It's really rude and insulting and she showed no respect to other schools! Not really bashing, mind you. But it's REALLY REALLY TOO MUCH!  The day went on quite nice actually. except that I'm quite sick. I reached home, cut my hair. it felt so refreshing.  I remembered that memory flashed back when I saw Jaslyn boarded the famart train. Yes. I remembered it so well and perfectly. It started off with a clear blue day. Then, it started to drizzle. Then. It started to rain. We were running like mad in order to reach farmart, "unwet". But it's a too naive thought. Everybody was wet. Even me, who was holding the umbrella. We went there, look around thn walked back to school! OMG. It's my first ever trip to farmart, but it's also quite fun. Till now, two years had passed, but I still remembered it. Cos it's my first ever trip being wet while walking...
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I really had no idea what is happening nowadays. They kept me in the dark until they gave their own secret away somehow in communications or something. I felt so left out. They kept on saying obvious things which none I would ever understand. They knew it. But they STILL talk about it. They are so ever tactless!  Today once again, I go and read her blog. Suddenly, I found myself filled with disgust after reading her feelings. How do girls fall for guys so easily!? They are only judging by looks and they can go extremely crazy for them. Capturing photos, dwelling in the past, thinking about them. HEY! You all are dreaming, all right!? They're so naive! C'mon, it's time to WAKE UP! I thought there was something wrong in their psychology. Capturing photos... Wah. It's like nightmare. Now I truly understands what my brother meant by "making your favourites until they're so ever disgusting". Good looking guys doesn't make themselves perfect. Of course girls will naturally dream over good looking guys but not until this kind of madness and craziness!! 
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Saturday arrived once more. Three weeks had passed since the school had reopened. Time seemed to have passed so quickly, unnoticed by anyone. The time was ticking away...which means my most worried fear is going to be here once more, the napha test. *gulp* I had no idea whether I can pass or not. I've been failing for years...not even passing once. My biggest problems are the standing board jump and the incline pull up. Somehow...I couldn't jump far and my hand had no strength to pull myself up. My brother couldn't pass his napha either. and it's national service to him... good luck, brother. =).  Satruday of course also means band practice. And the tutors are coming. And shiting with yina were not here... That means. I'm left with regina! *OMG* She's quite all right actually...confused between sharps and flats, fingerings, and her reaction is not fast enough.  Enough about regina...now about myself! I'm able to go through shenadoah more clearly now that there is less people, I cannot fret! Somehow, the feeling is lost. A feeling which I felt when the pressure which the seniors exerted on you. When I'm still with Jaslyn, the feeling is never gone. I can never be on task. I always depend on her. And when both of us dunno, I felt myself blushing. But now, I'm on task. I came in at the right beat. Everything is going on fine. Life is a lot more better than last time. (With the exception of regina's problem) Another problem is that the whole green file had gone missing. SIGH. I really felt like bashing up the person that had taken it away! That's  SO RUDE !!!The fingering chart is gone! REALLY! Gee... I only hope that the file can be in the cabinet by next friday...That's all I wished. That's all I wanted. Can't a simple wish be granted? I just want everything to be fine. But life is never going to be like that. Life is never smooth sailing... Human always wanted what they don't have. It's a nature. It's rare that once in a while, people get to appreciate things... 
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's sunday but there's hardly anytime to relax. When I woke up in the morning, it was already near to eleven o'clock. So I quickly finished up the literature assignment which took up 1 1/2 hr to complete. I just did it anyhow...then I discover I have finished my chinese homework, so I quickly finished it all up. By the time everythig was done, it was already 1pm. I on the computer then switched off then got visitors...I go read a book...until about 2.20pm. Wash up, got dressed, went out by about 3.30pm...I saw Jasreel and Lixiang on the bus, odd eh? Both of them actually recognised me! weird. Then board the bus and went to victoria concert hall. The concert is terrific! It's marvellous and nice. Especially for the Song, 'Godzilla Eats Las Vegas'. Although I can hardly make out the words on the screen, the pictures were hilarious. I regretted not bringing my spectacles along...sigh. Then go home... On the way actually, there were a lot of conversations on the subjects we choose. I could not decide, however. I don't know...which one is better? I don't want to get into biography nor dnt but there doesn't seem to be a choice. Pure science is really competitive but I'm not interested in literature or geography at all. I do not seem to make up my mind afterall... I'm so confused...people actually chose A,B,C,D. But I cannot make up my mind....there wasn't enough time. I'm on two minds, unable to decide... This is really a hard decison to make. 
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      God, tell me, oh tell me, what to do.................................. I don't want to live in this pathetic world. This world full of cruelty and disasters. This world full of jealousy and hatred. I don't want to be borned. I don't want to be here. I don't want to be alive... But how can that ever happened...unless I get myself involved in some cranky accident and get myself killed halfway. I don't treasure life, I really don't. 'Cause they're never easy, never smooth, they're always full of hardship, full of crazy ideas. Tell me, oh tell me, what to do... Living in this world is to suffer, although I must admit I am not suffering as much as others do. But the situation I am in makes living so pointless. What do I live for...Who do I live for? Why am I even here? I don't ever know, there ain't a single answer... The society gets more and more complicated everyday...I don't know, but my emotions are high. Minor things can really make me cry, though I fought back my tears. They never know. They never understand. but what can I do? No directions, nothing. Just plain space for me to fill up. This is group work, not single. Where's the team spirit? Where's the work? Why. why. why..... Things that I can never achieve but something which I yearn for...always disappoint me. Their behavoir, as I watched from afar, is always something I yearned. To be in the best pure science class, something which I target for, but can never be fufilled. I know. I know all this. But they're repeating over and over again before my very eyes... People said I ask too much questions. But my mouth can never stop speaking. Why? Why. Why...Nobody answer. Nobody tell me anything. The only world of survival in this world is only to depend on yourself..and no one else. No one else understand how you feel, what you want, how you want matters to go. Yes, I know. I know I ask too much questions but.....do you ever even wonder about it before? How strange a human's mind work...what's called jealousy and hatred and cruelty...the language people invented had been passed down for years. how come it is there and why are we using it. we never know. we can never know... She was the leader everybody elected, I know. Yet, before my very eyes, things are going very wrong. Just by asking her directions, I could feel her annoyance. Just by stating that I don't want to do work, she said fine. Really fine, indeed. I don't know why.......................why I am reacting like this.... I went to read her blog, instead of concentrating on the leftover studies, she brood about her clothes. Both of them, none cared about studies, none knew the importance of studies. This is our path of career, something important in life. But I'm really fed up, really mad with anger. Yet they didn't care at all, 'cause they know, that, in the end, I will still do the work and they don't have to do anything at all. Tell me, oh tell me, what to do.......I know I cannot get on like this. I know I'm going to collasp very soon. but when? I dunno................... Tell me, every single one of you, what to do................  The street once bright but now so dull The sun once up but now so dark The place once cheerful but now so quiet The road once busy but now so deserted The path I took The friends I chose The people around me The hatred continues................... I don't know when this ever will stop Something called war, something called jealousy Something called wealth, something called fame Life's never fair Life's never equal Life's always there But I don't want to be alive I don't want to be here... Grant me a wish, Let me be gone, from now on............ 
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It was a bright and sunny day...I got up early in the morning and prepared everything, ready to go to school. But something ruined my mood very badly, I don't know why. I always thought the end of the world is to have both of my parents up at the same time, because they will nag and nag and nag until non stop...something unbearable, something which is a torture. But now, that I realise, both of them were actually very concerned about my school work. They're worried, of course, but I'm tired of their behavoir. So I skipped off to lot 1 to board a bus then went to school...I found pamela with yingge and fanqin [and a 'him', nizam]. So I wait with them, ying ge went off, left the three of us. Nothing to do, I continued to wait with them....finally, janice showed up. So we head of to the sch...and I finally found jaslyn with huiqian and jiayi, then went off to the games stall... watch and walk here and there...sian. Then go to balloon hat stall! Walao...no people sia...thn play games... watch... thn er-went back to the stall, which is crowding with people...hehe. So go there, nth better to do, jiayi buy balloon hat....3.50 sia. Then jaslyn oso lor... thn huiqian stay there, dunno how hor...also helped. I wander around for the whole day, sometimes here, sometimes there. I actually run to grab his bag sia! hahaah.. .who tells him to give me the balloon! who tells the him the whole section sabotage him! hahahahaah.... great fun. Then I got lost from the usual crowd after I give zhen ye the flower balloon which unsually ends up in the rubbish bin! HMPH! jiawen actually threw it away afterwards sia!!! I asked kokting to make me one! hehehe. Then er...wander here and there to find them, sms them but cannot find them...haiz. Saw yuhui, thn listen to the co's performance...thn found them again! but I missed the band's performance...a great shame. Then went back to the stall to help out, sit there...do nothing...cannot play anywayz...must pay lehz..so I see them throw away a proper balloon hor, I go pick it up, thn untie and then play...haha. Huiqian make until so famous sia...Then go canteen and they eat and watch the show. end. I went off to find my mother. Something shocked me, I can't believe my mum is still at all! I told her not to come...since. It's damn late le. So...went up to the hall, wanted to enter but hestitated then come down then go upstairs...sit beside liting...yingge and qiying come.........with parents and sister..thn I sms jaslyn lor...attendence is taken lehz...then er. listen...for...2hr??? damn long sia..I saw nizam on the screen, I saw jaslyn on the screen but I didn't see myself on the screen! haiz... Listen listen, then wait wait....those two went off. Then I wait for the turn to discuss about subjects...thn quite disappointed lar............ must work hard from now on!!  
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I dunno what's happening nowadays. I dunno. I really dunno. I had no one to talk to, no one at all. They ran away, all, before I could even approach them. Now, I'm standing, alone. They don't understand it, and they never will. I don't know why, thinking all these doesn't matter at school, the emotions will all explode the moment I reach home.I dunno why. But recently, so many things happened. So unfair. Tears had dropped countless of times, yet the matters don't help at all.. they don't. A lot of unsolvable problems. A lot of troubles. How can crying help? I dunno.............I dunno. Matters don't help, they're giving more and more serious problems then ever. Just by changing a new bag, just by sharing the same colour, people talk. I know she don't like this but this is the bag I want. I would prefer it in brown but there ain't a choice. I need the bag..........but no. People giving me all sorts of attitudes and criticises. Life's not fair at all.......................... Early in the morning, I'm fully awake today, having slept through most of the time.english lesson is quite ok..............I scored pretty ok for the common test, quite satisfied. But PE came, my imagination run wild again....I automatically volunteered to run with yuhui but she directly, out of so many people, refused, once again and again. I dunno why but I really kan ta bu shuang nowadays....... she think she who sia.............. she had so many people, loved, in co, studies oso good............I regret. I really regretted letting her to read my blog. That had not lead to good terms, that had led me to think that she will only create more and more trouble for me. Because of one yuhui, I had to do it! It ain't fair! IT IS NOT FAIR!!! The teacher skipped the geography lesson. new eh? go to recess, eat, come up. On the way I encounter yina, I told her to come for band but she skipped in the end. Why. Why is everything only happening to the thirds? Why am the one doing all these stuff!? They're fortunate to be in band...they're so many things to learn, to be together as one united band, always. But.............but............but, why are people quitting band instead...I had no choice, I had to let her go once again. I know all her friends are getting the bad impressions of me because I went to find her every single time. But no matter how much I ask, she won't come back..............she's lost. There's maths and then science. Then is band........There's not much to talk about. The silence between me and those two. I didn't want to talk at all...I know I'm the outcast. I know. I know..........but then again.....please. please do not let me feel badder by whispering between yourselves, giggling silently without telling me a single thing of what you're talking about....it's not fair at all.....is it? Why. Why am I the one suffering? Why am I the one borned with the fate of getting no trustworthy friends at all....Who. who can tell me why.................. Tell me why. Firstly, when I reached the band room. I stopped being with them. I had enough, they won't notice my prescence anyway, my existance don't make a different to this world. Why am I even borned? I don't know...I don't know...so set up instrument, go wash reed, kaingee come back to band... we didn't speak for ages but exchange just side comments. Mr ong said he don't talk except to give the place for playing and directions. It was like doing a mime....lol! Had a great time laughing.........it was great. Nizam was lame....haha. Now I see what jaslyn meant by him being a lame guy.............haha. it was a great practice, though I longed that it can be longer. But something I absolutely hate is that mr ong actually suggested us to have band remedials! FOR 2HRS  EVERYDAY !!!! OMG. from today onwards, I must work hard!! VERY HARD!haiz... Didn't fall in. This is the best time! Then borrow instrument. I saw the two of them ran away before I could even call them and reluctantly follow daphne instead. Though I didn't spend a lot of time with her, she's quite a nice girl to be with. Then her car come, we said goodbye and I saw the pair come out of sch.  i didn't know why but I immediately turn and walked away. I don't want to disturb them anymore. Their mere prescence had caused something more.......it made me feel so out of place, so odd one out, so outcast, so alone................ All of the fears came pouring out of me the minute I reached home, laughter can only last for short term and only at school........ I feel that I'm going crazy....very soon. 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't know why... but since moral education lesson, it had ruined my day partially. Especially when it's silence between the group of us, my imagination starts to run wild... I can't stand silence, or long term communication. I don't know why... It started off with the same sequence again, early in the morning, half awake, half asleep. When I reached school, fanqin straight away criticise my bag. Hey, wad's wrong!? Say I copy huiqian's bag...walao. Cannot have the same colour mehz? I'm a blue freak, hey, you know that? I must agree with everyone that all of them WOULD NOT take a thought about buying your style of bag. It would make them all out of place. So first lesson, english, go com lab2, type feature article...quite ok...typed quite fast...one of the fews who completed the assignment earlier than the rest!=). Then history...haven't get back common test results...haiz. Then reading, recess, mt....forgot how to write the 'huan' character in the phrase 'huan fa', lively(?) and to think  I study until so hard sia!! Then maths...moral education...I beginning to have a impression that miss yani do not like me at all...However hard I try to explain to her, she just won't help me! She.......she's so...........just help, just trying to clear up the things, YET! SHE REFUSED! Trying to maintain her smile, I nearly broke into tears... This is so...so...so unreasonable..............................I simply don't know what to do.......isn't there a single person who can help me? Despite the unhappy event, I laughed when the three of them fought against kheng boon [the daffie duck!]. They ran out of the classroom, all over the place, trying to escape from his clutches, ending up in the washroom! Ke lian, ke lian... Then hand in dnt wb, I tried to catch up with the three of them but they ran off too fast. So I remained in the classroom, watching some of them doing the forgotten hw, then I realised I missed a page! So quickly copy =P, then run down with yuhui to submit the books... Then accompany her to the general office to hand in $$ for the australian maths competition. A very long time. Then we rushed upstairs to the kitchen and then see jaslyn and szehui so go to kitchen again...peek in but see no one but the sec1s...quite disappointing...thn miss yani come to rush us into the next kitchen. But I thought,  this  is the kitchen?? hmmm... Then we measure the flour and butter, collect the chocolate chips and almonds, eggs with the sugar! Then we started to play around...lol. But the mixture was done, we shaped it into round little balls then press it down with a fork to create a certain pattern on the cookies. We waited for 20min, and we helped ying ge and qiyng. Also, we toured around to take a look at other people's work...haha. Harold's work is a disaster....hahahaha. They say is nice but I personally think it's not. it had too much chocolate! It's too sweet!! But we enjoyed that. We ate jiawen's and it's quite nice and tasted lots of ours, which is superb! So I sweep the floor and they litter and sweep and sweep and sweep! Tiring sia... Then give up, dun wan ter sweep le! Then slacked off, run away! hahahaha. at first wanna go to band room but then band room not opened. Fed up, go here and there then go room. Silence~-......................They whispered between themselves and I can't be bothered with that. Met him at the bus stop, yucks...he cut his hair until...so....so....er xin. yucks. sat there...thinking..............................thn jaslyn's mum come and she go home and huiqian go home............. Walking on the pavement...................I just can't help thinking more and more and more..............why oh why....why am I the one? They don't understand, the seriousness of the trouble I am in, it is like being arrested without even commiting a crime or anything and you must pay the consequences............Sigh. All I hope is that this will clear up soon.................. 
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thursday...I hate thursdays! Sigh. Thursdays were usually well and relaxed because it's nearly the end of the week! I'm anticipating the cookie baking class today very well and thus was in a cheery mood. However, it ruined my day when I was called... I thought she was calling szehui but no, it's me. I went up, wondering what's going on to have my form teacher to call me. But no. Alas. From happy immediately turned to troubled, frustrated and fed up. Why!? It's that stupid st john thingy again! Why why why!? I HAD NOT put THAT as a choice in my cca form! And my name was right in the band list...why why why.............so troubled. I plead Miss Yani to let me off. It had been going on, since last year until now, this cca had been haunting me like a ghost. I didn't mean any offence or anything! Why can't they just let me off!? I'm in band! NOT ST JOHN!!! why why why? It's such a simple order, isn't it? Teachers had been calling me but I really really didn't put my name in...I don't even know why I am there...why............tell me why. Why can't I be just like other people? Why get me into more and more trouble... why am I the outcast... Other people, so happy, so perfect but me........is never normal. I can't even pass my napha test...not even have a trustworthy friend or companion......................... I dunno what to do anymore. ___________________________________________________ It started off with a fine day....but end off with a moody day....I really don't feel like typing anymore................I really don't know what to do...........nor do I know why I am even borned in this cruel world.... 
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I dunno how's today. Unexpected? I really dunno...I'm sleepy throughout the day, half awake, half sleeping, simply couldn't concentrate. Right after school, I felt so refresh but so tired to study my science. It's the same craps, over and over again, I'm tired... So everybody went down to eat, leaving just a few of us in the classroom. I had no energy to study or even to read...my eyes are drooping and I feel that I can fall asleep any minute... The common test was quite ok...knew most of the answers well...Then they said so band so headed to the band room...haiz...he cut his hair! All of the sudden, the feeling evaporated, he wasn't as shuai as before liaoz...haha. guess I still like to judge people by the cover... Then Mr Singh come upstairs and scold us ar...watever. bloody hell. Then we're informed that band is cancelled, so we went down buy things to eat again...Then headed off to the ping pong table...sat down...met jovan. He owe me the vcd sia! For a year liao...he still haven't give...Then er- saw him, idiot lar...YaoQing teased and teased...make me wanna collasp anytime. That nosy parker...Hmph. Then I saw something. I saw him with ray chua communicating, looking extremely bu shuang. The teacher went off and he sat down. I thought everything is going to be fine. But. He broke down. Right infront of everybody. Crying into his knees. What happened!? I dunno... I felt so helpless... He's my friend for almost a year...but I couldn't do anything to him... Talk for a moment, then jiayi went off, we also go to mama shop, both of them bought mysterious gifts. One is a card with a bracelet, another a toy which spin and flew into the air... So play...went back to school...then play...then go home... Filled with confusing thoughts...to see him break down into tears, that's my first time... Sigh. 
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After all the celebrations, the four day holiday had finally come to an end. Though it is such a great thing to be back to school again, there're more things to accomplish. And- he's back. HE IS BACK! Oh no... I dunno how much more work he's going to criticise... And of course, the band room would be open again! To practise... Early in the morning, I woke up, a bit drowsy, my mouth very dry. It was kinda feeling sick... Then wash up, ate breakfast, on the computer then go back to sleep again and at about 3.30pm, I woke up again then went out to grab something to eat. Both my brother and my mother were mysteriously not at home... Then go everywhere just to find a file but can't find anything...sigh. Homework completed, but there's more things to worry about still... 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm had never enter so many posts in one single day. But I was feeling kinda boring...She agreed! I know this is minor stuff but she agreed. I'm so relief that she ain't angry...cos it ain't worth it. Just glad and relief... 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm so frightened, so scared, I dunno how she'll react. Just by a simple message, it completely spoilt my day. From a jubilant feeling, it immediately turned into a frightened one. I dunno. I really dunno. I'm confused and afraid of the arrival of wednesday. How will she react? How. The horrible nightmares that haunt my dreams... What if...What if she dun wan to be friends anymore? Just over a bag? What if...What if she's mad at me? What if...so many 'what if's I really dunno...I'm so in despair. A joyous day can become this worried. I said I'll heck care but I just can't avoid thinking and my imaginations running wild. I can't concentrate on anything else... Since I've already bought the bag, I can't change the fact. It had been a year and I had never felt this regretful. Why though...why...I really dunno what to do.  I really dunno how she'll react...  
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I dunno That kind of Feeling That thoughts.. Of him  I saw him every week Everytime, charming as he is Though in reality He is not really that charming But in my mind He is  One person is really charming His smile His eyes Filled with warmth and welcome with friendliness But I never spoke with him Never  Another was another him One of a quiet sort Never does his homework Never that obedient Rebellious but smart I knew he is up to it It's just that he never did  Confusing, relationships are I never gave a thought whether they are true The topic, the constant chattering Perhaps this will be over soon  I knew I'm just being naive Just wishful just a little hopeful... Just don't want to give up this thought... 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Friends.. Friends.. What are friends.. People who are always there? They accompany you They're always there To talk to you To be with you To share your joy and your sorrow Your compliments And your tears  I don't know who they are behind the mysterious masks they're never really there they're always gone before I ever found them  Friends support, they cheer you on They did But I don't ever know.  So called Friends But never there When you're really in need for them They disappear in a puff of smoke Like in cartoons Like dreams Like a nightmare But not reality  Friends, my friends. The times when light is never there the times when sun always set the deserted dark street the mysterious nightmare  Tell me, oh tell me.  What are friends...  (This ain't true. This is the past. But now I'm sinking into boredom, thinking of the history. I don't know, this is something I always wonder. But in reality, they are there, so wake up, those who had this thinking. It's just that you don't know. Cherish, appreciate what you have...) 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Happy 39th birthday, Singapore! It had been 39 years, since our independence. August 9, this memorable day... After many disorder and chaos, this is what we get, a home. Many said we won't survive, but we did. it was a miracle we had achieved. This very special day... Enough about independence day, let's get on with life. I woke up early in the morning, a little bit stuffy. Bro always said that my room is always so stuffy and anyone who stays in this room for a day will surely get sick or something...haha. So woke up and wash up and then plan the day... Firstly, make the dough for the pizza!! heh heh. Then go Bukit Panjang Plaza buy my bag then go home lorz...and then sleep! Bake the pizza, eat, sleep, another day gone. Simple eh!? So wake up, drink juice then after two hours planned time, then go plaza! OMG. Mum took so long time...So took lrt and a very long walk, wait for the traffic then go window shopping, see the bags...Then stop at Ice Lemon Tee and bought a bag almost exactly the same to huiqian! bet she'll slaughter me on wednesday...*oops* haiz... went to buy mos burger..wait for 20min and shop ar shop..heheh. NICE! Very nice. Then go home, sleep, wake up, watch the ndp parade and eat pizza then enter the blog for the day... Quite well for me, dun you think? 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Testing over. SET! Now I've changed the website address and I won't allow anymore intruders into reading my blog any longer! I regret. far more than anything else. She misunderstood everything. I meant everything. My thoughts and my feelings. I'm confused, so confused. I don't know what I'm thinking... There's two...I'm thinking about. One him, Another also him. I don't know who... Confused. Very confused. She said it's him. Both of them already had stead, even though I'm not so sure who. Both in the same class, one far infront, another last. Yet I only think, this is the result of the crowd I'm in. Their constant chattering and topic...something I cannot avoid hearing.. Perhaps it will be over. soon. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It was sunday. It was holiday. But certainly, holidays felt so boring... I didn't get to see anyone else apart from my own family...Holidays are good once in a while, but long holidays are certainly not for me. I missed the big crowd, the noisy chattering, the band practices, the sectionals times, the humour, the times we've pulled through... Just two days and there was not a single band practice held. Just two days is enough to drive me crazy... There was not a clarinet to play, or to practise. There's nothing to distract me from my thoughts...There's just homework and still more homework, awaiting for us to complete all. Worries above worries to be troubling about. You call this a  holiday !? Next week, there's the PTM [Parent Teacher Meeting] about the streaming of sec2. So Band practice is once again delayed. There's also the family day fun fair on the very same day. Of course, plus the IPW presentation, which I've no idea when and the common tests. Sigh. My bag broken, my homework undone, the things that had happened...my thoughts. Two guys, one down and I don't know about the other. Something I regretted is letting  someone  read my blog... It was positive that now she knew everything... 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It had gone well. Early in the morning, though nervous and excited, we had done well. I knew it, we will. We had gone through so many rehersals specially just for this big day and this day was over now. Our triumphs earned our seniors' praises. None of them had expected us to play this well with so much confidence. Confidence is what we need. It was the first national day parade I attended at school...everybody is going to watch the process... Early in the morning, call somebody to headed to school. Shiting had specially arranged the score! [Thanks! I'm grateful! =)] She's so nice. So I went through the scores, practising the fingerings. Then fall in and say byebye to leonard and yuhui. Pammy specially came to give us the support. We fall in and it took a rather long time for the adminstrations to run up and down to search for the teachers-in-charge for the band room key! When we finally fall out, all of us were running upstairs frantically, and quickly set up the instruments and stands, take the score and everything else. So down we went with one trip, everything was set. The school was noisy with chatterings of excitement. I could hardly breathe. A lot of seniors came down to watch and helped us out in the tasks such as arranging the chairs and tuning. I had never seen so many of them coming back just to give the support. Even Kaingee was giving a cheerful smile and her scoldings were forgotten. 2/5 were there and jiayi pulled a face. Everyone was cheerful. I really wonder will everything go this well. We tuned and then quickly went back to the seats. I looked around the clarinet section with a pang of guilt. Two juniors had wanted to quit band. They're only sec1 and even though I admit I'll love to had regina to quit band, I just can't let them off just like that. Band is about devoting yourself to music. I really can't imagine the trend going on forever like this. The parade began and I put my mind off those juniors. Summerset march was wonderful, everyone was on task. Followed by 'We are Singapore' which was constantly driven on by the trumpets which were sort of giving encouragement and support. Then Allied Honour as the NCCs march in and it sounded just like usual except from the fact that it was a lot more louder and it sounded a lot more stronger than ever. Next was 'Made in Singapore', some clapped along and we earned cheers. Then General salute and fanfare, they were OK. Fanfare bar 17 to er...where ar? Euphoniums sounded so much better than usual. We all cut at the specified time, it's so much better than during the rehersals. Majulah Singapura was played with the most confidence ever. I gave a sigh of relief. It was partially over, now we wait for the speeches to be over and play the final march 'One people, one nation, one Singapore' and it was all over. It's just one more step. We could barely smile during the song of 'My people, my home'. The section was so rigid and we were worried about the result of this parade. We sway to the melody, our faces solem. When it was the speech, the three of them [Jaslyn, Shiting and Erica] were giggling with laughter! What are they thinking!? seeing their faces made me so much want to laugh too but I quickly looked away to retain my laughter. No way. It's a parade. But the giggling continued all the way until the [old clucky hen]'s speech and Elaine were staring at us so strictly. I could barely contain my laughter anymore but it was over. Our serious faces appeared once more as we played the final song. It was so long, my eyes were concentrated on the piece, it was good and better [except I forgot to repeat in the final time]. Peggy instructed us to go back to band room and over there, Joel told us to keep our instrument. It were only the clarinets... It was over. It was all over. It was the best performance I ever attended of hopes and dreams. Smiles and cheers, busy chattering about the performance were common after the dismissal. It was a good day and the seniors were proud of our achievements.  The best performance ever of hopes and dreams....  
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't know what had happened. I felt so nervous last night that I can't fall asleep even though I'm so sleepy. It was already twelve by the time I had finally landed on my bed and entered the world of dreams. Yet that alarm clock woke me up so early in the morning that it felt only like an hour had passed. I dragged myself out of the bed and refresh myself and got dressed. Then I gave that girl a morning call who replied she got up earlier than expected! I'm sure a lot of people can't fall asleep that night. It was nervousness that's doing the trick. So nervous that nothing can cheer me up.I'm so worried, what will the outcome be? What if it's a failure? What if... Then I reached school and after a while [Pammy was there to support!! =)] we fall in. I was almost jumping with nervousness. What are they doing to open the band room!? It's SO long!!! I rushed all the way up the stairs when we fall out [mr ong specially came to give us encouragement but he didn't stay] and I banged into everyone else and set up the instrument. I was so nervous, rushing everywhere like hell. Is the score there? Are the stands enough? How many had we brought down? The worries were endless until we tuned [and I took the wrong instrument out of carelessness] [ a lot of sec4s seniors were there to watch and direct us and helped us out with stuff like tuning and arranging of chairs] and very quickly, we settled down and soon the parade started. We played with lots of confidence. It were the best marches I've ever played. We're Singapore sounded OK and loud enough with energy. Made in Singapore was the best version which I've played so far. We cannot smile...I wanted to, but it was so...so nervous, so scared. The whole school was watching and every move you took was watched by the majors and section leaders closely. We played with confidence so proud hanging on faces. All except One people, One nation, One Singapore. This is the song I had not yet managed to master. In the end, I freaked out and forgot to repeat!! Then I walked extremely fast, ashamed of my mistakes. I didn't tell anyone except Jaslyn. Then we keep our instrument. I was intending on borrowing but was not allowed. Sigh. It was four days! A lot of time to practise! Why must they do the stock check at this time!? So we changed into our bright red t shirts and slacked off from aces programme. It left only half an hour when we reached there and a lot of other people slacked off, totally didn't join in. After that was the active citizen show which is being displayed with expiriences of various people. Then we went back to the band room to take our stuff and jackets to be washed and went downstairs to eat. Then went to find Jiayi to go to Plaza for bowling, Junyi went along. At first Qiuming want to go, but seeing Jaslyn's expression, he gave in. Such disappointment. I've forgotten to pass up the English homework and ran all the way back to school just to submit the assignment. Then we squeezed up in a bus and later saw joel [who yelled at me for blocking his way with extreme anger! I HATE HIM! Now I realised, he's not that obedient nor that capable! He's just ^&amp;$#%I)^ ] The three of them, Nizam, Masturah and Joel went to Plaza too. and the anger that stupid major had given me was beginning to erupt...I felt like hitting him so much! SO RUDE!! Then went to bowling, Jaslyn kept on trying to keep their trails but in the end lost them. So we went to bowling, me as the spectator and met another shuai ge there... cute actually. Pity from badminton, not band. haiz. Then Daphne, Wheelynn and Ivy were there too. After a while, the trio came. It occurs to me that those two, Nizam and Masturah must be getting alone! What else? They make a perfect pair! Plus, he's not as shuai as before ... his discipline level dropped so much after band, which kinda make him... er-not that perfect? Enough about him, I dun like him. There're other guys in this world, right? LOL. But Joel's shouts and yells had really dampened my mood for the day. Now I really kan ta bu shuang liaoz! Just for a minor matter, then he yelled. He think he who!? That's too much, all right!? But it's really a great day and many sec4s come back to see the band. I'm glad we've achieved what we wanted, the best performance ever... 
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tomorrow is the day. Since the day I had entered the main band of cck winds, we had never ever performed as an individual outside the school before. Each performance, each muster parade is just as important as any other. Each is led by countless amount of rehersal and practising. Till now, there isn't a single time when I am not nervous during the event. Since the sec4s seniors left, the pressure and stress upon us had evaporated like water. But when they come back, there is a feeling of guilt. Until now, I'm still not able to detect whether a pitch is sharp or flat. My rhythm is just as messy and unclear as before. And my embroshure is still not right. I'm so worried. Tomorrow is the day. The whole school will be there to watch us, our class, our seniors, our teachers and our principals. There is a lot of stress created, especially on the student conductor, Nizam. I remember vaguely seeing him putting the baton down with frustration with fanfare was over and we didn't get to play it at all. His brows were furrowed, a frown upon his face, his eyes staring straight with hatred. I don't want anymore mistakes to occur this time but mistakes can't be avoided. The more nervous you are, the more stressed you will become. But the whole school is out there! This is just Nizam's second conduct of the parade. I bet he is so nervous that he bound to break down any moment. Stress upon stress, the seniors knew that our band had been "Deproved" since they left. They had high hopes in us, they wanted us to get Gold, otherwise will only result in the retrench of Mr Ong. But I really don't know what to do, in this hopeless state we're in. Players we want, they left. Players which we want to kick out, they stay. I really really had no idea how long this band is going to survive. Kaingee just reprimanded me on how awful we had sounded. I really can't avoid that, the juniors all wanting to early depart because of their parents' wishes. I understood and I appreciated how much freedom my parents had both given me. They gave me no limits to freedom, the latest is during the concert until about 12am. I felt so frightened that time, my parents were not there to fetch me and I was walking, almost running on the deserted street, desperate for a source of light and hope... This is the time. The whole school will be out there. It's the judgement which the principal is going to give, the vision of the other part of the school on the band. This is a test, the only barrier we had to cross. This is the time, the right time. Although I am not filled with high hopes but I'm sure we'll do well! 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thursday! Time was passing slow enough, I had to admit. Heaven days over, hell days arrived, we know that, we all know that. It is expected, it is as if we know what is going to happen. I'm used to it though and I'm more defiant. So he circled the room, each time taking up a piece of work to comment. I had no idea why is he doing that? I mean, he's a teacher, isn't he? He's suppose to  teach  other than comment. When he came round my table, he took up my piece of work and began criticising. I  didn't  do that bad... did I? So when the bell rang, he asked for the work he wanted and he yelled like a maniac. Everybody did something and pass it up, all except me but I didn't bother about it and drive all his thoughts out of my mind. We all possessed a glummy look as I asked around for support of not completing his assignment. But I found none. Those who passed up were relieved and others were busy scribbling something down during recess. I don't get it at all. Is he that fierce!? I admit if he started yelling and shouting out of the blue, it is something to be afraid of. But that depends. This is ridiculous. Following was Chinese lesson which we spent the one period to learn the spelling and another for spelling itself. Right after was maths, which I'm extremely puzzled and confused with. What is she talking about? What ever.. Then is moral education which everybody greeted cheerfully. We were all excited about the baking of cookies as charity for the food and fun fair. We discussed about the items paid and it was settled for the next thursday. Then when I went down the stairs, I saw him. Now I know why people think he's shuai. His charming face, his bulging big eyes and his friendly appearence, his hairstyle...all were part of his fashion. My heart skipped a beat as our eyes met and I continued down the stairs, feeling my face going warm and blushing. He is  shuai  afterall!! lol. Did I really fall in? I'm so not sure...But I AM NOT. It's such a pleasure to be in the same school and cca with him. After that was the history common test which went through well enough [apart from miss yani's first ever shout] but I can't gurantee I will pass and score well. He was outside, there, waiting for our pieces of work. Most of the people went off, even people like harold and zhen ye. I really dunno why they will do his work. So I asked and all he wanted was to see how much we can write in 2 periods of time. Simple enough. But why do he have to yell and shout? So I hurried down the stairs, hoping for the band room to be opened but it was not. So I went home along with the gang instead. Yuhui and Jiayi quarreled over a minor matter. IT's so trival. It was really not worth to be mad about it. Though I do admit Jia Yi can be insensitive at times. So Jiayi headed off with a whiff and yuhui was mad with anger. God. Why things can be so easily solved yet complicated at times?? Yuhui got her mother to fetch her and Jaslyn had to buy ice cream for her mum. LOL. I'm going to morning call her!! haha. At a very very very early and unexpected time! As I strolled back to the bus stop, alone, I'm thinking...I'm really confused. which one? really... 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I remembered I had a very vivid dream today, early in the morning. I woke up to find myself unable to wake up. I wanted to continue the dream so much... it's not a dream about anything...I was so surprised to find myself dreaming of such imaginative things. I was at lot1, I remembered, with my two pals as usual and I searched my pocket for something...A wand, I think. I was so nervous to find it, but I never did. I felt so anxious, so desperate. I was murmuring spells in the book! In the end, the situation changed back to school. I began to ask each student for the wand... IT really felt so stupid. But it's so vivid. So real... I guess this is the result of reading too much Harry Potter... 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's Wednesday! But time seemed to be passing so slowly... Something dreadful. One good thing is that Mr Narain didn't come to school today! But we'll be expecting him tomorrow. damn. Just can't really let Miss Sarah go, she's such a nice teacher! It's better to have her than him! Right?? Uh huh. It's the truth. It's so sad to see her go...Heaven days over, torture hell is soon to be here once again. History remedial is cancelled. I think is because the teacher didn't want to teach and then came the enrichment. I spent my free time revising History. Starving like hell... Rushed to the canteen at the last 10min to grab something to eat. It's our last lesson and we received our certificates of participation and a small token, a highlighter, from Mr Laura. It's band!! Hooray! Hooray! HOORAY!! But something immediately dampen my mood when Mr Ong came! He told me to play my Eb major scale, concert Db major! Uh oh. Just anyhow play and many juniors escaped from the band room because of this reason. So I wander [and escaped!] around and wait for the time to play. Just when Huiqian entered, it's time to fall in. What? Fall in? But there isn't supposed to be any falling in! Joel had napha test, 2/5 had napha test, Peggy and Elaine had their remedials. Who will be there to direct? You won't believe it! Kevin is there to direcT! I must admit I almost burst out loud laughing while trying to tolerate his amusing and humourous commands. Really! [and he isn't strict enough. His smiling can cause everyone to slack off] LOL. After that, we headed downstairs with our instruments and of course the scores and stands. Later, we were told to take the chairs. But I slacked off. Too tired. And we tuned, my C is perfect. hehe. Elaine and Peggy arrived, which got everyone's groans as responses. It is a terrible thing to see one of them here after yesterday's so called 'scolding'. But rehersal turned out to be OK, though there're still things which I'm not sure of. We were swaying merrily, singing out loud, laughing and enjoying ourselves and giggling silently each time when we heard the speech was over. It was a really fruitful practice with Mr Ong around, (he suggested that we hang a life size portrait of him somewhere when he's no there to guide. LOL) he ensured that we always sound together and had the confidence to play out loud. This is the only barrier we had to cross. Once this is over, we can regain back all the trust. Peggy passed me her reed case and I can swear that I HAD PUT IT IN! Somewhere. Maybe in the blue ribbon case, which turns out to be Elaine's. Haiz!!! I'm going to check it out. So I spent the whole time while everybody else is rushing downstairs to fall in to check the cases for Peggy's reed case. Haiz. I SWEAR! Really! I had put it in...it might be the wrong case, but I did put it in!! Haiz. When I finally got to fall in, I landed in the position right next to Nizam! My heart gave a cheerful leap while those two infront turned around to give a sly grin. you know who, eh. But later...Harold fall in and later amin who stood next to me now. Sigh. He shifted position. I don't know that kind of feeling... when I'm sure I haven't got any kind of feelings for him! It's just that kind of shuai ge feeling...maybe. haha. There's another person who always cause me to smile with his blur looks and humour... and they never will know about it. Even though I know deep down, it's just my own wishful thinking... 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I really don't know what to do! Everything is like...climbing a mountain? At first, we're getting fine and we're reaching the summit soon. But once we reach the summit, you must go down again and going down is faster than going up. It takes just one section to slack, the whole band won't sound balance or motivated, confident. It takes just one person to change their position in their section and the whole band will sound so different. It just takes one roll for a person to dash down to the bottom of the mountain...   Today there is the napha test, which almost make me die with regret! It's just 10cm! JUST 10CM!! Yet that Mr Lee wanted to go home so much, he didn't want to sacrifice his time. What about mine!? I've never found myself putting others for blame when it's my very own fault. I didn't bother to practise half a year before. I didn't do my very best. I've disappointed everyone that had thought I can do it... I'm... so...sorry.    I hang a fake smile on my face, my heart is dead with regret. Why didn't I bother? WHY!? Sigh. So I dashed up to set my instrument and then get downstairs to play.    It just take one person to change their position to affect the whole band. We switched. Shiting flew to first while hani came over to the thirds. She couldn't play, my confidence disappeared and Nizam no longer had that kind of feel, that urge to enter on the first beat together. So we switched again, we changed over to Jaslyn and Hani went back to seconds. My old pal is back! We played through the pieces loudly and there was no problem until...   One people, One nation, One Singapore. So we changed again, she went back and Erica came in. There shouldn't be a problem. She's a primary school clarinetist! Just the problem with the loudness... Everything was quite OK... But it's pathetic! It's really pathetic! We had gone through everything yesterday! Yet it sounded a thousand miles different! God, what had happened!?    Nizam was in such fiery anger, something which I had not seen before since the last muster parade. It was the sec1s first muster parade, so we just let it off. But now, it's the second. We really cannot afford to lose anymore! Their comments had affected our band so much...  He no longer wear that friendly smile but a stern and strict face. It was so different. Everything can affect the mood of the music. The players who come in at the beginning must have the correct rhythm, correct pace, correct volume. They're the players who are supposedly to boot up other players' confidence. It's just like falling in, isn't it? Everytime, if someone started the trend to say 'ic' loudly with a special intonation, it will follow on and come to an end on a VERY PARTICULAR SPOILER!!! Qiuming!!! That idiot. And the amuse will die off. It's like the same, isn't it? But it's difficult to go up, but very very easy to come down...    And I didn't see Nizam coming out of the school... His anger, was something that had not been expressed a long long time ago... It's such a simple task, a task which every single one of us is capable to fufil. It's everyone's wish, but why? Why isn't everyone motivated? Many are dead with tiredness. My left leg is aching with pain...    I just wished everyone can fufil this very simple wish...  
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's monday! Monday means common test, monday means another week of working. Monday means...Monday means more hope! And brighter life! But Life certainly doesn't seem bright enough to bring more confidence to myself. The week is going to be full of work, rememdials, tests! It's endless working! And he's coming back! Oh no  oh no  OH NO!! I really can't imagine a week filled with desperate thoughts. Coming right up was the napha test, which I am sure I am going to fail. Can I really pass? I might have passed my 2.4...but my standing board jump will drag all my efforts down. At least something can cheer me up! That is the existance of more band practices than usual. From monday to wednesday, this means more time taken up to be sacrificed to band practising, but this is also important! This is the future of our band. I really don't know what to do, with all the sec1s wanting to quit band. It started off with Xuehua first and then more and more people joined in the trend. Is it really that difficult in order to join band? My self do not have any talent in music at all. I haven't got the passion for music. But do I join band? I'm asking the same question over and over again, to different individuals. I remembered that very special day, which is supposed to be a thursday if I'm not wrong. It's only the second day of school... But I'm notified that there's going to be a band open house. What's a band? A group? Or something? Ever since I went there, alone, I had fallen deep in love with music. Music is great. Music is everything! I simply demand people to at least stay with music when their choice is there. But I really can't. It's not really much... yet I see them, one by one, walking out of the band room, never seen again. That time, I remembered Jaslyn asking me a question, "What if we didn't join band?" That means I'm going to be totally alone. But that's not the case, they are still there. Even though, we're not really close friends, at least someone is there... There's the rehersal today for ndp rehersal tomorrow, which is supposed to be very very important. It's the event where we can manage to get the school to regain the trust in us. It's just a small little hope. Nizam stepped out again to conduct with his charming smiles, which not a single girl can avoid. I remembered during recess time, Jaslyn asked yuhui to see Nizam, to see whether he is handsome or not. Yuhui shook her head firmly. Oh my god. He is so shuai!! I spoke in defend. haha. He is shuai wad!! hehe. He's not the type who will say yes to defeat easily. He gives a special force everytime he conducts...a very special force which none of the passed out student conductors can give... It was a really hopeful rehersal, only that I hope there's more people around..I really wished once people had decided to put band as an option, they will not quit so quickly. They HAD put it there, and they shall take the responsibility. Yet one by one, they walked off the stage... I really don't know what's happening. I only wished it can be a fruitful band practice everytime.... 
      
</post>


</Blog>