<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CHAPTER 18   [Nicky’s P.O.V.]   *26th August*   [96 Days to Go]   I woke up feeling groggy in the morning…Lazily I slumped my body towards the kitchen.   Walking past Ben’s room I noticed he wasn’t in bed….hmm…that’s interesting, for once he actually got up early or maybe I just got up late…*sigh*…   Rubbing the sleep from my eyes I slouched on the chair and sat for a while listening to my own breathing…it seemed so quite…odd…   Scratching my head in concentration I began to think of possible solutions to as why the house was so quite, I wonder where Ben is, I still need to get him back for the last trick he pulled…urgh!...   My mind raced with images of the other day, I had to admit though Ben was a darn good actor…*sigh*…   I sighed heavily and motioned towards the kitchen to fix something to eat, there was a note on the bench…   ‘Gone out to work. -Ben’   Upon reading it my eyes bulged and my mind raced with thoughts…Ben had a job?! I wonder what he did. Was it a professional job?   Wow…   I stood in silence taking it all in…flabbergasted; I didn’t realize the knock on the door…   ‘Hello?! Ben! Open up!’ I heard a voice call from the other side.   Snapping out of my thoughts I gathered my senses and briskly  walked towards the door…   *knock, knock, knock, Bang, Bang, Bang!*   ‘Bennie? You in there?’ The male voice asked again.   My eyebrow jerked up…Bennie?.. What the hell? Was that Ben’s nickname?..   My mouth curved into a slight grin as I realized who was knocking on the door…must be Ben’s friend…I could gather information and use it against Ben if he ever tried anything stupid…hmm…interesting…   I unfastened the locks followed by a ‘click’ and opened the door for the stranger without hesitation…   I recognized the man instantly from Crystal Bar, he was one of   Ben’s friends I had seen when he got me fired.   His features were quite girlish but cute in a way…his broad shoulders and attire distinctively showed that he was a guy and his skin was like porcelain…*sigh*…he even had better skin than me…   ‘Uhh…hi…who are you?’ The guy asked before chuckling nervously.   I gave out a sigh of relief secretly after realizing he didn’t recognize me…   ‘Umm....I’m…Nicky, Ben’s friend, who are you?’ I answered him reluctantly…   ‘Oh, I’m Jake, Ben’s friend as well’ he stated while laughing light-heartedly.   He seemed like a pretty decent guy…hmm…I wouldn’t mind getting to know him, as long as he wasn’t as pig-headed as Ben…*sigh*…he could turn out handy as well…   ‘Ohh…’ I expressed.   Jake stood at the door like an idiot fidgeting with his hands…I guess the tension was pretty thick…   ‘Ben’s not home right now…did you want to come in?’ I spoke, deciding to break the silence first…   ‘Oh…okay…umm nah I don’t want trouble you’ he answered politely…   ‘Oh…it’s no trouble at all!’ I protested in a sugary sweet tone…   ‘Umm…okay then, sure’ he replied smiling at me…   I lead him into the house and poured each of us a cup of coffee before settling down to talk…   Turned out that Jake was a pretty cool guy…he was funny, easy going and down to earth…nothing like Ben…sheesh…no idea how they became such good friends, they have nothing in common at all…besides the fact that they’re both quite cute…   Hmm…let’s see…   Jake is Intelligent; Ben is slow and dim-witted…  Jake is funny; Ben is naturally stupid and annoying…   Jake is polite; Ben is pig-headed and arrogant…  Jake is easy going and respects women; Ben is un-gentlemen like and disrespectful…  Jake is decent; Ben is just plain cheap!   *sigh*…the list just goes on!   By the time I was finished with talking to Jake I managed to gather some dirt on Ben…   1. Ben used to have a pot-head haircut [I’d like to see that one!]  2. He was dumped by a girl when he was 16 [He’ll never live it down…HauaHaha]  3. He has a little sister called Ice  4. He hates being called Consti-Ben [No idea why…what does the ‘Consti’ part mean? Hmm…]  5. His weakness is money and girls  6. Looks are everything to him  7. He hates the color pink.  8. He keeps a teddy bear in his room but is embarrassed about it because he says it’s not masculine.  9. Gets jealous easy if he sees a hot chick with a good-looking guy.  10. He loves to show off about everything and he is quite big-headed [Jake didn’t tell me that one…I figured it out for myself…]  11. He has an imaginary fan club… [Figured that one out myself too]   I wrote the info down on a piece of paper and stashed it in my room for further use…maybe I could add to it…hmm…I sneer formed on my face as I thought of how I could use everything I had discovered against Ben…I got busy and conjured up some notes to remind myself…My first memo was…   • Use everything against him…    CHAPTER 19   [Ben’s P.O.V.]   *27th August*  [95 Days to Go]   Yesterday I went to work as usual…when I came back Nicky was cooking dinner…My heart skipped a beat when we exchanged glances…   She smiled at me innocently…was she up to something? My mind raced with thoughts and suspicion...I didn’t want to experience her vile ways of getting back at me again…I imagined what it would be this time…hmm…   ‘Sit down Ben’ she had said flatly.   I reluctantly took a seat near the table and waited for the dishes to arrive…when we had finally settled in I stared at her face searching for a little hint of suspicion…nothing…   Slowly I picked my chopsticks up and reached for the beans…I drew my hand away as I neared them remembering last times incident [Didn’t want that happening again]. Changing my mind I went for the fish…hopefully there was no poison in there…*sigh*…   Beads of sweat dripped from my forehead as my hand shakily clamped a piece of fish in the chopsticks…nearing my mouth I took a quick glance at Nicky making sure nothing funny was going to happen…   She remained calm and ate busily in silence not even glancing my way…slowly the fish entered my mouth and I rolled it around with my tongue while my eyes were closed tightly shut in anticipation, waiting for the hurtful blow to come my way, surprisingly enough…it was fine!   My heart beat slowed down and I began to eat without hesitation…  Lying in bed in my baby blue PJ’s, I stared at the ceiling wondering why she hadn’t put rat poisoning in the food…then I glanced at my clock and remembered work…   It was always 9.30am till 4.30pm…all I did was sit in my office and answer a couple phone calls and sign a few papers…   I’ve been working at B&J Corporations for quite a while now, Rainer introduced me to his adopted father’s company…I’m the Chief Executive’s assistant, but I hardly do anything all day because Rainer’s adopted brother, Derek takes his job so seriously!...   That’s a good thing though, I tend to sleep around and watch TV in my office a lot…did I mention I had a TV in my office? Well if I didn’t, I do, and it’s great! It’s just like being at home except I don’t have to pay for the electricity bills and I get paid too!   Thanks to Derek and Rainer, I have the perfect job….*sigh*….life would be so perfect if Nicky wasn’t around and if the stupid bold patch and bruises on my face would go away…   Oh wells…no point dreaming…or I’ll be late for work again…glancing at my clock it was 8:24am…I jumped out of bed and set   Mr. Patchy [My Teddy Bear] to the side…   ‘Bye Patchy’ I cooed at him.   His animated face stared back at me…*sigh*…it was his way of saying goodbye…I nodded my head at him…we had an unspoken understanding…   As usual I performed my usual routine…after stuffing my face with a quick breakfast and throwing on my suit I headed to the bathroom for my usual one hour facial assessment…   Clean shave? Check.   Neat hair? Check…oh no, hold on…   I picked up a comb lying on the bathroom sink and gently combed my hair fondly and styled it with some gel…   After a few excruciating moments I inspected my fine work…tilting my head from side to side and slanting this way and that  I inspected every angle to make sure not a strand of hair was out of place…   Managing to have covered my bold patch with some hair, my eyes glistened with pride… Ben, you’ve solved another dilemma!   Back to my check list…   Clean shave? Check.   Neat hair? Yup, yup, yup!   Good Facial complexion?   I leaned in closely to see the faint bruises that were caused by Nicky’s vicious, brutal acts…hmm…they were getting less clear, but still visible to the naked eye…   I rummaged through the cupboard behind the mirror to find something to hide the bruises….I didn’t have time yesterday so everybody could see the embarrassing bruises…   Surprisingly, no one mentioned it! Not even Derek who had the biggest and boldest mouth ever along with Jake…but I haven’t seen Jake lately…   Picking up a small tub of lotion I peered at the inscription…   ‘Foundation-For women who know themselves’   What the heck does that mean? I pondered for a while…Foundation?   Since when did I own this…and it was for women too!   For a fact…I would like to state that I, Benjamin Uy am 100% man! And I will NEVER be known as a man who owns a woman’s facial cream!   I puffed out my chest in the mirror with my reflection gazing back at me…now THIS was the Ben I knew! My eyes stared fondly at the dead, sexy male staring at me…who else could it be but ME!  *sigh*…My fans have got excellent taste if they like me so much…no, not like, love…they worship me….   The same, old, familiar saying popped back up into my head…   I, Ben, am literally a chick magnet…   Feeling good about myself I decided that either way women would love me…but I still had to do something about the bruises…  *sigh*…   I stood in thought for a few moments wondering how to cover up the stupid bruises done my Nicky’s vicious felonies [As I liked to call them]   My eyes gazed around the room and fell on the Foundation …hmm…maybe I could….but….no I can’t do that! Its girls stuff! But still…   I debated against my conscious over and over again…saying it was wrong to apply women’s make up on…but it was alright in desperate measures…*sigh*…   The result was very confusing…I glanced at my watch and my eyes bulged out of my sockets… 9:20am…if I didn’t leave right now I’d be late for work….Derek wouldn’t be very happy either…he loves to give me lectures about coming on time and taking my work seriously…*sigh*…   I decided to take a chance and I pampered my face with the stuff…after a few coughs I gave a quick glance at the mirror to make sure nothing drastic had happened…surprisingly enough everything was fine…and better! The bruises weren’t there anymore!   Forming a bright smile on my face I grabbed my suitcase and raced out of my apartment, down the stairs and towards my car…    CHAPTER 20  [Ben’s P.O.V.]   *27th August*   [At the Office]   ‘Morning Mr. Uy’ the secretary, Miss Tolentino smiled brightly at me…   I gave her a wink, my usual greeting…   ‘Morning Sir’ another female colleague spoke as I sauntered past her looking cool and sexy.   I gave out another wink.   *sigh*…I had a feeling that today was going to be a good day…I had managed to cover up the embarrassing bruises and bold patch  I had from Nicky’s felonies…   As I reached my office, Miss Javier another of my colleagues gave me a flirtatious wink…   ‘Hi Mr. Uy…’ she cooed while deliberately moving her hips from side to side in an attempt to seduce me…   I stared at her in wonderment…she really knew how to work a guy…but not me…no, no, no…I don’t date colleagues…if I could I would…but Derek strictly forbid me to go near any of his workers…he said it could lead to complications..*sigh*…   I winked at Miss Javier like I did with the other girls before entering my office and closing the door…   Settling down my briefcase I slumped onto my lazy boy chair and stared out at my window view…I had one of the big offices in the building with a large scenery view of Makati City. Seeing as how Derek and I were good friends, I had some privileges…but not as many as him, since he is the boss’s son…*sigh*…   I still don’t understand why Derek wanted to work as a minor when he first began and then make his way to the top when he could start out as the C.E.O. at the start…   I questioned him once and he answered with the most pointless words…   ‘I don’t want to cheat my way in life…a good boss is one who knows his people and position…not one who knows money and power…’ he had informed me…   I still don’t get what he meant by that…and I don’t think I ever will…scratching my head in confusion I opened my desk drawer and pulled out the remote for the TV.   Aimlessly I flicked the channels with nothing in particular to watch…anxiously, I waited checked my watch constantly while beads of sweat dripped down my forehead…   I loosened my tie awaiting my desired moment…Breathing in and out loudly I closed my eyes and listened to the shuffling of paper work and the repetitive ringing of office phones waiting to be answered…   A grumbling noise was heard every so often…beads of sweat dripped from my forehead as I cringed in anxiety with my eyebrows curved in an arch…   *Beep Beep*   ‘Lunch Break, I repeat, Lunch Break’   *Beep Beep*   I let out a long sigh of relief as I heard the all too familiar words coming out of the office speakers I longed to hear throughout the day...yum! Lunch Break!!! My favorite time of the day when I was working!   The grumbling was becoming unbearable through the grueling hours stuck in a stuffy office and listening to the sounds of workers busily walking around the building while shouting across the room for signatures to be signed and meetings to be held…   Don’t get me wrong, I don’t mind working here…it’s great! Derek is here and sometimes Rainer pops by to say hi…that’s why I like working here…the people are friendly and I have friends here too. Not to mention I don’t have to hold a lot of responsibility because Derek likes to do his job properly and without fault…he doesn’t like to laze around, he’s such a robot sometimes…*sigh*…   I guess he really takes the whole business thing serious seeing as how when his dad retires he is expected to carry on working here and maintain the company standard along with Rainer…but Rainer doesn’t really show up a lot…   I hastily walked to the cafeteria and picked up a food tray before lining up to be served…I love food…*sigh*…not to mention it’s free here!   I have to admit I’m a cheapo…but hey? Who WOULD want to part with money? Besides now that Nicky is going to live with me for…100…no…98?...no…96 days…yeah, that’s right…96 days…I need more money to support her…so I have to show up for work more…   I pondered for a while thinking about money and the problems that come with it…   Then I remembered Derek…he was probably inside his office being a workaholic as usual…he rarely comes out to eat…   Deciding to get him something to eat I told the worker behind me to save my spot and I sprinted to the back and got another tray for Derek…   When I got back it was my turn to be served…after giving a bow and saying a polite thank you I piled the two trays with food…   ‘Let me guess…for Derek?’ Mrs. Jang asked me with a jolly smile plastered on her face while her rosy cheeks shone in the cafeteria.   I nodded my head as an answer while smiling at her…   She was one of the many cooks at B&J corporations and she was great! Her food was so delicious and scrumptious!*sigh*…yummy!   ‘Have Fun Ben’ she called out to me.   I gave her a nod and a smile while I headed out of the cafeteria and towards Derek’s office…   Derek’s office was a door away from mine…Miss Javier was in-between us…   When I finally reached his office door I encountered another dilemma…how am I going to knock on the door? Both my hands are full by carrying both of the trays…   I winced in confusion trying to find another solution…I considered kicking the door open but that wouldn’t be very friendly…especially if Derek was talking to his dad…not to mention the BOSS of B&J corporations…*sigh*…   I had an urge to scratch my head like I always did when I was in thought…   After a few moments I came up with a few solutions…   1. Kick the door open.  2. Shout out to Derek to open the door.  3. Ram my way in  4. Knock on the door with my head   I pondered for a while wondering which one was best suitable for the situation…my tummy was beginning to grumble again and I was stressing over a little problem..*sigh*…   I settled upon knocking on the door with my head…   Here goes nothing…*sigh*…   *Knock, Knock, Knock*   ‘Who is it?’ Derek asked from the other side.   ‘It’s me…Ben’ I called out.   I heard the shuffle of papers and the sound of footsteps approaching the door…then the door clicked open…   Derek’s eyebrow jerked up at me with a questioning look…   ‘Here’s yours’ I told him while shoving a tray towards his chest…   After a few moments of Derek staring at his tray dumbfounded he took hold of the sides and said thanks before letting me in and walking back to his seat…   We sat in silence and ate out lunch…he seemed to be in deep thought, while I stared in space with nothing in particular in mind…I figured he was probably thinking of the merge of his company with other corporations or something…   Although Derek was older than Rainer and they weren’t related at all, besides the fact that they treated each other as brothers because Derek’s Dad had adopted Rainer…they had a shocking resemblance to each other…   When I first met them I couldn’t tell them apart at all…everything was exactly identical, there blonde streaked hair and facial features, their personalities and even the way they dressed…   But as the years progressed Rainer became more distant after an incident with his girlfriend Eugene…at least I THINK it was his girlfriend…he never gave us much details…just rambled on about the afterlife, reincarnation and stuff like that…   Derek didn’t change…his personality is still laid-back but serious when it comes to decisions about the future…but he still has time to joke around and stuff…   Rainer is always serious nowadays…you hardly see him crack a smile or a joke…   ‘How did you knock on the door if you were holding both of the trays in your hands?’ Derek asked me seemingly interested.   ‘Use my head of course’ I answered him while forming a grin on my face feeling proud of my solution…   So much for acting smart…Derek shot me another questioning look...*sigh*…   ‘Thought so….I knew you wouldn’t of thought of something simpler’ Derek shook his head and sighed loudly in defeat as if he could never figure me out…   I stared at him in confusion…   ‘What do you mean by that?’ I persisted curiously.   ‘Well…you could’ve just set the trays down on the table…instead of banging your head on my door’ Derek contradicted while taking a gulp of his Ramen noodles casually.   I gave him a dirty look and dropped the subject knowing Derek was right…   He laughed it off and shook his head at me…   ‘What’s that on your hair?’ Derek asked me in wonderment.   ‘It’s called G-E-L’ I retorted feeling smart that I had came up with a come back.   ‘I know that you idiot!’ Derek said defensively followed by a push on my forehead.   I groaned loudly while continuing to eat…   Derek gave out little sniffs…   *sniff, sniff* *sniff, sniff*   I glanced up to see what Derek was doing…he kept sniffing his hand…   ‘What are you doing?’ I asked him.   He ignored my question and touched the side of my cheek and ran his index finger across my jaw bone as if he was smudging off some dirt or something…   I gave him a weird look…   ‘What’s with you?’ I said while tilting my head along with  Derek’s movements.   Again, he sniffed his hand and rubbed his fingers together…   ‘Is…that, Foundation?’ Derek asked me, giving me his full attention…   My heart skipped a beat…how did HE know? My cheeks felt hot as my heart beat rapidly increased…how embarrassing…   I gave out a nervous chuckle trying to ease the tension…   ‘Don’t be stupid Derek…only GIRLS were foundation...I mean, COME ON would you ever catch ME…God’s gift to Women wearing Foundation?!’ I asked him while giving out a nervous snort.   Derek stared at me with a weird look…   I could feel my cheeks heating up while I looked around the room trying to avoid his gaze…after what seemed like forever Derek shrugged his shoulders and took another gulp full of noodles…   I let out a secret sigh of relief while I silently ate my noodles…   That was lucky!   I got home that day tired and exhausted even though I hadn’t really done anything all day…but hey? Nicky didn’t know that so she wouldn’t have to annoy me with being lazy now that she knew that I actually had a job.   She couldn’t say much either since she was a former bar-girl a couple days ago…   ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~TO BE CONTINUED~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      shot in hongkong -2002-  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CHAPTER 16  [Ben’s P.O.V.]  *25 August*  [97 Days to Go]  I woke up at 9.30am and lay in bed with my arms crossed behind my head while staring at the ceiling…  Thinking back I realized that ever since Nicky came my life has turned upside down…I’ve only been with her for 2 days…today is the 3rd day…*sigh*…thanks to sleep it cuts the long hours down…  I cringed as I thought about last nights events….I actually thought that she had forgiven me already and was being nice and feminine for a change…obviously I was wrong, after that Super Chili Powder….  As I laid in bed I began to feel a stabbing, sour sensation in the pit of my stomach….I lay still trying to find out what type of cramp I was having…My eyes bulged then narrowed as my nose twitched and my mouth jerked from side to side in wonderment…  That’s when it dawned on me…where’s the TOILET?!!!!!  I jumped out of bed and desperately opened my door before jolting to the toilet…  When I was finished I gave out a sigh of relief and exited the toilet…  ‘Those packets of chili powder sure do wonders!’ I said with a whistle and a sigh…WoW!  I patted my stomach and headed towards the kitchen in search of something to eat…  ‘Awww…shit! Who died in HERE?’ I heard Nicky’s disgusted voice as she entered the toilet.  Ignoring her rude comment I continued to walk to the fridge while yawning sleepily…  Rummaging around I found some milk and cereal lying around somewhere…busily I dug into my breakfast, narrowing my eyes to see how many smiley faces I could find in my cereal…there sure were a lot…I’ve never seen so many smiley faces…  I gazed in wonderment while busily munching away on my cereal…  ‘What are you doing Ben?’ Nicky asked me with her voice that made me feel like she was accusing me and saying that I was doing something stupid…  I pondered for a while…come to think of it…she always speaks to me in that tone…hmm...  I shrugged off the idea while busily munching away…  ‘Counting how many smiley faces I can find in my cereal’ I answered casually not bothering to look up at her…  ‘Idiot’ she mumbled  *Whack!*  I gave out an exasperated groan after she hit the back of my head…  ‘What was THAT for?’ I asked her annoyed that she had made me lose concentration…I was up to 31 smiley faces…  ‘You idiot…they’re all smiley faces!’ she said sounding impatient…  What was HER problem…she was the one who made me get the runs…if you know what I mean…and she got the last laugh when she didn’t HESITATE at all to pour all THREE of those chili powder packs into the stupid beans…*sigh*…  ‘How do YOU know that they’re all smiley faces?!’ I counter attacked her…  She gave out a hopeless groan…*sigh*…she wasn’t a very good actor…she only pretended to be angry…I knew so, why you may ask? Well simple. I know all girls…secretly she’s actually dying to kiss me…  ‘You Bimbo! Read the cereal box!’ she spat out desperately trying to get a point through…  ‘Fine then!’ I retorted making sure I rolled my eyes in front of her face…  What was HER problem…sheesh…she’s just going to make a fool of herself…  I picked up the cereal box with my hand while the other was clutching onto my spoon…giving her a nasty look I picked it up while munching the cereal bits in my mouth…  ‘Smiley-O’s’ I read out loudly so she could hear…  ‘Yeah…so?’ I asked her dumbfounded.  ‘Read the bottom you idiot!’ she said again before folding her arms and doing MY pose…the one I called ‘The Cool Pose’  I did as I was told and obeyed like a little boy…  ‘Smiley-O’s…Smile, coz every single Smiley is always smiling back at you!’ I mumbled while skimming through the words…  I looked up at Nicky dumbfounded…was she trying to make a point again?...what was her problem?...here I was minding my own business trying to count how many Smiley faces I could find in my cereal and she hits me on the head for no apparent reason…honestly the brain of this girl is seriously damaged!  Again, she let out a defeated groan before walking away… I stared at her turning figure as she went to retrieve the milk from the fridge…  Shrugging off the incident I returned to busily counting how many smiley faces there could be in my cereal…1…2….3….4….  ‘Where do you keep the milk?’ Nicky’s frustrated voice came back into hearing range…  ‘In the fridge….idiot’ I said mimicking her while mumbling ‘idiot’  I know that you pea brain! There’s only an empty carton of milk in there…where do you store the OTHER cartons of milk?’ she asked me again waving her arms around like a mad woman…  I stared at her confusingly and flabbergasted…what was the weirdo going on about now?  She groaned in annoyance.  ‘Give me your car keys…I’m going shopping’ she said demandingly…while motioning me to throw her the keys with her hand…  Now THAT I understood…no way was I lending her MY car…she would probably run off with it…could she even drive? Was she even educated enough?!  I started having a panic attack…think FAST Ben…she doesn’t like waiting…you’ll get another slap on the head if you don’t come up with an answer…I could hear a clock ticking in my head…beads of sweat dripped from my forehead…  My forehead creased in lines of stress while my eyebrows arched into a frown, my eyes narrowed desperately searching for an answer…  ‘I’m g-g-going…’ I started  ‘Spit it out you retard!’ she commanded at me  ‘I’m…I’m….GOING WITH YOU!!’ I blurted out in one desperate attempt.  I gave out a sigh of relief…now I was free of the stress and pressure…calmly I wiped away the bead of salty sweat that I had formed on my forehead from the ordeal…  My breathing slowly regulated as I took in deep breaths…  ‘Fine!’ Nicky answered before walking towards her room to change…  *sigh*…this was going to be a LONG day…  ‘I’m going with you’…’I’M going with YOU’… ‘NO…I’m GOING with YOU’….I walked and talked to myself while thinking of how easily and swiftly I had managed to dodge another hit from Nicky…*sigh*…I was just too good…and to think…no, I Benjamin Uy…certainly did NOT go into stress or panic at the time…*sigh*…I really was the most talented and calm guy in the world…     CHAPTER 17  [Ben’s P.O.V.] *25th August*  [At the Markets]  I pushed my dark shaded glasses up, making sure that they weren’t falling down…it was pretty cold today…  Following Nicky I walked closely behind making sure that no one had recognized me….I didn’t want to be seen with a pig like her…seeing as how I was CLEARLY the Beauty in this whole crisis….not in a girly way of course…I was OBVIOUSLY manly and masculine…I mean, just look at these bulging muscles!  I pulled my beanie over my head…this was very, very embarrassing seeing as how Nicky had managed to yank A LOT of my hair out and now I had an extremely LARGE bold patch on the side of my head..*Sigh*…   tried dressing casually…but everywhere I went people stared at me…was it because I was dressing too cool for someone with a bold patch and a couple bruises on his face *Sigh*…I must’ve looked like a gangster on patrol….it would explain why I kept glancing around to see if any hot chicks were looking my way…  ‘Hurry up Ben...I’m hungry and I want to buy milk!’ Nicky said turning around with her arms crossed impatiently…  ‘SHhh…SHhH!!’ I shrieked out desperately trying to get her to shut up…  I didn’t want her shouting my dead, sexy name out to everybody in the supermarket…it would give me a bad name if I was taking orders from HER…let alone, following HER…I mean, don’t get me wrong but I am what girls dream of…what they fantasize about…I am their dream hunk…yep…that’s me for you, God’s gift to women…  It’s not that she’s not pretty or anything…she is…believe me, but would it hurt if she acted a bit more feminine and if she made me look a bit more manly and in control..*sigh*…  ‘Don’t you SHHh ME Ben! Get your BUTT here right now!’ Nicky spat out, obviously annoyed and offended.  She stomped her foot on the ground and pointed at her feet forcing me to beckon at her call...  I lowered my head in embarrassment as passer-bys stood and stared at us oddly…  ‘Hurry up will you!’ I hissed at her when everybody had resumed doing whatever they were doing…  ‘You were the one that wanted to come along!’ she accused me.  I kept quiet not wishing to cause a scene…hopefully no one from Crystal Bar was around..*sigh*…so embarrassing they would see…Me… ‘Voted sexiest man alive’ with a simple Bar Girl...how demeaning of me…  We went into the markets and she picked up a carton of milk as well as some groceries and meats…  ‘That’ll be $29.40 thanks’ the counter lady said flatly  I gazed around expecting Nicky to pay; when our eyes met she stared at me expectantly…  I stared back at her refusing to give in…no way was I going to part with MY money…she was crazy!  We got out of the store…Nicky had a bright smile on her face while I slouched and walked carelessly with a glum expression on my face…  You can obviously see who had to pay…*sigh*…  ‘I’m Hungry’ Nicky complained.  ‘Great lets go home and eat’ I said excitedly in a hurry…  ‘No…let’s not go home and eat…let’s eat here’ Nicky replied with a sneer on her face.  Damn! She must have read my mind…*sigh*…no point arguing with the MAN of the house…seeing as how she seems to overpower me 99.9% of the time…urgh…  We reached the food court and she ordered Mac Donald’s for us while I sat down, left with the groceries at a secluded table waiting for the food to come…  When she came back we both ate our burgers devouring the taste…mmm…she was right, it was nice to eat Mc Donald’s for a change…  While we were eating I discovered the most evil plan I had conjured so far…this was going to be good…I smiled constantly…  ‘What the hell’s the matter with you?’ Nicky asked me annoyed at my happy expression…  ‘Nothing…’ I replied before looking in the other direction waiting for the perfect time to strike…  ‘Idiot’ she would mumble…  After we ate I offered to carry the groceries…she got up from her seat and I followed closely behind her…  As I walked behind her I tried my best to look as sad and down as a lost puppy…I walked slowly and lugged the groceries with me…people stared at me and gave out sympathetic whines of pity towards me…obviously assuming that I wasn’t the most happiest person in the world…  Nicky took long, quick steps…occasionally she would glance back at me to make sure I was keeping up with her…  When I was slow enough…she turned around and walked towards me…  ‘Oh stop being a wimp! They’re not THAT heavy’ she grumbled.  I retaliated and held onto the groceries as she reached out to carry them for me…  ‘Let go!’ she whispered with malice  I remained solemn and held onto the groceries with my dear life…  When her force was strong enough I let go of the food and it tumbled onto the floor with a thud…  Everyone stared our way…that was my queue…  I collapsed to my knees and picked up the groceries one by one while giving out soft whimpers and sobs so the whole food court could hear…okay so maybe it wasn’t that soft...but as long as it worked…  ‘What’s the matter? I’ve never seen a full grown man cry before’ a woman approached me full of concern…  This girl was quite cute too…  ‘I can’t say…’ I gave out a little wail…  ‘Shhh…it’s okay…you can tell me…’ she comforted me while the rest of the audience had crowded around me   From the corner of my eye I could see Nicky’s flabbergasted look as she watched everybody walk towards me to see what the commotion was…  ‘Oh…it’s nothing, just the children…they need me…’ I told her in-between sobs…  ‘What children?’ she asked me confused.  ‘The homeless children, I’ve dedicated my life in raising them and sheltering them…they need me’ I sobbed and whimpered creating more effect…  ‘I don’t have enough money…today I was fired…my boss told me that I wasn’t putting enough effort into my work…but I can’t help it, the children need someone to care for them…there’s 5 of them…they’re so young and precious to me…’ I said trying hard to form tears in my eyes…  ‘Oh you’re such a saint!’ the woman cried out in sympathy…  Everyone else cooed at me and told me it was going to be okay…  ‘Today I came to the markets minding my own business and spending my last $30 dollars on groceries to feed those precious little things…and…and…’ I broke down crying again acting more pitiful…  ‘It’s okay…you can tell us…’ the lady said putting a comforting hand on my shoulder as she knelt down beside me and the spilt groceries which were on the floor now…  I wailed and cried like a lost child…by now I had gotten the attention of the employees behind the counter of every food stall…  ‘That...that cruel and heartless woman over there, she was trying to snatch my groceries away…I tried explaining to her that the children needed them…and sh-she said…’ I stuttered as I spoke while pointed an accusing finger at Nicky…  Everyone turned her way and stared at her accusingly and disgusted at her…she gave me the most evil glare you could ever imagine…inside I was laughing my head off…but outside I had to play it cool in order to get maximum satisfaction…this was way too fun…  ‘She said…that…homeless children were….were….USELESS AND UNLOVED AND THEY DESERVED TO DIE!!!!!!’ I blurted out while tears trickled down my cheek…  I bawled my eyes out while the lady gave me a comforting hug…  I didn’t have to look but I could tell that everyone was glaring at Nicky like she was the most disgusting and fowl thing that ever roamed the planet…*sigh*…my plan was working perfectly…now all I had to do was finish it off…  ‘Well…*sniffle*…I don’t want to bother you…good, GOOD people but I must be going now…I can’t keep the children waiting…they need me, but I have NO IDEA how I’m going to explain that they will have no dinner tonight…or supper…or breakfast the next day…’ I said giving a sympathetic look to all the by-standers…  They gave me sympathetic, pitiful looks with little whines of sorrow…  One by one I slowly picked up the soiled vegetables from the ground while placing them in the paper bag glumly…  ‘Wait! I think I’ve got some money I can help you with!’ the lady said trying to help.  ‘No…I can’t take that…it wouldn’t be right.’ I refused.  ‘Yes it would...I want to help the children too!’ the woman reassured me…  ‘well…if it’s for the children….thank you…your help is kindly appreciated…wait till they hear the news…such an angel has come down to help them..’ I said with gratitude and relief in my voice…  I took her money and held it in my hand as if it was gold…soon after all the other people came up to me and said a few kind words as well as handing me money to by groceries for the ‘homeless’ children…*sigh*…  As they walked past me…they shot Nicky evil glares and gave her rude comments…  ‘Shame on you!’ one would say.  ‘You’re the one who doesn’t deserve to live!’ someone would spit at her..  ‘You need help!’ another would retort  Nicky opened her mouth to speak as her eyes bulged in fury and wonderment…in the end she sighed and crossed her arms in defeat…  NOW who got the last laugh…I secretly smirked to myself knowing I had the upper hand now…not to mention piles of money in my pocket…  When we finally got home Nicky couldn’t stop shooting me evil glares….  ‘What? Don’t you care about the homeless children?’ I asked her innocently while taunting and teasing her…  ‘Cheap bastard’ she mumbled…  ‘Say that to my face young lady!’ I dared her.  ‘Cheap threat!’ she yelled out before stomping off in one of her fits again…  Today was actually quite fun…although I paid P1,537…it was sure worth it…I managed to earn P9,895 as well as humiliating Nicky in front of a whole crowd…*sigh*…I was just too good…  *****************TO BE CONTINUED**************** 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I KNOW IM A HOTTIE!!! *wink*  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Chapter 11  [Ben’s P.O.V.] When we finally got to my apartment, I made sure she saw me give her a big glare before getting out of the car…  I still have no idea why she wanted 100 days for…and she didn’t seem like a BULC member so I haven’t a clue why she’d want to stay with me…  Maybe she was an ‘undercover’ BULC member, and she was supposed to report back to my fellow fans, to see how I acted in these types of situations…  I nodded my head agreeing with my theory…Benjamin Uy….you really are something aren’t you…  I smiled to myself leading the way to my apartment knowing I had figured out, yet another problem…  When we got to the front of my apartment I punched in the code and slid in easily while she followed closely behind like a second shadow…I had to admit, being the sexiest man alive makes you become anxious and paranoid at times…But I guess that’s the down side of being ‘God’s gift to women’…  Switching the light on, I slumped on the couch and exhaled and inhaled slowly taking deep breaths…finally, some relaxation…ahhhh…  ‘Hey!!! Shit-Ben…where do I sleep?!’  I stirred in my peaceful serenity when an arrogant feminine/Manly voice said in menace…  ‘HeLoOOo? Anyone there?!’  There it was again…please tell me I’m dreaming…I squinted my eyes shut hoping that I was just having a nightmare….  …Quiet….  I breathed in a sigh of relief and busied myself trying to get comfortable on the couch with my eyes still securely shut…I tossed and turned while hugging a soft cushion…  Sleepily I lay in a comfortable position and slowly began to drift off…  Something was tugging at my hair…I brushed my hair with an easy swift of my hand….after twitching my nose I prepared myself to drift off…  Again, there was this annoying tugging sensation on my hair…figuring I was just being paranoid I didn’t move and instead of swatting at my hair again I waited for the tugging sensation to go away…. ‘AAhhHHhHHhhHH!!!!!’  My eyes widened in shock and pain as I gently stroked my precious hair, I grumbled in annoyance and turned around to face my attacker…it was probably Jake being a jealous idiot because my hair was more silkier and softer then his so he had decided to yank out a whole clump of my hair…daMn idiot...  I turned around and my eyes grew wider…that lesbian girl…Sheesh…she just can’t get enough of me huh? I figured that she had yanked my hair out to put in her personal stash of her ‘BULC member possessions…’  My eyes narrowed into dime slots as I gave her my best evils…with my lips pressed together showing I was extremely annoyed I tried to intimidate her and make her feel uneasy…  She stood there with her arms crossed not the least bit moved by my attempt…Obviously my plan back fired…if I was trying to make someone feel small and nervous…That person would be me…*sigh*  ‘Stop looking constipated and tell me where I’m supposed to sleep’ she retorted.  ‘What?!...ME? Constipated?!’ I yelled back in astonishment  ‘Yeah YOU!!!’ She said emphasizing the word ‘you’  I had to admit…for pretty girls like her, she sure knew how to make me feel inferior, and I thought that GUYS were meant to make girls feel that way…  I gave out an exaggerated groan making sure I did it right in her face to show how annoying she was…  ‘Sleep anywhere…’ I replied.  ‘If you wanted to know you could’ve just asked you know no need to pull my hair’ I started again sounding aggravated.  Her face turned cherry red…huh? Did I say something wrong? I stood there dumbfounded wondering what had gotten her in such a crap mood…  ‘I DID ASK!!! YOU IDIOT!!! YOU WERE TOO BUSY IN LA-LA LAND!!!’ she blew her top off  Wow…this girl sure had temper problems…maybe I should steer clear of her for a couple of days…or maybe the next 100 days….  She stamped her foot like a little girl…in other circumstances I’d say she looked cute when she was angry…but right now, since I wasn’t in the ‘best’ mood I could be in, she had a shocking resemblance to a stubborn cow….hmmm….  I stood there staring at her while she chucked a tantrum…this was amusing, If I had been more tired then I already was…I would’ve been certain she had given out a loud, long… ‘MoOOOoOoO’  *Whack!!!*  While I was thinking, the lesbian Girl had somehow gotten close enough to me to whack me at the back of my head…urGh…she sure was violent.  ‘What the Heck was that for?!’ I said annoyingly at her while touching the back of my head.  She smirked that same, annoying smirk she always had…Man, she was really pissing me off…if she wasn’t a girl I would’ve wiped that smirk off her face by throwing a big, fat punch on her face…Ooo…that would be fun….  ‘You were staring at me you idiot…don’t you know it’s rude to stare?!’ she retorted rudely…  I stood there flabbergasted and dumbfounded…had I been staring? I didn’t realize…whoops...hehehe…  ‘Just staring at a stubborn Cow’ I said while facing the other way and feeling cool about my come back  *Thwack!*   ‘Aww…shit!!’ I yelled in pain when she hit me for the second time on the back of my head…  I spun around to face her with my deadly glare [Dime slot eyes and pressed lips]…She didn’t seem to be moved at all…*sigh*…again, I had failed my attempt to make her feel inferior…Damn Woman…  I ignored her this time and walked briskly to the bathroom intending to inspect the damage she had done to my hair…  I checked all parts of my hair and found a big chunk of hair missing from one side!!!...I leaned in to inspect the damage caused by the tyrant…  Oh shit…there was a clear and visible bold patch…great…not only was my face badly damaged by her Man-fist punches but now she had given me a frigging bold patch!!!  This was by far…the most miserable day I’ve ever had…how was I going to face my lovely fans?! They’d probably ditch me for someone who isn’t even half the man I am…they could even begin to worship ‘Fat Cat’…and that’s not even a bloody man!!!  Or maybe they’ll like pimps better…  *Ben’s Dreamy Thoughts*  Fat Man sitting on the couch watching TV surrounded by empty packets of chips and beer bottles…  His laughter sounds the room while he’s surrounded by my former fans…that are showing him affection…they used to do that to me too…  I’m sitting in the corner of the room while all the hot girls surround that-that-that….DOLL BLUDGER!!!   I crouch in the corner hugging my legs while rocking back and forth with endless tears streaming down my face….  ‘Girls…w-what *sniffle* a-about…your s-s-sexy man *sniffle* Benjamin Uy?’ I say in-between snuffles…had they completely forgotten about me?  ‘What about *sniffle* BULC what happened? *sniffle*’ I asked them while hugging myself tightly…my clothes were soaked with tears now…  One of the girls tilts her head towards me while she caressed the fat man’s chest….  ‘BULC? That was in the past…I don’t even know why I was a member of that stupid club…it’s BBLC now…’ she said in disgust while she talked about BULC…  How could she? It pained my heart…she was once one of the girls who loved me the most…  ‘BBLC?’ I asked her dumbfounded at her retort…  ‘BULL BLUDGER LOVERS CLUB!!!’ all the other girls screamed excitedly in unison while they pampered that disgusting animal like he was God…it was a disgusting sight…  From the corner of my eye I saw Fat Cat walk by with more fans surrounding ‘it’  ‘NoOOoOoOoOooOooo!!!’ I yelled in agony not wishing to believe I was unloved…  *End of Ben’s Dreamy Thoughts*  ‘No!!’ I shrieked.  Huh? What? Oh, it wasn’t real…Thank God…  I thought about what I had dreamt of…BULC? I think this is a sign from God that I have to do something unless I want that dream to become a reality…*sigh*    CHAPTER 12  [Nicky’s P.O.V.] After Ben walked to the bathroom ignoring my hit to his head I smirked to myself yet again, that idiot was such a sissy…  I looked at my surroundings and went exploring in his apartment…kitchen, bathroom, toilet, 2 bedrooms, and a family room…hMms…not bad I guess  One bedroom was Ben’s…I could tell because there were posters of cars and girls all over the place…the arrogant pig-head…*sigh*…  In the other bedroom it had a mattress and that was about it…I decided that this would be my new room…perfect…  Busily I went to the family room and grabbed my few belongings and settled in to my new bedroom making myself at home…  Just as I was about to go to sleep Ben barged into my new room like an idiot…  ‘By the way…what’s your name?’ he asked me flabbergasted…  He looked like he had just run a marathon…  I stood there dumbfounded for a while before replying…  ‘NIcky…Just call me Nicky’ I said not letting my guard down just incase he was planning to get revenge on me…  ‘Nicky hey? Hmms…that’s a nice name…but I prefer stubborn cow or lesbian girl’ he said before jolting out of my room like a flash…  I sat on the mattress confused at what he had said…when I had taken it all in and realized he was insulting me I ran out of my room and it was my turn to barge into his…  I turned the door knob furiously before realizing he had locked the door already…why that conniving bugger…  ‘Open the door Benjamin Uy!!!’ I yelled while pounding furiously on the door making a big racket…  ‘Stubborn Cow! Stubborn Cow! Stubborn Cow!’ he taunted and teased on the other side…  ArgH…that arrogant brat…Damn Him!!!  ‘OPEN THE FRIGGING DOOR RIGHT NOW IF YOU DON’T WANT A FISTFUL IN YOUR LOUD MOUTH!!!’ I yelled at the top of my lungs while turning as red as a tomato…  ‘I’m not completely stupid you know!!!’ he yelled back, obviously refusing to budge from his position…  ‘I’ll kick this door down if I have to…then you’ll be sorry…’ I said in a deadly whisper loud enough so he could hear me seething with wrath…  There was silence on the other side…he was probably thinking of an escape route…hahaha…he was in deep shit now…by the time I’m going to be finished with him…he’ll have a hell of a lot things to complain about…possibly a medical bill…  ‘Open the door now or I swear I’m going to kick this door down and you’ll be in for it!!!’ I yelled again deciding to give him a second chance…  ‘…1…’ I said beginning my count down…  ‘…2…’ the tension was beginning to increase along with the suspense…I backed away from the door intending to get a run up…  ‘…3!!!’ I yelled before charged at the door and closing my eyes…  Just as I was about to hit the wood of the door Ben unlocked the door and I ran straight into him causing him to fall down with a thump…  I heard him curse to himself about the pain he was in…I leaned in closely to see his hurt expression his forehead was creased and his eyebrows formed a frown…  For the first time…I began to realize that Ben really wasn’t a bad guy…he just acted like an arrogant pig now and then…but other then that, he was alright…his face showed sincerity and honesty…and he sure knew how to hold his temper! Although he thought he was all that it did make him look like a fool…even if he was quite cute…  Who knows…maybe he could be my entertainment for the next 100 days to come…I stared intently into his eyes while he looked into mine…It seemed as if he was searching for something…like he was trying to understand me…to find a weakness in me…  After a few moments we began to realize the awkward situation and both of us quickly turned away as I realized I was laying on top of him…I got up quickly and smoothed out my PJ’s…  He sat up from the floor and I got a good look at him…his PJ’s were very peculiar for a guy…Blue Care Bear teddy top and Starry Pants with Moon shapes as well…  I sighed loudly while tsking him…and giggling light heartedly…  ‘What’s so funny?’ he asked me confusingly  ‘Nothing…I’m going to sleep now...I think I’ve already gotten enough pay back for today…just looking at your girlish PJ’s will already make you embarrassed’ I said before walking back to my room trying to suppress my laughter…  I could picture Ben right now staring down at his PJ’s and looking in the direction I had walked in…then staring back down at his PJ’s before actually getting the message…and turning bright red…  I giggled to myself…*sigh*...Ben really was the most slowest pig ever…  I settled down on the mattress and pulled the covers over my body...I began to think how annoying and irritating Ben could be…him and his arrogant ways…it was quite amusing seeing him angry…  I began to drift off to sleep…     CHAPTER 13  [Ben’s P.O.V.] I woke up at 11:00am…earlier then Nicky of course…  Today is the 23rd of August...I decided that a Contract should be drawn up if both of us were to keep our word…obviously I would, I’m not that dirty and I don’t resort to trickery…but I can’t say so much about her…  I got out a piece of paper while I busily wrote down a contract agreement…My tongue always seems to stick out when I’m concentrating hard…and it was sticking out again…I never seemed to notice it before…but now I do…  When I was done it read-  Evidence of Contract Agreement  Nicky will stay with Benjamin Uy for 100 days counting day one as 23rd August…During the 100 days…she is not to physically abuse or insult Benjamin Uy, as he is God’s gift to women and should be treated with respect…  After 100 days when it lies on the 1st of December, Nicky is required to return the belongs that she had dirtily stole ferociously from innocent Benjamin Uy…who is the victim in this whole dealing.  On the bottom of this sheet, please sign your name as prove of agreement…going back on the deal will cause severe punishment to Nicky only as she is not Benjamin Uy who is a literal chick magnet…  Signature here Signature here Nicky- Benjamin Uy-  ----- I stepped back to admire my work…It looked a bit plain to me so I decided to decorate it a bit…on the side a drew a devil with horns…and an angel with a halo…I think these two pictures represent Nicky and I perfectly…  I trudged to her room feeling pleased with myself that I had thought of the whole contract thing and made it as fair as it could possibly be…I no longer thought that she was a BULC member...so I didn’t have to worry that she would tell everyone else that I was mean…  I knocked on her door and no one answered…it was 11:30am now…  I quietly twisted the door knob and opened the door silently…it made a slight creaking sound that made me wince…beads of sweat dripped down my face hopping that she wasn’t going to ambush me with an uncalled for attack…  Who ever said that girls were submissive must’ve had severe brain damage…I erased all thought of that stupid, false statement and decided to rely on my senses instead…that is if I want to survive the tyrants ferocious attacks on me…  To my relief I let out a contempt sigh as I saw her on the floor snoozing away like a pig…I crept up towards her face and poked her a little in the cheek trying to wake her up…she twitched her nose in reply and tossed her body to the other side…that didn’t seem to work…  This time I prodded her near her shoulder trying to get her to stir and wake up…nothing happened again…I whispered in her ear trying to tell her to wake up but to no avail she didn’t budge…  She sure was a heavy sleeper…after coming up with the conclusion that I wasn’t trying hard enough I decided to be more aggressive…besides I wanted payback for yanking a big clump of my hair out…  I reached out and her hair was in my grasp but then I thought to myself…what if she counter attacked and this was just a plan of hers and when I least expected it she would jump out at me…I withdrew my hand as more beads of sweat ran down my forehead…  Forming a frown on my forehead I had no idea what to do…this was the perfect chance to pounce on her and catch her off guard but I didn’t know what evil thing I could do to her…urgh…Benjamin Uy you really are thick sometimes…  I decided to see if she was faking it or not…  ‘Nicky…wake up!!!’ I said quite loudly…  She gave out a groan and mumbled a little before settling back down and pulling the sheets over her shoulders…  I let out a sigh of relief knowing I still had the perfect chance to get my revenge…  At that time I couldn’t think of anything really evil to do to her besides pull her hair…as I grabbed her hair in my hand gently I stopped again…and I thought of an evil plan…I smirked to myself and silently crept out of her room and into mine…  I got my stereo system and placed them all besides her ears completely surrounded her…then I cranked up the volume and put on a loud Rock Music CD in…  When the speakers were placed in position I crept back out of her room with the remote control in my hand…then I got a mop and held onto the opposite end while edging towards her face…I smothered her with the mop and I hear her muffled sounds…it seemed as if she was cursing…as soon as I sensed that she was going to wake up I quickly with drew the mop from her room and closed the door while pressing the ‘PLAY’ button on the remote…  All of a sudden I heard her scream as the extremely loud rock music boomed throughout the whole building…*sigh*…Music to my ears…this was my pay back for sure…and this wasn’t the end of it…  I heard heavy footsteps nearing her door…I held on to the door knob tightly not allowing her to escape the loud music…  ‘BEN!!! I’M GOING TO KICK YOUR SORRY ASS FOR THIS!!!!!!!!!!’ she screamed her lungs out…  I smirked to myself knowing I had got her this time…  After a few moments of cursing and threats directed my way I decided to end her torture and I turned the speakers off…she was probably deaf by now…I sneered when I finally let her out…  I turned around and walked to my room intending to get down to business and get her to sigh the contract leaving her free from her loud prison…  *Thump*  I heard the shrill scream of Nicky…I ran towards the direction and saw her lying flat on the ground clutching her elbow…  When I finally realized that the mop was wet and she had slipped on the puddle of water the mop had left behind I felt guilty…I didn’t mean to go that far…  For the next 5 minutes she kept complaining that her arm hurt so I took her to the doctor…he said that she had a fractured arm so he placed a cast around it…  When we got back she gave me a cold glare and continued to make me feel more worse then I already did…she threw curses and insults my way…most of which she called me an arrogant pig….  I constantly said sorry to her and repeated myself saying that I didn’t intentionally want to make her fall…  It was amazing how many curses she could say in one breath…I counted a total of 27…I never got bored of hearing her insult me…Don’t get me wrong…I found it really offensive but she sure knew a lot of swear words…not to mention threats that she directed towards me menacingly…     CHAPTER 14  [Ben’s P.O.V.] After she was out of breath I decided to bring up the contract…I sauntered to my room and got the agreement sheet I had drew up earlier….I was proud of my efforts…  I handed it to her without saying a word…  ‘What’s this?’ she asked me confused.  ‘Read it’ I replied casually…  I heard her busily reading the page while her eyes moved back and forth she mumbled the words…  With each second that passed her expression grew more angry and her forehead began to show creases with her eyebrows arched in a frown…  ‘What the hell is this?’ she started again, obviously being unfair about the whole situation…  ‘Read it’ I retorted  ‘I’ve already read it…this is a load of crap…in an agreement you can’t be bias you have to be fair!’ she yelled back feeling frustration and a right to have justice boil inside of her…  ‘What are you talking about? I’ve read through it, and it seems completely fair to me…there’s nothing wrong with it’ I retorted back defending myself…  She scoffed at me rather rudely…  ‘Nothing wrong with it? Let me read it again for you…’ came her reply as she pulled the agreement towards her face…  ‘Evidence of Contract Agreement  Nicky will stay with Benjamin Uy for 100 days counting day one as 23rd August…During the 100 days…she is not to physically abuse or insult Benjamin Uy, as HE IS GOD’S GIFT TO WOMEN AND SHOULD BE TREATED WITH RESPECT…  After 100 days when it lies on the 1st of December, Nicky is required to return the belongs that she had DIRTILY STOLE FEROCIOUSLY from INNOCENT Benjamin Uy…WHO IS THE VICTIM in this whole dealing.  On the bottom of this sheet, please sign your name as prove of agreement…going back on the deal will cause severe punishment to Nicky ONLY as she is not Benjamin Uy who is a literal chick magnet…’ she made sure she emphasized particular bits of the agreement…[I have no idea why though]   She stared at me after, waiting for some sort of reaction…  I remained calm and solemn still not understanding why she felt the need to justify my actions…what was her problem…this contract is 100% fair in every way…  ‘So? What’s wrong with it’ came my dumbfounded respond.  Again, she scoffed at me…obviously there was something I was missing or something that she didn’t see…maybe she hadn’t written up a contract agreement before…I nodded my head understandingly…that would explain why she thought my contract was unfair…  ‘Hmm…I don’t know…all of it!’ she retorted sarcastically…  I looked at her blankly not knowing what to say…I don’t get it…what’s wrong with it…  ‘What do you mean by ‘all of it” I asked her trying to get her to elaborate…  She sighed loudly making me feel dumb…  ‘Your discriminating me…which your NOT allowed to do in a fair agreement…you’re being unfair by saying ‘going back on the deal will cause severe punishment to Nicky ONLY’…what kind of a fair agreement is this…and you make yourself look like the good guy while I look evil and heartless!!!’ she retorted at me trying to make a point…  ‘Don’t be absurd…how can I make myself look like the good guy and make you look heartless?!...I didn’t write that down!’ I snapped at her trying to get her to see the facts…  Again she scoffed at me…damn…her scoffing problem was beginning to get annoying…I should’ve asked the doctor if she had any mental problems…  ‘Oh Yeah?!...how do you explain the constant praising of yourself and the constant put downs that you add into the agreement to make me look bad and make you look good?’ she asked me in a know-it-all way…  ‘I did not! I never wrote down… ‘Nicky is a stubborn cow’ or ‘Nicky is evil’!!!’ I retorted back defensively…  She groaned at me hinting that I wasn’t getting the message…but I got it perfectly well…she just didn’t know how to draw up an agreement…that’s all…  I was going to stick with my story…she was just jealous of my excellent skills…and I find it very offensive that she thinks that my agreement is worthless…honestly, she could show a little more respect towards my fine work…  ‘How do you explain the picture of a cow with devil horns and a red hot poker on the side where I’m meant to sign and on the other side where you’re meant to sign it has a picture of what looks like a male model with a halo on top of his head?!’ she screeched at me…  ‘Oh…you like my artwork?!’ I asked her excitedly forgetting about the whole point of this argument…  At least she could tell what the pictures were…I felt proud of myself again, not only was I blessed with shockingly good looks and charm, I was also talented with artwork…wow…you really are something, Ben…  She groaned even louder this time…she was beginning to get fed up with me…  ‘YOU ARE SUCH A SLOW PIG!!!’ she shrieked at me…  ‘Huh?’ I blurted out confused about the whole situation…  She sighed loudly and got out a piece of paper and pen…  ‘Sit down Ben’ she ordered me…  I did as I was told and I sat down obediently beside her as she wrote down the title…  ‘FAIR contract agreement’  She really was a stubborn cow sometimes…sheesh…I bet she just couldn’t stand the fact that my work was shockingly impressive towards her standards…and her, being the stubborn cow she is couldn’t stand the fact that I had thought of something before her…so she had to be the boss and draw up her own contract…  Just because she was new at this sort of thing didn’t mean she had to discriminate my good work…I sighed to myself disappointed that we weren’t going to use my contract…  Nicky raised an eyebrow at me but I chose to ignore it and brush it off…I stared into space while I waited for her to finish the contract…  ‘Done!’ she exclaimed happily I snapped out of my thoughts to face her…then I looked at the agreement…  It read-  FAIR Contract Agreement  Nicky will stay with Benjamin Uy for 100 days counting day one as 23rd August…after the finish date of 100 days [1st December] Nicky will be required to return the belongings of Benjamin Uy that she currently possesses.  During the 100 days Benjamin Uy is expected to treat Nicky as an equal and she, the same. In the household both parties will be allowed to do as they please, the only condition that they should follow is that the opposite party is expected to live before the 100 days are over.  Please sign at the bottom of this sheet to show your agreement is true.  Signature Here Signature Here Benjamin Uy- Nicky-  ---  I finished reading the agreement, I had to admit…It was relatively good…of course not as good as mine though…and there weren’t even any decorations either!  Who did she think she was, some rich girl with such a good education…sheesh…she didn’t have to use such big words…I mean…we’re no rocket scientists…I mumbled my feelings out…luckily she didn’t hear though…she just shot me another weird look…  Personally I think that my contract was by far better than hers…I don’t know what she was thinking about when she wrote her contract up…no idea…  Whatever she says…I’m still going to keep the original contract that I drew up because I really admire my work…hehehe…maybe I should even frame it…hmms…  I reluctantly signed the agreement and she did too….after the signing I decided to frame the agreement that she had drew up since we were using that one now…and not mine…*sigh*…  My original agreement with my wonderful artwork, I kept it in my room and stuck it on my wall…hehehe…     CHAPTER 15  [Nicky’s P.O.V.] *24th August*  I woke up at 8:00am and this time by my own free will…  Lazily I went to the bathroom to brush my teeth, Ben was already awake and he was in the process of squeezing tooth paste on his crystal, blue, brush…  ‘Morning’ he said not bothering to look up.  ‘Morning’ came my greeting as I scratched my head sleepily.  I took my green brush and he handed me the toothpaste tube…he started brushing his teeth and I soon followed after…  Lazily, my eyes gazed around the bathroom…Ben noticed me staring at a vase of flowers that were placed on top of the sink…  ‘They’re daffodils’ he tried to say while his mouth was full of foam and toothpaste…  I looked at him dumbfounded…then I looked at the flowers again…yellow…they look nice; I wonder if they smell nice…  As if Ben could read my mind he spoke up again.  ‘Daffodil’s smell nice; go ahead…take a whiff’ he told me inbetween brushing.  I looked at him hesitantly making sure he wasn’t going to try anything funny….he gave me an innocent look in return so I leaned in closer and clenched my toothbrush in my mouth…  When I was about to take in a deep breath of flowers, the tap suddenly turned on and Ben splashed water all over my face…I jolted my head upwards and…  *Bump!*  ‘AWw…shit!’ I cried out surprised…  I had forgotten that the bathroom mirror was also a door for a little storage place...and it just so happened that I was directly beneath it…  ‘ARgh! Benjamin come back here!’ I yelled at him…while I washed my face and spat out the foam from my mouth…  I could hear his quick footsteps already out of the bathroom…damn him!  ‘You’re going to get it Ben!’ I shrieked at him…  When I had finished wiping my face…I went in search of Ben…  ‘Ben?!’ I called out…  All of a sudden the bathroom door slammed shut…what the? Aww crap…damn that conniving pig…he was probably hiding next to the door all this time…  ‘You’ll have to come out sometime Ben!!!’ I hollered at him…  Deciding to wait at the door till he came out…I sat in front of the door…after a few minutes, I began to get hungry so I gave up…  I figured he’d be hungry too so I made us both some pancakes and syrup…  ‘MmM…can you smell it Ben…smells sOoO good!!!...it’s pancakes and syrup…yum yum!’ I taunted and teased on the other side of the door…  There was no sound…I wondered if he had already gone out…I placed the plate of pancakes and syrup on the table and I checked his room…empty…  That’s strange, I wonder what he’s doing…hmm…ah wells…he can starve for all I care…  I hurried to the table where I had left the plate eagerly wanting to take a bite from my yummy pancakes, to my shock it was gone…what the?...I spun around, just in time to see Ben, still in his Care Bear PJ’s rush to his room with MY plate of pancakes!...  ‘HEY!!!...BENJAMIN, YOU IGNORANT PIG!!!! THOSE ARE MY PANCAKES!!!’ I screamed at the top of my lungs…  He slammed the door shut and locked it…*sigh*…  The mind of that guy…sheesh…I shook my head in disbelieve…that cheeky little brat!  ‘YOU’LL HAVE TO COME OUT SOMETIME!!!...YOU KNOW, NO ONE CAN STOP YOU FROM GOING TO THE TOILET!!!...OR HAVING A SHOWER AND YOU’RE GOING TO HAVE TO EAT AGAIN ANYWAY!!!’ I yelled out loud enough for him to hear…  This time there was a reply…  ‘I already went to the toilet, if I don’t drink then I don’t need to go to the toilet…and umm…I don’t want to waste money so I’m not taking a shower today…and umm…I’m on a diet!!!’ he yelled back through the door…  What the? On a diet?  ‘That’s the most lamest thing I’ve heard from you Ben!’ I retorted.  This time there was no reply…I decided to settle down and watch some TV until Ben came out of his room…what a sissy girl…and he nicknames ME the stubborn cow…sheesh!  For the whole day Ben didn’t come out of his room…I was actually quite surprised because he had only eaten breakfast and that was about it…  When it was dinner time he finally came out while I was cooking…  ‘Oo…what smells so nice?!’ he asked me while taking a deep breath and inhaling the aroma of assorted fish, poultry and vegetables…  I smirked to myself…  ‘Oh…nothing much…just cooking dinner’ I replied casually like it was no big deal…  ‘You can cook?!’ He blurted out in surprise and astonishment  His eyes were as big as golf balls and his mouth was hanging open…I couldn’t help but giggle at his funny expression…  ‘Yeah…I can cook!’ I replied in an accusing way trying to sound as if I took offensive to his question…I didn’t want to make him think I was going soft…that way my next move wouldn’t seem so suspicious…  ‘Sit down Ben…the rice is almost ready…’ I told him while going back to my cooking…  He sat down obediently and waited quietly for me to finish cooking…  When I had finished I spooned rice into two bowls and placed all the dishes on the table…then we began eating…  I ate something from every plate except for the beans…  Mm...This tastes great…Oo...that’s good! Mmm...Delicious!’ he praised me…  ‘You think?’ I would say while laughing light heartedly at him…  I had to admit, the way he ate was quite cute…and boy could he eat! His mouth kept on chewing and his hand went back and forth grabbing fish, chicken and vegetables from each dish…  When his chopsticks reached for the beans…I couldn’t help but form a sneer on my face…my mouth began to curve and form a grin as he took a large serving of beans and drew them close to his mouth…  As the beans entered his mouth in one quick motion my eyes glistened awaiting the expected reaction…  To my surprise he just kept eating…and chewing…and gulping…my expression soon changed to dumbfounded…I scratched my head in confusion wondering why the 3 packets of ‘Super Chili Powder-Twice as much power’ hadn’t worked…  ‘AHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!’ Ben jolted up from his chair and ran to the tap like a mad man…  AHhh…it had worked…I must remember that Ben isn’t like any other guy…he’s a little slower…*sigh*…  I sat back in my chair and relaxed…*sigh*  ‘Music to my ears…’ I said to myself dreamily as I heard Ben’s shrill voice screaming his head off as if screaming would stop the burning sensation on his tongue…  I had to admit…it took a little longer than I had expected for Ben to cool down…the tap was running non-stop and his head was tilted on a side while trying to stop the burning feeling that he was experiencing he even stamped on his feet and waved his arms in the air like a hysterical weirdo…or someone who was undertaking a sever seizure right now…this was way too amusing…I should do this more often...  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~TO BE CONTINUED~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ ~~~~~~~~WAIT FOR THE NEXT CHAPTER~~~~~~~~~~~~~
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im so lazy...  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      im so innocent *LOL*  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CHAPTER 1  [Ben’s P.O.V.] I whistled to myself feeling sexier then ever while I winked at the passing girls…they seemed to show some interest in me too…secretly I smirked to myself knowing I, Benjamin Uy was literally a chick magnet…  As I whistled and threw my car keys in the air I accidentally bumped in to someone…  ‘Oh sorry sir’ a muffled, feminine voice said…  I was stunned for a few seconds before I peered down at the girl…she seemed about my age but her hair covered her face from my view…I could just make out two large hazel eyes…she seems pretty hot…but briskly walked away after apologizing to me…  ‘Right back at ya sexy!’ I hollered at her as she walked past me…  She didn’t seem to notice my extremely handsome features or my sparkling smile…I began to worry…was I growing old…but I’m only 23… surely I can’t have a wrinkle now can I?  I rushed to the nearest shop to find a mirror…Mc Donald’s was the closest and I barged in and knocked a few plates out of customers who were walking to a table…I didn’t care….they were the least of my problems…my looks were everything…everything!  As I neared the guys’ toilets I kicked the swinging door open not bothering to check if anybody was behind it…Frantically I rushed to the nearest mirror to inspect my face…to my relief nothing was wrong…the same sexy face peered right back at me…  It felt great to see a handsome guy stare back at me…I sighed to myself feeling better than ever…I decided to brand that girl a lesbian since she didn’t seem the slightest bit moved by my good looks…  Slowly I strolled over acting cool to the door of the guys’ toilets…I must have tripped on some water and I fell flat on my face…my world felt like it had crashed right down, how embarrassing…silently I cursed about that girl who had knocked into me…as my eyes adjusted and I attempted to get up a foot slammed right onto my back…I winced in pain…What the hell was going on…who ever did that was going to pay…my shirt was ruined…and even worse he could of made me permanently retarded with an imprint on my perfect body!!! Who would want me now…  ‘Who the hell are you?!’ I demanded in pain as I lay on the tiles smelling the disgusting odor of urine…  I turned my head a few inches to the side to see who to blame…a tall figure peered over me…his face was red and he seemed like he had just had a swim in the toilet bowl…  ‘The guy behind the door when you kicked it open’ he said with an evil smirk on his face…  Uh-oH…I’m in trouble now…I thought to myself…again I cursed at that bloody girl who hadn’t noticed me…if it wasn’t for her than I wouldn’t be in this mess right now…with an extremely bulky guy hovering over me with heaps of tattoos everywhere you could imagine…  I had to admit…it didn’t seem like I could take this humongous mass of muscle on…I mean…I was pretty strong myself but this guy was so massive he could flatten me…the odds were great and it didn’t look pretty in the end…  If you can imagine me…a beautiful faced guy walking into the gents toilets in a hurry…and then me, walking out like I had just being bashed to a pulp and had my head flushed down the toilet…it wasn’t pretty…believe me…  As I walked out…for the first time in my life I felt ugly….all the girls turned to look my way…this time it wasn’t because of my charming smile or killer looks…but the stench of urine all over me and the numerous bruises I had all over my face…  Like a zombie I made my way out, slowly lugging my tired body out Mc Donald’s until somebody approached me…  ‘Excuse me sir…’ a man asked…he was wearing the Mc Donald’s uniform and he had a badge on the left side of his chest labeled ‘manager’….  Drowsily I turned my head signaling him to go on…  ‘I’m sorry but the customers have complained about you…I’ve been informed that you knocked over their food while you apparently rushed into the gents’ toilets…’ he said in an accusing tone…  My heart began to thump…don’t tell me he was going to make me pay…I groaned to myself not wishing to part with my money…  ‘Umm…you have the wrong guy’ I said quickly while I motioned to the door again like a zombie….  He held me back with his hand before quickly withdrawing it away in disgust…my shirt was soaked in toilet water…it didn’t smell nice at all…  ‘Please sir…if you would kindly pay the amount of $30.00 for the food that you spilt it would be appreciated…please don’t lie to me or I’ll have to take you to the police station…I can understand that you had a major case of diarrhea or something like that but the customers want justice…’ the man said…  I was horrified and extremely embarrassed…they think I had diarrhea!!!...OMG…my swollen face turned even redder than before…I wanted to get out of Mc Donald’s as soon as possible but seeing as the stupid manager wouldn’t let me leave I quickly rummaged through my pants pocket to find my wallet…  To my horror and shock I couldn’t find it anywhere.....i checked both pockets of my baggy jeans and to no avail I found nothing…not even my cell phone was in there…my eyes widened in shock as I began to panic…what the hell was going on…this wasn’t the best day obviously…  The manager’s piercing eyes made my forehead drip with beads of sweat…he impatiently waited for me to pay the fee…while I rummaged for my wallet…where was it?!  Finally I gave up…slowly I withdrew my hand from my pocket and gave the manager a nervous laugh…he stared at me obviously not impressed at all while he tapped his foot continuously on the freshly mopped tiles…  ‘Hold on…I seem to have left my wallet in the bathroom’   I made a bolt for it to the bathroom hoping that my wallet was there…I clearly recall that the bulky guy hadn’t taken my money…or my cell…when I reached the bathroom I slowly pushed the door open which made a squeaky sound from the old hinges… I searched in every toilet dorm and every table sink…nothing…nothing…that’s when I remembered that lesbian girl…urgH….silently I cursed to myself coming up with the conclusion that she had mugged me when she bumped into me…damn her!...  I glumly walked out of the gents’ toilets and back to the awaiting hands of the manager…today just wasn’t my day at all…first I get bashed…then told to part with my money…and now I find out that I’ve been mugged…I sighed to myself not feeling good at all…if I ever see that girl again she’ll pay….  The day didn’t turn out as I had planned…the manager made me work off the $30 I owed…I didn’t do much of a good job though…I practically slowed down his business and I drove the customers away with my fowl stench…I felt like I was on show…all these hot girls walked in and out of Mc Donald’s pointing at me and laughing…I promised myself I would seek revenge on that girl if it was the last thing I did…    CHAPTER 2  [Ben's P.O.V.] At the end of the day I was fully exhausted…I drove home to my apartment and tiredly opened my apartment door #463…as I got in the lights were already on…now what is it? As a frown appeared on my face…this just wasn’t my day to get burgled…then I heard laughter…the T.V. was on…  My eyes widened in panic as I got a nearby beer bottle from the table that I had finished off last night…slowly I crept beside the wall and neared the T.V…who ever it was, they were pretty stupid to laugh so loud in my home…  ‘HAHAHAHAHA’ the laughter rang through my whole house…  Just as I was about to strike…something stopped me…wait a second…that laugh sounds familiar…I scratched my head in deep concentration…where had I heard that laugh from…that same high-pitched girly laugh…Tonti!!!...  I smirked to myself knowing I had got him this time…as usual Tonti, who lived right across from my door had let himself in again…his T.V. was broken and knowing Tonti he was to lazy to get it fixed…he had a room mate too…Jake…we were all friends around here…our other buddy’s lived a few doors down…the short guy. Rainer lived at #465… Blue was at #466, right next door to Tonti and Jake and Retchi lived with Blue…he was the baby out of us…  I thought of an evil plan and smirked at myself thinking I had got him this time…slowly I crept behind the living room couch and switched the light off…Tonti just sat there dumbfounded wondering what was going on…  That’s when I pounced on him…  ‘ARGHhHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!! RAPIST!!!’ Tonti yelled at the top of his lungs…  I covered his mouth with my hand trying to muffle his sounds…this was way too much fun...knowing Tonti…he kicked and screamed like a baby trying to fight me off…  ‘SMELLY RAPIST!!!!...HELP!!!! HELP!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!’ He yelled again…  He must have escaped from my grasp…his screams were so screeching I would of punched him in the face if he wasn’t my friend…suddenly somebody pounced on me and threw me on the ground….  ‘ARGH!!!’ I shrieked as I landed on the floor with a thud…I grabbed my side, aching in pain…what the hell was going on…who was that?...  ‘Get him!!!’ Tonti yelled…  Somebody threw a blanket of some sort over my face as I yelled in astonishment…what the hell?...  Now it was my turn of torture…Somebody pounced on me while I was still in shock…and I’m guessing Tonti joined in…  ‘AHHhHH!!! Get OFF!!!!!!!!!!!’ I yelled threw the blanket as they started beating me…  Tonti was going to die for this….  Between the blanket and the other two…I could hear faint sounds…they seemed to be talking about me…  ‘What are we going to do with the burglar?’ a guy said…he sounded like Jake…  ‘I don’t know…who ever he is…he sure is dangerous…did you see that?!! He almost raped me for God’s sake!!! He’s probably been stalking me…who knows…even fantasizing!!!’ Tonti shrieked in panic  ‘I don’t know…should we call Ben and tell him about the psycho?’ Jake said not knowing what to do…  Obviously he was over exaggerating like usual…I sighed to myself before taking a deep breath…  ‘SHIN TONTI AND DHONGWAN JAKE!!!!!!!!!!!!! GET YOUR FAT ASSES OFF OF ME BEFORE I BEAT THE CRAP OUT OF YOU FOR RUINING MY BEAUTIFUL FACE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!’ I roared at the top of my lungs…  I must have startled the two and they immediately jumped off of my ribs enabling me to breathe in regularly…  I pulled the covers off of my face as the lights soon turned on and blinded me…as I adjusted to the light I met the gaze of Jake and Tonti wide-eyed and mouths dropped at the sight of me…  ‘BEN!!!!!!!!!’ they both cried in unison…  ‘WHAT?!’ I said back rather rudely…  ‘d-did we do THAT….’ Tonti said while glancing at Jake then back at me…  I groaned to myself and got up with a heavy sigh…this just wasn’t my day…Tonti followed me along with Jake…they continued to observe my face taking a good look at the bruises that I got from the bulky guy in the gent’s room…  I ignored there stares and went to the bathroom to have a long shower before going to bed…today was a long day…and if I ever saw that girl again I’d show her a piece of my mind…     CHAPTER 3  [Nicky’s P.O.V.] Before I went to work…I noticed a stupid looking guy walking towards me...he seemed like the perfect person to mug…I mean…don’t get me wrong…It’s not as if I want to steal from anyone…it’s because I have to…ever since I left the orphanage and when times are hard I have to do it every now and then…it sure beats being a whore…  When I ‘accidentally’ bumped into him he called me sexy…I mean...what sort of a lame pick up line is that…little did that bimbo know that he had just been mugged…I smirked to myself as I thought of what had happened…  After I took his wallet and cell phone I rummaged through his wallet to find out his name was Benjamin Uy…he seemed like a rich guy judging by the way he walked…soon I found out I was way off…WHAT?! Only $5?!...this guy must be a pimp if he only has 5 in his wallet but dresses like a rich ass…what an idiot…  Of course I was disappointed to only see 5 bucks…I mean…how was that going to pay for the rent that I owed…I frowned to myself as I thought about what I had did… mugging someone who was as poor as me…I felt guilty….  I went to work at 11:00pm…the usual time…well the pay was good…but I always got it late…which wasn’t very good…what could you expect for being a ‘bar girl’…I worked at Crystal Bar…I don’t know why I took the job though…I guess I was desperate…the people there were alright and they treated me pretty nicely…but that wasn’t enough…after all…I did lose my dignity…  I worked till early morning until 4:00am…it was always like this for me…I was always the fill-in girl as well if people were busy…I needed all the money I got…and that was only for the rent and bills that needed to be paid…the grueling hours at work were endless…constantly being harassed and hooted at wasn’t what I pictured my dream…I don’t think it would be any girls dream…  Some guys offered me some cash…but of course, knowing guys…they always wanted something in return…I cherished that little bit of dignity I had left in me though…never would I stoop so low…I told myself…so that’s how I came into the stealing business…I only did it occasionally when times were hard…  After a while of thought…I decided to sell the wallet…I easily sold it to a stupid guy who paid $50 for it…I grinned to myself happily…knowing $50 would last me a while…I got $100 a night for working and I went to work every chance I got…I guess you could say that would be more than enough…but to me…it wasn’t…I hated the job but it kept me alive…I wanted to create my dream….to create a future for myself…to start new and go to college…to get a decent job…  When my shift was over I went home to my small apartment….i punched in the number code and slowly dragged my tired body up to the elevator…I pushed in the 5th level as the doors closed…  When I finally reached the right floor I slowly pulled my body forward while leaning against the wall half asleep to #005 my apartment number… when I got in, I managed to make it to my bedroom and I slumped on my bed….i was so tired…it was how it always was…I fell asleep….  When I woke up it was 3:00pm…I yawned and stretched my arms out feeling more refreshed…I still had make up on my face and my hair was all ruffled up…scratching my head lazily I walked out of my room to come face to face with my living habits…I groaned to myself remembering that I had said that I would clean it up yesterday…  On the floor were scattered clothes and a few empty bottles and chip packets…on the table was more food and a couple bits of scrap paper…the kitchen sink was a mess with dirty dishes that had been there for God knows how long…I frowned at the disgusting sight…I never noticed how gross it looked…  Immediately I set to work cleaning everything up…first I picked up all the empty bottles and chip packets before throwing away the scrap pieces of paper…I borrowed a vacuum cleaner from my next door neighbour who was a kind old lady…I got to work in getting every corner and crevice clean…  I stepped back to admire my efforts…I had to admit, it looked pretty good…I smiled at my achievement before I glanced at my watch…9:30pm….I frowned at how fast time had past…soon I’d have to go to work again…I sat on my couch and switched on the small T.V. I possessed…aimlessly I flicked the channels and found my favourite show on…Friends…after the show finished it was 10:30…I slumped on the couch comfortably for a while before I decided to make myself something to eat…  Taking out a pack of Nissin noodles I poured some hot water inside a bowl and covered the top with the foil…while I sat on a nearby stool waiting for the noodles to soften I drummed my fingers while staring at the clock…tick…tick….tick…it was so boring…  When it had been 5 minutes I opened the lid staring at the steaming hot noodles…my eyes lit up as I breathed in the delicious smell…mm….yummy…  After I finished my meal I wiped my mouth with my sleeve and gulped down the last of the scrumptious noodles…I turned to the clock again and saw that it was 11:45 now…  Quickly I grabbed my jacket and ran out of my house to Crystal Bar…I didn’t have a car so I had to go everywhere by foot…when I finally reached my destination I huffed and puffed loudly trying to catch my breath back…I glanced at my watch…11:55pm…I gave out a sigh of relief knowing that I wasn’t late…  When I entered the bar I was greeted with the usual loud disco music and heavy smell of liquor that always came my way…the smell was so thick it made me feel like vomiting the first time I worked here…but now it was a usual routine…  I greeted the bar tender who was also my boss and went to the back to get changed…busily I searched for number 7 on the clothes rack…I managed to find it right at the end and I undressed to my undergarments…when I put the skimpy outfit on I felt bare and naked…I had never gotten used to that…the uniform barely covered any part of my body…it was an extremely tight, not to mention short mini skirt with a tube top which showed my belly button…  I sighed to myself and began to apply make up…there was even a special method for applying it on…I was told to apply a large amount of bright red lipstick to match my outfit with a lot of blush on the cheeks…I might not be a whore…but I sure feel like one…  After I finished with my make up I walked out of the dressing room back to the crazy drunks outside…I envied the rich guys and girls who came here…they came to party, drink and go wild…they had no idea what kind of future they were throwing around…of course there were the occasional girls would make rude remarks about me…they always insulted the less fortunate people…they made me so angry…once I slapped one of them…the boss warned me if I ever did that again I’d get fired…as much as I wanted to lash out at them, I needed the job for the money so I kept quite…they would always refer to the less fortunate as… ‘People like you’…  After I served a few more beers and to people at tables a group of guys walked in…I noticed one of them instantly…the guy I had mugged…suddenly I began to panic but I kept my cover and went around serving beers to people while I secretly eyed them making sure I was a far distance from them…  The bar tender told me to serve table 4’s drinks...and I quietly obeyed taking the order and walking towards number 4…to my shock and horror…it was that idiot’s table…  I quickly placed the drinks on the table and briskly walked away…I let out a deep sigh of relief thinking I had gotten away with being caught….until…  ‘Hey…you with the red mini skirt….come back here…’ it was that idiot’s voice again…  Beads of sweat began to drip from my forehead and my heart began to beat faster and faster…slowly I turned around hoping he didn’t remember me…    CHAPTER 4  [Ben's P.O.V.] The guys and I decided to go to Crystal Bar the next day…I gave Tonti and Jake the impression that they had damaged my face…they wanted to make it up to me and take me out…obviously I agreed, who would pass up the opportunity of FREE drinks?...besides, my wallet and phone was stolen…  I’m a cheap guy…yes, I can admit it…to myself of course…not to anyone else…well, yes I flirt but I don’t buy drinks for girls…I expect them to buy drinks for me…hahaha…I mean, why should I buy drinks for girls…it’s meant to be the manly thing but most girls who hang around bars are usually rich anyway…they can afford to part with their money…  I’m not in debt or anything…I just don’t like wasting money…I don’t know why…I just don’t…  When the guys and I finally arrived at Crystal Bar…the place was lively with the smell of liquor…people were shouting at each other trying to get a decent conversation starting over the loud DJ music and cheerful screams of young, under-aged girls…  This was my style…where I belong…I’m the heart of the party…all I have to do is bust a few of my moves and the girls will be hovering over me like I’m God…this was my life…I was the life of the party…   Jake and Tonti ordered the beers for us…all the guys were here…including Rainer, BLue and Retchi…  The bar girl that came over was really hot…I smirked to myself while thinking I had gotten the girls attention…no, wait…not thinking…knowing…  To my surprise and astonishment…she placed down the drinks on the table and left…she didn’t even collect the bill…I called out to her and she stopped in her tracks…for a while I thought she was shocked that I, Benjamin Uy had noticed her and she was flattered…I smirked to myself...satisfied that I still had the charm…  I waited for her to grasp the concept that she had been addressed by ‘me’ so she could turn around…  Finally she turned around but her head tilted downwards avoiding my eyes…as if she was scared of me…slowly she walking towards my table with the guys again…there was something unusual about her…I felt like I had seen her from somewhere…somewhere recently…but I couldn’t quite pinpoint when…  ‘Aren’t you going to collect the bill?’ I asked her, still trying to remember where I had seen her before…  She remained silent not moving an inch…then after a few moments she spoke…  ‘$13.85 please’ she said in a small muffled voice…  Tonti had to lean closer to hear her…he sighed loudly seeming fed up…I guess he was in a bad mood because of earlier on when Jake and him had versed each other in rock, scissors, paper to see who had to pay the bill…obviously Tonti lost …the bar girl noticed his actions but said nothing and kept quiet…she most probably assumed that he was annoyed with her…  Her voice sounded so familiar…I was on the brink of finding out where I had seen her before…but I just couldn’t remember…  ‘I guess your new here…I don’t know why a girl like you is doing here but next time, don’t forget to collect the bill or you’ll be in trouble with your boss…okay?’ Tonti said…noticing that he had acted rather rudely before…he gave her a warm smile after handing her the money…  That’s it!!!...I know who she is!!...that girl who had mugged me…I smirked to myself knowing I had got her this time…I opened my mouth to show her a piece of my mind, when she interrupted…  ‘That’s right!!! You wouldn’t know anything about why a girl like ‘ME’ is doing here so mind your own bloody business!!! .you don’t even know anything about me…you have no idea…all you guys are just a bunch of rich assholes who don’t appreciate the great advantages you have in life!!!’ she burst out in aggravation…emphasizing the word ‘Me’ as if Tonti was judging her…  Tonti's eyes widened in shock at how the girl had changed all of a sudden…first she was quite and seemed unsure of herself…but now she was fired up…I was surprised myself…  'L-look…I didn’t mean it that way okay…and please don’t assume we’re that kind of people…you don’t know us…and we don’t know you…’ Tonti said calming down a little…  Tonti and Blue could manage their temper so easily out of all of us…Jake was quite calm but he had a temper problem sometimes…  Rainer became cold and distant ever since he lost his girlfriend Eugene…she was murdered and he was there when it happened…he’s never been the same ever since…at that time he kept rambling on about remembering his past life or something…he was adopted when he was small by Derek’s parents…he used to live with Derek, his adopted brother...but he decided he needed some space and moved into an apartment next to us guys…  I don’t have a temper problem…but I can get rather cocky when I’m in a bad mood…and I really want to show that bar girl a piece of my mind…not to mention get my wallet and cell phone back from her…  The girl’s annoyed expression soon calmed down to a frown crease on her forehead…I figured that she new Tonti was right and now she was regretting what she had said rather rudely…  This time it was my turn to have a go at her…but I wasn’t going to be nice or polite to her like Tonti was…this time it was going to get messy…  I stood up from my seat and confronted her, putting on my meanest face ever…I had practiced my ‘mean’ face in the mirror before…I new what I looked like to other people when I had the expression on my face…my forehead was creased and my eyebrows arched inward…  Once I had showed Rainer my ‘mean’ face asking what he thought…ever since Eugene…he had developed the most coldest and cruelest expressions you could imagine...the feedback I got from him wasn’t very nice though…his exact words were… ‘You look constipated like your dying to go to the toilet…now go away’…  With that he walked away leaving the rest of the guys laughing their heads off and clutching their chests trying to suppress their laughter…I wasn’t very happy obviously…but I knew better then to mess with Rainer…he was deadly when in a bad mood…but he was scary almost all of the time…none of us guys messed with him…we knew better than that…  Snapping back to reality…in front of me was a blank expression coming from the girl…    CHAPTER 5  [Ben’s P.O.V.] ‘WHAT?!’ she soon snapped at me noticing my unwelcoming facial expression…  I had to admit…when she was annoyed or angry…she looked hot…but I was never going to tell her that…I wouldn’t give her the satisfaction…  ‘Don’t ‘what’ me girly...give me back my cell phone and wallet!!!’ I yelled back at her annoyed at the disrespect she was showing…  Not to mention if any hot girls were watching right now…they would lose interest in me because I was shouting at a girl…which wasn’t manly or gentlemen like at all…but who knows…I might catch the attention of some girls too…some chicks like to see a man being dominant…I smirked to myself thinking of the up side of this little shouting contest…  The bar girls face became as white as a ghost…I guess she knew I had got her there…gathering up her senses she spoke again…  ‘I don’t know what you’re talking about…leave me alone!!!’ she said motioning that she was leaving the scene…  ‘Don’t think you can get away so easily you lesbian!!!…not this time…I’m not as stupid as you think…you know EXACTLY what I’m talking about!!!...Come back here...and give me back my stuff you thief!!!’ I yelled at her retreating figure…  She stopped moving and turned around…by now the whole bar had gone silent and everyone was listening in on our conversation…our voices were louder then the DJ music…all eyes were on the girl now…I guess she didn’t like the spotlight…I smirked to myself knowing that I had the upper hand this time…  ‘HOW DARE YOU CALL ME A LESBIAN…HOW WOULD YOU KNOW YOU SICK PERVERT…LEAVE ME ALONE!!!’ she yelled back in aggravation…  I don’t believe this girl…she knows exactly what I’m talking about and she still denies it…how stupid…Jeez…what an idiot…it’s a shame that she’s hot though…  I was about to yell back at her when the boss came across hoping to break up the brawl that we were having…I guess he had noticed that the whole bar had gotten silent and all eyes were on his bar girl and customer…who was obviously me…  ‘Alright…calm down please…what seems to be the problem…?’ the man said…making eye contact with the bar girl more then me…  It was clear that he addressing me though…  ‘Tell that lesbian of a bar girl give me back my things…she stole them the other day…!!!’ I ordered him…obviously unhappy…  The boss nodded to me…signaling me to wait a few moments while he discussed the situation with the lesbian girl…  After a few moments of small mumbles and whispers…the girl carried a smirk on her face…what was going on?...  I looked at the boss of Crystal Bar demanding an explanation from him…  ‘My employee tells me that she has never met you before…and that you tried to assault her a few moments ago…and your story is a way to cover up your harassing…’ the Boss informed me…  By now I was fuming with rage…what the hell?!!...assault her?!!...I’m not that stupid…Jeez…who does this guy think he is…and who does she think she is?!...no wonder she had such a smug look on her face…URgh…damn that girl  ‘BULLSHIT!!!...she’s making shit up!!!...if she doesn’t return my things I’ll sue your bar for all it’s worth!!!’ I said in a threatening voice…all the other guys joined in and supported me saying that the girl was making things up…  Of course I don’t have a lawyer…but it’s not like the guy knows that I don’t…besides…he wouldn’t jeopardize his business reputation would he?...I smirked secretly to myself knowing that I would get what I want…  The boss’s forehead creased in stress and he frowned desperately trying to find a solution…after a while…he let out a sigh of defeat…  ‘Alright…alright…but my employee says she didn’t take anything of yours…what do you propose I do?’ he asked me trying to negotiate…  This time it was my turn to put a smug look on my face…I knew exactly what I wanted and she couldn’t stop me now…no one could…  I scratched my chin which was forming new stubs…I smirked to myself...knowing that everyone’s attention was on me...and the fate of the girl was in my hands…even the bar girl remained silent waiting for me to decide her fate…she knew she had lost…and I knew it too…this was too much fun…  As the anticipated waiting continued…I decided to break the tension…  ‘Fire her’ I said flatly…with an evil look on my face…  He turned around to face the girl…obviously delivering the rejection…the girls face fumed with hatred and annoyance towards me…with her cold eyes she looked at the bosses frown and creased forehead.  ‘FINE!!!...I quit anyway!!!!’…with that she stormed out and grabbed her things…  After a while...everything died down and people began to dance again…I was right…I had caught the attention of more girls than I had imagined…they must of automatically assumed that I was rich and powerful...if I could sue the bar for all it’s money…I was loving the attention and devoured every single bit of affection or lustful stare given my way…  This was too good to be true…I was surrounded by so many hot girls…and then came the saying in my head again…one that I had always told myself…  ‘I…Benjamin Uy…am literally a chick magnet…’    CHAPTER 6  [Nicky's P.O.V.]  can't believe that prick!!! Who the hell does he think he is?!   This just isn't my day…getting fired because of that a*shole!!!...  He just made me so mad…if I ever see him again…I swear he'll get a piece of my mind…and I'll make sure it doesn't end pretty...  I grinded my teeth together in rage and formed fists with my hands…bystanders stared at me like I was a psycho…I didn't blame them though-picture this…I'm walking in God knows how high, platforms with an extremely tight and short mini skirt with a tight, revealing red tube top to match…  A guy hooted at me and whistled…my eyes fired up with rage and I shot him a cold, evil glare…his face went deathly white and he backed away from me not wishing to get involved…  I scowled at him menacingly and stormed off in an extremely pissed off mood…that loser at the bar was going to pay…I don't know when, but I was going to make sure he was going to pay…now how was I going to pay the rent that I owed with no job…  I stopped in my tracks…I'm not going to put up with this…why should he get away with ruining my life…he was going to pay…all I am is all talk and no action…I should make him pay shouldn't I?...I smirked to myself wondering what evil plan I would come up with…  'Nice legs baby!' a guy hollered at me…while whistling…  I snapped out of my thoughts and glared at the guy with cold, glassy eyes in a threatening way hinting him to back away if he knew what was good for him…  'Reow!!!...Feisty…I like that in a girl!' the prick said in a seductive tone trying to impersonate a cat…  I was beginning to lose my temper with him…he picked the wrong day to mess with me... 'How much you charging?' he said in a dirty tone…  By now I was fuming with aggravation …my eyes were fired up with annoyance and anger…what the hell…he thought I was a whore that A**hole!!!...  'Dare say that again…?' I said in a cold, raspy whisper…motioning towards him taking small steps…  'I said how mu-' He attempted to repeat himself but I couldn't take it anymore…  This loser was really pissing me off and I had given him all the possible hints to tell him to back off…what a pig…  I backed away from him escaping from the body heat he was giving off and I drew my arm back and punched him in the face as hard as I could….  'I'm not a whore so why don't you just mind your own f*cking business!!!!!!' I yelled back at him in rage…  Everyone on the street was staring at me now in utter shock and silence…it was completely silent besides the cries of pain from the loser I had punched…  I glared at each and everyone's face with disgust…people only new to assume…just because I was wearing this kind of outfit people thought I was a whore…did I look like a whore? Was I walking like a whore? Did it look like I was practically throwing myself at everyone who was passing by?  My whole body filled up with rage and hatred for the whole world…it felt like it had turned its back on me that I was the only sane one in this stupid society…why did this have to happen to me?  'What are all of you looking at?! Haven't you seen a girl hit a guy before?!! Mind your own F*cking business if you don't want to end up like this loser!!!' I screamed at the top of my lungs shooting an evil glare around me to the people who had formed a circle around me at a distance…  They remained to have blank faces but soon shuffled around and quickly dispersed and scattered back to their own business…  I huffed and puffed trying to catch my breath back…while my eyes remained wide on guard for any sudden movements…After I had regained my senses I decided to go back to the bar and vent out my anger on the loser…as well as collect my last pay check from Crystal Bar…  My platforms clinked on the cold concrete floor as I stomped off in rage…when I reached the bar it was 3:00am already…it was amazing how time passed by so quickly…but that wasn't important to me right now…  Just as I thought…the bar was still lively with the loud DJ music on and the heavy smell of liquor wafting in the air…when I entered nobody seemed to notice me which was good because I was in one of my fits and if anyone shot me a weird stare or look I would literally vent my anger on them…which wouldn't be good because I was intending to let it all out on that prick who got me fired…I think his name was Benjamin Uy or something…his driver's license photo wasn't very attractive…he had a pot-head hair cut…I mean, what kind of a girl would find a pot-head hair cut appealing to her taste…sheesh…  I trudged to the bar and asked for the manager…his name was Brian Joo…he was a pretty decent guy…really hot…I guess he attracted all the female customers…but I was never interested in him…though he might seem like a down to earth guy…how could he be if he owned such a bar which seemed to focus on the bar girls wearing such outfits…  Brian and I were on good terms…but he had once told me that his business came first…and he didn't develop friendships with his employees…I had nodded my head in reply not wishing to question his motives…although I never admitted it I considered him as my only friend…and now that I was fired by him…my only friend at that…you can obviously see why I'm in such an aggravated state of mind right now…  I understand why Brian fired me though…like he said…'business comes first'…  'Hey Nicky…sorry about before…you understand why I did it though right?' Brian's warm voice seeped into my skin and I began to soften up…  'Yeah…I understand…' I said softly turning to the side not wishing to look him in the eyes…somehow Brian always seemed to calm me down and make me feel better…it was like a special bond I shared with him that was never expressed through words…  I took a deep breath in and inhaled the thick smell of liquor before speaking again…  'Look…I'm sorry about before…I didn't mean to cause a scene or anything…I just came for my last pay check and I'll get out of your way…' I said glancing at him and then at the floor…  I could feel Brian's eyes filled with pity and sorrow on me…after a few minutes he disappeared to the back…  I remained still and stared at my feet…I didn't want to face him…I wanted to get away from him as soon as possible…no one had ever seen me cry before and I didn't want him to…  I had shut everybody out of my life…and that was how I wanted to keep it…I didn't want to love anyone…trust anyone…or open up to anyone…this was just the way I was…I guess I pushed everyone away…  From time to time I would wonder…is that why I'm not loved?...is this why I don't have any friends?...I never really knew why…and while I was growing up at the orphanage the nuns would try to encourage me to join in with the other kids…but I never wanted to…I didn't think I belonged…that they would accept me for who I was…that I'd be criticized and ridiculed just for being….just for being…being me….  Just like my parents didn't want me…didn't accept me…they didn't think I belonged…I mean…isn't that the reason why they left me…gave me up for adoption that is?...  Brian soon came back with a small white envelope…he handed it to me…and I extended my hand for him to place it in…  I lowered my head in shame and disgust with myself… 'Thanks…bye Brian…' I said in a soft muffled whisper while turning to leave…  Slowly I walked out of the bar and squinted back the tears that were on the verge of falling from my eyes…a tear escaped my eye and fell on the floor with a plop on the floor…  'Nicky…' Brian's voice came back to my head…  I had never felt so down in my life…I raised my head and took a deep breath…before I turned around I wiped my tears with my free hand…after taking a few sniffs I turned around ready to face Brian…  'Yeah…' I said plastering a happy face on…  'I'll…I'll need the outfit back…' He said in a soft voice…  My heart sank…and I remembered I was still wearing the slutty costume, not to mention make up…  I nodded my head in reply and walked back to the change rooms with my shoulders slumped…Brian new I took the job because money was a problem for me…I guess he felt sorry for me…but there was nothing he could do now…his reputation would be at stake if he took me back…I had to learn to understand this and live with it…  As I disappeared in the shadows to the door…the sensation of feeling Brian's eyes on my back died down and I relaxed a bit more…  After I changed back to my T-shirt and jeans, washed my face getting rid of the make up and brushed my hair…I looked pretty okay…it didn't look like I had been crying which was a good thing…and the only thing on my mind now was getting back at that Benjamin guy…  I walked out of the changing room after hanging up my outfit…well it wouldn't be my outfit anymore I guess…  With a determined face I confronted the outside bar again…  'The outfits on the rack…' I told Brian while I searched for Ben and his bimbo friends…  'It's been fun working with you and I'm going to miss you…take care aiite?' Brian said nodding his head…  I seemed to have cut him off with my head bobbing up and down busily searching for Ben…  My concentration was broken when a hand waved in my face…my expression soon changed to an annoyed one…  'What?!' I snapped at the person not bothering to see who it was…  'Umm…are you okay Nicky…?' Brian's voice sounded in my ears again…  My expression soon turned soft as I turned to face Brian with a sorry face for snapping at him…  'Oh…uh…I'm alright…' I replied not really paying attention…  My expression soon turned to a satisfied one when I spotted the bimbo crew dancing on the dance floor…  I began to make my way towards Ben who was really sweating it out on the floor…I had to admit he had pretty good moves for a complete idiot…I smirked to myself knowing I was going to catch him in complete surprise…  I was a couple metres within totally bashing it out with him until a warm hand held me back on the shoulder…  I turned around to face the person who had interfered with my plans…with an annoyed expression Brian was my interferer…  'Don't do this now Nicky…I know you want revenge…but not here…' Brian said giving me a contempt sigh…  He seemed to have caught up with my evil plan…I gave him a *don't-mess-with-me* look telling him to back off…  'Nicky…don't give me that look…you know perfectly how it's going to end…I know he seems like a totally insensitive prick and your really ticked off with him…but not here Nicky…now isn't the best time…' Brian said understandingly trying to negotiate and reason with me…  My face soon softened under his stare and I gave out a defeated groan…  'Fine fine…I won't now…but soon…believe me soon…' I said informing Brian that he had managed to cool me down for a while…but it wasn't going to last…not for long that is…  With that I walked out of the bar…still determined to show that loser who he was messing with…    CHAPTER 7  [Ben’s P.O.V. I laughed and danced through the whole night…The guys and I had split up, I had no idea where they were by now…I didn’t really care though  I walked out of the bar with Amy (a girl I had met in the bar) in my arm and a beer bottle in the other, we walked in the cold night towards my car, she lightly smacked me on my chest and I chuckled light heartedly at her attempt to hurt me.  As we neared the car her soft giggles died down and her face went blank…noticing her change I glanced towards my car and the blood instantly drained from my face…  It was the feisty girl who tried to pick a fight with me in the bar, she probably wanted revenge…I secretly smirked to myself gathering my sense back, knowing she couldn’t do anything to me…  Her expression was blank and dull…I couldn’t seen to find any signs of anger or annoyance in them…she seemed like a zombie…Amy twitched and wriggled under my arm, I could tell she was uncomfortable under the feisty girl’s stare…I had to admit, I was rather intimidated and felt uneasy as well.  I plastered a brave expression on my face and gave Amy a reassuring squeeze on the shoulder and a flash of my stunning smile, she smiled uneasily and looked towards the girl again…  We began to saunter towards my car, Amy’s heels clicked on the concrete floor steadily as we neared the girl, while we walked she never took her dull, glassy eyes off of me…although I loved the feeling of girls checking me out…somehow I didn’t get the impression that was what she was doing…  Nervously I looked around pretending not to notice her, I couldn’t shake her stare off, or the uneasiness that lingered in the air…Amy fidgeted around awkwardly not liking her stare either…  The feisty girl was leaning on my car door, she seemed laid back but as cold as stone…it was a frightful feeling…  When we were a metre away from each other I stopped and stood there with an unwelcoming expression on my face, she continued to stare at me with glassy, cold eyes…  What was this girl’s problem? I wondered to myself…Is she always like this?...sheeSh..She needs to get a life  We stood there in complete silence, to any stranger we would have seemed like we were having a staring contest…I looked at her menacingly and she shot me an icy cold glare, if this WAS a staring contest I was getting the feeling that she was winning…  The silence was awkward and eerie, I didn’t like the surroundings either…I mean, I don’t mean to sound like a sissy girl but…there was no one around and it was past midnight already…the only people in sight were Amy and the other girl…  Luckily I was half drunk so I wasn’t really in tune...although I knew perfectly what was going on…I regretted not drinking more alcohol…it would have made me feel better and not so high strung…  ‘What do you want?’ I asked her, deciding to break the deathly silence…  She ignored my question and continued to glare at me…boy, this girl had serious issues to deal with…not only was she a lesbian she was also a weirdo…coming to the conclusion, I settled for that she was a ‘Benjamin Uy Fanatic’  Secretly I smirked to myself knowing there were probably a lot more girls like her around... hopefully nicer though...I sighed to myself feeling contempt that one day they would probably get together and form a ‘Benjamin Uy Lovers Club… BULC’…  ***Ben’s Dreamy Thoughts***  ‘AaAaHHHHHHhHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!’ screamed my fan club  I smirked to myself loving the attention…this was WAY to cool to be true…  ‘OMG..I LOVE YOU BENJAMIN UY!!! MARRY ME!!!’  ‘NO..MARRY ME!!!...I LOVE YOU SO MUCH THAT I WOULD DIE FOR YOU!!!!!!!’  ‘BENJAMIN UY!!! YOU’RE MY HERO!!!’  ‘AAHhHHHhhH!!!...HE WINKED AT ME!!! DID YOU SEE THAT?!’  Screams of joy filled my ears…it was like heaven…I strutted my stuff and flashed my stunning smile to all the surrounding girls and even did a little pose..the crowd went wild and a couple of my fans fainted…  I winked at them all and even saw a large banner hoisted up in the air reading… ‘BENJAMIN UY…OUR LEGEND…’  Again..my motto rang in my mind again...  'I,Benjamin Uy am literally a chick magnet...'  ***End of Ben’s Dreamy Thoughts***  ‘Leave us…’a cold raspy whisper sounded in my ear…waking me up from my pleasant thoughts…  I soon found myself back in reality…as the cold dry air blew in my face I noticed Amy was trembling…I gathered my senses and picked the pieces together… ‘Leave us…’ the voice rang in my head and I assumed that the creepy girl had told Amy to leave…  She looked at me hesitantly looking for an answer…I decided to let her go, although I was extremely pissed off that I wouldn’t be able to have fun tonight I let her go…her facial expression said it all…she didn’t want to stay with me at all, especially if the weirdo was around…by that I’m referring to the feisty bar girl...or should I say ex-bar girl…  I tilted my head to a side as I watched Amy’s retreating figure…she walked briskly away while her heels clicked constantly on the cold floor…her hair blew in the cool breeze…The faint sound of her heels died down eventually and I realized how insecure I felt right now…this girl could be dangerous…  The obvious dangers dawned on me and it didn’t feel so good to be near her right now…especially after the scene at the bar…she must have been full-on pissed off at me…although I looked buff and manly…this girl seemed weird…and I had a bad feeling about her…     CHAPTER 8  [Ben’s P.O.V.] So there I was... all alone with the crazy stalker…and trust me…it wasn’t a nice feeling…  For some reason I felt like one of those spinefex balls would blow past like how they do in corny, old cowboy movies…  UrgH! What are you talking about Benjamin Uy?!...Your thinking like an idiot now…you have a serious situation here…this is your first encounter with a crazed BULC girl!!! Think of a plan you sexy thing!  I wanted to slap myself on the face for being so stupid…you might think I’d slap myself because I got the girl fired and now she was mega pissed off…but…no…I wouldn’t slap myself for that…never…it was her fault anyway, I have no feelings of guilt at all towards her…besides, she’s not worth ruining my face for…  Well as I was saying…I’d slap myself for not thinking of an emergency route just incase I encounter fans…I mean, if it’s one fan this time then what about next time…2? 14? 20?!…  Urgh! Benjamin Uy why do you have to be so slow sometimes I thought I had everything covered…the looks, the fashion statement…the charm…but I forgot the escape route just incase I encounter a Benjamin crazed fan...  ‘What do you want?’ I spat.  My voice was full of menace and arrogance…I didn’t mean to sound that way…I guess I was panicking…  Then I thought to myself…if this was one of my crazed fans then I would have to make a good impression…she could tell my other fans that I was rude and not all that…o.0…I guess that’s how it has to go when you’re the sexiest man alive…*sigh*  ‘Revenge’ she muttered  ‘Uh-hUh…and how are you going to do that?...you’re not like any fan I’ve seen before…instead of revenge I thought you would be worshipping the ground that I walked on, and besides me getting you fired…if I was you, I’d be thankful that I took notice in you…’ I replied back nonchalantly…while sneering…  I was beginning to feel at ease and I loosened my muscles while crossing my arms in a pose I had practiced many times in the mirror before…I called it my ‘cool pose’  Before she could open her mouth to say something I cut her off and started again…this time letting it all out…  ‘And I’ve never seen a fan stoop so low…honestly, if you wanted something that I possessed why not go to eBay auction?...no need to steal…you don’t even act like a fan…the only thing that makes you my fan is that you’ve probably been fantasizing about me and stalking me for god knows how long…’ I snickered to myself knowing I had got her there…  Any second now she was going to let it all out…and show me pictures she had taken of me going to my house, going to the shops…practically anywhere you could…imagine…maybe even an old Mc Donald’s foam cup that I had drunken from…who knows what extremes my fans would go to…  I turned my head to face her because I had been leaning on my car the whole time…  *!!!Ka-PoW!!!*  ‘AwWw...SH*T!!!’ I cried out in pain…  Did that just happen?!...I thought to myself…did she just punch me? But I didn’t have to answer that, the pain near my eye was enough…and sheesh...aren’t girls meant to slap…not punch…what a tomboy   When I had gathered back my senses, I straightened my figure and stared at her while snarling…she was really pissing me off…what was with this girl anyway?!  ‘What the Heck was that for?!’ I spat out.  Now it was her time to sneer at me…daMmit…I covered my hurt eye hoping I wouldn’t have a black eye later on...but the chances were pretty high…this girl could do some serious damage!...she had a lot of strength for a girl…  ‘Was that your revenge?!’ I scowled at her.   She had the biggest smirk on her face…that pissed me of even more…If she wasn’t a girl I would’ve hit her…but then again…she could have been a guy cause she had a lot of strength…and she acted like a guy to…not to mention I thought she was a lesbian, so she could’ve been straight, just that she was a drag queen…  I thought to myself for a moment with a blank expression plastered on my face…then I inspected her smirking face...she had large hazel eyes, a petite nose and small cherry lips…all her features seemed to scream out ‘perfection’ and ‘femininity’…  I shook my head vigorously coming to the conclusion that she wasn’t a drag queen because she had the figure of a girl too…*sigh*…I settled with the conclusion that she was a tomboy…and again, a ‘lesbian’…obviously because she had punched me…and if my other fans were here...they’d want to get a piece of her…  I could picture them right now…  *Ben’s Dreamy Thoughts*  ***[Rewind]***  *** [Play] ***  *!!!Ka-PoW!!!*  ‘AwWw...SH*T!!!’ I cried out in pain…  *screams* ‘Ben…are you okay?!’   I’d soon be bombarded with my fans…  ‘You’re beautiful face, Oppa…are you okay…’ another fan would be close to tears  Others looked like they had been punched…that’s how much my fans loved me…*sigh*…they felt my pain so much that it hurt them…  A couple of my other fans fainted from the shock…poor girls...I guess it was too much for them…  All of a sudden my fans got up…one by one…leaving a few of them still comforting me and smothering me with affection…  ‘You’ll pay for that you B*tch!’ one of them would say  ‘YeaH…we’re going to teach you not to mess with Ben….who the heck do you think you are anyway…to ruin his sexy face…you’re going down!!!’ another determined fan would yell out  The rest of them chorused in with a … ‘yEah!’  All of a sudden they were all screaming and charging towards the weirdo fan…*sigh*…where would I be without my fan club...  *End of Ben’s Dreamy Thoughts*  I was taken back to reality when the ex-bar girl, ex-lesbian and ex-drag queen spoke…wow she was a lot of ‘ex’s’  ‘No…that was just for making up a lot of sh*t’ she snarled in a matter-a-fact tone which pissed me off even more…  Urgh! I can’t stand her!  ‘Get in the car’ she said, her voice seemed to be calming down…she seemed more feminine now…  I did as she said thinking that she was going to let me go now…*phew*…this was enough for one day…as soon as I get home I’m taking a long shower…  I clicked the alarm and got in my car…while I put on my seatbelt the weird girl opened the passenger door right next to the driver’s seat…  What the hell?!...she’s not getting in with me! I’m not that crazy…she’ll probably bash me to a pulp…  She got in the car…and I glared at her mouth-open and eyes wide…what the heck did she want now?!     CHAPTER 9  [Ben’s P.O.V.] Again…I thought to fast and I thought I was allowed to go…but here I am again…in a car with some psycho…  ‘Now what is it?!’ I scowled at her while frowning…  Again, she wore the same annoying smirk on her face…I could tell that she had the upper hand already…obviously she wasn’t going to leave me alone unless she got what she wanted…*sigh*…she was lucky that I wasn’t the abusive type of guy if you know what I mean..  ‘You got me fired’ she said in an accusing voice  ‘You stole from me’ I said mimicking her tone  ‘I’m going to be homeless now because of you’ she said accusing me in a louder voice…  I paused for a few moments taking it all in…homeless? Is that why she stole? Is that why she’s a bar girl?  It dawned on me why she did all those things…and how she was so pissed off at me…bar girls earn quite a lot of money nowadays…and I got her fired…I was beginning to feel sorry for her…*sigh*……she probably needed the money...  But I wasn’t going to let her know I felt sorry for her...I’d probably get another black eye……it was so unfair though…because she was a girl I wasn’t allowed to hit her…and that pissed me off…  ‘You stole my cell phone’ I accused her in a challenging way while leaning closer to her…  ‘Because of you I lost my only friend’ she said again in aggravation…she leaned closer challenging me back  Retreating my head a few centimeters…I thought of a comeback…HmmS…  ‘You stole my wallet!’ I accused in a loud voice…  ‘There was only 5 bucks in there anyway you cheap prick!’ she yelled at me trying to defend her actions…  I was taken aback by her words but I managed to find a come back pretty easily…  ‘I don’t like carrying around a lot of money okay?! And 5 bucks is probably a lot more then you have!’ I spat back  As soon as I had finished my sentence…her face softened and I immediately wished that I hadn’t said that…maybe I was too cruel and harsh…  Before I could apologize I got another…-  *!!!Ka-PoW!!!*  Whelps…I guess you know what happened huh? Yups you’re right…another black eye *sigh* but this time I deserved it…   ‘ARgh!!! F*ck!’ I cried out in agony again…  DaMn…this loony wasn’t going to get an apology from me...never, not after my 2nd black eye…  ‘So what the heck do you want now?!’ I grimaced at her…hoping to change the subject…  ‘Like I said…revenge…’she sneered at me…  ‘Yeah…I’m not stupid you know…you don’t have to repeat yourself…’ I retorted.  ‘What do you want then?’ I asked her giving up the fight trying to get it over and done with while covering my ‘2nd’ black eye...  She snickered at me…urgh! I can’t stand her…she pisses me off so much...  ‘I’ll be staying with you for a hundred days…either that or you give me $100,000…your choice’ she said seeming as though she had thought about it for a while…  My mouth gaped open not wishing I had heard correctly…  ‘W-w-what?’ I managed to choke out while stuttering…  Her eyes met mine and she stared at me for a few moments before wearing a big grin from ear to ear…  ‘I thought you said you weren’t stupid’ she questioned me…  My face had a blank and confused expression on…what was she talking about…  ‘I’m not stupid’ I retorted back in a matter-a-fact tone  ‘Didn’t you say I didn’t have to repeat myself because you weren’t stupid?’ she asked me already knowing the answer…  ‘Yeah…so?’ I replied her curious to what she was getting at…  ‘Well you wanted me to repeat myself just then’ she said flatly  I paused for a short while taking it all in…she was right...I did…I wanted to strangle her right now…dammit...She was so annoying and I hated the fact that she was right…  ‘aRgH!...whatever’ I retorted, while crossing my arms like a little boy and facing the other way not wishing to look at her…  ‘Well…what’s your choice?’ she asked me while slouching on my car seat…  ‘What makes you think that I’m going to do what you say?!’ I snapped  ‘Well…besides the fact that you stripped me from my only friend, got me fired, and soon I’m going to be homeless all because of you…I also have your personal belongings…e.g. your cell phone and driver’s license…unless you want people to see Benjamin Uy the man with the afro…then I suggest you agree to my conditions’ she replied with a big grin plastered on her face.  My eyes grew wide with shock…  ‘This is blackmail!’ I accused her in disgust.  ‘Don’t you think I already know this?’ she sneered at me not expecting an answer…  I thought for a while and spoke again…  ‘You know…your offer is ‘extremely tempting’ but I think turning you in as a thief to the police seems more satisfying’ I retorted sarcastically.  I waited to see what she would say…it didn’t really matter though…because this time I had the upper hand…HuahahAHa…and it felt good too…  ‘Are you threatening me?’ she said in a low whisper while slowly leaning closer to my face…  She was so close that I could feel her hot breath on me…  ‘So what if I am? You started it by trying to blackmail me’ I snarled in disgust while leaning in close…we were so close that our noses were millimeters away from touching…  She paused for a while and gazed into my eyes…then she pulled away and leaned on the car door while facing me inside the car…  She grinned at me and all the while never took her eyes off of me…what was this weirdo up to now?...  ‘What?’ I asked her demandingly   ‘Oh…it’s nothing…it’s just that I thought you wouldn’t want your drivers license to be enlarged and stuck around the city so everybody could see that humungous, embarrassing afro that you had…and I thought you would want your cell phone back…that’s all…nothing much…’ she said casually…  With that she turned her body around and opened the car door motioning that she was leaving…  I was flabbergasted by her words…but as soon as it sank in...I knew my reputation as being the sexiest man alive would be ruined if she wasn’t bluffing...I mean…what would happen to BULC?!...  *Ben’s Dreamy Thoughts* ‘WE LOVE YOU BENJAMIN UY!!!’  ‘MARRY ME BENJAMIN UY!!!’  ‘YOU’RE MY HERO!!!’ *faints*  ‘BEN…I THINK YOU’RE THE SEXIEST MAN ALIVE!!!’  My fans surrounded me with banners and presents…I don’t like to boast or anything but a couple of the banners read…  ‘BENJAMIN UY…GOD’S GIFT TO WOMEN!’  ‘BENJAMIN UY…OUR LEGEND’  ‘SEXY=BENJAMIN UY’  ‘I LOVE YOU BEN…PLEASE BE MINE’  I chuckled light heartedly…to them, I was God’s gift…*sigh*…so perfect…  [Next Day]  Flyer papers were stapled and stuck up anywhere you could imagine…ranging from pink, blue, yellow, white, green and red…  ARgh! My driver’s license…and that hideous picture of me!!!..  ‘Hey…that’s Benjamin Uy…the guy on those papers…how embarrassing…I feel sorry for him’ I heard a girl say…  ‘Isn’t that Benjamin Uy...the guy with the afro?’ another pointed at me and laughed…  ‘Wow…he sure has changed…and to think I used to like a guy who had an afro!’ one of my former fans chuckled…  ‘NoOoOOooOOoooOooO!!!!!!!!!!’  *End of Ben’s Dreamy Thoughts*  ‘WAIT!!!’ I shouted back to the weird girl’s retreating figure…  I wasn’t going to let her ruin my reputation...never...how embarrassing…I shook my head vigorously trying to brush the image out of my mind…what a frightful image…  She turned around and sneered…it was like she already knew I was going to agree to her conditions…that pissed me off as well…how she was always right...and she got her way all the time..…urgh!     CHAPTER 10  [Ben’s P.O.V.] ‘So what’s your choice?’ she snapped again…  I thought for a while…and obviously I didn’t have $100,00…I mean...who would have that amount of money...besides some rich person...and obviously I’m not the richest person in the world…I don’t like to part with my money either…I’m cheap okay?..  ‘100 days…’ I muttered obviously not happy that she had won…  She smirked at me satisfied that she had succeeded in getting what she wanted…again…she got in my car and shut the door behind her…  ‘After the 100 days…I want everything you stole from me back okay?’ I snapped at her demandingly…  ‘Yeah...whatever’ she muttered back while putting her seatbelt on…  I started the engine up in my car…  ‘Why do you want to stay with me anyway? I can understand you’re one of my ‘many’ fans and all…but you sure don’t act like one…you act like you despise me’ I retorted…making sure I emphasized the word ‘many’ deliberately in an attempt to piss her off and tell her that she wasn’t that great herself…  I sat there waiting for her to answer my question…it was quiet for a while…the engine was still running and that was about the only thing that you could hear…  ‘Three strikes bimbo!’ she hollered  *!!!Ka-PoW!!!*  ‘ArgH!!! Damn you…you’re really pissing me off you know?!’ I scowled at her while clutching my eye… (The one she had punched first)  The pain from the first punch was already bad enough...and she just had to punch me again…on the same eye too…oh no…wait…which ever eye she punched it would be the ‘same’ eye anyway…because she had already punched both of my eyes…  ‘So what the heck was that punch for?!’ I asked her extremely annoyed…  ‘Simple…I hate repeating myself…the answer was ‘revenge’…at the start I told you I wanted revenge…then you asked me again what I wanted after I punched you the 2nd time…I told you again that I wanted revenge…then you told me you weren’t stupid and that I didn’t have to repeat myself…and here I am again…you want me to repeat myself…’ she snapped at me  I thought back to the previous events…again…she was right…*sigh*…that would have been three times…  ‘Well…now you know that I don’t like to repeat myself three times in a row okay?...if I do repeat myself again then you’re going to get another punch for being an idiot…got it?’ she said demandingly  ‘Whatever’ I muttered under my breath…  I started up the engine again and I drove her to her old apartment to grab her stuff…then we drove to my apartment…  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~TO BE CONTINUED~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, to give you some facts about this fiction story the characters like me-->(BEN) that I used here are real, I just changed their jobs but I didn't change their personality. Hope you love it. Enjoy Reading and have Fun!!! Thankie!!!  Forewords:  Main Characters:  Ben- Age>23 Average guy who thinks he’s the hottest male in the universe, he likes to get his way all the time and flirts a lot. He relies on his good looks for everything because he hates to part with his money…  Nicky- Age>21 She was given up for adoption when she was a baby, when she was 16 she was forced to leave and fend for herself…she works as a bar girl right now. She’s rude and mean to people she doesn’t know and she tends to get herself drunk a lot…not what you would call the richest person.  Minor Characters:  Ben's friend-Tonti, Jake, Retchi, Rainer and Blue  Ben's Parents-Mr. and Mrs.Uy  Ben's sister- Ice  Derek Wo- Ben's Boss  ^^Story Set in the Philippines^^
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Every one of us has a love story to tell, some are very inspirational and some love story was a sad ending. Why am writing this kind of journal? Well, madami kasi akong friend na gustong malaman ang love story ko. Madalas nilang itanong ang tanong na toh, who is this lucky girl??? Where did you meet her??? Well guys if you really want to know just read this journal.  2nd week, June 2002 first day ng class sa AMA University ng nagdecide ang barkada na huwag ng pumasok sa last class namin dahil that time hindi pa naman regular ang class sa AMA. We decided to have a drink in our tambayan (tapat lang ng AMA) puro boys lang kami that time. Around 1:00 or 1:30pm ng may pumasok na girl sa tambayan namin. She’s tall around 5’7 to 5’8 ang height, slim, fair complextion, sort hair, parang model na may kakaibang karisma. She’s alone that time buying her lunch food, confident and may strong personality. Syempre that time medyo nagulat ako sa character ng girl na pumasok, sabi ko pa nga sa sarili ko noon ang lakas naman ng loob ng babaeng itoh na pumasok sa tambayan ng mga lalaki siguro freshmen or transferee ang babaeng toh. Pero that time alam ko na sa sarili ko na crush ko sya. Lahat kami that time nakatingin sa kanya and siguro napansin nya na may nakatingin sa kanya, tumingin sya sa amin and sabay taas ng kilay. Grabe ang lakas ng loob talaga!!! That time binulungan ako ng bestfriend ko, sabi nya ung girl na un transferee and nagboboard sa boarding house ni ate lhot. Syempre, that time napaisip ako. I said to my self that this girl is different with the other girls I met and I said to my self that I want to meet this girl as soon as possible. That time paalis na yung girl, sabi ko sa sarili ko mga 30 minutes pa susundan ko sya. Nang nasa boarding house na nya ko, ang palabas ko eh naghahanap ang cousin ko ng boarding house nakausap ko yung landlady (ate lhot) nila then I ask her about the tall girl I saw. Awa naman ng diyos pinakilala nya ako sa girl. Nicky ang name nya, 18 yrs old. Kabado nga ako that time habang kausap si nicky and I don’t even know why? I try my best para maging interesting ang conversation naming dalawa pero that time it didn’t work. Hawak-hawak ba naman ang cellphone and ni hindi man lang ako makuhang tignan mas gusto pa atang magtext kesa makipag-usap sa akin. Pero grabe talaga ang tama ko sa kanya pakiramdam ko nga inlove na ko that time sa kanya eh. After that day I decide na ligawan sya, after a couple of weeks awa naman ng diyos sinagot nya koh, that very moment pakiramdam ko am the luckiest guy in the world.  As the day pass lalo akong na-iinlove sa kanya because of her personality because she’s very charming, sweet, cool and very interesting ang character nya. Masarap syang kasama i never had a single moment na nabored ako sa kanya siguro isang explanation doon ay ang pagiging pareho namin ng personality para kasi syang girl version koh. Pareho kami ng hobbies and ng trip. Sa lahat ng naging girlfriend ko sa kanya ko lang naramdaman ang ganon na pakiramdam. Ang dami naming mga memories na masasabi kung may kakaibang spark. Para bang laging may bago sa relationship namin kaya hindi nakakasawa (gets nyo ba ibig kung sabihin?) Basta yon na un ang hirap kasi i-explain eh. I’m so happy that time until one night when I visit her in her boarding house nakita ko syang umiiyak and hindi lang sya basta umiiyak, she was sobbing hard until she notice my present tumayo sya sa kinauupuan nya and she hug me crying badly. The only question in my mind that time is, why is she crying??? Ako ba ang rason ng pag-iyak nya??? That very moment I feel so bad at that moment and pakiramdam ko lahat ng lakas ko sa katawan ay nawala, yakap-yakap ko ang babaeng pinakamamahal ko and I don’t know what to do to make her feel better. Nasasaktan ako na nakikita ko syang umiiyak *did anyone of you fell this kind of pain*. Yakap-yakap ko sya while whispering in her ears not to cry because I feel lost when she do that then she stop and look in my eyes with tears in her eyes and said im sorry because pinag worry kita that badly, I promise I will never do that again. After she said that I hug her and told her how much I love her and cherish her. I asked her why she’s crying that hard, but she didn’t tell me. The next day nalaman ko na lang sa landlady nila na ninakaw ung hamster (Russian dwarf hamster) na binigay ko kay nicky and that night hindi alam ni nicky kung paano nya i-explain na nawala ang hamster na binigay ko sa kanya and she’s so worried na baka magalit ako sa kanya that’s why she’s crying. At that moment lalo kung na prove sa sarili ko na this girl is really different and that moment I realize how much I love her, she’s the only person na nagbigay ng halaga sa akin *you want to ask why?* because I told her that hamster is represent me as her special love one and that she need to take care of that hamster the way she take care of me.  Well, our relationship went smooth as I expected dahil sabi ko nga pareho kami ng hilig simula sa pc games hanggang sa kind ng music na pinapakinggan namin. Pero siguro talagang may relationship na dumadaan sa mga trials na nagiging dahilan upang hindi magwork ang isang relationship. Of course nangyari na rin sa relationship namin ni Nicky ang bagay na yan. 3rd week ng July 2003 when Nicky and Ritchie (one of my bestfriends) decided to go to my house in Caloocan to surprise me. That time naman on the way na ko sa Boarding House nya to pick her up. They went in my place and ang nadatnan nila ay ang mommy ko. Let me first tell you guys something about my mom. My mom doesn’t like Nicky as my girlfriend because she’s a pure Filipino, gusto kasi nya Chinese or kahit half Chinese man lang. But nicky doesn’t know that my mom doesn’t like her, ang alam nya gusto sya ng mom ko as my girlfriend. Hindi ko kasi sinabi sa kanya na ayaw sa kanya ng mom ko coz I know she’s gonna be really upset. I don’t know what really happened in my place all I know is my mom told Nicky that she doesn’t like her and she want her to get out in my life. Pero Ritchie told me na hindi lang yon ang sinabi ng mom ko kay Nicky may mga masasakit din na salita na sinabi sa kanya. That time naman nasa labas ako ng boarding nila Nicky waiting for her, around 7:00pm ng umulan medyo nag-aalala na ko sa kanya dahil hindi pa rin sya dumadating I didn’t notice na dumating na pala sya she’s standing back at me kasi. That time naramdaman ko na may problema sya, I ask her what’s wrong??? She look me in the eyes and told me about what happened in my place. That moment alam ko na masamang-masama ang loob nya and I know that she wants to cry pero pinipigil nya. Gusto kong yakapin sya and tell her that it’s okey to cry, na okey lang na ilabas nya ang sama ng loob nya coz I’m here to listin pero hindi ko magawa. Pakiramdam ko kasi noon eh galit sya sakin dahil hindi ko sinabi sa kanya yung tungkol sa mom ko. She then told me that we have to talk about our relationship. Mahal na mahal daw nya ko but tama daw ang sinabi ng mom ko about me that our relationship will never work. Sabi nya kailangan nya muna ng space dahil magulo ang isip nya. That moment I want to shout, to cry, tell her that we don’t need to do that pero i have no guts to tell that kind of words to her. Pakiramdam ko that moment nag stop ang mundo ko. She said that we need to have a space between us, wala akong masabi that time sa kanya ni hindi ako umiimik that moment. Then a couple of minutes pass she hug me and walk away from me. I called her name but she didn’t look back, I know she’s crying that moment and I know she didn’t want me to see her like that. Nakatayo lang ako habang pinagmamasdan palayo ang babaeng pinakamamahal ko, naramdaman ko na lang na umiiyak na ko (napansin nya kaya yon?). It’s almost 1 hour when I decided to leave that place, tinawagan ko si Ritchie at sinabi ko yung nangyari sa amin ni Nicky. I want to get drunk that time kaya inaya ko na rin ang barkada na umiinom. I decided to go to her place again, to talk to her and convince her pero sinabihan ako ni Ritchie na na ipagpabukas ko na lang ang pagpunta kina Nicky dahil nakainom na ako at para magkaroon si Nicky ng time na makapag-isip. Well, I decided to go the following day pero hindi ako nakapunta dahil may pinaasikaso ang mom ko na papeles na kailangan sa business namin. I called Nicky on her cellphone that day pero naka-off. Tinext ko pa rin sya kahit alam kong naka-off ang cellphone nya and told her na pupunta ako kina-umagahan para makapag-usap kami, I know naman that time na wala akong matatanggap ng respond mula sa kanya pero still pursigido ako na makausap sya ng personal (gusto ko kasi talagang ayusin ang relationship naming dalawa.)   *TO BE CONTINUE*  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Her height should be around: >As long as she's not taller than me  Body: >Skinny  Her personality: >Kind, thinking about other's ahead, cool and funny  Age difference between her and me: >1–2 years younger than me  Out of her body, the first place I look at: >height, hair and eyes  Favorite hairstyle: >Anything that looks right on her  Favorite fashion: > Anything that looks right on her  Overall image: > Instead of sexy... Clean and cool   What she should always have: > Plenty time of life. Not stressed  What I can appeal to her: > Strongness and Honesty  To my girlfriend, what I really want to do? > Hold hands and go to the park. > Go to beach and eat cotton candy  If I found out that she was cheating on me: > Depressed and never ever see her again...  If I loved someone else other than her: > I don't want to do that  If someone that I don't know, proposed to me: > Of course reject!  I proposed really hard but get rejected: > Try 10 times. Try 100 times until I die...  In front of love, I take action or take slowly at a time: > Action. Of course it's hard  What I think love is: > Growing old  I'm this type of a guy' introduction: > I'm a type of guy who doesn’t change. But in front of love, I change. > I might look cute because of my outside image but I'm a real man and sometimes act like a child.  To my girlfriend: > I'm going to make you happy > I really really love you! For being my half... > Loving you is what I'm going to do... 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      1. I was circumcised at age 7... *ouch* 2. I had intercourse at age 16. 3. I rolled my car into a ditch at age 17 because I was drunk. 4. I have a deep passion for music. 5. I love different kinds of sport cars. 6. I have 4 different cars in manila. And 1 car here in Singapore. 7. I love American foods. 8. One of my favorite movies is Cruel Intention. 9. My favorite drink is Beer. 10. My favorite colors are Black and Blue. 11. I was terrified of thunder and lightening when I was in my high school time. 12. I watch the weather channel. 13. I don't have tattoos in my body. 14. Warcraft is my favorite pc games. 15. I have my own business already. 16. I love my girlfriend so much more than anybody else I know in my life. 17. I do not own a gun and I have never fired one. 18. My parents didn't cut my hair until I was three... *waaaaaaa* 19. I have to admit, I am a cute guy! *wink* 20. I'm a smoker. 21. I walked around in nude in my pad here in Singapore. *blush* 22. I'm good at sports. 23. I'm a car racer. 24. I'm a good swimmer. 25. I love reading different kinds of books. 26. I don’t get drunk that easily. 27. My worst sport right now is golf. 28. I'm already 23 turning 24 this coming June. 29. I wish I was more interested in education when I was younger. 30. I’m good in math. 31. I like chicken wings. 32. I like Australian wine. 33. I don't think crop circles are made by humans. 34. I think the universe was made not just for us. 35. I don't like wearing ties. 36. I believe in love at first sight. 37. I want to go back in manila right now. 38. I miss my girlfriend so much. 39. Rome is one of the countries I want to visit right now. 40. I'm sometimes an asshole. 41. I hate line ups. 42. I have two best friends. 43. I owned 2 different colors of contact lenses. 44. R&B is my favorite kind of music. 45. Subic and Boracay are my favorite beaches in Philippines. 46. I never hit the snooze button. 47. I don't sleep enough. 48. I like having time to myself. 49. I used to be so damn stupid. 50. I have piercing in my ears. 51. I prefer to have a bathtub than a shower. 52. I also wish I have a license to kill. 53. I wish I have a dog. *bark* 54. I love rainy season. 55. I chat a lot in the chat room with my girlfriend. 56. I love perfume. 57. I have 50 collectable CD's in my room. 58. I'm still a student. 59. I've done weird stuff lately. 60. I have a bachelor pad in manila. 61. I know how to bake. 62. My dad died when I was in my high school years. 63. My favorite fruits are orange and mango. 64. I wish my girlfriend is here with me right now. 65. I miss my dad. 66. I have a driving license. 67. I miss my friends in manila. 68. I don't dance well. 69. I'm good in handling money. 70. I don't take drug. 71. Mark and Spencer is one of my favorite signature clothes. 72. I'm an open minded person. 73. I'm not scared of the dark. 74. I believe in karma. 75. I take a bath 3x a day. 76. Drinking coffee in the morning is one of my daily routine. 77. When I was a kid my ambition is to be an astronaut. 78. I'm a half Chinese and half Filipino. 79. I know how to speak Chinese and Tagalog. 80. I say weird, give me a break, and stupid most of the time. 81. I love to watch movie. 83. When I’m still in manila me and my girlfriend eats cotton candy while drinking in Starbucks Cafe. 84. I think my eyes are my good physical attributes. *wink* 85. I wore a pink hair band when I’m still in AMA University. 86. I adore Cameron Diaz. 87. I can stay awake in 3 days without sleeping. 88. I had my first car when I was 16. *broooommm* 89. I hate the politics in the Philippines. 90. I watched mutant ninja turtle cartoon when I was a kid. 91. I love water sport. 92. I wish I'm a secret agent. 93. I'm not a model, and never will be. 94. I have 4 pillows in my bed. 95. I don't play any musical intrusment coz I don't know how. 96. I'm a cancer sign. 97. I'm 5'11 tall. 98. I hate people that snore. *grrrrrr...* 99. People describe me as an arrogant, snobbish, prank and intimidating person. 100. I'm a very lucky guy. *wink*  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *cool me!!!*  urlLink     Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>