<Blog>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a pretty good day. Last night Avram and I decided we had to change Stella's schedule, that her teenager hours of going to bed at 12:30 am and waking up after 9:00 am was making it hard for us to get anything done. Me? I love to sleep and have been relishing these late mornings in some respect, even though Stella often crowds me on the bed and I wake up feeling like we've already missed the party. For example, in warmer weather, by the time we get out to catch the playground scene, everyone--even the freelance stocking capped unshaven slackers--are wheeling their kiddies back inside for naps.  So this morning, we joined the rest of the toddler world and I literally dragged Stella out of bed at 7:30, kneeling first to change her diaper before she was conscious enough to protest. She dozed on couch until about 8:00, totally numb to getting kicked by Zoe who was watching "Arthur." And she had an early nap, and we had time to chill in the park before getting Zoe. I will weep with joy if she goes to bed by 10:00.  So today I was on the west side with Stella at a toddler meeting run by this woman (who has her own 17-year-old Zoe) who taught our childbirth class when I was about to have our Zoe. She's a snacker, this woman, sits on a birth ball and snacks and talks. Very relaxed. It was an open forum. I talked about work and money issues. Afterwards, I forced the plank-like screaming Stella into her stroller, pushed her up to 34th St., strolled into H&M and bought myself a skirt that reminded me of 1950's Sophia Loren. But thinking about it now maybe it's just Sarah Jessica Parker "Sex and the CIty." If it is, if that's what it turns out to be for me . . . why then I'll have to take it back.
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Suffering through the late-mid winter doldrums, the same boring clothes pulled on again and again, the same boots, the same coat, I always enjoy--as corny as it is--celebrating Fat Tuesday. I'm not Catholic, and I guess it's technically a Catholic day--the day that precedes Ash Wednesday, but this fairly cool and very kid friendly cajun/Italian restaurant (called Two Boots, get it?) near our apartment--with Iggy Pop on the jukebox--always celebrates it and they have a special Mardi Gras menu and the staff hands out masks and beads, and you don't have to take off your top, and you can eat alligator, which tonight they did not have.  At 7:00 there was even live music and free firewater shots were being passed around. The featured performer was billed as "Lower East Side legend" Phoebe Leger, who was this aging (like me) bombshell (not me) with long blonde hair, and who tonight wore a red vinyl devil jumpsuit complete with tail, a red cowboy hat with a big tacky feather and a cape made of stitched together scarves, kind of Steven Tyleresque. (Rumor had it among the waitstaff that she'd once appeared in Playboy.) She roamed the restaurant playing cajun music on the accordian and singing into a straped-on microphone. She was backed by two guys, one playing a strange metal washboard percussive contraption, the other on guitar, It was gleeful, and Zoe and her two girlfriends rushed forward to dance.  Zoe is definitely having a very different five-year-old-hood than the one I had.  Stella freaked out though--even though she was thrilled to wear a mask and beads, and even when I picked her up to dance with her--and would not stop crying until Avram took her home.  Emmett and Shelley came, too, and I'm always happy when she makes the trip from Brooklyn to see us.
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the past few days I've had a knot in my stomach brought on by intimations that Nader was going to run for president. I've been amazed by how emotional I've been because of it, and then I talked to my sister Shelley in Brooklyn who told me that recently she woke up in the middle of the night and couldn't go back to sleep out of anxiety that Nader was going to run.  Well, now he's running, and I urge everyone to tell everyone not to vote him. Don't get me wrong--I love Ralph Nader. I even find him foxy in some kind of cock-eyed, off-beat way, and I've already voted for him twice. But this year, it is my mono-manical goal to get evil puppet man out of office.  This is a life or death situation. Don't vote for Nader, and don't give him any money, and don't sign any petition putting him on the ballot.  What a boring blog entry this is.  On the up side, I worked on my novel today and it has some cool stuff in it. I was excited about what I was writing. I was in a cafe by Zoe's school, and they had a great mix of music on the I-pod or whatever it was: "She's a Rainbow" by the Stones, an obscure Partridge Family song. I was singing along and it was fun for me. My pleasures are small.
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We were all on the L train last Sunday night coming back from Williamsburg, Brooklyn and all these Williamsburg hipsters were in our car. I couldn't tell the gender of one really lean hipster in particular, until she spoke.  It was a girl with this great Ramones' aesthetic: painted on jeans all the way down her ankles, Chuch Taylors, too small black leather jacket and a great dyed black mop of hair. She and her friends got off with us at 1st Avenue. I kept thinking, where are they going? What are they doing NOW? Shelley thought that maybe they were just going to someone's house to watch "Curb Your Enthusiasm" or something at the pad of some friend who had cable.  It reminded me of when Joey Ramone and I passed each other on 9th Street in 1998. I was nine months pregnant with Zoe. He was knock-kneed and walking a little too laboriously. I was freaking out, and we both seemed to be moving in slow motion. Neither of us were walking too fast. He was probably ailing then, most definitely, full of cancer. I wanted to say, "Hi, Joey," or "I love you!" or something, but of course I was too shy. I still miss seeing him in the neighborhood.  I love you, Joey Ramone!
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I never touch dirt, or grass, or trees anymore. As a kid I remember how much I used to love hugging trees. They were always warm and seemed to be breathing. I still love to hug them, although the ones in Tompkins Square Park are so old, their trunks are so large in circumference and they're often so gnarled from being peed on?--I'm not sure--that hugging them doesn't give me the same pleasure.  This reminds me of one summer here in the East Village, I was stretched out in the fenced-in grass in Tompskin's Square Park having a bucolic, Emersonian moment, and some haggard guy a few feet from me--also stretched out--turned on towards me and started vomiting wretchedly into the grass. No judgement. It's cool.  But I was just thinking about my life and how I never touch nature, and I feel a little sad about it. Granted, it's too cold to touch anything outside. It's often too cold to stop and give the homeless guys money, and right now they really need it.  Hey, tonight I was in Brooklyn and Zoe and I looked up and for the first time I can remember we saw stars in the night sky. 
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I walked around in kind of a funk. It was sunny and in the 40s and I had some time off--Avram took Stella to breakfast--so I should have been happy, but most of what I felt was ineffectual.  I sat down at the computer and looked at my novel. Added a couple of sentences and then thought, maybe I should put this back into third person--I had recently eerily added a first-person narrator. Shelley called and I stalled on the phone with her for a bit, talked about our other sister, whose birthday was yesterday.  Then I left the house to run a birthday errand before I had to retrieve Stella and meet Zoe at school. Some parents had decided that Zoe's teacher, whose birthday is today, needed a present. So I was off to Barnes and Noble with a fistful of donated cash to get the teacher a writing journal, which was another parent's suggestion. So I wandered around wasting time, noticed with chagrin a remote Utah friend's second publication--a collection of stories--stacked on the browsing table. And she's a mother of two, too. How does she do it? Why am I so lame?  After that headed to a lame ass Starbucks, got a bottled water and took out my little red notebook and sat there and worked on my novel. It keeps jumping back and forth between characters, not a bad thing, but I'm doing a lot of weaving trying to keep all the threads intact. I kept staring at this striking girl in a long red coat, long dark hair, taller than me, wondering what my life would have been like if I'd been her. She looked up and saw me. Does she think I'm some crazy lesbian? Suddenly these days I'm feeling old, like my youth is gone. I remember feeling that way at 20, but this time, this time it's REAL! 
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got up, got a shower, put on on outfit I like which included purple tights, pink beaded bracelet and witchy star pendant, like the one that--is it Bon Scott? wears on the cover of "Highway to Hell," and went to a La Leche League meeting with my kind of new friend J. If there's another woman I'd like to look like right now it would be J. She has a big beautiful smile, thick lustrous brown hair, and has a strong, sturdy yoga instructor's body and a great personal style. Today she wore her Jutta Naumann(sp?) boots and carried her daughter R in a sling. We took a cab because we were so late.  I reconnected with the Leader there, whose this just damn nice Southern gal, mother of two. She's a lactation consultant and after a meeting she and her daughter and another woman from the meeting--a groovy social worker and her daughter and Stella and I all went for sushi. All of us have two daughters, we were all lunching with our second daughters. Moments like these make me feel like I really belong in New York.  I am in the middle of making a turkey meatloaf, but I wonder . . . if the turkey has gone bad . . . .
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everytime I sit down to add an entry, the conditions in the apartment are exactly the same. Z and S are watching a video, there's a mess in the kitchen, Avram is out, I'm tired. It's all coldness and darkness. It sleeted and rained all day. The landscape is slush.  I have to find something good about this part of the winter. Something to really love about it, because it's a drag feeling so complainy all of the time.  I just bought Johnny Cash's song "The Mercy Seat" from I-tunes. Well, I think it's actually his cover of a Nick Cave song. The lyrics are amazing. Cash's voice is from middle earth. It's a first-person narration of a man on death row, but the ending is ambiguous. Did he do it or not? I find that I get very easily caught up in death-row dramas.  Zoe wants more capers. She loves capers. I can't believe I have to go already! See how my life is?  If anyone wants a recipe for chicken and garlic stew that's very easy and takes almost no tending, email me.
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The best freeform radio station that I know of is wfmu in New Jersey. You can listen on-line at www.wfmu.org. I'm listening now. It makes me feel like I'm doing something fun even though I'm not.  This morning on Democracy Now! (www.democracynow.org) I heard the story of Kevin Cooper. Tonight he's on death-row in California for multiple murders: three people dead in two minutes. Something like that. One of the victims clutched ten strands of blonde hair in her hand. Kevin Cooper is black. This piece of evidence never went before the jury. He is scheduled to die Tuesday night. Cooper refuses to choose the execution method (gas or injection). He refuses to choose a last meal. He is not cooperating in the death rituals. Call Governor S. tomorrow and request a stay: 917.445.2840.  Stella wants me to play catch, so I have to go now. I'm glad that I have the freedom to play catch with Stella.
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm back in the closet. Stella again has a dirty diaper that I am putting off changing. Avram is off somewhere doing something--heleft before he could get Zoe to sleep. So it is 10:17 and Zoe is up having watched endless reality television with me: "American Idol," and "America's Next Top Model." See how I'm poisoning my children? Go ahead. Call social services.  I hate this time of the year, waiting for the winter to end. My tiresome winter outfits: tights with knee socks over it, and then these leg warmer things, and then some old boring skirt. And then the top has to be layered, and then over that two jackets, and then I have to find my hat, scarf, gloves. And then I have to do the same for Stella. Sometimes I take her out to the lobby to dress her: open up the vestibule door like a sadist so that she will really, really understand that she really, really needs to put on her coat. 
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got up late this morning. Stella and me. Avram had already taken Zoe to school (Zoe, who woke up with another bloody nose this morning), and it was almost 10, when we rolled off the bed. The first entry on this site (or blog or what have you) was written by Tina: just one word--"Test." I have been Tina's friend since 1984. I first saw Tina in a photo booth strip, tiny in black and white. I couldn't yet tell she had vibrant red hair, which in the photo she is pretending to cut off. She actually brought a pair of scissors into the booth. This photo strip was on the desk on a guy I'd been making out with for a week. Tina was his girlfriend. And he told me so when I asked. I was crushed, but was so young, I couldn't get mad, couldn't say anything. A year later, I was Tina's roommate. I still love Tina, in fact. She inspired this web journal.  Tina has her own blog, which is amazing and sensitive and funny and heartfelt. It's like reading her diary. Which is why I'm not going to provide the URL. Not until I ask Tina. Tina is really good at making things around her beautiful, which is why I had her design this site, which is a very simple site, (because I'm having a problem with my Paypal account--can't remember the password and they won't give it to me--and so I can't post any photos here yet (yeah, as if I know how to do that.))  Wow, this is a boring first entry from me. I am hiding from my two daughters, ages two (Stella) and five (Zoe). I am in a closet with my computer. They are listening to a cd Zoe made with her class last year. Her teacher was this charismatic(sp?), handsome, celebrity of a teacher who (I was a little afraid of) and who taught the kids Clash and Prince songs, plus his own original songs. At the end of the year, they made a recording, and Marcello--that was his name--burned 20 cds, one for every little kid.  I must have more to say. I don't want to change Stella's diaper yet.  Here are some good things from today (lists like this inspired by Tina, who is such an appreciative and thankful person):  1. Having tomato soup with my sister at a trendy (Austrian?) place in Brooklyn. They have five dollar goulash Mondays. Our waiter was cute, wearing two t-shirts and very nice about the mess Stella and Emmett made.  2. Lots of people helped me with the stroller on the subway today. And I got the escalator exit at Delancey Street.  3. Because of one mini cupcake, Stella was occupied and happy during the subway ride home. It was great how long it took her to eat one tiny cupcake. I would like to spend 45 minutes eating a tiny cupcake.  Okay, I guess that's it. An inauspicious beginning.
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like my neighbors. Two apartments up is a very sweet guy who fronts a band called Guster. He's gone most of the time, on tour, and fresh-faced friends of his (plus, most recently, his girlfriend who moved into his pad while he was gone) are occasionally dropping by our apartment to pick up his keys--since we are ALWAYS here. Today I ran into him getting out of a white stretch limosine--strange, even for a minor rock star who was on Leno about six months ago. He asked me if I had missed him, and you know, I think I had.  We have another neighbor who lives on the other side of the building, several floors up. She used to date Moby, published an article about her anorexia in Jane, and has her own b & d exercise class called Slavercize, for which she wears a t-shirt that reads "Beat Your Fat." She is sweet, though, rescues dogs from what she calls the "kill shelter," and has a collection of rescued chihuahuas, one of whom is named Batgirl. Recently, I saw her strapping on rollerblades and weeping by the dumpster, because someone had stollen her bike for the third time! (From our prison-style fenced in courtyard!!) And then soon after, a rat had crawled through up her toilet and into her apartment. We kept our own lid down for a long time.  I'm already thinking about what I will do the morning after Bush gets elected--if indeed he does, and am still casting about for ideas. Wear an "Impeach Bush!" teeshirt every day for the next year? Why can't I think of anything better?  Today I spent the afternoon with Zoe. She had stayed home from school today. She performed some really bad magic tricks for me, but of course, I told her how great they were. The sword-swallowing parent, who was a regular at the Coney Island Side Shows, recently performed at her school (using his own kids as assistants), and I think she felt inspired.
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I got a package from my grandmother of stories that I wrote while at BYU. I've been loving looking through them, contrary to what I had thought I'd feel. They were all written almost 20 years ago, and in some ways I think back then I was a better writer, more interested in the texture of language or some such corny notion.  Stella just assaulted me and then fell down and hurt herself. My life is a series of constant interruptions. Especially when I try to do something creative.
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just wrote an entry that slid from my fingers down the cyberhole. Here it is again in tired sentences: Zoe and I went to big rally on Saturday. Zoe made peace signs with a Sharpie on the subway. Got out on 28th Street, held up our signs. Put stickers on our coats. Took 30 minutes to walk five blocks. Zoe was tired--she kept getting hit by bags and couldn't see anything! We talked a cop into letting us sit on a bench and watch. Saw the Radical Cheerleaders (with boys!) and their pink and black pom poms.  Afterwards, tried to eat at an organic live food restaurant, but there was nothing on the menu for Zoe. "Zoe, that's the nut burger platter--are you sure you're going to want to eat that????"  I'm real tired. Cooked up a storm for my doula client. Today I told her what a plugged duct looks like. It was our last visit. I saw her for 27 hours over three weeks. She feels a lot better about being a mother now. Yeah.
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was going to write about Spaulding Gray today, and my friend Michael in dewy Portland beat me to it. (He has a great blog, by the way: mushika.blogspot.com.)  I am sad about Spaulding, although on a personal level I would have found him infuriating, but also would have been charmed by him, and would have developed a small, annoying crush on him in spite of myself. I saw Spaulding perform a couple of years after I moved here--maybe in 1997?--outdoors in the Prospect Park bandshell in Brooklyn. He did this incredible thing where, before the show, he stood outside the gates and watched the streams of people entering, and then at near random, chose a few people he felt like he connected with somehow. (I remember seeing him out there, looking a little tentative.) He had only a few seconds to decide. The show consisted of Spaulding interviewing the few he chose on the outdoor stage impromptu style. He was a great interviewer and made these seemingly innocuous people seem like the most fascinating creatures on the planet.  Stella and Zoe are fighting over a pair of shoes and so this will have to stand as my tribute to Spaulding.
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've had really bad sleeps for two nights straight. Did I say this already? Stella's been up a lot, restless all night long, kicking me, whimpering, needing comforting back to sleep. Every time I sit down--on a park bench--on a hard kitchen chair, leaning against a pole at a bus stop, I feel like I'm going to drift off and the snow will blanket me.  I also had to work this morning, help that new mother with her new baby. The time goes fast; I showed new mom how to breast feed lying down, and kept her baby calm while she took a shower. Then the new mother put on the new Norah Jones before she left the room and that nearly put me to sleep.  Listen, I don't want people to think I'm all square because I'm advocating supporting the Kerry campaign. I have always had crushes on anarchists. I will always have a soft spot in my heart for communal hippies, progressives, Reagan-bashing punk rockers and radical politcos, and I'm sorry, I don't think Bush and Kerry are interchangeable, like my friend Julie on the far left, or my dad on the far right, do. I don't think Kerry is would take us to the depths of hell.  On another subject, for a real escapist good time at the movies (in your living room) rent the video or dvd of "School of Rock." It warmed the wintry cockles of my anarchist loving heart, and I can't stop singing the song all those cute kids perform at the big concert.
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just heard on Democracy Now! that a recent poll revealed that in a three-way race Bush would narrowly defeat Kerry if the election were held today, with Bush receiving 46 percent of the vote, Kerry receiving 45 and Nader receiving 6 percent of the vote. (Damn that Nader.) I know just a small sampling of people are polled, but this news is freaking me out.  Yesterday I forwarded to several friends a message from moveon.org that urges people to contribute to the Kerry campaign. A good friend in Salt Lake City wrote back saying she just sent 25 bucks (had wanted to anyway before my email). My sister sent in 100. I even contributed in a very underemployed way, but even donating my paltry sum made my heart beat faster. I urge everyone reading this to contribute: www.moveon.org. You can contribute to Kerry's campaign from this site. You'll feel like a patriot if you do.
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haven't written in awhile. I only have brief spots of time for myself, and even now, I feel like I should be working on my novel, instead of adding to my blog. I've actually had some paid work this past two mornings as a postpartum doula for a shell-shocked lady with a newborn way out in Brooklyn. I enjoy the work. I really was in the trenches with this woman getting her started with breastfeeding--grabbing the breast of a stranger, molding it and ramming the baby's head into it. It made me realize again how unfinished we all are when we're born, and how much help everyone involved needs. It feels good to help, and to make money doing it (hahaha). But I'm thinking lately that I'm missing my former life on campus, taking classes, teaching, hanging out in the grad students' carrel(forgot how to spell this) lounge talking about art and ideas. I kind of have this sick fantasy of moving back to Utah, finishing up my botched and tattered PhD, doing it right this time, and then what? Trying to get a job in academia? I'm not sure. I'm not sure I'm willing to move to any old place just to have a teaching job at a university.  Anyway, I wouldn't go back to my old program without a novel in hand, something I never seem to get to work on.  In other news, Stella's been going to bed consistently by 11:00, sometimes by 10:00, and everyone's getting up earlier and it feels good. We were actually able to watch "Lost in Translation" before the Oscars, and I really loved it, although Avram only liked the first hour. I thought it felt very much like a great short story, very poetic, and now I really want to go to Tokyo, because it makes NYC feel like a provincial little township.  I'm feeling sad and out of sorts today. A lot to worry about, financial crap, finishing the school newsletter, the toxic chemicals in the cleaning agent that the building's cleaning lady keeps using and the fumes permeate our apartment. Maybe I should hit the streets.
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My sister Shelley just got back from a big birthday party where she talked to this guy from Salt Lake City about this other guy I once knew--the first guy I ever kissed. I was 19 and a sophomore at BYU. His name was Kevin. He went to the community college. Kind of. He was older than me and he was in a punk band called the Bad Yodelers. We had been going to the Tuesday night dollar movies for several weeks, not really talking to each other much. I was really freaked out to be with him, very nervous. (Omigosh! Why me?) He showed up once at the door with his hair dyed in an argyle-sock pattern. One night we went to a friend of his house in the Provo hills and watched Eraserhead. Just as I was about to leave the pad for my Chevy Nova (a great car, circa 1974), he grabbed me and did it and I freaked out. I remember driving home shakily, really stunned, and then waking up my roommate, telling her and then we both jumped on our beds for awhile, screeching, of course.  Kevin would later make out with this roommate behind my back for several months--but that's another story.  Anyway I found out that Kevin is living in Springville, has put on, according to this source, quite a bit of weight and has a much younger wife (and I think several children). I wonder what else he's doing. He was really into thrift-store shopping and once sewed a bunch of old wigs to a sweater for a gig.  A lot of good things happened once in Utah.
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Above headline is from the current Onion. What have I been wanting to write about? Our couch--the only couch we've ever owned in this family-- is continually being eroded by vomit and trampolining. It's okay. A lot's happened on that couch, not just vomiting episodes, but like thousands of hours of nursing babies, and recovering from childbirth--and the day we get rid of it will be a sad one. Also, Zoe had a big nosebleed over her pillow. It's like we live on a ship here in this apt. We keep very few supplies around. Sadly, we don't have a huge amoire full of linens and pillows, like someone I know out in Utah. We'll have to use the nosebleedy pillow for awhile.  Yesterday, we went to the Bronx Zoo for the very first time, and it was all misty and rainy outside--very Pacific Northwest. It's huge, this zoo. In several hours, we saw relatively little. It was like visiting a national park. I was very intrigued by the ornate 100-year-old buildings--now administrative offices--which used to house lions, etc, before people realized that that was a stupid way to house lions. Oh yeah, and the gorrilla forest is amazing, with lots of new babies cuddling with their mothers, and males staring sternly out at us where we stood behind the plexi glass barrier. Looking at them is completely uncanny. I love you, gorillas!  (Also, the Bronx Zoo was the first institution to bring the bison back from near extinction.)  Oh, yeah, saw a great film on DVD over the weekend--Together, which is a Swedish film about a commune in Stockholm set in 1975. Those Swedes, even when they're funny, they're dark. Someone else see it, so we can talk about it. Zoe's having a break down. Damn. I can't concentrate. Sorry for the lame entry.
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been proofreading a 9th grade standardized test prep math book and it's making me sick. I sat at the kitchen table working through it while Zoe was home sick, herself. (Stella's sick, too.) Of course, our living room couch is only about ten feet from the kitchen table so Zoe interrupted me a lot. Avram got her two videos, as per her request: Beauty and the Beast and Sleeping Beauty. The nerdy, ass-kissing student in me piped up enthusiastically: "hey Zoe, why don't we write a report for your teacher tomorrow, comparing and contrasting the two Beautys and also the two evil characters in both movies!" She looked at me totally confused, and said okay, very bored, looking away.  What she did want to do was reenact Sleeping Beauty. I put my proofreading away. She let me play the main character, which--good thing for me--entailed a lot of sleeping, first as a newborn than as the sixteen year old under the spell. Zoe played all of the other roles, including having a fight with herself as both the evil queen and the prince who rescues me. I kept thinking, hmmm, and she's too sick to go to school??? Anyway, not a lot of work got done. Sometimes I feel like we don't have time for gainful employment.
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And all I got was this lousy sample. Okay, that was lame, but I really did go to Moby's bake sale. Last Saturday, Move On (of www.moveon.org) put their names on thousands of bake sales held across the country in almost all 50 states. It was their Bake Sale for Democracy campaign to take back the White House. There were two within a stone's throw of us. One of them was Moby's. We got there early. Moby was slouched in a baseball cap on an Impala sort of supervising everything. An hour later, Janeann Garafolo was selling cupcakes, and about 30 minutes after that Al Sharpton and Al Franken were side by side selling cookies and scones. A huge line snaked down the block.  Zoe and I went home, baked our own cookies, and took them to the non-celebrity bake sale around the corner from Moby's. She had made a sign: "Zoe's Organic Cookies" and decorated it with a drawing of a girl and flowers. Do I have to tell you she was a big hit? She stood very shyly behind the table--they made room for her--and she sold out her cookies before anyone, making about 40 bucks for the Kerry campaign.  Which brings me to my next point. It was odd that all of these people, umbrellaed by Move On, were united in their efforts to raise cash for Kerry. Because everyone involved seemed so much more progressive than Kerry. I mean there were some kick-ass lesbians running a bake sale in Brooklyn that Zoe and I visited a little later. It's amazing to see the throngs that want Bush out of office by any means necessary, even if it means getting behind a guy who doesn't seem all that cool. To quote my friend Michael in Portland, "I'd vote for a bag of Fritos instead of Bush." I would, too, and it wouldn't even have to be a full bag. In fact, there could just be a few Frito crumbs lingering. I'd vote for that.
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sick. Not bad, but sick for me. So I'm inside working while Avram has the girls out at Minerva's painting studio in Soho. The aptly named Minerva is the wild, grey-haired grandmother of two of Zoe's friends. She came to New York to be an artist in the '70s, leaving her four children with her husband, who left Minerva for another man. Her youngest child, Jessica, is the mother of Zoe's friends and is still pissed at Minerva for leaving her with her stern, parsimonious, ego-driven, painter dad (and albeit, his kinder, gentler boyfriend). Anyway.  This has been a crazy week. On top of Passover (we hosted a seder), Easter, Shelley's birthday, and Zoe's Spring break (which we're still in), I had four visitors from my past: my poet friend Lara, who came out from Utah with her experimental musician husband Christian, my crazy sketch-book artist friend Hailey, who phoned me out of the blue, and an old graduate school colleague Claire, who's now a tenured professor of English and creative writing at a state college in PA. Their respective visits in such a short span of time, taken as a whole seemed to foreground something for profound and significant for me--that I've been really out of touch with myself as a writer, and that it is possible to devote yourself to your art and still support yourself and your family.  Lara and Christian, after all, have four daughters. (Hailey just had her FIFTH!) Christian's a professor of music at the staid BYU, where I met him when we were both freshman. Last Friday night, I saw him perform his own compostion in the West Village with some notable and amazing avant-garde musicians. And the scene itself was amazing. There's this freakish, bookish, insane, bushy-eyebrowed look that at least NYC-based experimental musicians have and I was totally blown away. Lara's poetry was sung throughout his piece. I left totally enlivened and inspired, and also like I've been wasting tons of time. 
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I went out to Shelley's to celebrate her birthday I brought her the latest copy of Spin with Kurt Cobain on the cover. He died on her birthday--today-- en years ago. This got us into a rock mood and we put on Nevermind. I started dancing, jumping around, writhing on her rug. She got out her video camera, video taped me and then the cover of Spin. I hope I didn't look too ridiculous at my advanced age. I hadn't washed my hair in three days, so it was lanky and dirty, very grunge. It was a good feeling.  I had come out to Brooklyn alone. I've been kind of getting in touch with my pre-mother self lately. It's made me feel giddy.
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Check out the Web site www.ralphdontrun.net.  Also, last night I had this very, very vivid dream that David Cassidy came to this place where Shelley and I were attending a funeral. David knew the deceased, too. His brother Sean had showed up, looked around arrogantly and left, but David--sweet David--took out his guitar and started to play. We knelt really close to him. I started to tell him that as an 8 year old I had written him a love letter (which is true), but then became shy. Damn. It was one of those dreams you hate to wake up from. He was still hot in his fifties--in my dream, he was! I don't think he actually still is in waking life.  I'm wondering if this dream was in part inspired by earlier in the evening, staring at Gram Parsons on the inside of that Burrito Brothers tribute cd I have. Their respective '70s selves resemble each other.  Hey, take some time to wish my sister Shelley a happy birthday today at forestgreen44@yahoo.com.
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Martin Luther King Jr. was shot dead on this day in 1968 in Memphis. He was 39. My exact age. And what I have done by comparison? Really not much. Kind of depressing. And I've really got to stop comparing myself to Dr. King. (hahaha) I do have a sick tendency to compare myself to other people, physically (hair, shoes, teeth and clothes) and otherwise--feeling I always come out on the short end. It's okay. What else can I do?  My friend Lara is still here and she is reading her poetry tonight at Arlene Grocery, where I am going in one hour and 45 minutes. It's just around the corner. She's reading with established poet CK Williams, and oddly enough, this very mediocre, limpid poet who was in graduate school with me.  In the meantime, I've got to keep going on that novel. Everyone's finishing stuff but me. 
    
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just broke a Chinese spoon from Pearl River Mart. Is this good or bad luck?  Zoe says she likes to have hot chocolate on rainy, blustery days. I like how she always suggests it, but now the ceramic spoon I got out for her to stir her hot chocolate with is broken. It's still raining, though.  Saturday was sunny, and we were up in Central Park and I decided to take her to Strawberry Fields. It's an area of the Park off of 72nd Street and Central Park West. This is the corner where John Lennon was gunned down--right in front of his building where Rosemary's Baby was filmed (one of my favorites).  So I like this corner, and Strawberry Fields is so beautiful in spite of all the tourists taking disposable camera photos in front of the "Imagine" mural which is set into a wide, shady part of the sidewalk, and the corny guy on the bench who plays Beatles song after Beatles song for hours, in tribute. I think he's there every day.  This day someone had pushed together mounds of pink rose petals over the mural in the shape of a peace sign. Someone had also put a water damaged album cover of John's "Milk and Honey" album there. Zoe was very interested in all of this, and so I told her the story of the killing. And then I felt guilty. Is this too much for her to know? That a person can just come up to you on the street and kill you? I sometimes wonder how much she knows about the war. I do know that--thanks to me--she wants Bush out of office.  I think about that woman in Texas who drowned her five children because she was--i don't know--overwhelmed and severely depressed? I also heard her say in an interview that she felt like she'd ruined her children and that's why she had to kill them. For a split second, sitting there on the grass, I related to having that kind of guilt as a mother. It's so easy to ruin things, and hard to make them great.
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Monday morning Stella and I were walking down 10th Street, between A and B, enjoying our morning, and ran into Randy, Spencer's dad (Spencer's in Zoe's class) sitting on his front stoop waiting for the UPS guy. We started talking and he told me he's lived in the same apartment for 25 years, moved in when he was a student at the School of Visual Arts. He told me vivid details of how different the neighborhood was back then: how he'd step over passed out bodies in the hallway, needles and syringes, how many times he and his roommates were robbed, how Tompkin's Square Park across the street was basically a homeless shelter, and he never traversed it. I tend to romanticize my neighborhood's past, you know, in a Richard Hell kind of way.  Now Randy lives in the apartment with his wife and two kids and he's the super for the building and for several other of the really great buildings along the block. We said goodbye and kept walking. A few doors down, we ran into this old hippie with long hair and his massive dog (not a St. Bernard, a mastif??) collapsed on the sidewalk in front of Tompkin's Square Bakery. They were both friendly, so we stopped to talk. The dog was named Stella! And so Stella pet Stella. The hippie told me to rub the dog's ears which were as big as potholders. While we were doing this, along comes Eva Heinnemann, who has a a reallly slapdash, but great public access theatre review show and a boy with heavy black glasses about Zoe's age named Alfie (Eva won't tell anyone who Alfie's father is). Eva looks like a walking muppet, wild hair, glasses, no chin. She bursts out, "Omigod! I almost forgot! I have another Jewish holiday coming up!!" "Which one?" I ask. "Oh, you know, the one when we got the ten commandments!" This is all expressed very loudly, crazily. The hippie smirked. I cracked up. I love this block, this street, my neighborhood. It all felt very cozy, like Sesame Street.  Now I'm all tied up in knots about this new terrorist threat. Something happening this summer in the U.S. WIll it happen here again? All day I've been trying to think like a terrorist: Will I bomb the obvious? Or terrorize people who least expect it? I've been thinking about how I've never given away our double stroller. I keep it in case we have to evacuate the city quickly, pile the kids and some belongings into it and walk over the Williamsburg Bridge like a handcart pioneer. It gives me a little peace of mind.
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Is it May 19th or 20th?  First of all, I hate that I misspelled Andy Kaufman's friend's name. It's "Zmuda" not "Zamuda" (thanks Michael).  Secondly, I went to the Biennial at the Whitney Museum. I took Stella, which is not the optimal way to view an exhibition that has a twelve dollar entrance fee and only comes around once every two years. But we had a great time. Artists I liked there: Christian Holstad who crocheted a campfire with the yarn flames reaching in a spiral to the ceiling. Stella REALLY wanted to touch that installation which also included stylized roller skates and other funky '70s pop paraphenalia. I liked Amy Cutler(sp?) who paints in gouache "ugly girls" (Shelley's phrase) on paper doing strange things like sewing together wild animal pelts and sleeping under tents made from their own dresses. I was simultanously intrigued, jealous and annoyed by Andrea Zittel's installation (you sit on her graduated plateau desk with cushions, surrounded by roadster magazines) and accompanying slide show which explains how she lives her entire life as art. She lives out in Joshua Tree national park on some old homesteaded desert land, and she's really tall and pretty and savvy, and when we discover in the slide show that her parents live on a boat for most of the year, This woman next to me got up in disgust and said, "Oh I get it. She's rich. I can't watch this anymore."  I especially loved this artist who does entirely straight representational renderings of '60s protests and marches in graphite on paper. Who is this guy? He was great! There seemed to be something so audacious about doing that. There was more, but I've had a hard day.  Afterwards, I pushed Stella through the rain (holding my umbrella in one hand, and pushing the stroller with the other) all the way from 75th and Madison down to 28th and Park, where I finally just couldn't take it anymore and carried the stroller down the subway stairs to the train.  Last night, I cried my eyes out watching a rerun of Oprah telling Diane Sawyer about how she totally kicked ass and brought thousands of orphaned and/or poverty stricken (need I say) black South African children a giant Christmas party complete with clothes, new shoes, presents, food, games and entertainment, and in the aftermath decided to open several schools for girls and sponsor several children she had met there. (One orphaned 15-year-old girl who was taking care of a younger sister alone in a shack told Oprah that all she wanted in her life was six dollars to buy a uniform so that she could finally attend school.) It made me feel ridiculous for ever feeling sorry for myself. (Wanna donate cash? Go to www.oprah.com, and while you're on the web, check out www.billionairesforbush.com. They are amazing.)
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is a postage stamp-sized baby/toddler playground at Union Square Park. Today it was teeming with Tibetan and Caribbean nannies and the white children they take care of--and in the southeast corner, there was set up a really blandly fabulous looking playgroup of about five or six thirty-something mothers, all white, all slim--about five foot seven or eight inches tall--with fabulous hair pulled into ponytails or buns and tattooed ankles and babies of about six to eight months old and those new, 700 dollar Bugaboo(sp?) strollers all pulled into a circle like covered wagons. One of them took a round of salad orders and about twenty minutes or so later, they were all--ALL--eating take-out salads of various textures and hues, slathered with a variety translucent dressings. The whole thing was quite a spectacle and it really, deeply amused me.  Later, Avram and Zoe came back from their trip to New Hampshire and we all went to eat at Zen Palate just off of Union Square Park. While we were waiting for our food, an elegantly dressed dad with salt-and-pepper hair at the adjacent table yanked a small, plastic toy from his son's hand, threw it on the ground and started violently smashing it with his big shoe. It was really loud, actually, and the boy just sat there stunned.  I wasn't quite sure what to make of it all. I did think, "And that happened in a place with 'soy medallions' on the menu?" I was glad to get back to my own neighborhood, where I saw a nice rocker dad with two full-sleeves of tattooes and jet-black hair walk his pale blonde eight-year-old daughter wearing a Jimi Hendrix tee-shirt lovingly down the street. I love rocker dads.
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tomorrow, May 15, marks the 20th anniversary of Andy Kaufman's death, which he talked about faking, and he said he'd come back . . . on the day which would be tomorrow. So his best friend and writer Bob Zamuda actually thinks he's really dead, but just in case there's a big event tomorrow night at House of Blues, Los Angeles, and ads have been placed nationally and internationally to let Andy know.  Zoe and Avram are out of town and the apartment is very quiet, as if the apartment really was just meant for two people.  Now I'm crabby because I just got off the phone wth a friend who's switching her daughter from public to private school, and who called to gloat about that fact that '80s supermodel Paulina and Ric Ocasek's(sp?) son Oliver is in her daughter's class this fall, and went on to talk about how lovely the new school is and all the wonderful things they have there. I think about my daughter's falling apart public school building, and the all the things my daughter does not have at her school. Why can't I just be happy for people? Ah, this blog has become tiresome. 
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't seem to have the libido for this journal lately. I've had a sad past few days, and I'm not sure why. Today Zoe's home again with conjunctivitis. She's watching Caillou. Stella's drinking chocolate soy milk which she always demands in an imperious way.  People have lives much harder than mine--why should I be bumming?  Yesterday Shelley and I, with Emmett and Stella, walked for miles through the city. We ended up at the cafe in the East Village. The guy behind the counter, Peter, is this charismatic, dynamic friendly guy who is only 22. He was playing this interesting local band, the Scissor Sisters. I had this weird moment. I had always in some weird fashion considered myself a peer of Peter's. (I mean aren't I a hip, cool gal in the know? Don't answer that.) What I realized yesterday is that we are in completely different generations, that I am technically old enough to be Peter's mother, and that he probably sees me as very old. As I did at 22 when I encountered someone of 39. I don't know what I'm getting at by all this, but for the first time, I felt pushed forward into time, closer to death. Sigh. And it was a pleasant, sunny day, too.
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Even though I'm feeling better, I'm still down. I've been working hard trying to earn some cash. Tonight I tried to work on my novel, but can't find my red notebook where I did some writing away from home, and maybe I should quit this damn blog right now and look for it. Stella wants to sit on my lap right now anyway.  Listening to wfmu.org (on-line) out of Orange, NJ, which is the best radio station I know of these days. The very funny deejay just played the Fall, right after Slade.  Also, what is it May? and I had to dig my winter coat out of the laundry again to make a juice run because it was COLD OUTSIDE!
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't believe it. I am sick again. I've been in bed all day, working on an editing project, listening to Air America radio for hours. I'm surrounded by crumpled tissues. The one bright spot is the darling Al Franken. In fact, I love every single commentator on Air America. I don't care how dorky they are.  Speaking of darling, my darling husband walked through the rain, with Stella in the stroller, to pick up Thai food (extra hot) and bring it back to me. I needed something to burn through my sinuses, but it only works for as long as I'm eating it, and now I think I ate too much, because my stomach hurts.  Shit.  My husband, Avram has been working hard writing songs for a long time, trying to get another break. The other morning in the park I talked to a dad I kind of know--I'm better acquainted with his wife--and found out he's a record producer who worked on Christina Aguilara albums. I was pushing his son on a swing, alternating between him and Stella because he was feeding his six-month-old a bottle. Later, Avram told me I should have got his card or something. I know, I know. I was trying to play it cool. I'm still not used to living in a place where people on playgrounds are so "connected." Well, next time I see his wife, who's a sardonic New Zealander with bright red hair, I will make sure to get their number.  Sometimes when you live with young children, it's like you and your husband are just roommates, passing each other in rooms, shouting out orders to each other. It's a drag.  Can anyone please babysit? 
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes I hate this web journal. I go back and read my previous entries and cringe. It's like the feeling I have that I want to destroy every copy that exists of my master's thesis.  I watched "American Splendor" for the first time tonight. Is this why I feel this way?
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi - Foobario here, sneaking in a guest post while Writermama isn't looking.  She's always talking talking talking about being a Mama, but you've got no proof, right?  She could be yanking your chain.  Think about it - no pictures, at best only anecdotal evidence that she was maybe near a kid or two once in awhile... she could be making the whole thing up.  She might not even be in New York.  Fortunately, I've got pictures of her cherubic chilluns, so I'm going to set the record straight.  A  urlLink previous post  mentioned Zoe at Strawberry Fields, the John Lennon memorial:    urlLink     And here's Zoe's with her little sister, Stella, from a bit further back:    urlLink     Personally I think either of those would make a good album cover.  Here's a more recent pic of Stella and her cousin Emmett:    urlLink     I've known Writermama for 17 years but I haven't met her mate, so I can't speak to his contribution to the way the girls look, but to me they look like if you morphed the two of them together, you'd get their mother.  Of course they are young yet, and changing rapidly, so who knows what they look like now.  Certainly not me - I keep asking for more pictures, but Writermama keeps making up increasingly implausible excuses for not sending any: Zoe's in the hospital, my apartment got flooded, King Kong is loose in Manhattan, blahblahblah whatever... she never calls, she never writes... *sniff*   :)  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;-&nbsp; urlLink Foobario 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been away from the blog for so long because we've had a hard, hard time lately.  It kicked off with our apartment getting flooded.  Rising rainwater in the alley spilled into the lobby of our apartment and then into our apartment itself.  I was beating it back for awhile like Sissy Spacek in a Sissy Spacek movie, then just gave up and had Zoe help me get stuff up off the floor, while Stella kept slipping and sliding in the water.  Avram was gone, recording some song, but came back in time to help me clean up, including throwing out a ton of Zoe and Stella's books, which really sucked.  Then a few nights later,  Avram and I tried to go out together to dinner (which we almost never do).  Shelley babysat, and we ended up at this really stupid restaurant which was really just a hang-out for swinging singles.  All they offered were these dainty little "tasting plates" which we had mistaken on the menu for entrees.  Avram's lobster club was something like Mamie Eisenhour would have served at a White House tea--all twelve bucks of it.  My "mediterranean plate" could have been pushed under a cell door as a punishment.  I was thinking it could also have been something a very depressed Georgio Armani would have designed when he was just starting out.  It was like a slap in the face.  I put my napkin to my face (good thing it was cloth) and sobbed into it.  Then I couldn't stop sobbing.  The twenty-something waittress was embarrassed and tried to ignore me.  We paid our stupid check and went three doors up the street to the Clinton Street Bakery.  For fun, I tried to tell the sweet waitress what had just happened, and then started crying again, and she made me stand up so she could give me a big hug.  I ordered a big bowl of cold pea soup and a cucumber salad.  Then key lime pie (all green food), the pie they gave us for free.  (Everyone:  go to the Clinton Street Bakery when you're in town.)  THEN on Tuesday, it started to pour rain again.  Avram started to move the sand-bags into place, and Zoe got very ill.  She was writhing in pain.  So I scooped her up with one arm, held the umbrella with the other, and walked to the corner to get a cab to the ER at St. Vincent's.  We were there at the ER for hours, and after a urine and blood test, they said she had a kidney infection.  Put an iv in her little hand, which was harrowing.  And admitted her into a room.  She was miserable.  We lay there together for hours until Avram switched with me and he stayed with her through the night.  She stayed there another night.  And then most of the next day, Avram and I switching off kids.  I had a writing deadline, so I brought my computer into the bed with her, tried to get work done between taking her to pee, taking her down for her CT scan, which was also harrowing.  She had an infection in her right kidney and a ton of gas in her intenstinal track.  We watched a lot of Cartoon network.  Zoe got better.  I met my deadline.  I got my haircut  today by my hot twenty-something hairdresser who has a ring through her septum, and who buys thrift store clothes and makes them over in the most beautiful ways.  She's very sweet, wears spike heel shoes and tiny skirts, and doesn't charge me the full amount because she says, "it doesn't take long" to cut my hair.  That was a nice thing I did today.  Zoe came with me and watched.  I put on Air America so we could listen to Al Franken interview Ron Reagan, then Michael Moore, then Bill Clinton.  Speaking of which, it was amazing for me to hear Clinton again.  Even if you never agreed with his policies you had to admit he was always eloquent.  I mean we used to have a president who spoke in intelligent, coherent PARAGRAPHS.  It was amazing.  I don't take that for granted anymore.  I hope everyone gets to see Farhenheit 911.   
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, I really tied one on last night.  Up late with that Penelope section, dropped off, before she got to all those yeses.  I'm really paying for it today.  Had to get up early to give Stella her chocolate soy milk fix.  We were all out of it, and she was pissed.  It's all sultry hot outside, but I loaded her into the stroller and we made our connection, brought our own cup from home.  She drank some before we left the store and immediately went into a Jim Carroll nod.   Since she was calm, I went over to the post office to drop off my dad's father's day present.  On the way back, I noticed some nighttime guerilla postering.  Pasted over some giant Timberland ads were the following ultra-professional looking posters:    ONE GOD, ONE PARTY REPUBLICANS FOR A DISSENT FREE THEORACY  (too bad they left out that crucial "c")  and right next to it:  BUSH + CHENEY IT'S ARMAGEDDON IN AMERICA  Why they took the trouble to put these up in the chronically lefty East Village, I have no idea.    
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If anyone Googled today you may have noticed that the second "g" in Google is disguised as James Joyce.  For today is Bloomsday.  I got up this morning and told Zoe's teacher, "Today is Bloomsday!"  To anyone who I thought would care, "Today is Bloomsday!"  Joyce's novel, Ulysses takes place on one day:  June 16, 2004.  One hundred years ago today exactly, and as I write, I listen to Ulysses being read by local actors at Symphony Space on the upper west side.  I went once to this annual reading about six years ago when I was pregnant with Zoe.  This is the 23rd year of the reading, which goes on--it always goes on--for hours and hours.  It started earlier today punctuated by Irish music, musings on Joyce, a brief tour of the novel.  Very nerdy and I love it.  If you've never read Ulysses is quite bawdy, sexual--it is an encylopedia of the entire English language, the entire history of our language.  It is a profoundly thorough accounting of love, eros,  a marriage, and travels of a psyche.  It's all in Dublin.  Leopold Bloom winds his way through.  In a way it's completely bourgeous(sp?), a mundane accounting of one day, what was eaten, what was said, what was thought, what was worn, an account of defecation, an account of climbing into bed and drifting off to sleep beside an adulterous wife at the novel's close.   In 1933, a federal court of appeals ruled that Ulysses was not, in fact, obscene.    (Damn, I've missed seeing the papier-mache sculpture of Joyce--this was just announced at the break.  Joyce "luring customers" off of the street.  Tomorrow I'll write about another writer . . . also, about this blog's beautiful new home.)  Then wife, Molly, still awake, has the last words.  (by the way, her final musings make up the last 40 pages of the novel.  It takes more than two hours to read aloud.  It's all one paragraph, a giant tide of language seeping in, no punctuation.  These are the last few words of the novel:    "I put my arms around him yes and drew him down to me so he could feel my breasts all perfume yes and his heart was going like mad and yes I said yes I will Yes.     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I went back to American Apparel to get the skirt--but they were out of stock in my size. The skirt had been snapped up by better knowing girls. Unafraid girls. Probably much younger girls.  I saw one of these girls wearing my skirt at a poetry reading last night. It was at a bar called Arlene Grocery. Oddly, the reading featured someone else I had known in graduate school. (Why all these Utah connections so far away from Utah?) The girl in my skirt was sitting down, one leg crossed over the other, so that the skirt slid far, far up and displayed an extravagant expanse of thigh.  I pointed at it. "I know that skirt," I said.  "Isn't it great?" she said. "Don't you love that store?"  I sighed. "Yes."  The poet I know from Utah is tall and bald with an awkward fashion sense: leather motorcycle jacket and sandals, which--you know--should work in theory, but . . . I'm trying to be dipomatic about this poet. Over the years, he's been lavished with literary awards. He asked if I was still writing. I said yes. I hate the way he reads his poetry. Very affected, like a bad art rocker about to be dropped from his label. His nine-year-old son was there. I remember ten years ago when the poet was dating one of his Writing 101 students, who worked at Brumby's in Salt Lake. Well, the student got pregnant, then they got married, and then the poet went a'travelin, ignored both of them, and he still ignores his son, even when he's in the same room with him.  I tried to engage the poet's son. I even entertained burning my own hair in a candle on the table when the poet's son suggested it.  All evening, I was distracted by that skirt.
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was in American Apparel (great company--everything made in LA, I think, and no sweatshop labor--employees treated very well--everyone should shop here) with Stella. I was trying on skirts. I found one that Kim Gordon would have worn on stage. It was a mini, ended about four inches above my knees, and was basically a series of ruffles: brown, then sky blue, then orange. It was fantastic, the kind of thing I would have snapped up in my twenties or even in my thirties, before I had children and didn't have to bend over a lot and/or climb playground equipment.  I tried it on and I loved it even more. Just to be funny, I held up the skirt and asked two strangers the following: "I'm going to be 40 this year. Do you think I'm too old for this skirt?" The strangers were two women, shopping together, picking out very drab items, I noticed later. The oldest barely regarded the skirt, said to me, "Everyone's too old for that skirt."  I was a little crestfallen. I shouldn't have asked. I was just trying to be funny. Neither of them laughed. Can't a gal make corny age jokes anymore?  Speaking of age, I told Peter at Ciao for Now yesterday about my sudden realization that when he told me he was 22 the other week that it was the first time I felt really, really old, closer to death and all that. He nodded sympathetically, got me Stella's mini-cupcake, my tofu dog in a croissant blanket. I feel like he gets a lot of people confessing things to him.  Sometimes I think I should just shut the hell up.  I'm in the middle of a big job right now, writing a heinous standardized test for 2nd graders for the state of Texas. I get to be creative, but I can't write about vegetarianism or riding your bike to the store instead having your mom drive you. Bastards.
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So hell yeah, I'm forty!! Woohoo! Rock on!  And I got that skirt I mentioned in two previous posts, and I'm wearing it right now. I also wore it to see Sonic Youth in Salt Lake City, and this little club on the west side, only half full (where I ran into the second guy I ever made out with in my life at BYU in 1983. He was registering people to vote.)--another "pro" of SLC, easy to see shows there which would be sold out in NY or LA.  It's been a pretty good day, I think. I got my two front teeth fixed. They've been chipped since I was 8 years old. The dentist who did it this morning was a bi-racial woman, younger than me in a tank top. So she was dressed for a party, and I love my new teeth. Then I went and got a juice drink at Earth Matters. Then I walked over to H&M and went shopping for my birthday party. Then Avram met me with the girls, both of whom were crying. Zoe had just fallen hard off her scooter. Stella was crying because she hadn't seen me all morning. They both cried for a long time. Avram was stressed. When you're a parent of young kids, it's hard to have your birthday be totally about you, which is fine. We ate at Rice on Mott Street, and then I was going to take Zoe to the Whitney but instead she burst into tears again, because she wanted to be with Avram desperately. Weird. It was late, so I walked over to Ludlow Street and got my very first facial ever. (A very Oprah Winfrey thing to do on my birthday.) It was great, done by this sweet Romanian woman. I guessed her accent. She even dug out my black heads for free! What a day this has been! Still haven't unpacked from Utah. Got to look at my new clothes. Wrote a new paragaph for my novel. Next, I'm going to run up to Two Boots to rent my FREE birthday video. Probably "Shampoo" because I'm a girl in an election year.  I guess being 40 will be okay. Damn.
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I got back from Utah and turned on C-Span and watched hours and hours of the Democratic Convention until my eyes bled. I'm a dork and I loved Barak Obama. Maybe someday he will be president.  Just got back from Utah, where you see no black people. Well, there must be a handful somewhere. You don't see them on the evening news. You don't see them working behind counters.  We stayed part of the time in my friend's Pleasure Palace, her second home on South Temple (all addresses emanate out from the Mormon Temple, which marks the exact center of the city). It was decorated by the designer of Ceasar's Palace in the late '60s, and is very kitschy opulent in pure Vegas style.   I kept thinking of the pros and cons of Salt Lake, because every time we go, we can't help but think how easy it would be to live there with our kids. (Harder in some ways, given that the Republican Mormons dominate the state legislature.) What follows are the pros and cons of Salt Lake:  Pros:   *Easy access to nature--a five-minute walk from my friend's downtown house brought me up a canyon with a creek running through.   *I have great friends there, some of whom I've known for twenty years.  *There is a cafe called the One World on 300 East at South Temple. They grow their own organic produce. No menus, you eat what they're cooking, tell them how much you want, and pay what you think it's worth on your way out by putting money in a wooden box. The owners have no idea what you've given.   *Beehive Tea Room. An old acquaintance of mine with long, auburn braids is a single mother and owns a tea room on 300 South that is very stunning. Long live single mothers who run Tea Rooms!  *A great new library with tons of places to sit and plug in your computer and work, tons of computers, huge space with great vistas, free movies in the auditorium. While we were there, there was a Frankenstein film festival.  *Native American culture--lots of Indian singing, drumming and dancing in Liberty Park on Pioneer Day  *All of my friends own great, cheap old houses they have fixed up and furnished with very cool cheap thrift store artifacts. Neither to be found in NYC.  *Really wide streets and zero traffic allow me to make tons of driving mistakes with no repurcusions. I never heard anyone honking the whole time there.  Cons  *No street life. I walked many, many blocks in the blazing sun and saw noone but the saddest sack transients on the street, listless in the grass.   *Hard to be a pedestrian  *Mormon Republicans control the state legislature  *400 South is just plain ugly, despite the library (Shelley and I walked there one day with strollers in the punishing heat. We got cranky.)  *The downtown is really dead. Very sad. Great old buildings totally vacant, while some dumbass built a brand new outdoor shopping center called "Gateway" which looks like it could be in West Covina, California. (The mayor should convert those buildings into low and middle-income housing. Then students and artists would move in, then businesses, then people would start to go downtown. This is what happens in NY. Who cares what I think?)  *Terrible stores for groceries. The new Fred Meyer Smith's SUCKS! It's huge and there's nothing to buy. Despite the store's immensity, the organic produce section was the size of a bathtub and really dingy. I also got really tired walking around in this store.  *Farmer's market is only one day of the week for five hours.  And not even year round.  Wow, do I sound like a primadonna. Is this what I've become? Go ahead. Answer that.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A gal riding a rickety bike up my street. Cigarette dangling from her lower lip. She's steering with one hand. In the other hand, she eyeballs a copy of the Onion. (Somebody marry this girl!)  Days later, two languidly trim twenty-something girls in Tompkins Square Park. Loosely coordinated outfits: one wears drop-dead mod plaid knee-lenth skirt with inverted pleat in the back, knee-length, bare legs, heeled black Mary Janes. Fitted brown tee. The other wears a beige tank and man-styled fitted trousers. They are playing croquet in the grass with ancient wooden mallets. Behind them a tastefully flowered picnic blanket, plaid thermos, lovely totes. It was all like a photo shoot, but where were the cameras?   Zoe and Stella and I has a picnic in the grass near them. We were in the trajectory of one of their wooden croquet balls. We played hide and seek around a giant elm tree with branches so heavy and old they arched over and brushed the ground. Good place to hide.  The two girls played croquet for a long time. White home boy in wife beater and sweats jumped over the black-iron fence to join them. They were kind. They let him play.  One of the reasons I forget I'm married is that I rarely spend any time alone with my husband.  But tonight we went out to dinner--  and blah, blah, blah. It was great and I want to have my 40th birthday there.  More about that later.  Now it's July 14th and I'm leaving for Utah. If I don't die in a fiery crash tonight, then I'll be posting again on the 27th.  Cheers!
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm think I'm in love with Barbara Ehrenreich. Maybe she'll marry me. Oh, wait, I'm already married. (Sometimes I forget.) This op-ed piece resonates tons with me as I have a kid sister who's a financially struggling single mother, and more than once, I've heard relatives wish she would just give married. Yeah, it would be great it one of the Google guys would marry her, but that ain't gonna happen.  Let Them Eat Wedding Cake   By BARBARA EHRENREICH     Published: July 11, 2004   Commitment isn't easy for guys  we all know that  but the Bush administration is taking the traditional male ambivalence about marriage to giddy new heights. On the one hand,  it wants to ban gays from marrying, through a constitutional amendment that the Senate will vote on this week. On the other hand,  it's been avidly promoting marriage among poor women  the straight ones anyway.   Opponents of gay marriage claim that there is some consistency here, in that gay marriages must be stopped before they undermine the straight ones. How the married gays will go about wrecking heterosexual marriages is not entirely clear: by moving in next door, inviting themselves over and doing a devastating critique of the interior decorating?   It is equally unclear how marriage will cure poor women's No. 1  problem, which is poverty  unless, of course, the plan is to draft C.E.O.'s to marry recipients of T.A.N.F. (Temporary Assistance to Needy Families). Left to themselves, most women end up marrying men of the same social class as their own, meaning  in the case of poverty-stricken women  blue-collar men.  But that demographic group has seen a tragic decline in earnings in the last couple of decades. So I have been endeavoring to calculate just how many blue-collar men a T.A.N.F. recipient needs to marry to lift her family out of poverty.   The answer turns out to be approximately 2.3, which is, strangely enough, illegal. Seeking clarity, I called the administration's top marriage maven, Wade Horn at  Health and Human Services. H.H.S. is not "promoting" marriage, he told me, just providing "marriage education" for interested couples of limited means. The poor aren't being singled out for any insidious reason, he insisted; this is just a service they might otherwise lack. It could have been Pilates training or courses in orchid cultivation, was the implication, but for now it's marriage education.    As recently as 2001, however, Horn was proposing that the administration "show it values marriage by rewarding those who choose it" with cash "marriage bonuses."   When I suggested that  with food pantries maxing out and shelters overflowing across the nation  poor women might have other priorities, Horn snapped back: "It's fine for you to make the decision on what low-income couples need." Silly old social-engineering-type liberal that I am, I had actually doubted that marriage education might be helpful to couples doomed to spend their married lives on separate cots in the shelter.   Besides, he went on, low-income people are eager for government-sponsored marriage education. Lisalyn  Jacobs, who tracks T.A.N.F. marriage policy at the women's group Legal Momentum, told me she finds it "obscene" that, in the face of coming cuts in housing subsidies and other  services, H.H.S. is planning to spend any money at all on marriage, much less the $200 million now proposed. But she may be unaware, as I am, of the mobs of poor women who picket H.H.S. daily, chanting: "What do we want? Marriage education! When do we want it? Now!"   If marriage were a cure for poverty, I'd be the first to demand that H.H.S. spring for the Champagne and bridesmaids' dresses.  But as Horn acknowledged to me, there is no evidence to that effect. Married couples are on average more prosperous than single mothers, but that doesn't mean marriage will lift the existing single mothers out of poverty. So what's the point of the administration's marriage meddling? Jacobs thinks that the administration's mixed signals on marriage  O.K. for paupers, a no-no for gays  are part of the conservative effort to "change the subject to marriage." From, for example, Iraq.   But this may be too cynical an explanation. Quite possibly, the administration wants to ban gay marriage so that gay men can be drafted to marry T.A.N.F. recipients. Think of all the problems that would solve, and, if the Queer Eye stereotype holds true, how tastefully appointed those shelters will become. 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is unfinished, but will have to do for now.  For the past two nights, maybe longer (I'm kind of in a fog), Stella has been up until 1 in the morning.  Getting her to sleep earlier seems to elude me/us.  Around midnight last night, I put her in front of a video, turned off the lights and went to bed.  I heard her in there fidgeting on the floor. Finally, she stumbled in wanting to sleep.  It makes me feel like a bad mother, neglectful, so if anyone has any ideas let me know.  (Note: we don't have a crib, or a room with a door.) We have also tried getting her up really early the next morning, but that hasn't worked either. What this means is that we are in taking-care-of-kids mode about 17 hours a day.  No breaks.  In my therapist's office yesterday, I was telling her why, my whole life, I wanted to be a mother.  It sounds corny, but I wanted to be the mother I always wished I had.  I see them only once a year, my mom and dad, and it seems like the older I get, the less tolerant I am of their quirks and the things they say that make me crazy.  My sister Shelley told me that my dad told her on the phone recently that Kerry was evil because he is pro-choice and that means he wants to "kill babies." (Granted, he also thinks Bush is way evil, too.)  My mom, though, is another story.  She has been a source of pain for me my whole life, very distant, but also like a hurt child, or a wounded puppy.  Very defensive and emotional when confronted about even minor things.  Anyway, we're all going to be staying with my 95-year-old grandma who my parents don't get along with too well.  So think of me starting on about the 17th of July, and how I will be wishing I had a perscription for Prozac.  And I know many people who can say wholeheartedly they feel deep affection for their mothers.  I'm very jealous of that.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I always like to read blogs which basically detail the everyday events of people's lives, and I've  wanted mine to be that way, too.  But today on the 4th of July, I felt the need to paste in Barbara Ehrenreich's op-ed column from today's New York Times.  Enjoy.  Their George and Ours  By Barbara Ehrenreich  When they first heard the Declaration of Independence in July of 1776, New Yorkers were so electrified that they toppled a statue of King George III and had it melted down to make 42,000 bullets for the  war. Two hundred twenty-eight years later, you can still get a rush from those opening paragraphs. "We hold these truths to be self-evident." The audacity!  Read a little further to those parts of the declaration we seldom venture into after ninth-grade civics class, and you may feel something other than admiration: an icy chill of recognition. The bulk of the declaration is devoted to a list of charges against George III, several of which bear an eerie relevance to our own time.   George III is accused, for example, of "depriving us in many cases of the benefits of Trial by Jury." Our own George II has imprisoned two U.S. citizens  Jose Padilla and Yaser Esam Hamdi  since 2002, without benefit of trials, legal counsel or any opportunity to challenge the evidence against them. Even die-hard Tories Scalia and Rehnquist recently judged such executive hauteur intolerable.   It would be silly, of course, to overstate the parallels between 1776 and 2004. The signers of the declaration were colonial subjects of a man they had come to see as a foreign king. One of their major grievances had to do with the tax burden imposed on them to support the king's wars. In contrast, our taxes have been reduced  especially for those who need the money least  and the huge costs of war sloughed off to our children and grandchildren.    Nor would it be tactful to press the analogy between our George II and their George III, of whom the British historian John Richard Green wrote: "He had a smaller mind than any English king before him save James II."   But the parallels are there, and undeniable. "He has affected to render the Military independent of and superior to the Civil power," the  declaration said of George III, and today the military is indulgently allowed to investigate its own crimes in Iraq. George III "obstructed the Administration of Justice." Our George II has sought to evade judicial review by hiding detainees away in Guantnamo, and has steadfastly resisted the use of the Alien Tort Claims Act, which allows non-U.S. citizens to bring charges of human rights violations to U.S. courts.   The signers further indicted their erstwhile monarch for "taking away our Charters, abolishing our most valuable Laws, and altering fundamentally the Forms of our Governments." The  administration has been trying its best to establish a modern equivalent to the divine right of kings, with legal memorandums asserting that George II's "inherent" powers allow him to ignore federal laws prohibiting torture and war crimes.    Then there is the declaration's boldest and most sweeping indictment of all, condemning George III for "transporting large Armies of foreign Mercenaries to compleat the works of death, desolation and tyranny, already begun with circumstances of Cruelty and perfidy scarcely paralleled in the most barbarous ages, and totally unworthy  the Head of a civilized nation." Translate "mercenaries" into contract workers and proxy armies (remember the bloodthirsty, misogynist Northern Alliance?), and translate that last long phrase into Guantnamo and Abu Ghraib.   But it is the final sentence of the declaration that deserves the closest study: "And for the support of this Declaration  . . . we mutually pledge to each other our Lives, our Fortunes and our sacred Honor."  Today, those who believe that the war on terror requires the sacrifice of our liberties like to argue that "the Constitution is not a suicide pact." In a sense, however, the Declaration of Independence was precisely that.   By signing Jefferson's text, the signers of the declaration were putting their lives on the line. England was then the world's greatest military power, against which a bunch of provincial farmers had little chance of prevailing. Benjamin Franklin wasn't kidding around with his quip about hanging together or hanging separately. If the rebel American militias were beaten on the battlefield, their ringleaders could expect to be hanged as traitors.   They signed anyway, thereby stating to the world that there is something worth more than life, and that is liberty. Thanks to their courage, we do not have to risk death to preserve the liberties they bequeathed us. All we have to do is vote.        
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've had no time to myself, lately.  No time even to do the paid work I have to do.  No time to post to this blog.  Zoe's in an art workshop every afternoon at her  urlLink old nursery school .  On the second day, she didn't want to go.  She sat in the  urlLink park with Avram  and cried.  Sobbed.  We had paid $400 for eight days of art workshop.  I didn't want to be a hard ass, but we were going.  I dragged her along on her scooter, tried to get her to tell me what the problem was, told her we should talk to Viorica, her teacher, first before she drops out.  I felt bad making her go.  (And feel free to tell me that I shouldn't have.)  When we got there, she wouldn't let me leave the room.  So I stayed, and Stella stayed.  Truth be told it was kind of a nightmare--Zoe wanted me right by her side at all times; Stella wanted me on the other side of the room at the exact same time.  Cut me in half.  No more mama.  But it was good I stayed, because I found out that the art workshop is actually pretty hard, and it gave Zoe more confidence having me there, helping her build her clay turtle (which was not easy!)  I was tired, though.  The night before I'd taken the girls to a  urlLink Moveon party  at a stranger's house, hosted by single mother and her strange seven-year-old daughter.  The computer for the live Michael Moore address was set up in the mother's bedroom.  But before that there was a dinner, pastrami, corned beef and rye bread, and secular Jewish radicals in late-middle age with their pubescent daughters.  And the strange seven year old.  At one point, Zoe ran into the living room crying.  It seems the seven year old wanted all the kids in her room to offer up one idea to get Bush out of office, and Zoe was upset that she had no ideas.  We went and talked to the seven year old, but later I overheard the seven year old talking to two twelve-year-old girls and this it what she was saying about Zoe and her five-year-old friend:  "I mean those girls knew what they were getting into when they came to this party.  I mean, they had no ideas about getting Bush out!  All they want to do is play!"  I cracked up, but I still wanted to throw something at her.  Thanks to  urlLink computer god, Michael  for helping me with all these linkages (and for the surprise Ninja posting).  I hope you like the linkages.  (Here's another cool one featuring the "kids" of  urlLink  Tompkin's Square Park , which is my favorite park.)
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight for the first time ever--in recent memory at least--I am sick of my apartment.  We moved in almost five years ago.  Compared to the apartment we had before, this new one seemed like a palace. I felt like Ivana Trump because we didn't have to keep our refrigerator in the living area like last time, and instead of just three inches of kitchen counter space, we now had like three feet of kitchen counter space.  Nothing is ever good enough for very long, right?  I used to be so happy here.  We do have twice as many kids as we had back when we first moved in.  And Avram's home all the time now.  The fact that we're both freelancing here is really trying, sometimes.   Avram composes music in a tiny corner of a fake bedroom.  I work in a closet with kid's clothes hanging over the computer.  I guess I shouldn't complain.  Zoe's best friend lives in less space than this.   There's no way in hell we can move now, unless we live far out in Brooklyn or Queens.  We couldn't afford to move into our building now.  It makes me feel even more trapped.  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So check out my new painting  urlLink here .  Once you get to the site, click on the gallery link and page through the site a few times. What I bought is called "Barstool Racing." The artist is my very first boyfriend ever when I was 23 and I had just graduated from BYU and moved to San Francisco to seek my fortune.  Jesse was a student at the San Francisco Art Institute, who I was set up with by a friend I had just left in Provo, Utah.  Inspired by someone who got ahold of me via the internet several years ago, I googled Jesse several months ago and found out that he was still painting.    I spent my birthday money on "Barstool Racing" and I couldn't be happier about it.  This brings me to something else I've been wanting to say.  I hope no one thinks I'm bragging when I talk about running into former "boys (who are no longer boys anymore) who I've kissed!" I mention them because I think it's remarkable that I ever got into that situation with the opposite sex at all, me spending all those adolescent years and all those years in my twenties very shy and insecure around boys/men, not feeling pretty enough, blah, blah, blah.  So when I run into people like this from my past I am reminded what a remarkable thing that was that I did something that was for the most part so cool and that everyone else was doing so effortlessly, and it wasn't even like I was having sex, I have to say--approaching that, but not enough to get me kicked out of  urlLink my school .  Which brings me to my next topic.  I am working on my BYU novel again.  I finally know who the narrator is, and she still hasn't had sex either.
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Weird night. Took a trip up to Avram's grandmother's pad. We rarely see her because she lives in another world: in Woody Allen's "Everyone Says I Love You" neighborhood (this is actually where Woody lives with that Soon Yi, I think) about 94 blocks up the road from us, and we also rarely see the grandmother because she's 92 years old and doesn't feel like seeing people half the time. She's like Norma Desmond in this heavily draped huge apartment, and I'm always on edge while there. (Years ago, when Zoe was a baby she literally trapped me inside, just like Norma does in Sunset Boulevard.) This time was no exception. After about 20 minutes, she managed to insult both Avram and me, although she did admire the children. That's so lovely.  Luckily, we had a party to go to. It was for our good, good non-judgemental friend Smita (real name Meg; Smita is her new Indian spiritial name), who is moving to southern India with her girlfriend (also going by a new name) for six years to live at an ashram. It was great to be around a ragtag bunch of new agers crammed together surrounding a table of ragtag potluck. Some really great food actually. And there was good will and well-wishes, and conversations about astrological charts over my shoulder. And I thought of Avram's grandmother ten blocks away watching television alone (except for the 24-hour home attendant)  in that huge apartment where she treated Avram's dad and uncle like shit.    I'm not going anywhere interesting with this. I'm just really sad when the good people go, and I found myself also envious of Meg, and myself longing for some kind of radical adventure like this.  I was also thinking about how my best friends in the whole world don't even live here. And also Shelley's leaving for Sweden tomorrow, gone for two weeks.   Does anyone without kids have any idea how dramatically kids can fall apart into tantrums and became so easily frustrated and collapse in a heap, and they want you to rescue them, but don't know that they do, and sometimes I just stand there shaking my head and let them go on?  You know, I'm still not done with my freaking birthday.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trying to get out the door this morning. I have both girls by myself today for the first time in a very long time. Avram has a job this week doing some manual, but pleasant labor at this fancy Italian lighting fixture company that an old friend of ours works for. So this is good. I finish a job on Monday, and he starts one. We need to keep this kind of thing going.  But these little girls who live here are being hard, demanding, and I hate to admit it, a little bratty. We just can't stay in the apartment too long because then everything breaks down and there are too many opportunities for fighting. Gotta keep moving. All my birthday self-love has totally vanished, the effects of my facial (I have a big zit on my nose) because I've had my hands full of kids. There are still some things I'd like to do for myself, but I don't know when that's going to happen.  There's a lot of stuff I want to say right now but can't. Probably not that interesting anyway.  My sister's going to Sweden on Saturday. Wish I could afford to go with her.
    
</post>


</Blog>