<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know that this was a long time ago, and i know most of you already know the story, but i just remembered about this happening and i had to write it down.  Gimme just a sec to stop laughing at the images floating through my mind...... OK.  It was at graduation on the last day of school when it happened.  The ceremony was over, and me matt, and jon were walking on the feild lookin to talk to some seniors or what not, when all of a sudden i start to get choked from behind.  It really wasn't a choke, but a grapple, but anyways it was only jonny ford-peterson getting the jump on me.  He grabbed me, and i slipped backwards, on accident, right into him, so he started going back too.  We took a couple steps, and then i noticed we hit something hard.  I looked back just to see a 70 year old grandma hit the ground.  Oh shit, me and jonny both thought.  But when she started talking i knew it wasn't that bad, but it kinda freaked me more, because she was calling us both goddamn kids, and was staring coldly at us.  She then told us to stick around and threatened to sue us, while swearing even harder now.  But thank god her son came over, and said that it wasn't very smart to do that in a place with lots of old people, we agreed, and he let us go.  Me and jonny then turned our backs, and walked away while laughing out of earshot of her.  I just wanted to tell you of my random act of violence towards grandmas now so you would be warned if you ever decide to introduce your elderly folks to me.  No really it  was  an accident though.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oi, don't you just love macaroni and cheese.  I mean come on, its pasta with melted cheese.  Whether its kraft, or homemade, its irresistable.  Except when youve been eating it for an hour like me, and are about to burst.  But I put cut up hot dogs in it, so that might be why I can't finish my bowl.  Along with a lemonade soda, lunch time heaven.  So wish me luck as i dive right back into the macaroni, in a hat nonetheless.  (Really, how bored can you be to write about macaroni and cheese.)
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please look at this site. OMG. HAHAHA. http://www.ebaumsworld.com/santatomb.html
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well that was fun.  If I've sparked your intrigue of what i meant as fun, it was skateboarding.  I just got back from shredding up almost the whole of McKinleyville with minor mishaps.  Of which i mean a few run ins with the police (nothing serious).  I actually just went to Alex's house to see how long it would take me to get there by skateboard (i was bored, what else could i have done in McKinleyville).  It took me half an hour from my house to hers.  I don't know if Alex was there at 1:00 but i was pretty thirsty, and almost called her to see if she would let me in, but i didn't.  So i left.  I was then going up the hill to see if i could get to Colleen's house, but then figured out i was on the wrong road, and it would take me forever to get there.  So i just went home.  And  i'm not wearing a shirt right now, (just in case you were wondering). 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes.  It is Father's Day, and I just got out of going to work.  I told my boss that I had some kind of flu, and that I shouldn't come to work today.  She let me off, but I could tell she was angry.  Ah whatever, and what was worse was that she would've been there tonight as hostess, and it would have been busy as hell because of Father's Day, and the Fish Farm thing going on in Trinidad.  But the thing is I didn't actually make it up, I am sick with something.  I was sick last night when they called me in, and I almost threw up, because I was so dizzy and light-headed.  Plus i got out of there at 11:30.  And the cut on my thumb from that soda can is infected i think. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, at seascape last night, we had a little situation with one of the customers.  It seems Melinda, the hostess, accidentally skipped over one of the people waiting for a table.  And so when I went up to check the waiting list to see what the table needs to be set for the lady was yelling and screaming and looked like she was gonna try and strangle me.  She picked up a menu, and threw it across the room, and then came up to me and said "Do you know what she did?!"  I said "What?"  And then she said " She gave our table away to another person!!" I said "I'm sorry" (with a pretend sad look on my face), then she said "Ya, I'm sorry too!"  Then I ran away and started laughing at the bitch.  She then kept trying to complain to me, and that made me angry, which is why I wrote this entry.  She then filed a complaint against Melinda.  People need to chill, we were very busy, and you don't need to break things, just because you didn't get your food. Damn.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know whats fun.  Being naked.  When you're naked, you feel excited about doing anything that you regularly do, becasue you're naked.  Like you could be driving, and all you're thinking about is what people are gonna think of you as a newly appointed streaker.  Well i've never driven naked, but you know that it would be a very fun and exciting time.  I know that you all have you're minds in the gutter right about this time and are imagining me naked and doing bad things, but that is definitely not the point if this entry.  The point is to live life on the edge, and be excited about things that you normaly wouldn't be excited about.  Do things that will make you have fun no matter what.  Becasue you will have a funner life that way.  Yaaaaaaaaah naked.        As long as I'm alive I'm gonna live illegal. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YES!  I just found out last night that I only have to work from Sunday through Wednesday at Seascape.  I get Thursday, Friday, and Saturday off.  My hours are 4-closing on Sunday, and 5-closing every other day (just in case you want to visit me).  Also I am the busser every day I work, which means... NO MORE DISHWASHING!!!  YES!  The only time I'll ever have to wash dishes is when I might have to cover the dishwasher's break.  So that right there just made my bloody summer.  YES!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I thought i was never gonna make one of these things because they looked like they were something for nerds, to write in a digital journal, but i guess now i am one of those people. Whatever, i make these people look better when i started to make these.  Hahaha just joking.  I guess these can be a good way to waste time on when you're bored, like i kinda am right now.  At least i wont post news stories like jon pimentel. hehe.  (Is that better Maya.)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is this?  Ronald McDonald is here.  So is the Burger King and the Jack in the Box.  Arby as well.  What now.  I realize it is Wendy's birthday.  I will die here if i don't leave.  But if I leave the clan will kill me.  I go to bathroom.  Wait for the first foe to come through door.  Slice! Shoom! Tack, Tack, Tack(shuriken)!  I have just slain Ronald McDonald.  I look at the floor and see the furry wig and fuzzy red nose.  I know now my mistake and what I must do.  I walk out door and became surrounded by kids.  Why, because now I am Ronald McDonald.  Wendy see's that it is not the right Ronald.  She beckons me to her side.  You are not Ronald!  White 99 cent value meal ninjas arise!  I am surrounded. Hope is not lost.  The lowly Arby comes to aid.  Curly Fry Gunslingers jumped through the doors.  The ninja's flee and take my beloved Wendy with them.  I thank Arby, and give chase.  Right then and there my dark clan's power rose up in me.  Dark Dragon Yogurt Parfait Wave!  Wendy was blown back to my arms, as the ninjas flew up into the air on the wings of the Parfait.  Wendy then sees what I have done and knows that i am the ninja for her.  The End
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was a still quiet day.  Training was just recently finished.  First mission as part of Ronald McDonalds dark ninja clan.  Mission: assassinate Wendy.  Armed with shuriken and trusty Kitetsu Shoozer took off.  Wearing Wendy's employee uniform.  I arrive at the house of Wendy at 6:46 a.m..  I see Wendy through window.  She had pigtails and rosy cheeks.  Love has fallen upon me.  But mission is uncomplete.  Love is not part of mission.  Must complete mission.  What can i do...?  Carl Jr. shows at door.  Comes with flowers for Wendy.  New mission: kill carl.  I go to back. Wait on steps with Kitetsu in hand.  But no i was not expecting that...   To be Continued
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well here i am writing the last post ill write for two weeks or more, because there is gonna be no computers where im going. (At least not accesible to me).&nbsp; And in case you didnt know, I'm going to Vancouver, Canada&nbsp;"the best city in the world"&nbsp;as voted on by the city raters (I'm not joking either).&nbsp;&nbsp;Have a fun rest of the summer, and ill see you when i get back on the 8th.&nbsp; And so I guess I'm out......and about (haha, couldn't help myself).    And like the angel you are, you laugh creating a lightness in my chest.&nbsp; Your eyes they penetrate me, (you never cease to amaze me) that's when i got up and left. &nbsp; hehe    
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hot and Spicy Chicken Fried Rice kicks ass.&nbsp; Especially when there are also crab cheese puffs on top of it.&nbsp; Im gonna go eat the rice now, later.&nbsp; (Hows that for a journal entry.) *sigh*  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well guess who went to the bar where the oxygen is at.&nbsp; That's right me and jake went.&nbsp; We sipped on flavored oxygen for 15 minutes each, and then took oxygen shooters afterwards.&nbsp; Ya my flavor was "Sex-me-up Watermelon" and jakes was "heavenly pear" or something like that.&nbsp; We could switch flavors any time we wanted, so i also had passion fruit and tangerine, but mostly hung around the watermelon.&nbsp; It doesn't really get you high, but it does get you hella relaxed.&nbsp; That was the most relaxed i've ever felt, ever.&nbsp; And the shooters were liquid oxygen with magnesium.&nbsp; It was about 18 dollars all together, but it was quite the experience.&nbsp; Probably will go back there sometime.&nbsp; And farewell to all those that be leaving on the morrow, which consist of albert zie(ei, sorry, still dont remember)linski (honeyishrunk) and maya wolf.&nbsp;&nbsp; I'm sure you both will have fun at your destinations wherever they may be.&nbsp;&nbsp; :-    &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will definitely be the last song game entry, but this is a good song, and I thought I'd share it with you.  She said don't.  Don't let it go to your head.  Boys like you are a dime a dozen, boys like you are a dime a dozen, she said.  You're a touch overated, you're a lush, and I hate it.  But these grass stains on my knees, they won't mean a thing.  And all I need to know, is that is there something that you'll be missing.  Maybe I should hate you for this, never really did ever quite get that far.  Maybe I should hate you for this, never really did ever quite get that.  I'd never lie to you.   Unless I had to, I'll do what I got to.  Unless I had to, I'll do what I got to.  The truth, is you could slit my throat, and with my one last gasping breath, I'd apologize for bleeding on your shirt.  And all I need to know, is that is there something that you'll be missing.  Maybe I should hate you for this, never really did ever quite get that far.  Maybe I should hate you for this, never really did ever quite get that.  Cause I'm a wishful thinker with the worst intentions, this will be the last time you get to draw my name.  Cause I'm a wishful thinker with the worst intentions, this will be the last time you get to draw my name.  Hey fuck this madness, and you're a liar.  Hey fuck this madness, and you're a liar.  Hey fuck this madness, and you're a liar.  Hey fuck this madness, and you're a liar.  Hey fuck this madness, and you're a liar.  Hey fuck this madness, and you're a liar.  Hey fuck this madness, and you're a liar.  Hey fuck this madness, and you're a liar.    Wwll I'll miss you song game, but i guess it's over.  Good bye. -Ace
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know nobody really cares (except maybe maya), but I thought i'd put just one more song game out there, so here goes:   Hello, I waited here for you, everlong. Tonight, i've thrown myself in two. From out of the red, out of her head she sang. Come down and waste away with me, down with me. Some how, you wanted it to be.... Im over my head, out of her head she sang. And I wonder? When i sing along with you, if everything could ever feel this real forever? If anything could ever be this good again? The only thing I'll ever ask of you, you gotta promise not to stop when i say when. She sang....! Breathe out, so I can breathe you in. Hold you in. And now, I know you've always been, out of you're head, out of my head I sang.... And I wonder? When i sing along with you, if everything could ever&nbsp;feel this real forever? If anything could ever be this good again? The only thing I'll ever ask of you, you gotta promise not to stop when i say when. She sang....! And i wonder? If everything could ever&nbsp;feel this real forever? If anything could ever be this good again? The only thing I'll ever ask of you, you gotta promise not to stop when i say when.   It's a pretty popular song, by a pretty well known band, so it wont be too hard (i dont think). Oh... and no cheating (ya im looking at you).  -Ace    
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well..... Apparantly my joke caught up with me before i could even realize it.  By that i mean the tea house joke (hahaha i still cant believe it).  But ya, I think that I should  arrest this man he talks in maths  or at least be  in a intastella burst i am back to save the universe! .  Hmmmmm...  It seems that i have radiohead on the brain, and only one thing will solve that, i should go listen to it. Yay!  I have to go anyway, because i have to wake up early to escort the insurance people around my truck tomorrow, damn me! Later.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      try this one (i dont think you'd get it, unless you had the cd):   Twenty-six years and seems like I've just begun to understand my intimate is no one.  When the director sold the show, who bought its last rites?  They cut the cast, the music, and the lights.  This is my line.  This is eternal.  How did I ever end up here?  Discarnate.  Preternatural.  My prayers to disappear, ungranted in dead time left me disowned, absent of grace, marked as infernal.  To this nature, so unnatural.  I remain alone.  Twenty-six years end.  Still speaking in these tongues.  Such revalations while understood by no one.  When the new actor stole the show, who questioned his grace?  Please clear this house of ill-acquired taste.  Give me something.  Give me something.  Give me something real.  I lay strewn across the floor, can't solve this puzzle.  Everyday another small peice cant be found.  I lay strewn across the floor, pieced up in sorrow.  The peices are lost, the peices don't fit.  Pieced together incomplete and empty.  Well thats it.  Same rules apply: just name of song, and who sung it.  And if no one gets it in a couple days, i'll give a hint.  Good luck. -Ace  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I meant the first one to get the song right will get the prize.  So..... get to it!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Please could you stop the noise and try to get some rest? From all the end of checking voices in my head. Whats this? Whats this?  When I am king, you will be first against the wall.  In your opinion, which is of no consequence at all.  Whats this?  Whats this?  This shirt makes you look pretty ugly.  Kicking, screaming goosh you little piggy.  You dont remember, you dont remember.  Can you remember my name?  Out of his head, out of his head now, do you remember my name?  I guess you do.  oooooooooooo.   Rain down, rain down, come on rain down on me.  For the great high, for the great hiiiiiiiiigh.  Rain down, rain down, come on rain down on me.  From the great high, from the great hiiiiiiiiiiigh.  Ya sexy, you leave me, the crackin of pig skin.  The dustin, the screamin.  Can I please live again?  God loves his children, god loves his children, yeah.  If you can name this song, and who sang it, then i'll give you a prize.  A big smooch from me.  Haha no im kidding, but i'll think of something. -Ace
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, i don't know.  But im writing in my blog for some reason (somebody please stop me).  Yahoo, and diddly de, im having fun, how about thee? if anybody for any reason reads this, please post a comment, so i know that someone is still caring whatever the hell im talking about, which i don't even care myself, so i dont think i should expect anything, maybe?  What the hell does that mean.  Whatever, bye.  Yayaya, times. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>