<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm actually at Dexter High right now, but my "boss" is off on another floor. We've been hacking today, trying to find loopholes in the network. A crapload of fun, until my eyes started wigging out on me. I'm suprised they weren't twitching...  Anyway, I gotta go before I'm caught...
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well...after reading Tony R's blog(and being highly disturbed about his comments on male testosteronal-fueled growths), I've decided to post my opinion on abortion.  Abortion ticks me off so freakin' bad! These people have no respect for life. They don't a conscience, so as long as they're making money, they don't care. Professional mutilation, that's what it is. Posted about it on Anime Angels. Haven't gotten much of a response...ah, well...here's that post...   My honest opinion of people that get abortions and then don't care, is that they deserve their own place in hell where they can hear the silent scream for eternity. I'm sorry if you don't agree.   It makes me cry almost every time I hear about abortion. THERE IS NO EXCUSE FOR ABORTION! Yet, most of these abortion cases(not all, however) blantantly disregard their privilege to be a mother, and quite literally, throw that gift in the trash. It's professional mutilation of a human child.   And don't get me going on this "fetus" crap. They say it's not a human child. Okay...the mother is human...the father is human...so therefore, from the time the first cells form in the mother, that is a human, not complete, yes, but human nonetheless.   But one thing some pro-lifers forget to realize, there is forgiveness for this hideous crime. There is forgiveness and a second chance. Please don't forget this.   As for abortion of children that are a product of rape? I wrote something on that.   Despite Beginnings   It's not your fault  That since last night  Because of a sin  You carry a life  But just because he has sinned  You have no right to kill within  She breathes and lives  A beautiful start  Within eight weeks  You'll hear her heart  No matter how shameful she did begin  You have no right to kill within  A seperate life  Depends on you  Someone will love her  Just follow through  And as unjust as it may have been  You have no right to kill within  Your indecision  Inside will grow  When you have seen  Tiny fingers and toes  Above all of the pro-choice din  You have no right to kill within  Even though her life began with sin  You have no right to kill within   Some people argue that abortion is alright if the mother will die if the baby is born and a C-section isn't possible. This may sound harsh, but I believe that as it is the mother's duty to care for that child, she should be willing to die for that child. Harsh, yes, but that's my opinion. And opinion never changed fact. What the fact is, remains to be seen.   I'm sorry if my opinion offended anyone. This matter...well...I can't use the language to describe what I truly feel about it, without losing my Christian testimony.    My opinion on abortion wll never change as long as I live. It's wrong. Plain and simple.   And as a POD song says:   Abortion is murder  There's nothing you can say or do  To justify the fact  That there's a living breathing baby inside of you  -POD, "Abortion is Murder"   If I was drafted into the army, would I run into Canada to avoid the pain? No. Why? Because it's my duty to my country. Motherhood is a duty. But everyday, women run into the proverbial Canada by commiting abortion. They avoid their duty, because it'll be inconvienient.  You can say I'm on a soapbox, you can say I have no clue of what I speak of, all I know is Truth.
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm happy. Really happy right now. I've got an unofficial intern position working with computers at Dexter High School. We're working on the networks right now, but tomorrow, me and my friend Adam get to try to hack into the things as students. It's to test how much students could get away with under their user profiles. Boring to you, major fun to me. Sorry to bore you, but this is big news to me.    Current song: TFK-"Phenomenon"  
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm bummed. The World Cyber Games 2004(th e video gaming Olympics)are coming up, and I won't be able to go to play Halo. I could go pretty far, too...but it's $35 to register, and $25 bucks for each tournament after, plus traveling expenses...there goes my dream...
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I went to Six Flags New England. Yes, I saw two pairs of lezzys. Yes, I am thoroughly digusted.  But, love the sinner hate the sin, right?  I did find out why I don't like theme parks. It's like I can sense the frustration of people trying to fill their meaningless lives with something, anything. It really brings a new feeling of urgency to me for trying to reach the world. But it's slightly hard when you're only 5'10 in a really BIG world...kinda depressing...
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Zilch: Hmm. I like filesharing! Vyse: You're evil then. You're going to hell. Zilch: Why? Vyse: Because that's stealing. Zilch: No. Vyse: Huh? Zilch: These people are just giving me stuff that they legitimately got. Vyse: Well...just because you challenged me, you're going to Hell. Zilch: I can't go there. Vyse: Why not? Zilch: Because you'll be there. Vyse: Oh...I suppose even God has his limits on punishment. Well, how about we have a battle of wits to see who gets into heaven? Loser goes to Hell. Zilch: I can't get into a battle of wits with you. Vyse: Why not? Zilch: I don't fight unarmed men.  (Vyse drops into Hell.)  Zilch: Lord, did you have to do that? God: Yup. Zilch: Why? God: Hey, you think  I  want him up here, either? Zilch: Oh... God: I hate holier-than-thous...and liberals...okay, so I love them, but not their constant sin.  (Meanwhile in Hell, boxes of Kazaa, Bearshare, WinMX, and Limewire are chasing Vyse around.)
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Zarn Ishtare: Punk #1  Annoying in the sense that he wants to one-up me on everything. Calls himself a playwright, but has the writing talent of a pregnant hippo on speed.  christiangirl: Punk #2  First off, she has an unoriginal name. Very. That annoys me greatly. Second, she posts nothingness and uses cutesy little emoticons, such as ^^. Ruined the best Arena thread on the boards, singlehandedly.  Ronin of Kirai: Punk #3  Always looks for attention, and whines when he doesn't get it. Wuss. 100% wuss.  Vyse: Punk #4  Somehow manages to bring the evils of bootlegs and filesharing into everything. He wins the RIAA Boy Scout of the Year award.  Pretty much all members under 16 on the boards annoy me. They should be banned. Banned and definistrated(in other words, thrown from a second story window).  Current song: Evanescence-"My Immortal"
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHEN ARE PEOPLE JUST GOING TO LEAVE ME ALONE!? I'm friggin' sick of it! I don't need people. People suck. The whole human race sucks, because they're human. Humans are fallible, fragile beings all trying to help one another. Even the strongest human is subject to death. So, really, can I get a point to something here? Why are we here, or more importantly, why did there have to be a God? Why does he exist? Why did anything have to exist? Why couldn't we just be mindless robots that worship our Creator? Would we know the difference? Would we care? Would we rebel? So...why? Why existence?  I guess the real point is, how do we exist? What is the basis for all existence? Do atoms really make up everything? Still, that does not make for basis of existence? How did the atoms get here? Is there something even smaller(or bigger?)holding everything together?   There's something wrong with everything, no matter which way you look at it. We are existing in reality. But what is reality exactly? How do you view reality? Is reality a box we're in, or part of a network of boxes, linking dimensions and hyperfolds? So, if that's the case, if you find the key to what reality is, then do you discover what existence is? No. Reality dwells within eistence. Reality is just a smaller form of existence, then, when this reality is finished, a newer version of reality is put upon, thus, we still exist. Can we really explain everything with science?  ...no. There's too much outside the realm of science. There's so much that can't be explained from our five senses. There's so much outside the realm of human understanding. Thus, I believe in a Holy, Omnipresent God. Thus, I am forced by my own intellect to serve God. There is no other way. Therefore, humans are needed, if just for me. So, I have to tolerate them nonetheless.  So, if by my own understanding, I realize there is a God, and I read His Word, I see that He loves me. That He created me special. And that He has an eternal home prepared for me, outside of this reality, but still within existence. A different reality, same existence. And that is why I love my Heavenly Father.  Too much for your mind? Sorry. I'm intellectual in this area, so I frequently go over people's heads.
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm a bit more relaxed. Two straight days of gaming will do that for ya...about 7 total hours of Dynasty Warriors 3(which is safely within my backpack for borrowing pleasures) and about 6 of Onimusha 3(which is quite the gorefest, but fun nonetheless), along with 2.5-3 hours of Half-Life: Decay, and a good hour of Red Faction multiplayer(let the debris fly!!!). Add that to 2.5 hours of swimming at Jeff's camp, and you have a well-rounded weekend. In the words of Strong Bad, "I feel so...cleansed..."  Great. Just peachy. My mom's mad at me just because I wasn't thrilled at the idea of watching a movie with her and Dad. It pisses me off that she thinks I don't care about anything outside of a screen. Just because I spend a lot of time online and in video games doesn't mean I don't love my family. I realize that I have a life outside the virtual world, but apparently, she doesn't see that. She sees me enjoying something electronic, and it seems that she deems them as evil because I spend more than an hour a day on them. She never says a thing to Nick about his obsessive guitar playing.   Maybe I'm just pissed at the world for no apparent reason. I've rather irritable lately. Maybe I just need to go to bed early tonight...
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got warned on CAA today, for standing up to a little punk that's against everything in the world. Uber-conservative little putz. I don't hold it against Aaron from warning me. I think I probably deserved it, and he was just doing his job. But, still...  I wonder if there's a way to beat people over the Net?
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I am, thinking I'm fine and all dandy...and then I see Hailey. [SARCASM]That's just GREAT![/SARCASM] I forgot all about her...the way she affects me...the way her eyes bore into mine...geez...here I am, talking about having no distractions...when I have this awesome girl walking around the youth group...I think it's time to give up...as much as it kills me...I've hurt enough people. I won't do it again. If I have to tie myself to a flagpole, I will not hurt anymore of my friends. I can't. I can't put myself through that again...I won't put myself...(insert long strings of expletives)  Current Song: Tourniquet-"Pathogenic Ocular Dissonence"
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got Ashley(the Texas one) hooked on Mad At Gravity! MWAHAHAHAHA! I'm so malicious...anyway...  I just got a call from California, from Heather of all people...oddity...to tell the truth, I had almost forgotten about. It's funny to almost lose people that were once such a big part of your life...but I feel worse about the stuff I said about her...  After she broke up with me, I went nuts and dragged around an intense hatred of her. I called her a whore and a skank, and Lord knows what else...I've almost forgotten...and then I never made things right with the other people who see her that way now...  It's my fault...I was the one who told her I would never judge her...and now look what I did. [SARCASM]Perfect. Just perfect.[/SARCASM]I'm the one who has judged her the most. And old stories without solid proof. But I think I see now. She's scared. She's afraid of no one being there. She's afraid of being by herself...  She's just like me...  Current song: Thousand Foot Krutch-"Small Town"
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Deep inside This heart of mine Lay these scars that Layer my life  Time again These memories rise Giving pain to me Long received  Unresolved I lie alone in bed Dying inside Again and again  Cold steel Pressed on my head Pain will end Or is there a different way?  One hope Burning in my mind One God above Hearing me  On my knees Sobbing out my anger Against myself Healing me  Aversion of a self-inflicted crime Has happened here tonight
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sick...ish. I'm sorta am, sorta not, but I'm not taking any chances...  I just finished working at the church. It's the first time I've driven something more than a few feet...unless you count peeling out on ice in my driveway about a year ago...but let's not go there. I've always had an unearthly fear of driving. I'm not sure what it is, but I just can't push myself to hit the accerator unless IhitittoofastandIrunintosomeoldgranny then I slow      down     to    a      slug   on   drugs    pace    and     I     have     people    behind    me     honking     at    me   and      showing    me    the     way    to    Heaven    in     no   uncertain    terms. Ah, well...I'll learn...  Current song:Detrius-D.I.G.M
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Current song: Mad At Gravity-"Letter To Myself"  showers are wonderful things...anyway...  I'm bored...there's on one here, and I don't have a job yet...errgggh...I need to find one. I just haven't completely filled out any of the applications I've grabbed...
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Current song: Linkin Park-"Faint"  I'm feeling a lot better today. I feel focused on something, like I finally have a purpose and a goal. My drive is so much better, and I feel...awake...one thing I do need to do, is take a shower...My hair is incredibly greasy, and that annoys me...eww...but, that's what happens to me over the summer. Hygenie(along with spelling) goes out the window like it's propelled by a baseball bat.  New Current Song: Linkin Park-"In The End"  I don't understand the debate about Christians listening to secular music, yet...they watch SECULAR TV!*insert crowd gasp* Isn't that...oh, I don't know...hypocritictical?  New Current Song: Linkin Park:-"Numb"  Another thing is the whole deal about filesharing. 5 years ago, people were taking rented VHS tapes and copying them, and who cared? It's the same idea, so why the big deal? Anyway, I need to take the aforementioned shower, so, laters...
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Find me I'm falling  And fooling myself that it's flight  Imperfect  I plummet  And ponder  Pushed away on principle   Walk away and I stare  Would you stand me up again?  Wonder if I've said too much  And we'll never speak again   Forfeit  My future  For feelings of few far betweens  Mindless  Of merciful  Measures  Making ends preempt the means   I searched your eyes for an answer  And shuddered at what I found there  As my skin shrunk away from conclusion  That you lack the strength to care   Walk away and I stare  Would you stand me up again?  Wonder if I've said too much  And we'll never speak again   This is the way it has to be  That you would turn your back on me  And you and I should walk away   Walk away and I stare  Would you stand me up again?  Wonder if I've said too much  And we'll never speak again 
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel so empty right now. So very empty. It's like there's a hole in my chest and someone dropped a wrecking ball inside. I just want to break free of something...if I only knew exactly what that something was. Is it my past? My present? Am I worried about the future? I'm angry...at myself?  Maybe it's simply the fact everyone sees me as something different than what I know myself to be.  It's hard to know who you really are. To stare yourself in the mirror and seeing what you are. It's hard to say that you're a perv. A sicko. A dink. To know this. And to have people still smile at you. That kills me. I want them to run from the monster I am. I don't want forgiveness. I don't deserve it, so why give it to me? Me. A player. A porn dabbler. A freak. A pimp. I'm sick of me. If I could just shed this skin, I might be happy.  Then again...  There's the side of me that screams for forgiveness and attention as much as the other side screams for shunning and punishment. A side that longs for love. A side that is the little boy I am. I'm screaming for me to come back. But, who would come? Would it be the side that everyone says I am, or the side I know myself to be?   I don't mean to hurt people, but my lust drives me to it. Forgive me, Jordain. You hold a large part of my heart. But something deep inside tells me that there's someone else. For you. For me. Just please...don't cry...I never meant to hurt you. But we're children. Fairy tales don't always come true.  But either way, I'm stopping my sick side here. If I have to do it with just me and God, I will, but I'm going to fight this. I'm going to be the man God wants me to be. I'm going to accept the fact I'm imperfect, unclean, and unholy, and that God wants to use me just the way I am.  Ashley, I'm sorry. Your intuition failed this time. Good try, though. But right now, I can't have any distractions, no matter how miniscule. Thanks for praying for a prick like me.  I'm breaking the habit tonight.
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I AM going to keep this blog updated! I HAVE to!  I'm trying a new blog, and to really write out my thoughts. It's hard for me, however, because I prefer to keep things inside. But, if you'll listen, I'll try, okay?  You know what I really hate? Is when people rite lke ths. It's lke they haff a spch inmpdmnt. It annys me. Dsn't it u?
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So many feelings, so little time...  Or is it the other way around?  Bah, who knows?  I feel like I've betrayed someone. I feel like I need to reach out to them...but...oh, I don't know...All I DO know is that I'm confused. It's really the only clear emotion at this point.  I have a choice: to keep walking on the path I'm headed, or take a different path(Yeah, I'm aware that's an uncreative look at circumstances. Shut up.). Both paths have their ups, their downs, their rewards, and their consequences. Neither are bad, just different.  I could go the easy way, and have my guilt quenched. But that would leave me wondering if I did the right thing.  I could go the hard way, and see if opportunity opens up to me. But that would leave me wondering is I did the right thing, and it would also leave me with an incredible amount of guilt. And again, this is ONLY if opportunity opens up to me.  Meh.  Anyway, I forgot to mention that I have a job, working on restoring an old house for one of our youth workers. It decently cool, other than the mice, snakes, and bats we have to deal with(it's a pretty old house). But for 8 bucks an hour, 10 hours a day? It ain't bad work, I tell you what.  It also slipped my mind to tell you I picked up some cardboard Sprite Remix signs that our local hardware store threw out. Once we get my room painted, one of tehm is so going on my wall. The other one I'll give to charity(AKA someone in my youth group).  Sorry I'm typing so much lately. No one seems to be on instant messenger when I'm on, and it's very lonely when you're a night owl like me with DSL.  So very lonely...  Oh! Billy just signed in. I suppose I could talk to him.  Evening, chaps and chappesses...  
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everything I thought was real Every dream, every feeling cold All the ghosts I tried to run from All the storms rusting into me  So tell me how to feel Now that you aren't real There's nothing to reveal  I ran on glass, broke my bones so I could find you I cut myself to Be around you And when I bled, you disappeared Just like you knew I always feared I closed my eyes, and climbed on you so I could breathe I hung my noose around your tree Suffered addiction to the air around you Now my whole world exists without you  I was a son, I was an angel falling from heaven I was a slave to your oppression The prophets never spoke of reasons For me or for my bitter freedom You spit on me, filled my Dirt with seeds of black As I carved your name across my back Burned out my eyes into your sun Oh, can’t you see now what you’ve done to me?  If I close my eyes, will this all go away? If I take your pill, will it all fade away? If I wake myself, will my darkness peel? I can’t sleep away because nothing is real.  There's nothing left to feel So tell me how to feel 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay...I'm confused, pissed, tired, VERY confused, grouchy, and slightly twitchy all at once.  Let's get things straight...  A: Aaron is fine being single. B: Why does Aaron like girl? C: Girl has partial boyfriend. D: Aaron's not going to intrude on other guy's territory E: Aaron's fine with that.  Now for the kicker...  F: Why does that bother Aaron so much?  It doesn't, but...it does! What the crap is up with this? I was fine just a couple days ago, but now...geez...it's driving me up a fricking wall. I didn't even like this girl up until what...Sunday? Geez, Aaron get a hold on yourself...  Then I have another girl who...well...I don't know what the crap is up with her, but apparently she likes me...AGAIN.  When do people give up? When do people leave me alone? When do people just piss off and leave their noses out of some things?  Man, the human race annoys me sometimes.  Had enough? I'm not done yet.  I've had the calling(and many confirmations) that I'm supposed to be a leader in the youth group. Up to this point, it seemed to be working out fine.   But then I started thinking...  How can I be a leader when over half the youth group(including the recent converts) are all more spiritually adept than me? They're speaking in tongues, prophecing, discerning things...I should be happy...right?  Wrong.  In fact, it's made me extremely depressed. Here I am, almost 12 years of being a Christian, and I can't even speak in tongues. It's not that I haven't sought for it, it's not that I haven't had the faith. Maybe I just haven't had the paitence. But it's very saddening to see your friends getting a blessing when you pour your heart out to God, and you get nothing but warm fuzzies. I don't want warm fuzzies. I don't want earthly pleasures. I don't want girls. I don't what earthly fame.  I want Jesus.  I've been seeking and seeking and seeking, but every time, it's only my friends getting the blessing.  Why do I have to wait? Why do I have to seek and press when they walk up and start speaking in tongues? Why do I have to sit back and cry, watching them get the good stuff, when I'm starving for Jesus? Why? Why? Why?  Why am I left behind when I'm supposed to lead them?  When they're supposed to be watching my actions?  When they're supposed to look up to me?  What good is a a leader that no one can see? 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Ever felt this way reading this blog?       Ph34r.       Well, duh.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and I can't tell if I've slept or not. At the most, I got 4 hours of sleep. At the least, I didn't get any. I think stress kept me awake...maybe a smattering of closure to boot...  Meh. I think I'm done with any of the girls in the youth group. Might as well not bother with them, because my reputation's shot from all my other flings, anyway.  Not that it's a bad thing I can't get a girl. It's probably better for me right now. But still...  I'll be patient. Nothing more to it.  Do I really have a choice in the matter?  Nope.  I'll shut up now. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Beautiful Paranoia  I'm sick of being a seat away from you So near, so far From everything&nbsp;I saw you to be At least you know my name I'm sick of watching you run When all I want you to do is stay So I can protect you from the world At least I'd know you were happy I'm sick of the way your teasing eyes Lock with mine, leaving me with questions Unanswered, because you still love another But why not me?  Why can't you see? I'm sick of the way your image Is burned in my mind Consuming my sanity'cause &nbsp;I have to keep you happy I'm sick of the way you can't trust What he did was wrong But will I be the same? Probably. &nbsp;Supposedly. I'm sick of being caught in the middle As the sides rage back and forth in my head You're not mine, I have no say in this My wishes aren't your decisions I'm sick of it Will you ever see me? The one that has been waiting for you to open your eyes? For years? Maybe it was love at first sight But I've found that love isn't everything It's cracked up to be Maybe I'm just as paranoid as you Oh, well... Part of being a man is learning when to give up But it still sucksI'll just give up Try not to stare I can't give up You're under my skin I&nbsp;won't give up Someday will bring A binding of wounds But for now They're open And you're pouring the salt Everytime I look at you Talk to you Listen to you I feel..uneasy Like I know you're watching me But are you really? As much as the desperate tone in your voice Drives me to madness I can't do anything I feel...inadequate Like I should just leave you alone But I would rather fail at something I loved Than succeed at something I hated Therefore... I am driven forword Regardless of odds Regardless of old wounds still healing Regardless of the pain I feel when I see you  You have become my beautiful paranoia 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To the tune of Queen's "Bohemian Rhapsody"   Is this the real life?  Is it just fantasy?  Caught in my schoolwork  No escape from my study   Open your books  Page 22  And see...   I'm just a poor dude  Void of all meriting  'Cause from class  I would go  Before&nbsp;the teacher  Told me so   Anytime the bell rings  Doesn't really affect...  Affect me...   Teacher  I just lost my work  Put the mouse up just to save  Power's gone, and now I rave  Teacher  40 pages done  But now I've gone and&nbsp;lost it anyway   Teacher, ooooo...  Didn't meet the deadline  I'll be up until this time tomorrow  Cramming on, cramming on  Learning subject matter   Too bad  My paper's gone  Four-thousand fifty lines  Carpal tunnel wrist I find   Goodbye to my studies  I've got to go  Gotta leave you all behind  My brain's now&nbsp;poo   Teacher, oooo  I don't wanna lie  Sometimes I wish hadn't been given that study hall   I see the little contents of a study  Is that it? Is that it?  Can't you do any better?  C's and D's lurking  Very, very irking  Galileo, Galileo  Galileo, Galilieo  Or Einstein I am not   I'm just a poor dude,  Nobody needs me  He's just a poor punk  From Room Two Oh Three  His backpack ain't light  It's a monstrosity   All my grades  All time lows  Lazy, I suppose   I'll say so!  Don't say so!  He's failing!  So what if he's failing!?  I'll say so!  Don't say so!  Will not let you fail!  Let you fail!  Will not let you fail!  Let you fail!  Will not let you fail!   Cafeteria mysteria  Meatloaf!   His algebra has become way to difficult  For me  For me  For meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee   (insert guitar solo)   So you think that I know 3.14 equal pi?  So you think I'll remember all these dead guys?  Oh, maybe  Sometime I just maybe  I guess I'm too loud  Cuz the office is two doors from here   Nothing's really staying  Not inside my brain  I guess I'll be a bum  Living on the system  'Til I'm fourty&nbsp;  Guess what? I really wrote this by myself! Cool, huh?&nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Breathe, trust, bless me and release Climb, hard or never be seen Closed off, rescue to breathe Just bless me  Two sided time Your rebirth can't hurt Branch out behind, the pain  Closure has come to me myself You will never belong to me Closure has come to me myself You will never belong to me  Had to&nbsp;turn, lay down Your sting of disease Phase you out, should've seen this coming Go on, confusing this soul Hold my breath 'til you rupture  Three days aside Your rebirth can't hurt Branch out behind, pride  Closure has come to me myself You will never belong to me Closure has come to me myself You will never belong to me  Like a leech,I hold on as if we belonged To some precious pure dream Cast off, you've seen what's beneath Now fail me.  Forget closure Forget closure Forget closure Forget closure  Closure has come to me myself You will never belong to me Closure has come to me myself You will never belong to me  So breathe 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Triumph and confusion all in one night.   I don't understand myself...   I'm waiting...   Waiting for what?   Just one sign.   From who?   Her.   Her who?   I can't say it...   Why not?   Too many people would be disapointed in me.   Well, they love you, nonetheless.   I know...   So what's on your mind?   Her.   Again, I ask, who?   Just...never mind...   No. Tell me.   I don't want to.   Whatever...you're stubborn that way...   Simple motions are pushing me over the edge...   What?   Her...   There you go again.   What are you worried about?   That...I'll never have her...   I thought you were "over" her?   I thought so too...   
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did fairly well at the Halo party. I won one of the deathmatches(11 people at once= INTENSE!), and scored quite&nbsp;a few times during the capture the flag matches. It was a crapload of fun.  Well, I'm glad to find out that I'm not the only one that's getting the jibblies about Derek and Ashley's "friendship". Seems I have allies in other places besides my alternate personalities...  Current song:Soul Embraced-"Immune To Emotion"  &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      current song: Rhapsody-"Knightrider of Doom"  ...wow...wow, wow, wow...   Is it just me, or am I constantly being labeled as the bad guy? It seems like everytime I open my mouth I say something "wrong". I can't help it if I have a bad feeling about Derek and Ashley's "friendship". It's just...starting out the same way I did. The pledges of "Oh, no, I'll never go behind your parent's back!" and "Nope, no physical contact for us!".   Something about it gives me the jibblies...and I can't explain it fully...but I get a bad feeling every time I see them together. Maybe it just reminds me of Heather and I...   You know, it's been a year, almost exactly, since she broke up with me.   Ah, ...I had my chance, and I lost it. Due to my disobedience, I lost the girl of my dreams. That's what I'm worried about.   If they disobey, they may lose each other.   Well, that's beside the point I don't think they're right for each other. But, hey, I'm just[QUOTE=Ashley]acting like an immature kid. No one can be happy if you're not happy.[/QUOTE] So what do I know?   Enough. Quite enough. Enough to know that I have a bad feeling about this.   Maybe I'm just overprotective.&nbsp;God knows I have a knight-in-dented-armor disposition. I don't know what it is about their relationship, but something's not right. But some people have to learn the hard way...   The fading illusion the sirens' grey tears  It's here in the cold air the town's tragic fear  The breath of infernos the rise of the dead  The portals of chaos the seventh black flame  (RIDE) Destino (KNIGHT) mi arrendo...al tuo dominio del tempo!   In this bloody dawn  I will wash my soul  To call the spirit of vengeance  To deny my wisdom for anger  To break the scream of the silent fool  And to be the&nbsp;knight of doom   The rites of the unborn the dragonship's fall  The waves of my ocean the twins' holy call  The march of the heroes the call of the gods  After the rituals on the silent shore   
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I AM OFFICALLY A GEEK!  Yeah, I&nbsp; downloaded the entire Final Fantasy(for NES) instruction manual online. I am a geek.  But that's okay.  I"m going to a Halo party on the 23rd, and I am STOKED! Jeff, JJ, and I are going to try to be on a team together. We're calling ourselves...(ahem) &nbsp;  THE MIGHTY FIGHTY SHUSHBUGS!    &nbsp; What? You mean that didn't strike fear into your heart? That's odd...well, no one will&nbsp; be able to withstand the barrage of Tego Marr, Adain Carr, and Grand Fragmaster Zilch(also known as Zilch). We're gonna whoop serious tuckus. &nbsp; Another funny thing... &nbsp; I'm going to help DJ a party. Got's to download some more techno tonight... 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This desire is rising within me  So fierce of a delight  My past will rise to haunt me  If succumb to it this night  It promises me happiness  If I follow it to sin  But after tonight will I  Try to quench the guilt within?  Instant pleasure seems a goal  Worthy of my time  I just don't like to see  Any reason besides mine  What happens if I sacrifice  My love, my trust, my hope  Will You be there to hold my hand  In darkness that I grope?  I see the clear reasons  I see the obvious signs  Wrong or right, lies or truth?  To be straight or misaligned?   
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from Steve's birthday party, and I completely overloaded on sugar. If I see one more Dot or Mike & Ike, I swear I'll get a beer gut...(looks at Reese's on desk)...well...one won't hurt much...  In other news, the spiritual enemy I've been fighting has been pushed back, and is headed for the hills. Complete victory is assured when reinforcements arrive tomorrow. Fear will fall, and the world will be a better place. Until then, I cling to my Savior for everything I need.  I really wonder sometimes of where I would be without Jesus. I would have been into drugs, porn, sex, and Lord knows what else. Not that I'm perfect now, there's no question I'm not, but it's good to know that I have a reason to live and a hope to look forward to.  Where would I be without my beautiful Savior?  That's one question I'll never have to answer... 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Won't you come away with me tonight? We can fly past the moon and the starlight It doesn't matter where you've been before On a night like this It doesn't matter where you've been before I'll love you like this But she cries...  Can't you see I won't leave? But you have to open your eyes Here I stand Take my hand Let go of the fear that you hold  Don't throw your pearls to the swine tonight Don't let them take your innocence Just remember the times that I held your hand And kept you close Just the remember the times I held you up And now? She cries...
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 2:51, and I'm sick...stupid Chinese...I hate Chinese food now...
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from Jeff's again. A good old-fashioned all-nighter with video games and 4 cans of Sprite Remix and 2 Nestea COOLs. I was playing Metal Gear Solid 2 until about 4:30 this morning. Fell asleep in a chair and my leg went numb. Average day. Ho-hum.
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really don't want to post right now.  That's a first. I usually want to spill everything out on the floor, but tonight...my feelings are so jumbled, I don't know even what to write,  My feelings toward someone was torn between another person tonight.  The person who broke my heart? Or the one whose heart I broke?  Maybe some people are right. Maybe I'm just horny. Lord knows I have a hard time containing my emotions...but...  No.  I refuse to believe that. I'm meant for so much more.  I'm human.  But that doesn't make me without control.  It's time I start thinking before I speak. It's time I start planning before I execute.  It's time to mend broken hearts and protect newly-sown ones. 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have no words, phrases, quotes, or expletives to describe my feelings right now.  Heather came over tonight.  Old feelings aroused.  On both ends? I believe so...  Boyfriend in Manchester.  I honor that connection.  But still... 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi all.  I'm working at Dexter High again, installing new Pentium 4 compys(insert girlish squeal)!  The one I'm typing on right now has a 17" LCD flat screen. So very nice.  WHOA! What's that smell? What the crap did I eat this morning...wow...that's raunchy... 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Great...just...frickin'...great...  I have to miss a Halo party, just because my mom decided to host a junior high youth group party at my house. Just because "I should help out", my mom says. Geez...I have more creative ways to burn brain cells...  I can't help it if my cousins have no social life. I can't help it if no one understands them. The other kids should include them...the little dinks...picking on my cousins like that...  Just because someone's different, it doesn't give you any right to shun them like that.  I've seen it in action, too. I feel so bad for them sometimes, because they're so cool to me. I want to bring the other lame kids into our world of video games and anime. Into a world where everyone is equal...  I can't believe it...I'm on the verge of tears as I write this post. It just sickens me that the others won't include my cousins.     <> I'M GONNA BEAT 'EM INTO THE FRIGGING GROUND! STUPID FRICKING TEENYBOPPERS! DIEIDIEIDIEDIEDIEDIEDIEDIEDIEDIEDIE!!!        I'm not gonna take this.  Maybe I don't feel so bad about missing that party...  Okay...I still feel bad. Halo is so much fun with 8 people...and I would have wiped the floor with them...  *sigh*   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was just making a post on the Guild of Redeemed Gamers, and Nick decides to leave me, just because we were late for the first time...geez...what's ten minutes? That kinda ticks me off...but anyway...let's view that post I was making...   This spoothead(AKA Last-Attacker) posted this website( http://www.jesus-is-lord.com/games.htm ) on the GRG, and takes it as truth. Dear Lord, how LAME can you be? So I replied...(anything quoted somes directly from jesusislord.com)   Okay...I lost interest after your website immediately cracked down on Christian rock. I know for a fact that Christian rock has a huge message, but all the holier-than-thous don't like the music style, so they'll automatically call it demonic.    [QUOTE=People too dumb to pee without help]"… Yes! You only have one fourth of this incredible epic. That is because most of you have paid us nothing or at most, very little. You could steal the game from a friend. But we both know you'll be punished by God if you do. WHY RISK ETERNAL DAMNATION? Call 1-800-IDGAMES AND BUY NOW![/QUOTE]    Ahem. Here we have a joke. And they turn it into a blasphemous statement. Id software was being sarcastic, the same way I would be if I said that God liked me better than anyone else. Goodness...    [QUOTE=more statements from the short bus]In some games, there is an "invincibility mode", which makes the player invulnerable to enemy attacks, so the player will not die. However in recent years, it seems the industry is changing the term "Invincibility mode" to "God mode". I think that this is another way Satan wants people to think that they are gods, when they are really not (Genesis 3:5). But there is only one God (Mark 12:32). [/QUOTE]    God mode simply shows invincibility. If anything, these "Satanist" programmers are paying a Deity(whom they say doesn't exist) a homage. They're saying God is omni-powerful, and completely in control. Funny thing is, they don't believe in God...and they say he's weak...yet they call their most powerful code "God mode". Bit of an oxymoron here.    There's a reason you got flamed, Attacker. There is no expletive in my vocabulary to describe how this site makes me feel. Do you realize you can't take everything for granted online anymore? This lady(yes, a woman runs this site) probably has never played these games before, and is running on another site's research.    Holy crap, don't these spootheads have anything better to do?    Amazing how you're posting this when your avatar depicts a gory game that includes swearing and people's organs flying all over the place. Are you sure you're in the right boat to judge Id software?    Without Quake, there would be no Half-Life. Games would still suck. Majorly. Granted, DOOM and Quake ARE both demonic, but geez! To actually waste cyberspace and domain payments on telling people that don't know, don't care?    Anyways, this author failed to mention you fight the hordes of Hell in both games. You don't use any demonic weapons, and you beat the crap out of Satan. It's just not via spiritual warfare. You use shotguns. People just freak out when they see Satanic symbols. That's like saying a mall is bad to shop at because they have a Hot Topic store.    Some people need to learn how to chill...  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that when people get mad, they automatically target my love of all things cyber?  Why is it that when I'm sarcastic, everyone get their feelings hurt?  Why is it that people spew off crap about me when it's gone, forgotten, and done with?  Why is it that every girl I show a picture of Rikku to, they quickly say how ugly she is?  Having my life involved in all things cyber doesn't make me without feelings. And right now, they're incredibly hurt. I can't tell you how many times people have made fun of my online and video gaming fetish. I can't help it if the current-day teenage-melodramatic world doesn't interest me. I can't help it if I enjoy writing tags and links more than I like to got to the mall. It just doesn't make sense...  Why do the geeks get targeted?  Why is everyone so opposed to us having our own world when they have their own?  As Sony would say, live in your world, play in ours.  I'm just extremely offended at people right now.  Mostly at people that take low blows when they're angry... 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever felt an inch-and-a-half long splinter go into your finger? It's not exactly the coolest sensation in the world, I tell you what. Along with that, I've got a blister on my right index finger from playing my bass when I had just washed my hands, thus softening my callouses, and thus leaving me in a world of pain when I type.  But, hey, that's really not that interesting, is it?  Ever wonder how you're going to end up? Like what job, what spouse, what impact you'll make on the world? That's kinda the situation I'm in right now.  I'm 16, and I need to figure out what I'm going to be doing two years from now. It makes you think about choices and consequences, and whether or not the things you do are really worth it. Should you study or go hang out with some friends? I mean, it's only one test, so why bother? It can't hurt you much, right?  Well, what happens when that test brings your final score down .13 points, thus making you miss getting a scholarship to a college. So now you have to work for 3-5 years at fast-food places, trying to make a living and get a further education somewhere when you could have just stayed home and studied that one night.  See my dillema?  You don't always know the end of your actions. Think before you rush into a decision. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've watched almost eight episodes of Full Moon wo Shagashite...just tonight! And I want to watch more! ACK! 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry that it's been so long between posts, I've been grounded...I thought my mom knew I stayed up until 1 AM on a regular basis...  Anyway, I'm officially going to Higgins now. I found out that my English testing was the one of the best they've seen. My English comprehension is high enough to graduate from public school. I'm taking Old Testament history and sign language, so I'll have something new to learn. I'm trying to challenge myself this year so I don't have to work so hard next year.  Geez...I'm gonna be a senior next year...I'm not ready for the real world yet...  I'm just a little kid trapped in a 16-year-old's body. I guess you have to grow up at some point, eh?  In other news, I'm okay with the fact that Nick and Hailey have feelings for each other. My concern was genuine, although I thought it was out of jealousy. It's hard to read myself at times...I just looked Nick in the eye and told him to take good care of her...and I'm hoping he will keep that promise...  I've decided I'm done with the girls in the youth group. The only ones I could be interested in are...  A: taken B: too blonde to pee without help C: too freaking obsessed with me(shudder)  I mean, this doesn't mean I'm not going to be their friends, and that I'm not going to support them in any way I can. I just need to look elsewhere for wive-ish material.  Oh, speaking of girls in the youth group, we have a new girl in youth. Holly is a FINAL FANTASY FAN! Do you have any idea how long I've waited for this moment in time? When someone would walk into our youth chapel and actually claim to play RPG's? I was the only RPGer up until this point, but now I'm not alone! Granted, she's not a HUGE fan like me, but I find it heartening that we have someone that's played through Lunar, Final Fantasy X, and Chrono Cross(none of which I have done. everyone, start gasping). I'm playing through Gandia II right now, but I've been on a FPS(first-person-shooter, for the uninitiated) bender the last few weeks, so I haven't played it much.  I just hope I don't get so busy over the next year that I lose my zeal for video games...that would be sad...    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...lies a hope beyond human comprehension...just thought of this today...  pathological disturbances (yes, that's supposed to be lowercase)  I have reason for living. There is cause for my existence There is reason for living This reality, inside me, inside this fence I have reason for running My legs have strength to go on Fear doesn't fuel my speed It only powers my blood-scarred song Something flows through my viens Antivenom won't satiate This fatal infection of You Causing my flesh to disintegrate  You are my death You are my life Nothing exists outside of You And never will You leave  You are my beautiful disease Rotting my flesh away in folds You are my beautiful cancer Unbearable bliss is taking its toll You give me everything I need You are my constant Provider You give me shade in this heat Your love is my constant reminder Jesus, you are my incredible Lord Jesus, you're infecting my soul Jesus, you'll never leave me alone In you, my Savior, my existence is full  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (sigh) I hate my frigging computer. Shuts off right when I'm about to finish a blog post...  Anyway...  I really don't care about her anymore. I don't. If she's so enamored by my brother still, by all means, throw yourself away. Heck, Nick, go ahead and rape her. See if I care.  Okay...so I care enough so I don't want her hurt, but that's it. But this is what I prayed for. If it wasn't right, I wanted a lack of interest. And here we are.  Speaking of lack of interest, I wish some people would learn. I wish they would go away and stop tempting me to use them as a safety net. It's called "moving on". It's something you do after you break up. Welcome to the real world.  Ah, Lord...why did you give me such a realistic view of things?  Another thing that's pissing me off...  I was talking to Billy, and he said people told him I was a jerk with girls. I can't believe friends I trusted(even though I don't know who it was that told him this, I still trusted them) with my life are spreading this crap around about me. Yes, it's true, I have been a jerk, but you know what? It's under the Blood. Let it go.  I can't help the fact I get a guilty conscience just when a girl really starts to like me. I can't help it when I don't finish what I shouldn't have started to begin with. And if people get upset and crappy about it, guess what?  I'm bigger than that. Jesus was, too. In trying to be like Him, I end up having to deal with stuff like this. But He said He'd never put me through anything I couldn't handle.  Meh.  It's hard.  But perservence has never been my strong point...  Guys, I'm just really upset right now. And no, I don't want Nick to rape Hailey. I'm just upset enough right now to say something like that.  And being lonely doesn't help...  God, I need You so much...
    
</post>


</Blog>