<Blog>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
           "If you want to be one of us all you have to do is dress like us, talk like us, and listen to the same music we do.... Oh yeah, and you have to hate conformists." -  Matt Stone and Trey Parker     What is the perfect life? To many it seems that success, wealth, and status answer that question all to well, and yet, I disagree. We live our lives in pursuit of what we think will make us happy, but what we THINK will make us happy, and what actually will make us happy, are two very different things. Lets take for example, physical appearance. Every human in the world thinks about their appearance dozens of times a day. As a race, we are extremely self-conscious, which is to be expected as we are also extremely appearance-orientated in all aspects of life. Makeup products, plastic surgery, clohing and apparel, all of these areas are multi-billion dollar industries, and this is not by accident. But why is it that we are so engrossed in appearances that we are willing to throw away so much money to improve them? That is an answer, I fear I will never have.    The fact of the matter is, however, that beauty is a losing-battle. All to often we are bombarded with images of beautiful models, sex, status, and style in everything we read, watch, and hear. We are told how to dress, what is cool, what music is good, and what is beautiful.What strikes me as amusing is that despite all our vanity,and superficiality we fail to realize how fickle appearances really are. We see it everyday on television, and throughout the media, love, relationships, marriage, everything which we consider personal seems to be appearance orientated. Intelligence, personality, we say they are the most important factors in attraction, but in this we only succeed in fooling one person: ourselves. Beauty is cruel master, and bows to no person. We define beauty through appearances, but physical appearances have a tendancy to fade with time. No matter how beautiful a person may seem at age 20, they too will one day age, and with their years lose that title. There is a popular cliche that says "Beauty is only skin-deep," but therein lies the distuinguishment between appearances and reality. To many, beauty appears to be what we see, and yet in reality it is much more. As long as we fail to recognize the reality, we will fail to break free from the chains of superficiality that bind us so powerfully.    Furthermore, it cannot be denied Money and power are the calling cards of success in our society, and the indicators by which we judge a person's worth. But as someone once said a few decades ago, "All the money in the world wont buy you more life." So why is it that we drain away the majority of our life in the pursuit of money, and status? From ages 3-63 we spend on average 5 hours a day either in school, or at work, and for what? When you are on your death bed at age 80, will it matter how much money you have in your bank account, or how many sports cars you have parked in your 4-door garage? Hell no. But I will tell you what will matter when you lay on the edge of your mortality: the fact that you threw away the best, and brightest years of your life, and youth slaving to the whip of greed, and ambition.   "Money can't buy happiness." Of course we have all heard the cliche more times then we can count, b"ut how often do we actually think about it? We say we know that money and possesions wont make us happy, but do we honestly think so? Not bloody likely. We will continue to buy everything in excess, from clothes, to shoes, to cars, and hats regardless of how well we know this moral.    -More to Come
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         "In life there will always be questions and answers. What is important, is how you navigate between the two." -Frank Herbert                                                  Imagine the perfect world. Think of a place devoid of any disturbance, a pristine utopia where life is perfect in every aspect. In this world of soothing serenity, and complete relaxation, there is no disease, no pain, and no suffering. Here, there are no conflicts to struggle against, nor are there any obstacles in life to overcome. No one here need feel sorrow, anger, or despair. In fact, here there is nothing at all to feel. Imagine this “perfect” world. Do you think it is somewhere you might be happy? Think again. Despite what some may think, a world such as this is not nearly as desirable as it sounds. As humans, it is through the complications in life that we grow, and mature into who we really are. No person should want to have everything in life go their way, nor should they always take the path of least resistance. To do so is to deny what makes us who we are. A life without conflict is a life no one should desire. Despite popular belief, true fulfillment in life is found in struggle. 	Adversity is the calling card of humanity. Every person in the world faces some kind of conflict every day, and to know this, is to understand that our flaws and shortcomings are what make us human. Think of it this way, when is the last time you met someone who had no physical, or character flaws? There is no such thing as a human being whose appearance is without blemish, and who has never been faced with any problems, or obstacles to overcome in life. The question is, however, even if there was someone fitting such a description, would it be someone with who you wanted to be friends? It is through struggling against, and then overcoming our problems in life that we build character. If someone had never come across a situation where they were forced to deal with a complication, they would have no character. In fact, they would likely have	  no emotion whatsoever. Perfection is not a human attribute, it is a robot’s. In a world where everything was perfect, we would all be robots. Through facing adversity, we ascertain that we are truly human. 	Through overcoming the adversity we face in life, we come to know a sense of achievement. If life was flawless, and there were no problems to overcome, there would be no point in living. As humans, we need to feel that there is meaning, and purpose to our life. Without a sense of accomplishment, we cannot achieve this sense of purpose. True satisfaction is found in facing the odds, and winning, not through taking the easiest route to victory. Imagine you are in the Olympics, for sprinting. You have trained for the past decade without pause. The majority of your life has gone towards this one, final competition. Years of struggle, pain, sweat, and tears have brought you here, and now it is time to test the fruits of your labour against those of your opponents for the chance to win gold. What if right before the race you found out your opponents were toddlers? Surely you could win easily, but even if you did, would you feel as if you had accomplished something?  It is through struggling in a battle against our obstacles that we find meaning in our life. 	By overcoming obstacles in life, we attain dignity.  As humans, we could never have dignity if everything in life was handed to us on a silver platter. Dignity is essential for human happiness, and without a sense of integrity a person cannot have dignity. By sticking to our guns when a situation turns unfavourable, and persevering, we remain true to ourselves. Respect is essential for dignity, and someone who has no conflicts in life to overcome is not respected. Think about it, would you respect someone who had everything given to them in life? Of course not. In fact, you might think that person was spoiled. Despite what we think, by not always having life go the way we want it, we achieve dignity. It is through struggle, not relaxation that we come to discover just who we are. Adversity is what defines us humans, and it is through struggle that we come to know who we are. 	Adversity is the fulcrum of life. It is through the hardships in life, that we find true happiness and fulfilment in life. If life were perfect, and flawless, our personalities would be like a blank painter’s canvas. Perseverance is the colour of life that fills the canvas of our character, and makes our life more then a bland bleary painting. As humans, we can choose to take the road of least resistance, or we can actually live our lives by rising to each new challenge that is thrown at us. In life, we can either choose the former path and be robots, or we can take the latter route, and be truly human. The question is: what do you want to be? 
     
    
</post>


<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, the idea for this blog started after I had already finished the first book in A Song of Ice and Fire, A Game of Thrones. I am now reading A Clash of Kings.  A Game of Thrones was an interesting and very entertaining read. I've become hooked on Martin's form of writing and the story he has created. It is amazing; the good guys do not always win, there is much violence, and it is an epic.  It was crazy what happened to Eddard Stark, I knew it was going to come because of Martin's reputation but it was still surprising, he was an extremely important character. I also like Jon quite a bit. I have a feeling that he is actually the son of Rhaegar and Lyanna and will somehow hook up with Dany to rule the world. :p  More to come later.... 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>