<Blog>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today i have recieved a mail from Manish Bucha. I like to share it with you.  "A candidate for a news broadcasters post was rejected by officials  since  his voice was not fit for a news broadcaster. He was also  told that with  his obnoxiously long name, he would never be famous.  He is Amitabh Bachchan.  -----------------------------  A small boy - the fifth amongst seven siblings of a poor father,  was  selling newspapers in a small village to earn his living. He  was not  exceptionally smart at school but was fascinated by  religion and  rockets. The first rocket he built crashed. A missile  that he built  crashed multiple times and he was made a butt of  ridicule. He is the  person to have scripted the Space Odyssey of  India single-handedly  - Dr. APJ Abdul Kalam.  ----------------------------  In 1962, four nervous young musicians played their first record  audition!  for the executives of the Decca recording Company.  The  executives were  not impressed. While turning down this group of   musicians, one executive  said,   "We don't like their sound. Groups of guitars  are on the way out."  The group was called The Beatles.  ------------------------------------------  In 1944, Emmeline Snively, director of the Blue Book Modelling  Agency  told modelling hopeful Norma Jean Baker, "You'd better learn  secretarial  work or else get married." She went on and became  .....Marilyn Monroe.  ----------------------------------------------------  In 1954, Jimmy Denny, manager of the Grand Ole Opry, Fired a singer   after one performance. He told him, "You ain't going nowhere....son.  You  ought to go back to driving' a truck." He went on to become  .....Elvis Presley.  ---------------------------------------------  When Thomas Edison invented the light bulb, he tried over 2000   experiments before he got it ! to work. A young  reporter asked him  how it  felt to fail so! many times. He said, "I never  failed once.  I invented  the light bulb. It just happened to be a 2000-step  process."  -------------------------------------------  When Alexander Graham Bell invented the telephone in  1876, it did  not ring off the hook with calls from potential backers.  After  making a demonstration call, President Rutherford Hayes said, "That's an amazing  invention, but who would ever want to see one  of  them?"  --------------------------------------------------------------------- --- In the 1940s, another young inventor named Chester Carlson took his  idea  to 20 corporations, including some of the biggest in the  country. They  all turned him down. In 1947, after 7 long years of  rejections, he  finally got a tiny company in Rochester, NY, the  Haloid company, to  purchase the rights to his invention -- an  electrostatic paper copying  process. Haloid became Xerox  Corporation.  ------------------------------------! A little girl - the 20th of 22 children, was born  prematurely and  her  survival was doubtful. When she was 4 years old, she   contracted double pneumonia and scarlet fever, which left her with a paralysed left leg.  At age 9, she removed the metal leg brace she  had  been dependent on and  began to walk without it. By 13 she had  developed a  rhythmic walk,  which doctors said was a miracle. That  same year she  decided to become a  runner. She entered a race and  came in last. For the next few years  every race she entered, she  came in last. Everyone  told her to quit, but  she kept on running. One day she actually won a  race. And then  another. From then on she won every race she entered.  Eventually  this little girl  Wilma Rudolph, went on to win three Olympic gold   medals.  -------------------------------  A school teacher scolded a boy for not paying  attention to his   mathematics and for not being able to solve simple  problems. She  told  him that you would not become anybody in life. The boy was Albert  Einstein.  -----------------------------------  The Moral:  Adopting easy ways can only make you an ordinary  person.Only  through experiences  of trial and suffering can the soul be  strengthened,  vision cleared,  ambition inspired and success  achieved. You gain  strength and confidence by every experience  where  you really stop to look fear in the face.   "FACE YOUR FEARS LIVE YOUR DREAMS"   Lead your destiny the way YOU want...    Manish   
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        These are the personal views of   Mr. R. Gopalakrishnan  , Director - Tata Sons. Great Stuff from a great ex-HLL manager.  A Story on how to manage your career &amp; your expectations by R.Gopalakrishnan.    There is a Thai saying that experience is a comb which Nature gives to man after he is bald. As I grow bald, I would like to share my comb with your people, about their career ahead .  &nbsp;  1.   Seek out grassroots level experience    I studied Physics and Engineering at University. A few months before graduation, I appeared for an HLL interview for Computer Traineeship.When asked whether I would consider Marketing instead of Computers, I responded negatively : an engineer to visit grocery shops to sell Dalda or Lifebuoy? Gosh, no way. After I joined the Company and a couple of comfortable weeks in the swanky Head Office, I was given a train ticket to go to Nasik.Would I please meet Mr. Kelkar to whom I would be attached for the next two months? He would teach me to work as a salesman in his territory, which included staying in Kopargaon and Pimpalgaon among other small towns.I was most upset. In a town called Ozhar, I was moving around from shop to shop with a bullock cart full of products and a salesman's folder in my hand. Imagine my embarrassment when an IIT friend appeared in front of me in Ozhar, believe it or not! and exclaimed, "Gopal, I thought you joined as a Management Trainee in Computers". I could have died a thousand deaths. After this leveling experience, I was less embarrassed to work as a Despatch Clerk in the Company Depot and an Invoice Clerk in the Accounts Department. Several years later, I realised the value of such grassroots level experience. It is fantastic. I would advise young people to seek out nail-dirtying, collar-soiling, shoe-wearing tasks. That is how you learn about organizations, about the true nature of work, and the dignity of the many, many tasks that go into building great enterprises.  &nbsp;  2.   Deserve before you desire    At one stage, I was appointed as the Brand Manager for Lifebuoy and Pears soap, the company's most popular-priced and most premium soaps. And what was a Brand Manager? "A mini-businessman, responsible for the production, sales and profits of the brand, accountable for its long-term growth,etc.,etc. I had read those statements, I believed them and here I was, at 27,"in charge of everything". But very soon, I found I could not move a pin without checking with my seniors. One evening, after turning the Facit machine handle through various calculations, I sat in front of the Marketing Director. I expressed my frustration and gently asked whether I could not be given total charge. He smiled benignly and said, "The perception and reality are both right. You will get total charge when you know more about the brand than anyone else in this company about its formulation, the raw materials, the production costs, the consumer's perception, the distribution and so on. How long do you think that it will take?" "Maybe, ten years", I replied, "and I don't expect to be the Lifebuoy and Pears Brand Manager for so long"! And then suddenly, the lesson was clear. I was desiring total control, long before I deserved it. This happens to us all the time - in terms of responsibilities, in terms of postings and promotions, it happens all the time that there is a gap between our perception of what we deserve and the reality of what we get.It helps to deserve before we desire.  &nbsp;  3   Play to win but win with fairness    Life is competitive and of course, you play to win. But think about the balance. Will you do anything, to win? Perhaps not. Think deeply about how and where you draw the line. Each person draws it differently, and in doing so, it helps to think about values. Winning without values provides dubious fulfillment. The leaders who have contributed the most are the ones with a set of universal values ¡V Mahatma Gandhi and Martin Luther King for example. Napoleon inspired a ragged, mutinous and half-starved army to fight and seize power. This brought him name and fame for twenty years. But all the while, he was driven forward by a selfish and evil ambition, and not in pursuit of a great ideal. He finally fell because of his selfish ambition. I am fond of referring to the Pierre de Coubertin Fair Play Trophy. It was instituted in 1964 by the founder of the modern Olympic Games and here are two examples of winners.A Hungarian tennis player who pleaded with the umpire to give his opponent some more time to recover from a cramp. A British kayak team who were trailing the Danish kayak team. They then stopped to help the Danish team whose boat was stuck. The Danes went on to beat the British by one second in a three hour event! What wonderful examples of sportsmanship! Play to Win, but with Fairness.  &nbsp;  4   Enjoy whatever you do    Sir Thomas Lipton is credited with the statement, "There is no greater fun than hard work". You usually excel in fields, which you truly enjoy. Ask any person what it is that interferes with his enjoyment of existence. He will say, "The struggle for life". What he probably means is the struggle for success. Unless a person has learnt what to do with success after getting it, the very achievement of it must lead him to unhappiness. Aristotle wrote, "Humans seek happiness as an end in itself, not as a means to something else". But if you think about it, we should not work for happiness. We should work as happy people. In organisational life, people get busy doing something to be happy. The more you try to be happy, the more unhappy you can get. Your work and career is all about your reaching your full potential. Working at one's full potential, whether it is the office boy or the Chairman, leads to enjoyment and fulfillment. A last point about enjoyment. Keep a sense of humour about yourself. Too many people are in danger of taking themselves far too seriously. As General Joe Stilwell is reported to have said, "Keep smiling. The higher the monkey climbs, the more you can see of his backside".  &nbsp;  5   Be Passionate about your health    Of course, as you get older, you would have a slight paunch, greying of hair or loss of it and so on. But it is in the first 5 - 7 years after the working career begins that the greatest neglect of youthful health occurs.Sportsmen stop playing sports, non drinkers drink alcohol, light smokers smoke more, active people sit on chairs, starving inmates of hostels eatrich food in good hotels and so on. These are the years to watch. Do not, I repeat do not, convince yourself that you are too busy, or that you do not have access to facilities, or worst of all, that you do this to relieve the stresses of a professional career.A professional career is indeed very stressful. There is only one person who can help you to cope with the tension, avoid the doctor's scalpel,and to feel good each morning - and that is yourself. God has given us as good a health as He has, a bit like a credit balance in the bank. Grow it,maintain it, but do not allow its value destruction. The penalty is very high in later years.  &nbsp;  6   Direction is more important than distance    Every golfer tries to drive the ball to a very long distance. In the process, all sorts of mistakes occur because the game involves the masterly co-ordination of several movements simultaneously. The golf coach always advises that direction is more important than distance. So it is with life.Despite one¡¦s best attempts, there will be ups and downs. It is relationships and friendships that enable a person to navigate the choppy waters that the ship of life will encounter. When I was young, there was a memorable film by Frank Capra, starring James Stewart and Dona Reed, and named IT'S A WONDERFUL LIFE. It is about a man who is about to commit suicide because he thinks he is a failure. An angel is sent to rescue him.The bottomline of the film is that "No Man is a Failure Who Has Friends".  &nbsp;    Conclusion    My generation will never be twenty again, but when you are older, you can and should be different from my generation. Ours is a great and wonderful country, and realising her true potential in the global arena depends ever so much on the quality and persistence of our young people. Good luck in your journey, my young friends, and God be with you and our beloved Nation.  
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          Article sourced from: Lasting Legacies (Tata Review- Special Commemorative Issue 2004), brought out by the house of Tatas to commemorate the 100th birth anniversary of JRD Tata on July 29, 2004       Angry letter from a young lady made JRD Tata change his rule. Sudha was livid when a job advertisement posted by a Tata company at the institution where she was completing her post graduation stated that "Lady candidatesneed not apply". She dashed off a post card to JRD Tata, protesting against the discrimination. Following this, Sudha was called for an interview and she became the first female engineer to work on the shop floor at Telco (now Tata Motors). It was the beginning of an association that would change her life in more ways than one. THERE are two photographs that hang on my office wall. Everyday when I entered my office I look at them before starting my day. They are pictures of two old people. One is of a gentleman in a blue suit and the other is a black and white image of a man with dreamy eyes and a white beard. People have often asked me if the people in the photographs are related to me. Some have even asked me, "Is this black and white photo that of a Sufi saint or a religious Guru?" I smile and reply "No, nor are they related to me. These people made an impact on my life. I am grateful to them." "Who are they?" "The man in the blue suit is Bharat Ratna JRD Tata and the black and white photo is of Jamsetji Tata." "But why do you have them in your office?"" You can call it gratitude." Then, invariably, I have to tell the person the following story. It was a long time ago. I was young and bright, bold and idealistic. I was in the final year of my Master's course in Computer Science at the Indian Institute of Science (IISc) in Bangalore, then known as the Tata Institute. Life was full of fun and joy. I did not know what helplessness or injustice meant. It was probably the April of 1974. Bangalore was getting warm and gulmohars were blooming at the IISc campus. I was the only girl in my postgraduate department and was staying at the ladies' hostel. Other girls were pursuing research in different departments of Science. I was looking forward to going abroad to complete a doctorate in computer science. I had been offered scholarships from Universities in the US. I had not thought of taking up a job in India. One day, while on the way to my hostel from our lecture-hall complex, I saw an advertisement on the notice board. It was a standard job-requirement notice from the famous automobile company Telco (now Tata Motors). It stated that the company required young, bright engineers, hardworking and with an excellent academic background, etc. At the bottom was a small line: "Lady candidates need not apply." I read it and was very upset. For the first time in my life I was up against gender discrimination. Though I was not keen on taking up the job, I saw it as a challenge. I had done extremely well in academics, better than most of my male peers. Little did I know then that in real life academic excellence is not enough to be successful. After reading the notice I went fuming to my room. I decided to inform the topmost person in Telco's management about the injustice the company was perpetrating. I got a postcard and started to write, but there was a problem: I did not know who headed Telco. I thought it must be one of the Tatas. I knew JRD Tata was the head of the Tata Group; I had seen his pictures in newspapers (actually, Sumant Moolgaokar was the company's chairman then). I took the card, addressed it to JRD and started writing. To this day I remember clearly what I wrote. "The great Tatas have always been pioneers. They are the people who started the basic infrastructure industries in India, such as iron and steel, chemicals, textiles and locomotives. They have cared for higher education in India, such as iron and steel, chemicals, textiles and locomotives. They have cared for higher education in Indiasince 1900 and they were responsible for the establishment of the Indian Institute of Science. Fortunately, I study there. But I am surprised how a company such as Telco is discriminating on the basis of gender." I posted the letter and forgot about it. Less than 10 days later, I received a telegram stating that I had to appear for an interview at Telco's Pune facility at the company's expense. I was taken aback by the telegram. My hostel mate told me I should use the opportunity to go to Pune free of cost and buy them the famous Pune saris for cheap! I collected Rs 30 each from everyone who wanted a sari. When I look back, I feel like laughing at the reasons for my going, but back then they seemed good enough to make the trip. It was my first visit to Pune and I immediately fell in love with the city. To this day it remains dear to me. I feel as much at home in Pune as I do in Hubli, my hometown. The place changed my life in so many ways. As directed, I went to Telco's Pimpri office for the interview. There were six people on the panel and I realised then that this was serious business. "This is the girl who wrote to JRD," I heard somebody whisper as soon as I entered the room. By then I knew for sure that I would not get the job. The realisation abolished all fear from my mind, so I was rather cool while the interview was being conducted. Even before the interview started, I reckoned the panel was biased, so I told them, rather impolitely, "I hope this is only a technical interview." They were taken aback by my rudeness, and even today I am ashamed about my attitude. The panel asked me technical questions and I answered all of them. Then an elderly gentleman with an affectionate voice told me, "Do you know why we said lady candidates need not apply? The reason is that we have never employed any ladies on the shop floor. This is not a co-ed college; this is a factory. When it comes to academics, you are a first ranker throughout. We appreciate that, but people like you should work in research laboratories." I was a young girl from small-town Hubli. My world had been a limited place. I did not know the ways of large corporate houses and their difficulties, so I answered, "But you must start somewhere, otherwise no woman will ever be able to work in your factories." Finally, after a long interview, I was told I had been successful. So this was what the future had in store for me. Never had I thought I would take up a job in Pune. I met a shy young man from Karnataka there, we became good friends and we got married. It was only after joining Telco that I realised who JRD was: the uncrowned king of Indian industry. Now I was scared, but I did not get to meet him till I was transferred to Bombay. One day I had to show some reports to Mr Moolgaokar, our chairman, who we all knew as SM. I was in his office on the first floor of Bombay House (the Tata headquarters) when, suddenly JRD walked in. That was the first time I saw "appro JRD". Appro means "our" in Gujarati. This was the affectionate term by which people at Bombay House called him. I was feeling very nervous, remembering my postcard episode. SM introduced me nicely, "Jeh (that's what his close associates called him), this young woman is an engineer and that too a postgraduate. She is the first woman to work on the Telco shop floor." JRD looked at me. I was praying he would not ask me any questions about my interview (or the postcard that preceded it). Thankfully, he didn't. Instead, he remarked. "It is nice that girls are getting into engineering in our country. By the way, what is your name?" "When I joined Telco I was Sudha Kulkarni, Sir," I replied. "Now I am Sudha Murthy." He smiled and kindly smile and started a discussion with SM. As for me, I almost ran out of the room. After that I used to see JRD on and off. He was the Tata Group chairman and I was merely an engineer. There was nothing that we had in common. I was in awe of him. One day I was waiting for Murthy, my husband, to pick me up after office hours. To my surprise I saw JRD standing next to me. I did not know how to react. Yet again I started worrying about that postcard. Looking back, I realise JRD had forgotten about it. It must have been a small incident for him, but not so for me. "Young lady, why are you here?" he asked. "Office time is over." I said, "Sir, I'm waiting for my husband to come and pick me up." JRD said, "It is getting dark and there's no one in the corridor. I'll wait with you till your husband comes." I was quite used to waiting for Murthy, but having JRD waiting alongside made me extremely uncomfortable. I was nervous. Out of the corner of my eye I looked at him. He wore a simple white pant and shirt. He was old, yet his face was glowing. There wasn't any air of superiority about him. I was thinking, "Look at this person. He is a chairman, a well-respected man in our country and he is waiting for the sake of an ordinary employee." Then I saw Murthy and I rushed out. JRD called and said, "Young lady, tell your husband never to make his wife wait again." In 1982 I had to resign from my job at Telco. I was reluctant to go, but I really did not have a choice.   I was coming down the steps of Bombay House after wrapping up my final settlement when I saw JRD coming up. He was absorbed in thought. I wanted to say goodbye to him, so I stopped. He saw me and paused. Gently, he said, "So what are you doing, Mrs Kulkarni?" (That was the way he always addressed me.) "Sir, I am leaving Telco." "Where are you going?" he asked. "Pune, Sir. My husband is starting a company called Infosysand I'm shifting to Pune." "Oh! And what will you do when you are successful." "Sir, I don't know whether we will be successful." "Never start with diffidence," he advised me. "Always start with confidence. When you are successful you must give back to society. Society gives us so much; we must reciprocate. I wish you all the best."   Then JRD continued walking up the stairs. I stood there for what seemed like a millennium. That was the last time I saw him alive. Many years later I met Ratan Tata in the same Bombay House, occupying the chair JRD once did. I told him of my many sweet memories of working with Telco. Later, he wrote to me, "It was nice hearing about Jeh from you. The sad part is that he's not alive to see you today."   I consider JRD a great man because, despite being an extremely busy person, he valued one postcard written by a young girl seeking justice. He must have received thousands of letters everyday. He could have thrown mine away, but he didn't do that. He respected the intentions of that unknown girl, who had neither influence nor money, and gave her an opportunity in his company. He did not merely give her a job; he changed her life and mindset forever.   Close to 50 per cent of the students in today's engineering colleges are girls. And there are women on the shop floor in many industry segments. I see these changes and I think of JRD. If at all time stops and asks me what I want from life, I would say I wish JRD were alive today to see how the company we started has grown. He would have enjoyed it wholeheartedly. My love and respect for the House of Tata remains undiminished by the passage of time. I always looked up to JRD.   I saw him as a role model for his simplicity, his generosity, his kindness and the care he took of his employees. Those blue eyes always reminded me of the sky; they had the same vastness and magnificence.   
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today i have recieved a mail from a friend and i wish u read this:    These are the personal views of  Mr.Subroto Bagchi , Chief Operating Officer, MindTree Consulting
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      All expansion is life and all contraction is death...By Swami vivekananda. IMPOSSIBLE: I M Possible, during my interview with Mr. Mubarak Ibrahim for Sudan office. Follow the instincts of nature....Neha. A song "a malik tere bandey hum aise hoon humare karam, naki per chalen aur badin se talen, tanki haste hua nikle dum". As i cannot reason out whether one gets a chance to live another life, so i must try doing what i aspire to do, in this life itself.  Thinking beyond boundaries.... I know that you will become a succesfull chartered accountant...Mom Follow your heart....Vishal bansal destiny can be changed....Mr.Gurmeet Uberai don't care about others work, just do ur work...Mr. Deepak Menon inspiring songs....from akshay's music collection move ahead...papa Balbir's punchline: we have come from outside. Balbir often refers it as a anectode to success, as he says when a person leaves his home and moves to another place than he is more focussed.  
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It is a strange coincidence that whenever i try to frame my foot towards legal profession, i get some surprises from chartered accountancy profession.  To be more precise, on July 13th 2003 i was attending a seminar on Indian taxation laws in Chandigarh. It was organized by AIFTP, a premier association of tax practicionals in India.  I was attending that seminar, with an intention to join legal profession and i intended to come up with some law firms where i can begin my legal profession.   But on that very day CA May 2003 results came out and i scored 23rd rank in India. And here came the diversion.....  Finally i joined Irevna equity research in Chennai... But still i felt something missing in the job.....  Some took it as if i was feeling home sick, very little thought that i am not satisfied with the job.... And i replied what other person intended to hear... But the truth is that in the core of my heart i felt that it was not the right time to get into equity research. i thought that research is more serious a business, than most people think it to be....and it really needs more experience And i thought it to be a concluding stage of a professional's life rather than to be an entry-level position...  And i finally gave up the job, with an intention to practice the CA profession...  i aspired to do the high quality work..... But i found no hope, working with my uncle or friend in his business can not land me in that work profile.... Neither practicing in Abohar, on my own could be a source of satisfaction...  So here comes the temptation.... i could see law as a profession which could give me that high profile work and indeed it gave me an opportunity...  Today as i entered Supreme court of India, i was thinking towards giving up CA certificate of practice and taking up membership of bar council of India.. i was looking forward for an opportunity in taxation laws... My mobile was switched off but someone was trying to inform me that i have been selected for Ernst and young (Muscat) And any guess? Like July 13th 2003, this time also the call was routed through my parents... Last time i was in tax seminar and this time i was in court no. 5 of Supreme Court of India   I am moving towards core field of chartered accountancy.  Keep track of this blog.... i plan to chart my life in public domain.... ur suggestions r cordially invited u may respond at: rvatrana@rediffmail.com    
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i hope things to settle down within a month and i may be in a position to find an appropriate direction for next 2-3 years.... or may be for a much longer period  and once this is settled, i shall begin my daily update on blogspot  luv retesh
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I saw the movie " In Hell " in Chennai. At that time i noted some dialogues, these are thought provoking and inspiring. May be this inspire you to see the movie.....  Today, while unloading the luggage i found that page. Here are the dialogues:  "Hate gives me strength, even when there is no hope. Tomorrow is the time it will make. Still hate gives me strength."  "We all have our own way of dealing, some choose to run other stay and fight."  "When you have taken your last step, when you can't go no more. You find that dark place, deep inside, forget the world you come from, embrace the world you are in."  "You think you win, when you been play there game you are lost, you lost self."  "Without evil we would never recognise good."  "Most of us know that there is a mask behind us. Sooner or later it shatters, than you really find the man you really are."  
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Silence speaks in volumes in friendship ..... these were the words, i read when i went with sood to meet Salil in his hostel at Madam Noyce secondary school for deaf in Delhi on august 1st 2004. Salil, i see him as a person who smiles amidst his hardships.. He can not hear or speak properly, but still i see the spark in his eyes... The spark to do something marvellous... Amidst his silence, i feel the strength and he is the one to whom i dedicate my friendship day  In the first part of the day, i meet maneesh and arvindan. We are going to join E&Y Muscat... begining of the adventure to world...
      
</post>


</Blog>