<Blog>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Have I posted this one already?  It's worth publishing again and again.  This was taken in front of my friend, Cara's, house. &nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    As many times as I have seen this picture, I've never noticed the slobber spot on the pillow until now.  That's kinda gross.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    I just have to laugh&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Matt and Evan at Evan's 6th birthday&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    We set the camera up on his trash can so we could get some pictures of ourselves. &nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Another awesome picture of Matt and Evan!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Gushy and in love&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Don't Go Into The Light!!!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Best Looking&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Why aren't they smiling?  Why so serious?&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    This is Matt at his Dad's wedding. When I first saw him in that tux, I nearly melted!  Could he be any more handsome?&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Evan's school picture 2004&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Evan and Dixie. This was taken as we were loading up the cars to leave NC to come back to Atlanta.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       &nbsp;I think that this pic was taken at my sister's reception.&nbsp; We&nbsp;had a bunch of disposable cameras for the guests to&nbsp;use, and I think that&nbsp;this came from&nbsp;one of those.&nbsp; I&nbsp;swear, every picture of these two is frame-worthy!&nbsp; I just love them!&nbsp; urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Matt and Me&nbsp; urlLink    We took this photo in January 2004 at Angela's birthday party. 
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink   So, I guess I have to start typing down here. OK. So be it.&nbsp; Now, this picture was taken in Foscoe,NC at my parents' mountain house on the weekend of my sister's wedding. We all had a blast, as Evan can attest. Matt and Evan&nbsp; urlLink    
      
</post>


<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I just don't get it.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    We could get arrested for this, I'm sure.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My puppy channel&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I heard  urlLink    this story     on NPR last week.&nbsp; I think a puppy channel is a great idea,&nbsp; although I don't even have to turn on the TV to get laughable dog antics in my house.&nbsp; I think it would kind of be like the weather channel, though.&nbsp; I turn on the weather channel, not so much for weather info, but I find it eerily soothing.&nbsp; This guy's idea was to have a channel that would make people happy.&nbsp; Puppies, he found, make people happy.     
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hi! It's Me!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    We were soldiers                                                My Dad is on the far right, and that is Lt. Col. Hal Moore in the middle.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is Dad, Mom, and I at my cousin, Caroline's, wedding Sept 2003     We were pretty exhausted&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Beth Geddes&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Dad, Aimee, and I starring in "That 70's Show"    I was the first trans-gender cast member&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    She really is a looker.  Good thing I fixed her, not that there was anything wrong with her.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This was Lucy at about 4 months old.  I think she was just realizing how photogenic she is.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Blair Griffin   "I'm so scared"&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is the best day EVER!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is the back of our house.  How is it that I don't have a picture of the front?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The ladies who brunch    Every Christmas, all us girls go to brunch at Truffles!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Somer, Beth, Aimee, Carol, and Lauren at the rehearsal&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Evan and Hunter    Evan was so "star-struck" by this soccer dude!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Evan's school picture 2004&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The boulder in front of the mountain house. Mom and Dad really like this rock!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The bride dancing with her father.  He's my father, too. That's Bill.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I stole this shot from the pro photog.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The McDowells&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Mom, Aimee, and I at the rehearsal. Valle Crucis is beautiful!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Matt and Evan&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My only professional photo shoot. Got my hair done for free!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why'd ya have to go and make things so complicated? ...Gettin' me frustrated!  Life's like this! I suppose boys have the same effect on her that computers have on me.  Web pages and Blogs will be the bane of my existence, so why do I keep coming back for more?
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink RHAPSODY Link 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink RHAPSODY Link 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink RHAPSODY Link 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink RHAPSODY Link 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Isn't She Lovely&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    2 cool dudes&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my boys&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>