<Blog>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As Father's day draws closer, I cant help but feel somewhat down but I feel even worse because my baby boy is in pain. Steven's father has been dead since before he ever got to know him, a car crash or something, I'm not really sure because he never talks about it. He usually comes over Sunday but I dont think he is...he just wants to sit in his room for that day. I dont blame him and I know what some of his pain feels like. I sometimes think mine is worse because I knew my daddy and I was SO close to him and then he abandons me last year at 14. It's hard to cope. Yet, I couldnt imagine what Steven must feel like...and I bet he would kill to have had even a minute of what I had. I'm not going to calm him by telling him I know what it feels like because number one, I dont because my father is still alive, and number two, I always hated it when people said it to me. Father's day is coming...I wish it didnt exist...but I also wish Steven was here. I cant expect him to help ME with my issues with my father because at least I can tell him, and I could touch my father if I wanted to...but he cant, his is dead...so I wish he wouldnt spend it alone...but I dont know.
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I feel SEXY SEXA, he he he, I dont exactly know why, but I feel this way and it feels great. My boyfriend makes me feel this way, *sigh* great...great day. I'm sorta disappointed in Lisa for fucking some 21 year old and telling the boy she was 17, but I dont really give a S*H*I*T. Oh besides that life is a big a chips. Oh and it's Jazz's birthday, ya'll. SO HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO HER! *sigh* not much else to say except it's a pretty good day       Disorder      Rating        urlLink Paranoid :    High       urlLink Schizoid :    Moderate       urlLink Schizotypal :    Very High       urlLink Antisocial :    High       urlLink Borderline :    Very High       urlLink Histrionic :    Very High       urlLink Narcissistic :    Very High       urlLink Avoidant :    High       urlLink Dependent :    Very High       urlLink Obsessive-Compulsive :    High       --  urlLink Personality Disorder Test - Take It!  --      
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I enter into a new chapter of my life, I decided to write down my experiences on the internet. I'm fifteen, I'm not a virgin, and no, I am defintely not a slut. I gave my "innocence" ( Or what I had of it) to my boyfriend of a lil' over 9 months ( at the time it was 7 1/2). I lost my virginity (Sexual intercourse)on May 2nd ,2004. I do not regret it and even through I lost it on my couch, I wouldnt change it for the world. My feelings for Steven are more than love as of now. I feel complete, whole, and alive. I do have "wandering" eyes and wonder how it might feel with...maybe a different guy, but for now, I've remained faithful. I hope to continue to be. I love him and I want to marry him, and althrough I'm only 15 ( 16 on Dec. 3rd) I know what I want, and I believe I obtain the maturity to mold my future wisely. I'm still just a teenager and I realize for the most part that Steven and I wont be together for all of our lives, but I do  believe  that if we split paths in life, somehow we will end up with each other in marriage. I love him, and he's helped me through alot. He helped me realized that all men arent like my father and not every single human that has a penis will abandon me when I love him. I thank him for that. Even if we break up, I wont ever say that I regret having sex with him, because for me it wasnt SEX...to me it was making love and giving him everything I am for us to connect. If we do split, I'll still know that at least THEN we were in love. I'll always love him no matter what I do, or he does. We're human, we F*U*C*K up, it happens, but forgiveness is not my strong point. As for the rest of my life, my dad abandoned me at the age of fourteen, but it didnt start that way. *sigh* Looking back, I was such a "Daddy's girl", I loved him completely and felt safe when I was with my father ( which is one of the things I love about Steven). Then my father got stationed at Killen and we didnt want to move ,and the commute was too far to come home every day, so instead he got an apartment there with one of his co-workers named Frank ( very nice man with a family basically in the same situation as my father..commute too long and such), and they shared the rent. My father came home every weekend after work, and this worked out for a year. It was straining, but at least I had time with him.*sigh* After that, he was sent to Utah, and my mother refused to move because of the case of young girls being kidnapped, raped, or taken by Mormons, so my father tried hard to get a different place. *sigh* Looking back, I wished we just moved to Utah. I would've gotten over moving away from everything. (sorry, I'm crying)*sigh* Anyways, then he found a job that was okay. Since he was bi-lingual, he was able to go to a remote location for a year ( remote meaning he cant take his family there)...we thought why not, it's just a year and he could visit. Honduras was the place. *crying* I hate that place..I really hate it.  *sigh* Anyways, we went the airport on Feb. 17,2003. We cried so much. I wish I wouldnt have let him on the plane...I REALLY wish that day was completely erased out of time. Well, once he got there..things were okay. He called every now and then, but then...after like a month or two, he didnt call...or if he did he was drunk off his ass ( and my father never drank) and then he went clubbing and partying ( and my dad was usually the type of person you see standing in a corner at a party that FORCED to go to)...then he only called to fight with my mom. My First Day of my first YEAR of highschool...everyone called to asks how it went. Except my father. Oh, he showed up on the phone drunk about 2-3 weeks after that, but he never called for me. I felt torn..I felt like my dad wasnt talking to me because I was bad, or not good enough or not worthy...whatever the case. I felt horriable. I loved my father, I had the best relationship in the WHOLE world with my daddy. I loved my daddy! and here he was...not talking to me. I told my mom, and she had me call him. It took a couple weeks to get ahold of him...b/c he wasnt in his room...at 3 A.M. When I did get to talk to him, I cried...I couldnt do anything except cry and tell him that I missed him and I thought he didnt love me..and I cried. ( i dont cry about things..but I couldnt help it). He said he'd start paying attention to me, that lasted all of the entire 2 days! Finally in early Sept of 2004, I had enough and since he closed all the doors of communication to me, I finally walking across the river and burned the bridge. Later on Sept 24th, I got with my current boyfriend Steven. A day later, I think, my mom got a phone call from a lady( I wont ever call her that after this) in Honduras tell my mother to divorce my father because she was a "Christian women" and it didnt look nice for her to be with a married man, also that my father had a house there with her( which isnt allowed by the Army base to have a house outside because it's a remote location) where HE provided for her and her child ( not my father's). My mom was a wreak obviously. My world shattered and burned beneath me. I learned more of Honduras, and I learned that surrounding the base of where my father was at was whores...and lots of them. The are called something in spanish that when you translate it to English it's basically means "the Spiders". they are named this because when the base doesnt allow their gates to be swung open to the many whores, they climg the walls like spiders to get in. What a classy whore my father has. The base knows what's going on..but no one does anything. NO ONE! It pisses me off. Well, alot of time has passed. Here's a flash-forward. My father came in March, shut down our cable,light, water, and stole alot of money from my mother's account. lovely huh? And then after he was safely back in HOnduras, my mother was served with a divorce paper. It all comes out to her at one time. My poor mom, but she stood her ground. She got a great lawyer, and then went to court June 11 2004 for the divorce. My father's lawyer wanted to leave my mom with barely enough money to pay the house, the car, and feed herself ( let alone feed me), and on top of that...the lawyer wanted to force my mom to pay HALF of my dad's debts (which 93% was spent on the whore). Luckily, My mom once again stood her ground. My mom's lawyer broke my father in two and now he barely has enough to feed himself...guess his whore will have to work overtime. My parents finalized the divorce that day. I'm happy but sad that the man I used to call Daddy is dead and the man that stands before everyone trashing my daddy's reputation is a pile shit that God will make sure gets what he deserves. My Daddy died Feb. 17th 2003. It's sad, but it's true. That is pretty much my life right now. My life in a (long) nutshell Real blue stays true Peace!
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is no point to be angry at Steven for not calling me until late/ or early as the case is...knowing I can only talk for 10-15 min. max.  I left messages as he told me to call an hour later, and if he wasnt there to call 30 min. after that. I left him messages. And then called again at 10:00 and 10:30. And he calls at 1:40am? Whatever. I dont care, no point to be upset, it doesnt matter. If he wants to talk, he'll call me. If not, he wont. I'll get over it. *sigh* Life's a bitch.
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It may be my jealousy, my father, or my hormones but something is making me have weird dreams concerning Steven. I can't remember it well, but I see a pretty girl who is short, black hair, nice tan skin, and just REAL pretty ( she kinda looks bitchy too). Anyway, she tells me " What he thinks you don't know, will hurt you....But what you truly don't know, will agonize you." And then I see a picture of Steven and me laughing, and then a  quick flash and then I'm on the ground crying....just fully crying my eyes out. Then I hear a guy's voice "I'm Sorry, forgive me, please?" And I scream. It's not an answer, it's just like a LONG scream as if I'm in pain. Then I wake up. I dont remember anything else. I dont even know if it's about Steven. But I know I woke up around 3 or 4am and couldnt go back to sleep 'til later on. I didnt wake up today 'til 6:07 P.M. I dont know but I feel kinda down. Maybe my rags about to start. Oh well. Stupid teenage emotions.
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Steven saw his ex-girlfriend Bianca, and I’m cool with them talking and shit, that I don’t care about.  Yeah, it worries me that Bianca is pretty much to Steven what Chris Pelkey was to me. My first love was Chris, and Steven’s was Bianca, only thing was Chris and I never took our relationship to a sexual place…while Steven and Bianca did. And yeah, that does bug the SHIT outta me to be honest but I cant be mad him ( well, at least with it making sense) for his past because I understand at the time he loved her ( ouch, that really hurts me...but oh well). *sigh* Okay, anyways this bit…um I mean girl is calling Steven everyday, and I’m like “what the fuck bitch, you know” but um, it’s not like I can help it or it’s not like it doesn’t make sense. I have a hella good reason. I would be mad if ANY girl called Steven everyday, and I guess it sorta adds to the anger when it’s his ex….not to mention his ex-love. The only other girl he fucked without a condom except me…so yeah I’m pissed.  And I’m not stupid no girl calls a guy everyday if they don’t like him and today…Steven found out it bugs me…what he doesn’t know is it pisses me off greatly and honestly if  knew the bit…um girl…it wouldn’t be pretty.  I…no, I hate anyone trying to take my guy...fuck that…I hate it when girls tried to take away my ex-boyfriends and I didn’t give a shit about those guys…so imagine Steven. Some chick trying to take my love who I’ve been in a relationship with for 9 months, trust him with my life, heart, body, I gave him my virginity, and who I know I wanna marry? Aw Hell Naw, fuck that shit up the ass. And Well…Of course Bianca called today and said some shit like “I have feelings for you” ( I say…”like duh!) and well Steven told me he told her they couldn’t talk anymore….( I don’t know if it’s true...but I cant do anything about it ‘cept trust him…so I guess that’s what I gotta do).  Well, whatever…I’m just saying…This shit pisses me off…and ooooh, god, if I knew what her last name was……it’d be sweet, but I gotta chill down, you know? I cant go…pulling favors for some dumb shit and some dumb reason…so I aint about at pull some shit over it. According to Steven, he don’t have feelings for her…I sense bull….because once you love someone…you cant forget. I loved Chris Pelkey, and damn, I know I still do, but I learned a long time ago…that…it’d never work out. So I don’t know I guess I’ll have to trust Steven…and the rest….welll….whatever. All I’m saying…is…this shit aint cool..so yeah.. .. I’m not cool with it at all..I think it’s some stupid bitch ass hoe shit *sigh* but then again I’m just pissed. I got a short temper, I think I’m bout to be on  my rag, and on top of that all….I’m Puerto Rican…so..yeah…aint a good time for this. Whatever….this shit is dumb. 
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Steven and I are fine, great. I feel gross and think I am have disordered eating...I dont like it. I mean I do wish I was thinnner...but still. Yeah not much time to write...I'll be writing later.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I Hate the G*ddamn WORLD! I havent been able to talk to Steven for more than 10 min at a time and no more than 15 min. in one day for this whole week. He's only called me like 3 fricking time this damn week. And tomarrow the day I was gonna spend with him chilling upstairs my mom's best friend from when she was 10 is coming. 2 adults. And 5 gotdamn children. I wont get any time to talk to Steven. What the hell's the point? I hate this gotdamn week! To make matters worse I saw A little princess...that movie made me cry when I did have a father that I loved, and it mad me think how bad I would feel if I lost him. Now I have. AND thanks to the TV...I have opened a wound. thatnk you..FOX FAMILY. GOD I HATE HATE HATE HATE this week!!!
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Weird-o-rama!Froggie came over today. It was cool, and it was nice to be chilling with him, but…I don’t know. I really like him but….I don’t know. I mean he seemed kinda nervous and I don’t know why. And I don’t think he was trying to, but he was like real speedy like  I don’t care take off my shirt, I like what I look like and I‘m comfortable with it, but I don’t know…it didn’t really feel like that should have gone down today. You know? *sigh* As for the kiss, um….I don’t know. A kiss isn’t fast and I didn’t really mind that, but once again he seemed nervous or too quick about it. It’s a kiss not a race. But it was cool chilling with him…lol. Although I think I should keep my shirt on next time. As for my babe, I still love him and all, but you can not blame me for getting a little bored after so long! I really like Froggie, he’s a cool friend, and nice, but I dunno…it sort of felt weird. I’m not sure how to explain it. Plus, I don’t even know what this means between us...you know? Like  does it mean he likes me?Or does it mean that he wants...like..I don’t know a relationship ( I doubt THAT’S gonna happen b/c I aint dumping my Steven yet. I aint ready to…)Does it mean he just wants to keep it on the Down low and mess around ( which is totally fine with me and all) I still like chilling with him tho.  It’s just all. I dunoo man So I dunno. Time shall tell, huh? Lol. Okay… Peace.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh* I need to vent. Okay, here it goes. I love my babe ( Steven Perricone) very much, but ( I know...I hate the “but” too..) I’ve been with him so long, and I feel safe with him. I mean safe isn’t bad, but I’m TATIANA, I’m the girl who always goes after the hard to get bad boy rebel and I usually win but I don’t actually get a relationship out of it. *sigh* Yey? I won? I got exactly what I wanted, and I feel good. Just kind of safe and boring.  I mean I feel bad because he always talks about marriage, and love and stuff. I’m not ready for marriage…I love him….I don’t want kids until like 26...and he also doesn’t really understand my need for letting go.( example: He doesn’t want to let me go away from him. Like College, THAT is what he’s scared of. Of losing me. And I need a breather) I love him. Seriously.  I lost my virginity to him, he’s the first GUY I actually gave oral sex to {I’ve been told I’m “outstanding“} ( well…willing oral sex. Long story short. I was real drunk, gun to my head…yada..yada. Didn’t remember for a while), and he was the first guy to see ME. Not just how I looked, but ME. I love him so much and I don’t want to hurt him. And if he even felt half of the way I do, I’d be crushed. Completely. *sigh* That’s half the story. I’ve known another guy since a while but I actually liked him in 8th grade, and a little this year. I don’t love him, but I do really like him. I like chilling with him, even if he does say I’m boring. He’s my little Froggie, I would actually die if he read this, but I doubt he will. So it’s cool beans. I mean I hung out with him today, it was nice, it was also werid because I kinda wanted to kiss him ( I didn’t. Kinda regret it…but whatever). I mean this guy has something my boyfriend doesn’t….I can actually chill with him without having to think about sex, drugs ( as fun as those may be) , or how “uncomfortable” I am. Actually I don’t think I wanna have sex with him, but I really like him. For real. He’s a genuinely nice person to me but I don’t usually have a relationship with nice people…since they tend to make me lose interest pretty fast…and usually end up hating me afterwards . And I don’t want things to ever get too weird between my Froggie and me because…I like him and because we live close. *ppffft/sigh* It doesn’t really matter much about what my feelings are anyways( as if they ever did)…because nothing can happen between my Froggie and me while Steven and I are going out. I guess it’s okay with me because although I do like Froggie a lot, I don’t think a relationship would actually work out. Hell, I doubt even a secret relationship would work out...for 2 main reasons and a bunch of other details.. 1. I don’t think he likes me that way anyways( most guys in this neighborhood don’t.. …2. Even if he does like me that way, I doubt he’ll want to like make-out and mess around my boyfriend’s back and even if he‘s okay with it...somehow he’d tell or something and it’d get back to Steven and well…it’d be hell. I cant do that. Yeah, so I guess I’ll try to leave things the way they are now unless something new happens…or...I dunno. Time will tell. Thing will chill out… PEACE!
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jhame, froggie's brother is dead. mSteven and I are improving....I tolod him I was bored...and he's working on the realtionship with me. And I'm trying to as well. School's about to start and I'm on my rag, my eyes are burning from using my contacts too long. I feel bad for froggie and will pray for his family. I'm blind...sorry I cant type well. love you and bye 
    
</post>


</Blog>