<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It turns out that Hotmail has given news that they will increase user's inbox space to 250mb. This comes after the move of Google's Gmail and Yahoo's email service both at 1000mb and 100mb respectively. Email will never be the same. And who comes out winner? Us the consumers :)
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The blogger that I use records the time as pacific time since the company that it belongs to (Google) is located somewhere where there is pacific time. So NO I did not wake up at 6 to publish my thoughts. Ok goodnight for now.... it is not 8pm its 11pm so dont ask me why I go to sleep so early. 
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With the great increase in gas prices and my lack of a "real" job. I would like to ask for all of you to please send me some gas money. The truth is I will not be able to drive my car in a while and how will I be getting from place to place??? I will have to walk there!!! or use my brother's scooter which is pretty gay :P  . To send money email me chinomora@msn.com or send me money through paypal to the same email ^^. Thank you to all who send money and to those who dont, I wish you go to hell and burn!!! :)
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woot Woot! Google/Gmail has sent me 5 more invitations to use their service if anyone wants one contact me at chinomora@gmail.com or yim: lvlr_chino :)
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to the gym, and I have been going this whole week. My body is kinda sore but with luck I can look like the hulk when school starts.  ;P
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Gmail   This kind of email is the shit. I got an invite from a friend and I'm currently giving two invites for the beta service. Get your gmail account before anyone else :) 
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Damn I hate pop-ups with a passion. If you guys out there have too many pop-ups the best thing out there is to install the google toolbar and enable the popup blocker and to run spybot to get rid of all the adware. Good luck with your popups ;)
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yahoo has really stepped up in the internet world. They have increased their email capacity from a measly 4mb to 100mb. They are trying to compete with gmail from google which gives users 1000mb=1gb of space. Hotmail however has fallen back, still offering just 2mb forfree accounts. I for one thank yahoo and gmail for the additional space because I always hated the hotmail account saying warning you are reaching your inbox limit when i barely had like 20 email. With yahoo and gmail, internet will be much better off. =)
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   This is a lg where you play yahoo pool for bux. I play when ever im bored (like now). Hopefully I win. :P
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello to anyone reading this. This is my new blogger and Im going to try to blog as much as I can. (For no purpose really) But thats ok :)
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whats up!!!! Look im writting in it!!!!! :P
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Or at least some gas money. And by the way my car does not need $20 to fill up it just needs $16 because its fuel effiency is much better than any green 2 door chevrolet something that noone has even heard about. :P oh and abel is gay :P 
    
</post>


</Blog>