<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ---------------Sup Kids-------------------------------- So, a new week. i haven't made anew post in two weeks, and i was about topost one about the trade between HOU and ORL, but eh. Afer Stevie met magic management, my post would've made me look completely foolish. Or just exemplify it. Anyways, On with the Program!!!!! ----------Welcome to the H.R., B****------------------- This year, the mayor of my fine hometown of Chesapeake, Va-William E.Ward (or is that homeowner guy?)-is retiring, after a decade and a half of service (not coincidentally, i was born around the time he started). This means that an "election" will be held at many  schools, tax-exemption buildings called churches, and random peoples' garages and carports. So it is, but i do wish one thing upon the election: do not follow the steps of knoxville, tn. Last november, there was an election,in about the same circumstance in k-town, with long-time headman Victor Ashe (now the US Ambassador to Poland-TRUE!) retiring, to go to Poland. A lot. anyways, the election wound down to two front-runners: the conservative Bill haslam(President of Midwestern gas-sation giant Pilot)and the liberal-leading Madeline Rogero. (there is no party-affiliation allowed). It's not that a conservative is a bad thing, but the Pilot Oil Company iIS based on Knoxville. Which means that people here vote like people in California-with fear. CA-they vote for the Terminator (yeah Jadakiss, why did they let the Terminator win the election? Fear. and no info.) b/c  they don't know who to vote for and waiters-i mean actors/hollywood run the state. even in fresno. and here, they vote for the guy because he runs an oil company! also, if you guess the banner on july 6 on my blog's frontpage, i'll write about your topic. submit your entries in the comments section!
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      right now it's just june 18th, and it's gonna be a june 19th soon. Not really gonna post on and on, cuz it's late , and i just don't feel like adding on. Just this: In the land that is Hollywood, some things erupted, i guess. 1)P-Jax is no longer coach of the LAL. eh. 2)Kobe8LAL is now Kobe8FA. and 3) shaq wants a trade. More tommorow.
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ---------------------Sup Kids?------------------------- Ok, the other day i wrote a really sketchy post about the lakers losing as opposed to the Pistons winning. My arch-rival/friend KevMart disagrees. Maybe he'll write a guest column. Maybe not! It's just that he thinks he has it all and whatnot. I'll post it, completely unedited. whenever. Time to get on to the Bias part, kids. A little politics, a litte football HOF. ---------------------Bias------------------------------    I'm going to start this out with a little political observation, kids. My observation is this: Swing voters don't vote on issues. They vote on popularity-well, duh. My point is that no real prsident has been elected since Eisenhower (and that may be a stretch). Analysis: Dwight Eisenhower was voted on for a little think called the invasion of normandy, and people seemed to be caught up in the postwar effort, so they picked a guy they could say, "Hey! He was in WWII! Let's take him!". yeah. Then, JFK. JFKennedy was voted on b/c he happened to present himself for the firts televised debate. LBJ-TX, he succeded JFKennedy, of course, and just kept the wave. Nixon was voted on b.c 1)LBJ-TX didn't run, and 2)the sad event of Vietnam. Carter was elected b/c he wasn't Nixgate. Reagan was voted for b/c he wasn't Carter, re-voted b/c Mobdale, was well, short. GHWB, VPs usually are elected anyways. Clinton:he wasn't a continuation of the Reagan ideal. and Bob dole, was well, old. Gangsta Dub:he wasn't Clinton, he didn't have a history of Scandal. This year, it looks like JFKerry will be picked b/c he's not Gangsta Dub. But it'll be close. Now, time for football.       Year after year, some NFL vets/execs vote in football greats for the Pro Footbal Hall of Fame in Canton, Ohio. But you knew that. First, a fact that might surprise you. Year after year (again, i know), Jerome Bettis continues to surprise myself and the football world with the fact that he is 6th all time in yards. I think this is surprising, since he isn't the fastest guy around, and seems to be  justa short-yardage guy. But top 10? who knew. My second complaint is that Art Monk (WAS) isn't in the HOF. u're thinking he's a skins fan! No, i'm a dolphins guy, but good play deserves to be respected. Art Monk is 5th in Receptions, and 9th in reception yards, yet no1 votes him in, but they vote in execs no1s heard of. great. -------------------Bagels------------------------------    Nothing much, just that Dodgeball opens 2morrow. watch it!. Guest columns, please.
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        In Memoriam    First, I'm going to keep this short. Right now I wopuld just like to say that this blog was a response, sort of, to the death to the late great Ralph Wiley. Much props to Wiley. Much props.  ------------------------------------------------------         Basketball   Woo-hoo! Woo frickin' hoo! The Dee-troi Pistons won the NBA Title! The two people who make out beautifully (get minds out of gutter) in this situation are 1) Pistons owner Bill Davidson, who has won 3 titles in the last years, as in owner:The WNBA Detroit Shock (eh), The Tampa Bay Lightning (In florida-Lewis Black on the daily show said it best: They won the cup ina state with no natural ice!...The French Connection i guess, are supposed to be the next Sakic/Forsberg|Yzerman/Shanahan.No hockey next year. ), and the creme de la creme [or whatever]the Dee-troit Pistons, winning the First Title for the NBA's Eastern Conference since MJ/Pippen's Bulls. Anyways, time to break this dawwn. Kind of.     1.MVP:They've said it everywhere (I,Max, ATH, PTI)..this guy exemplifies team play...the MVP needs to go to every player, etc. I say Chauncey Billups deserves it b/c he made that crazy lay down-in the air-and hit it-OT forcing 3 in the East semi-finals. And he's that good, when he know his position.     2.Darko:Darko has more NBA championships than LBJ23, Melo, and Wade combined. Ha.     3.Leastern Conference:With the balance of power shifting to the East thanx to the Pistons, The East will no longer be so miserable. Here are some reasons: 1. NJ:Not that bad of a team, just needs a big guy. 2. CLE:With prodigy LBJ23, they can be grest. They just needa true PG, we all know this. And i say Z can be a good big man. 3. DET:They aren't that old, and the Lakers look like they're heading for  '98 Bulls-like Breakup, starting with P-Jax. 4.MIA:a reformed Odom, underrated 'Melo, Caron, and street ball legend Skip to My Lou (rafer alston). 5. OrL:Maybe...if they keep T-Mac, get a coach, and draft Okafor.         4.quick history:since the 2-3-2 format was instituted in '85, DET is the first team to win the middle 3 games. But you knew that.         5. Quote from the game: D.Fisher-"They just wanted it more". Thanks for the cliche, .4 Do we really need the cliche, .4? Huh?         6.P-Jax: Did you see P-Jax's kids at the Press Conference? They were all matched wih the clothes...and all looked like they were in the basement,not having jobs. Hope kids are cool with Pops dating a former pinup. JW.That was very good writing was it? No.  His quote on coaching next year for the LAL: "I'd say there's a pretty slim chance of me returning". OK. go to Alaska again...cuz this is what i see happening (though it's a longshot): MJ-CHI buys a team , and then hires P-Jax as coach of that team. other stuff naw.          Bias   Knoxville,TN isn't a college town. It's the town of the UofTN football team. If they actually cared about the UofTn it would be hi-larious! But that's not going to happen. Luckily, I'm going to be going back to where I;m from--Chesapeake,Va. Some things:Va is a commonwealth not a state, it'sa city near VA Beach (home of the Neptunes production team/N.E.R.D.), and it's not neccesarily the 'South". South of washington? yeah. But so is Delaware and a large portion of Maryland. Ok? great.              Bagels   Quote of the Week:"If you go to a house of Worship, you are more likely to vote Republican. In other news, the more you go to the International House of Pancakes, the more likely you are to eat syrup."-Stephen Colbert, The Daily Show.   urlLink  -Justa link to a news site.                 Later This Week      Look out for a guest columnist.
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First off, i'd like to say hello to everyone who is reading this atempt at anger management through verbal execution through the execution of electronic prose. Ah, technology. while I acknoweldge that the wealth of people that will be reading this are aqauintances/friends/rivals/enemies/trust-fund conservatives (Yes! they do exist!)/penguin obsessers, i urge you to forward the link....http://scamelo.blogspot.com...if you find any of this desirable or high quality reading. First off, the title: Bias-has nothing to do with the unfortunate Len Bias , the great basketball player for te Terps of UMd in the mid-80s, but NBA/NHL/MLB/NFL/Xtreme ping-pong bias. Second, Bagels aren't really part of this equation, they're simply a hopeful use for alliteration. Thrid...basketball is interchangeable with:Xbox, football, soccer, baseball, new hollywood fad dodgeball, ice cream, my romantical ineptitude, oscure collectible toys made only in the state of Nevada, and pop art criticism. just kidding about the pop art.                 Basketball            IMO, the NBA (David Stern, particularly) hasa fixation with the Lakers. Then again, this the opinion of many people who consider themselves sports pundits or a variation of that. But it's not the fact that the Lakers don't have their reasons for popularity or reasons to drive up last years dismal ratings:they have first name recognition:Phil(!), Kobe, Shaq/thebigAristotle/diesel, Gp/Glove, Mailman, Medvedenko. But their counterparts in the Finals(DET)also have first name recognition:Rip, Tayshaun, Big Ben, Darko(!), Rasheed-or as he's been known, Tech. But the Lakers have had everything...more tomorrow.
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      -------------------Sup Kids----------------------------  It's a new month, which means, i'm still angry/angst-ridden. Whichever you prefer. But since it's July, that means where smack-dab in the middle of baseball season, and the good news is that the tribe and the mets have an actual chance of winning their divisions! Not the tribe, so much, because their top 3 starters: 1)CC Sabathia 2)Cliff Lee 3)Jared Westbrook....and the white so top 3: 1)Loaiza (still) 2)Buerhle (still) 3)Freddy "Look who got fleeced because miguel olivo needs surgery and he's on his 3rd team this season" Garcia. And the Twins aren't that bad either. go tribe. --------------------Movies. No reference here.--------- Want to know something? It's July 1 and i haven't seen spider-man 2 yet. how a geek must cringe within because they can not contribute to someone else's monetary gain! But please, if you read this, read my comments. Por Favor.  -------------------Bagels------------------------------It's July 4 this sunday, which means we get to celebrate the day our forefathers declared we wanted out of this colonization deal. Have Fun! ----------------Fantasy Baseball Update---------------- I've decided to post how I'm doing in each of my fantasy baseball leagues each, week, for no reason. Team        |   League   | Place|    Record Doc Ocs       M.L. Gondol    2       62-46-2  Chichester  |  da illest|    4       132-131-45  SEVA        |  Public   |    8  |    50-52-8 Only Major League Gondol Ball really matters to me, because i have "friendz , kid" in that league. -------------Until------------------------------------- Next Time, I'm Scamel, and i'm outta this piece kidz.
    
</post>


</Blog>