<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi once again,just came back frm "so calles holiday".This holiday was the worst.Everyday i am always at the hospital seeing my mothers brother.Oh yeah forgot to say where i went.I to malaysia for a staff trip.Actually i am not supposed to go at all.It was beacuse 1 of my teachers grandma passed away so she cannot go.So they ask me to go.I didn't want to go.They forced me.So i had to go.Malaysia is such a boring place where i have been wen i was young.Going there for me was like nothing.Somemore went with the staff.Teachers i know wen i young 2.Every where i go they spy on me.No peace.Go by bus come back by cruise.So tiring.Came back yesterday.But at least i saw my long lasting friend.It was my principal daughter.She still can remember me.We like frm young know each other.Cool.And now i am so stress up.July got so many events.SJAB enrolement night and St.John day.July got practice for NDP parading.Can die.3 or 4 hrs in hot sun.That is all i have to say 2day.Gtg now.  Bye
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once again hi.It is such a tiring day as i am so stress up,after doing my maths book.Almark is so difficult.Today my mom is coming back fom New York.It is so  worse for me.She comes the house will be a volcanic eruption.Every thing is tear a part.Lolx.Sigh.As you all know i am such a boring person.The weather is so hot and i am dying for thirst.My maid is so irritating.Now a days maids thing that they can rule our lifes.My maid order me to this and that.I can't stand her at all.Even i put music,she say off it.Really is irritant in my life.I for to tell you something.I went for my St.John camp.So boring.Get scolding for no reason at times.Wah loa that day need to do 100 push up.But they decided to do 50.But we did 30.If i am not mistaken.Than on camp night we have to put a item.Every group have to put.And my grp was not ready at all.All of them act like nerds.I can tell you.Everything i have to do.And my grp had to do singing.And my friends said that singing was the most easy.When it was our turn,my grp were so blur and looked like nerds.It was the worst camp night for me.but i dunno about the rest.Than every grp have to do patroling.So tiring.We slept on benches.My backbone was gone wen i came home.But about this camp i learnt something.Being together is always better in life.The most thing i like about this camp is the trust walk.We had to hold other pple hands.And we were blind folded.I was so exhausted after that walk.  That is all i have to say for today. Gtg,Bye 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello my name is Sumitra.Pple call me Sunny.Now i am going to intruduce myself.I am funny at times.Or hot temperped.Nv see my hot temperted mood.Sometimes i am very boring.I luv to Play Tennis,Watch Tv,Go Out With My Friends.Sometimes i like to be stay free and easy.Some times i am be a irritant to everybody around me.Even my dog.But i like to act cool.For me life is interesting at times.Sometimes boring as usual.I laze around like some kind of mad dog roaming the steets.Just kidding.Some am some kind of kid that luv to laugh like hell if there is no joke.I luv to travel around the world.If i am bored i gloo my eyes on the tv.1 time i did it.It was about 6h+.Lolx.That is all i have to say about me.  Gtg go now. My email is, (sumitra47@hotmail.com)or (sumitra_sivalinagm@yahoo.com)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is so pathertic.2mmrow is SJAB day.Freak.I just hate it alot.Got that Stupid marching to do.Than there is that irritaing NDP.Also must do marching.And i am not good in it at all.But they say that they would re select if we dont to properly.So i am not going to do properly.Now a days,i am so srress up.Got alot of HW.1st week of skul already got hw from my new maths teacher.Almark can die.My brain is like going to burst any minute.GTg now.  BYE
     

    
</post>


</Blog>