<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i guess it's that time again, boys and girls! school! woohoo! well, not really, school f*cks big time, and in addition to all those teachers who love guai-lan-ing me, i suppose i'm in for a whole load of bullshit. so what's a guy to do on the few days before school starts? get drunk and high i suppose. probably at east coast or pasir ris i suppose... hopefully i don't get too high and kill someone, or like rob some hawker.seriously speaking, the holidays have -sucked-. going to school for the first two weeks, going to 2 functions,spending the rest of my time watching fushigi yuugi (actually it pretty much rocks, thanks to genrou) and getting acquainted with merry (2nd album out next month i think...) it's been pretty much of a bore. ah well, at least i managed to flirt with some girls, given that i'm a a perpetual babe repellent, but life's a bitch, you win some and you lose some, so i suppose life and i are quits now. next time i blog, i suppose i'll be ranting about a run-in with the cops or something in the context of that. boo-yah! 
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           uh-huh... not once but twice today. firstly, the sin of hentai games. whoever designed/invented/came up with hentai games should be paid lots and lots of money to come up with one every month, or week, god forbid. since quitting smoking, nothing illegal has been this fun(well except vandalism, but that's a story for another day). And, may i add, while crappy european men took 3 1/2 hours to finish "Nocturnal Illusions", i(and i'm proud of it) took only 2 hours. am i good or what? i suppose i'll be searching and playing hentai games for the rest of the holiday then...       and the second sin, oh i should be shot for this.. NOT LISTENING TO MERRY. under the influence of bands such as despairs'ray, kagerou, kagrra and occasionally baroque, i ignored the true gem of them all - merry. merry's music style can't be described in words. are they ska? no. are they punk? no. are they heavy metal? no. are they all those plus many other genres all rolled into one. hell yeah. furthermore, they're from previously known indies bands like shiver, after effect and syndrome. why do i suddenly love merry so much? here are 5 reasons why YOU should like merry(and want to marry them if you're female) 1. They're f*ckin' talented. with gems such as tokyo telephone and t.o.p, you're sure to be headbangin away as if you're listening to diru's umbrella 2. They're fun lovin nonsensical bastards. gara having a hentai rating of 1000%? they're erotically grotesque? crazy assholes. 3.they're supported by diru and kiyoharu. damn. the almost biggest visual band of this generation supporting you? you know you're bombin! 4. neroisms! drummer nero, who's i think a bit crazy is freakin cool. his drum solos freakin rock like hell live. hear him and weep, you stinking linkin park faggots. 5.they're like baroque! the officially coolest oshare band in the world! only more perverted and dark! is that cool or what. can't be helped, especially since both bands had members spawned from after-effect and shiver. 
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn i've got nothing to bitch about. i guess i'll have to act like some dumb chick and bitch/rant/rave about how the new fashions are so fab or about how cute some humans are. or how some ass from blue's voice is wuuuundeeeerfuuuul.that really bites, like reality.(i feel like an idiot now that i've said that). or maybe i should post some dumb fanfic like how some i saw some member or some band make out with another member of another band of the same sex. how sick is that. women. tsk tsk. i'd rather watch videos of bill goldberg wrestling over and over and over again than read those productions of satan. damn i'm bored. maybe i'll do some album review or something. like review something by britney spears or some n'sync fag with toilet brush hair. well, at least i managed to bitch for eight lines plus... i suppose i'm done for today. by the way, today i found out from some poser that cali gari is "waaay cooler" and "more rawkin" than kagerou. how poserish is that. ciao.
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haven't slept for 4 days... according to medical books, i should be hallucinating by now, but i'm still sane. no images or forms of barney or the teletubbies floating around yet. hmm... yet. should i sleep? no. so what am i doing now? blogging. apparently 3/4 of singaporeans blog. sad to say, i've become one of them. the so-called "victim of conformity" ah well... might as well go with the flow. so apparently i should be blogging/ranting about my day. well, what did i do today?(as if you people want to know). I went jamming with a band, followed by a wonderful day at drama and then i went home to watch one piece over and over and over again. interesting eh... goddamn bloggers... hovever do they do it... i'll catch up someday. hmmm... someday.
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      blogging is downright gay.. and i've been forced to do it... why? don't ask. i'm not liking blogging very much now. harumph... maybe sooner or later...
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the world is rose colored for me now. just like how kirito sees it. today school finished early, at around 11 plus, after mass. before that was just geography lesson with the spinster. she kept going on and on and on about studying. i should have gone on and on and on about how if she didn't get mr right soon she'd be left on the shelf. then later after school went to eat chicken rice. bloody nice food and the people there also damn friendly. eat already then walked all the way to serangoon mrt with paul, aloy and lionel. then walked back to wee lee to jam. felt stupid because we didn't really play any complete songs. however we did get in a few drums solos and my tearful rendition of "accidentally in love" with my pro guitaring and crappy singing. ah love. it's a many splendored thing, or so they say. now i've turned mushy, but who cares anyway. not drey. heehee. came back home and talked to her till she had to go for british council( i could never see the point in british council ). then went to century square to play percussion freaks. i love percussion freaks. then saw johnson, tua bui and zhu ping. never see them for so long liao, even johnson turned from squeaky voice-d to a more manly tone. people change alot, balls. then went home to talk to -HER- online. happiness! still talking to her now! happiness! tomorrow meeting her for breakfast/lunch/dunno? happiness. going now. no time for blogging. blogging is boring now that i have other important things to attend to. sayonara, suckers. 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah, f*ck you. stupid blogger. before this i posted an at least 3 page blog. then it didn't appear. what a f*cking waste of time. you is so-and-so. so-and-so is a bloody eunuch. i was really sick, and this time i didn't lie. what? you don't trust me? too bad. but hey, you know what? i AM a un-trustworthy sonofabitch. i lie, cheat and steal all the time( okay i don't steal ). and your stupid attitude pisses me off. you and your sarcastic remarks. so i need a haircut? don't make me answer questions to which the answers you know already. and i can't answer you because it would be an act of defiance and it would provide you with another round of ammunition to bitch at me with. you know what? i think i need something more important than a haircut. i need a&nbsp;.44 caliber bringer of happiness and love. thank god i don't, or else i would pump you so full of lead-y happiness that you would cry. in happiness? no. in pain. in bleeding, suffering pain. ah... suffering. suffering my long-lost friend. come to think of it, i wouldn't kill you. i'd kill your wife and kids. hell, i'm so crazy i'll even kill your maid. point is, sexx is capable of acts beyond your worst nightmares. sexx won't kill you. sexx'll make you suffer. suffering is not dying. suffering is not bleeding to death. suffering is suddenly becoming an insomniac while holding a six in the morning to 7 in the evening job. suffering is being married with kids but waking up in the middle of the night in an empty king-sized bed and going to the kids' room to find it empty and un-used for the past few years. believe me, sexx is capable of that. in fact, mr so-and-so, what sexx would like is to see you watching your loved ones beg for their lives while you bleed to death. that would be the icing on sexx's blackforest ice-cream cake. but back to reality, .44 are hard to get here. which means sexx has to comply with authority. sexx will go cut his hair into a mullet, because if he doesn't, then he will be in trouble for doing nothing wrong, except being in a f*cked up society. anyways, back to my unimportant life, did nothing much today, except skip p.e. and the run-in with d.k. you know what, mr koh? you should let us call you d.k.... might as well have a slightly cool nickname to be called by before you retire. and then later during chinese brent kept making FALSE ACCUSATIONS by vandalizing desks. screw you brent. but not enough for me to want to kill you. then later went to eat turtles with my dad before going home. i never felt sorry for the turtles. as usual, been on the computer since then. well, quoting a bit from the hives,"sexx is law. you, however, are the crime." hopefully i'll find something to bitch about later. right now i hope i fall asleep and dream that i'm sexx that cool motherf*cker. thank god i'm not him in the first place.  
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yellowcard - "october nights"  Warm October nights You came and cuddled next to me Our noses brushed so close I wished it was our souls Drifting off to sleep I could hear the little snores you made Watching eyes shut tight Like doors to something sweeter where you rest   Tear me off a piece of blanket Keep me warm and we can make it Here's my heart, I'll let you break it Touched your skin and I can't take it   Light will creep in soon And I still haven't slept a wink I wish the sun would hide its head So I could watch you dream some more I wanna watch you dream some more   I wanna watch you dream some more I wanna watch you dream some more girl I wanna watch you   
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      miffed after a long day out... in school, revived the Who'd You Like to F*ck game. played it non-stop for a few periods with mark and medwin. laughed like shit when mark kept choosing horribly retarded teachers to f*ck. hahahahaha those censors are back! f*ck f*ck! then continued crapping by taunting medwin about him being the only one in our group of 3 who hasn't watched the entire 1st season of the O.C. haha he's only at chrismukah... then got into a spat whether anna, summer or marissa was hotter. stupid bunch of asses( me included ). i like anna her short hair is kinda of cute. mark chose freaky summer and medwin chose anorexic marissa. i freaking hate mischa barton she's like a walking stick of pocky. in the end the two freaks got 1 vote each while anna got 3. wahahaha. but summer really DOES get hot at the last few episodes. then jumped around screaming like a kid when miss goh said that there was no remedial. off to jabba i went, with shijie. we got there like, freaking early and walked around a bit before meeting florence and gang. brent came awhile later followed by the chuas. jabba's always serves crappy food. i prefer domino's or shakey's. but, paid for the crap so i ate. talked cock with brent and jessica and randall while eating, then left while later. went to that ah beng shop, yellow, to get a friend a cig case. 9 freaking dollars it was. stupid pizza talk like yoda making me it is. 9 freaking dollars can get you 20 sticks, ryoudamnit. blah, decided to get him a pack instead for his birthday( how cheap can i get, but then again, cigarettes aren't cheap anymore...) then went home, rested for awhile then had TUITION! nuclear physics! wheeee! then back to the com to play gunbound and blog like a bitch. blog ends here... later days!( was that the grish or josh matthews? i forgot. ) 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ryoudamnit! my mom came back and said that i should just drink hot tea and rest and see what happens tomorrow. of course i'll be&nbsp;better tomorrow i want to see the doctor now while i'm sick so i can skip school! well, not really. hopefully i'll still be sick tomorrow so i won't have to go to school. maybe i'll just stay up late and get real tired and get eyebags. this nausea thing is really killing me, so maybe i really won't make it till tomorrow. crap. while typing this i spilled hot tea on my genital area. words cannot express my pain. why have i become accident prone for the past few days? have i done something really wrong? have i really done some one so much wrong that i had to 1)fall on my back while walking 2)fall on my back while being flung off a merry-go-round 3)get some crap stain that smelt rotten on my pants 4) and worse of all, the hot-tea-spilt-on-testicles. is that just plain unlucky or is that just plain unlucky? then due to my ponning of lessons i have yet to find out what will happen to me tomorrow at school. wish me luck. god, i promise if i don't get into trouble tomorrow i will be nice and helpful and friendly and good to everyone (even daryl yap and hai kiat ). now to listen to yellowcard and dir en grey! urgh.......*pukes again*... this be bad, yah? 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Prophet kyo Guitar kaoru Guitar Die Bass Toshiya Drums Shinya  Formed in 1997 with the sole purpose to spread the feelings of hurt and sorrow people face caused by weakness, shallowness and egoism of humans.Since then, their grotesque ways, their warped affection, and their crazy live shows took the independent record scene by a storm, putting them on the very top.    In 1999, their fame caught the attention of then CEO of East West Japan, signing them to a major record deal, debuting with 3 singles at once.Of course, all 3 songs ended up in the top 10 on the charts.After that, all their releases would hit the top 10 on the charts with the increase of fans that sympathize with their lyrics.    In 2002, during their Asia Tour in Shanghai, public safety officers had to be called to calm the excited fans.    When they first formed, their expressions of pain came from struggling and writhe, hiding inside the feelings of hurt and suffering. But as time passed, their pain became not only an expression but also a message.>From their unstable beginning, the band itself has gone through many changes and revolutions. Now it is clear that the music is their tool to send out their message.They are the only Japanese in the world that has dealt with tremendous hurt and sorrow.Until the day comes where there is no more hurt in this world, Dir en grey will carry the emotions of hurt and sorrow in their music, and they will continue to scream.    ( beautiful words, aren't they... *cries*......*screams* )  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      urrgghh... sat on some rotten shit today. then it looked like i shit my pants. rather cool actually. the stain was all oily and all that... sick shit! had to walk around as if i had a fire inside( piles ). then i skipped math after school to go home and play computer. my neighbour had a rather nice surprise for me though. new supply of videos! mwahahahaaa... checked the quality and sound out, then ripped them to the com. hope i don't get found out by my dad... but i think&nbsp;if i tell him that i use them to trade online i suppose he'll be okay with it. now i know that if i want to get goods i shouldn't look in malaysia, but rather bangkok. then when i started to clean up my pants i puked all over the place like i was&nbsp;niimura in the child prey video. all that was missing was the shot to the head and my brains splattering all over the wall behind me. almost blacked out... bloody nauseating. at least later i'm going to the doctor to get a diagnosis, and hopefully a MC. *prays*. then i can stay at home all day tomorrow and listen to YELLOWCARD, WHO ARE BETTER THAN BLINK. later, people. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      urgh... head is spinning not very nicely. fell on my back while walking dizzy and fell of a high-speed modified merry go round. then eardrums got shattered when brent banged a see-saw down next to me. and all this happened in the short space of about 5 minutes today.&nbsp; what a nice excursion to that garden. but before that... SCHOOL!!! gaaaaack! monday sucks the most plainly because it has geography, math, history and physics. all sian periods. then hong juan hiong-ed out after school after being provoked like shit. guess this means one thing. i retire from punchcock. punchcock has dented the lives of many people.&nbsp;if punchcock is allowed to go on, i don't know how many more lives it will affect... juan then&nbsp;proceeded to attempt to fight short and brent.&nbsp;brent ended up&nbsp;with a facial injury and juan ended up&nbsp;with a bloody lip.&nbsp;ryou-san would not be pleased. neither would sexx. stop freaking fighting and be&nbsp;a nice guy like me.&nbsp;then after school went to eat at florence's parents shop and&nbsp;then went to that&nbsp;park place with shijie, brent, audrey, florence and their friend( omg i'm so sorry i forgot your name ). was a good location to go when ponning school i suppose. isolated, quiet and serene. also good for dates and to ambush people. the most excellent spot i've seen this year. also had FUN swings and merry-go-rounds. dizzied myself up too much. i think maybe i have internal injuries. and full apologies to florence again for my hiong-ness at the merry go round! gomen ne again! sianning at home now... tuition cancelled... off to play gunbound like the pendek that i am. anyone have the kyo photobook to sell? needs it like hell... attempting to collect all dir en grey "books". although i seriously doubt i can since dragonfly is OUT OF PRINT. booyah!   
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sunday. the best day of the week. plainly because the next day i have to go to school! weehoo! anyway, i didn't do much the whole day except freaking around on the computer. at least i hauled up some cool pics (check out miyavi over there ). then the freaky stuff started in church in the evening. saw this girl from my batch holding hands and acting lovey-dovey with this guy who i swear was like, 25+ years old. is that freaky or is that freaky? 25-17=8! eight freaking years her senior? f*ck f*ck f*ck! crazy shit. then there was this dumb-ass fillipino choir who kept singing out of tune. f*ck f*ck f*ck!&nbsp;after church&nbsp;it was life as usual, sit infront of com, check out&nbsp;sites, kao peh on msn and then blog. blah blah&nbsp;blah blah!&nbsp;end of&nbsp;blogging. goddamn short-ass&nbsp;paragraphs! (oh yeah on a final note if anyone&nbsp;wants to hear the na moh ami tuo fuo&nbsp;remix, drop me a tag or a message. i'm circulating it for my dj friend.) 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      uhhuh. seriously beautiful. tuition in the afternoon was cancelled. so i went to paya lebar to meet&nbsp;the S.A. guys(not all of them)&nbsp;and eat. talked cock for 4 plus hours before going to bugis to act like bengs and play arcade. didn't feel too right. sucked completely at soul calibur... then couldn't play percussion freaks cos got some zai guys there. i can play all the extreme shit and all that but without bass. these freaks could play tamayura with bass and still get a S rating. freak. freak. freak. chewguy also freaked these lians out with his guitar freaks playing. freak. freak. freak. nester(jim) did nothing but laugh. freak. freak. freak. in the end had to play the only game i could complete with 1-2 credits. time crisis 2. i LOVE time crisis. then we went to laugh at bengs and lians playing para para and initial D. idiots. then went to 7-11 outside to drink crap. then we plotted to make various teachers seem like paedophiles, sex addicts and druggies. then went back to paya lebar at around 10 plus to buy drinks and snack around. then talked more cock. no one can beat us at talking cock. we talk cock the same way we talk cock. very professionally. then took a cab home. not many highlights, but still quite a fun day i suppose. wedding on monday? i hope so. i can't find all my shirts so i'll be there in my standard hawaiian shorts, t-shirt and slippers okay randall. oh yeah and pray that your fiance doesn't marry the wedding planner. that'll be bloody shitty( and bloody hilarious too... i can just imagine that happening).  
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what a blast the band concert was. school was a blast too. we only had 10 minutes of geog because mrs tan-chin came in to lecture us about the upcoming o levels. yes she was right i had improved from writing 1 line source based answers to 5 lines. and i improved from leaving structured questions blank to actually writing 5 to 6 lines. then, while mr quayle gave oral during the english lesson in the imac lab, i was busy making fun of local kagrra fans on the online forums for not owning rin on its release date. what fun. then it was the usual napping time during grandma's lesson. after that i went home to listen to my rin CD(note: CD not mp3) before taking a bath and going for the BAND CONCERT. me and the s.a. members shouted like shit at lick my leg and aloy and bedick. whole gang in that sitting area all shouted themselves hoarse(except some bo jio people). then mr denis koh didn't get a token of appreciation but&nbsp;his wife and another vice principal did. UNFAIR! if he wasn't there i suppose many if the people would have done more than shouted. he gets my vote for token of appreciation next year.&nbsp;today i also punched hong juan's cock once and ridzuan's twice. then i helped randall zham the pillar before making racist comments(not funny!) on the train as we passed little india. urgh i feel guilty. then because chomp chomp was full, no thanks to the yuppie crowd, we had to settle for the other market where all they sold was bbq crap, noodle crap, satay crap and the crappiest of all, char kuay tiao crap. the char kuay tiao was so crappy and full of hum that it felt pendek. pendekseh! had to settle for 3 cans of ice cream soda. then magically and amazingly managed to catch 2 buses home. then while walking past the 7-11 i felt suicidal and managed to crawl in to buy a super lemon tea big gulp. i didn't feel good downing it, but it sure as hell made me feel like i died. suicidal tendencies curbed! it also felt good crawling through my main door and taking a bath. then here i am in my earl tan t shirt and hawaiian pants fooling around with the computer. rather nice day, i should think. next year if i go for the band concert i will and must have isshi hair. then i will look like isshi. that will be good and bad at the same time. but i will not be gay and touch people. what a great day( 23 july not the 24th because i came back late you idiots.) kagrrarocksmorethanyou!(simply because they rock more than sexx, who in turn, rocks more than you. ) 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wonderful day, today. but still not that fun. started off the day with a rainy conference outside the chem lab. talked cock like girls for a full hour. i won't elaborate on the physics lesson and p.e. lesson because they were just as about as exciting as a drowning cow. then at chinese lesson, phatsam, boss and aloy unveiled the brand spanking new Boss, Phatsam and Aloy Interrogation Session Chair. sweecheebye( a new word ) sia! the BPAISC consists of 4 chairs, strategically placed and a crutch. the victim of interrogation will sit in the middle of boss and phatsam and aloy will sit in front of the victim. during the session, the rules imposed are 1. no lying, 2. no lying, 3 no lying and 4. no lying. lying will result in a nasty surprise from our resident lunatic aloy. altogether, about 3 people were interrogated and many truths were known, or should i say, extracted from them( some of which i cannot print ). bottom line was, the interrogation session was a success. from today onwards, every tuesday and thursday, boss, phatsam and aloy will hold the interrogation sessions for one hour after recess. join us, won't you? in other snippets of my boring life, grandma let us off early today. boring. then i proceeded to attempt to immmortalize my name on the school grounds by trying to carve my name onto the school steps. failed! at least tomorrow is the band concert where after that the whole gang is going to F**K THE TOWN RED!(or so i hope, lah). remember, kids. sexxrocksmorethanyou!(you remember? i kiss you on the forehead as a reward!)now i feel gay all over again. 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and i'm still not very into orchestral music yet. i mean, i can get into that nice, serene mood, but not shite by mozart or some wig wearing fag. i mean good ol'classical infused ROCK. orchestra stuff by dir en grey and x japan never fail to bring tears to my eyes. i hope the school band will surprise me by playing something like tears or ain't afraid to die. ah... ain't afraid to die... completely classic. the best ever dir en grey song to lay upon my ears. i go to sleep with it every damn night. not because its boring, but its soothing. classical music puts you to sleep because its boring. child prey by dir en grey puts me to sleep because its soothing(hyuk! hyuk!) enough about music then, i could go on for days about how much linkin park sucks, but i won't. they at least suck as much as today i suppose. can't seem to find the reason why the past few weekdays have been such a bore. is it because i haven't been routinely attacking eugene? maybe. or is it because i've practically been sleeping in class for half of the past few lesson hours? possibly. maybe its because me and aloy have stopped XXXX on the&nbsp;XXXX of marists watching XXXX? (i had to censor that because there's still that chance of denis seeing this blog. then we would be in deep shite, wouldn't we, aloy?) wait. i think i've got it. has the week been so boring because this friday at the band concert i'm going to make a hell of a ruckus and force them to play 10,000 encores while i shout aloy rocks and then after that i'll kidnap aloy and force him to go out with whoever's going out and then we're just going to make another hell of a racket possibly disturbing falungong practicioners and then we'll go fuck around till late and wake up the next day with a hangover? nah. i'll just wait for the next few days to see how things go around. maybe friday night i'll go play magic instead of going to the concert. i miss playing cards like a nerd. till tomorrow(or who knows when), sexxrocksmorethanyou! (haha no more boo-yah-ing for the time being) 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just couldn't think of a better title. rather average day i should say. at least today i found a good place to sleep in the tennis court. at recess, the breeze is fantastic and the risk of your organs being hit a flying ball is astronomical. splendid! crap if i sleep everyday how the crap am i going to get out of secondary school.... i wonder... also, my physics teacher stole my favourite word(shitty) and used it. now, oficially, "shitty" is not cool. you must all use pendek. and brent keeps stealing my lines. soon, he will also be stealing my one-liners. then i will not be able to go around and make people angry with my unique phrases. at least tomorrow i'll have friends with dyed and long hair with piercings coming to make feel inferior. i wish i had long hair, just like in the holidays. short hair stinks. contrary to belief, bengs now prefer short, punky hair to long hair. now i want long hair, because bengs stink. chinese music stinks. bengs like chinese music. urgh! what a short post, i must be running out of brain cells. must...think..more... must...write...and....bitch....about.....crappy....life.... band concert is in two freaking days! must pump up self with lots of classical stuff, like shit musicals like the wizard of oz! wee-hoo! 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ah yes... sexx. any of you remember sexx? no? ah well, sexx is still around, and maybe i should bring sexx back. sexx is like me, only thing is that i am polite, while sexx is a rude alchoholic. and i play rock, while sexx loves punk. and, the most important point of all is that i am not sexist(anymore), while sexx is a woman-hating mean motherf*cker. woman-hating mean motherf*cker. damn sexx was a cool ass. today, i went home with sexx. after a shitty day at school,&nbsp;i heard sexx say,&nbsp;"screw kagrra i'm listening to sum 41" and "what? only coke in the fridge? where's the freaking stella artois?" you could see that sexx was angry because 1)sexx loves kagrra and 2)sexx loves coke. you won't like sexx when he's angry. sexx is the most insensitive piece of shit this side of males. sexx is rude and uncouth. sexx loves blink 182, no matter what you say to him. well at least sexx is fun to be with. sexx likes all his friends and if you don't like sexx and is his enemy then sexx will just have to beat you to a bloody pulp. bottom line is, the walls have ears, and sexx says that if he finds out that the walls have been speaking, then sexx will be mightily freaked out. so freaked out that he will have to hurt the wall. (yes, sexx likes to hurt walls, see how unstable he is). sexx will have to break the walls down ( a la Chris Jericho) and then proceed to lay the freakin smackdown on the poor defenseless wall. everything is defenseless in front of sexx. just don't push him. at least he's not going for the wonderful band concert on friday. sexx bloody hates orchestras, and( oh well you know the rest ). only three more days! 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn. i never have anything good to write on saturdays and sundays. its always the weekdays that are filled with fun and excitement. all i did today was go to church and i've been on the computer since 11 a.m. That really sucks balls. I can't wait to go to school tomorrow and shove crutches up randall's ass. Then i shall proceed to twist him into a human pretzel.&nbsp; whatever am i going to do after i blog... i would sooner hug a gay man than watch that&nbsp;horrid NKF charity show.&nbsp; not that i'm insensitive or anything, but people doing stunts for money belong in the circus. what? you can raise&nbsp;tons of&nbsp;cash&nbsp;by making fann wong walk a tightrope.&nbsp;hey i'll share with you a secret on how to raise TWICE that amount in HALF the time. ready? you sure? make some hot female celeb strip on national television. even if its only to her underwear, it WILL work. &nbsp;if&nbsp;20000 males watch it and think its good(trust me, they -will- think it's good)&nbsp;, and each of them donates 2 dollars each, you would get 40000 dollars&nbsp;by almost doing nothing. for a tightrope walk, you need a person willing to train and work hard for days, heavy equipment, stunt specialists and coordinators and a waiting ambulance. that will major-ly burn a freaking hole in your pocket. for a strip dance, all you need is a pole and a celebrity who is willing to prance around in minimal clothing (okay and MAYBE the ambulance, just look at the amount of elderly rich people). now, that won't cost much, will it? so you see, you don't need to&nbsp;keep people&nbsp;in suspense to make them donate. just give them&nbsp;what they want to see.&nbsp; i feel so bored that i think i'll watch that charity show, then i'll go hug the gay man. bye for now. 
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      got home at around 12 from brent's place. come to think of it, yesterday was a really smashing party. it should be done again sometime this year. and again and again and again and again. members of the public have expressed their dismay at me not using names(sorry for previously calling you a dwarf, eugene). oh well if you insist. but some of you guys should know about the trouble that i got into last year for my site. you don't? i will tell you sometime. anyway, what's in a name? i was never really fond of names. randall(there i used a name. happy?) brent(pendek) and i(excuse my grammar, this sentence may be wrong) went to go retrive his ez link card that was stolen yesterday. then we took a bus from the punggol area to bishan. boy was it a long bus ride. then we ate at mcdonalds and went home. then my pendek tuition teacher proclaimed that after a night of not sleeping, i would have to go for tuition. that was complete crap. then after tuition i came home and got myself a SHINY NEW PINK shoutbox. is that gay/effeminate/homo-metrosexual or what! damn you pink bengs. and i learned some html. maybe now i can attempt to pick up chicks by being uber-geek-nerd-cool. watch out adam brody. gee...after so much blogging, i think i've finally gotten the hang of it. argh i gotta restart com... maybe i'll blog again later. time to bang some people. mwahahahahahahahahahahaha(and like a few billion more ha's) booyah.(no ! today)   
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      crap. i&nbsp;woke up at&nbsp;6 a.m. yesterday and was f*cking around till now. &nbsp;notice how i always like to say crap. rather puzzling.&nbsp; slept through school then went to a party. lotsa stuff happened, like the standard cake-in-face routine that is so revered at all parties. ooooh. chocolate cake being put to waste for the sake of displeasure and utter chaos. didn't do much attacking except for awhile... then left the place at 11 plus and found out there was no train home. then had to go to friend's house to stay overnight and blog this dumb post. damn i'm out of shit to blog cos it's 3 in the morning and that i've been saboed umpteen times today and i not be feeling too good. boo-yah! 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      was out from 5 am till now. got trapped at paya lebar playing magic till ten. i never knew magic was that fun when you seriously had nothing to do. and did you know that some posers actually take up magic because since seth cohen plays magic they think that its geek-cool. foolish pendeks. panjang=long. opposite of long is short. short=pendek. (insert name of asshole) is pendek. like my neighbour is pendek because he is scared of kagrra. he is being scared because he is very afraid that isshi will come all the way from japan to touch his parts. anyway, had a rather fruitful shopping day. shopped from city hall to bugis and then to parkway. stupid pendek "you-know-who-you-are" didn't want to buy pantyliners and condoms. (altogether now) pendek seh! haha then went to play magic again. i'm starting to feel the seth cohen geek-coolness (not). so today i 1)skipped school 2)ate breakfast at 7 a.m. 3)played magic till ten 4)went to the poly till 12 5)was at citilink browsing 6)was at bugis looking at beng stuff and puking and buying XXXXXXX 7)was at katong finishing up gift buying till 3 8)played magic till 5... and then i went home. fruitful eh? maybe i'll post my Posers and Not-Posers article, where i claim that daigo stardust is poser and miyavi is not-poser, and that cali gari is poser and kagerou are not poser (how the hell can kagerou be poser anyway? its like saying you like jesus and broads at the same time. (ready for my grandma grace mark?) GEEZ! or maybe i'll get some rest... it'll be a long day tomorrow... parrrrrrr-taaaaay!(i think/hope)
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      feels good. settled a big fat load of problems today. first off with that horribly irritating fellow on a piece of wood with wheels. argument ended. problem solved. we're both happy now, eh?(i hope) well, at least we didn't have to fight like the irish. i would have liked it to end as like in braveheart. mel gibson is such a sadist. unlike me who is kind and helpful and nice and friendly. happiness! joy! and i finally understood the principles of waves and optics. temasek poly design school here i come! hah, no tank-top wearing gay-boy's going to deter me from going (i hope [again]). what a beautiful day. and did i tell you that there's NO SCHOOL TOMORROW THE 15TH OF JULY? oh you mean you have school? argh... you wouldn't want to be me then. i've got a splitting headache and i've got to stay home (what a liar i am). anyway you know what i'm going to do.. but i'll still be on my medication, my head really feels like someone hit it with a skateboard (note to self: stop intergrating anything that has to do with "skate" into your logs). maybe i'll feel better if i listen to kagrra (new shit out 21/7). but i think i'll have to deal with my kylie minogue and atomic kitten shit. i feel gay all over again(but i feel good [not because of the gayness]) f*ck these stupid brackets! i have to go now! look at me i'm agressive because i use exclamation marks! i need to go to the toilet to take a piss! if i shouted that in public i'd be arrested! this is lame! it must be because i have not taken my medication! i will stop now! (bye[no exclamation mark]{damn you stupid brackets})
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wednesday moooorning! crap i woke up early. now i've got to f*ck around till 6 o'clock thenn i'll make my way to school to carry out the ultimate plan. i so i hope. i'm, like, not feeling too good anyway in the first place. i suddenly don't feel like using force to do stuff anymore. well at least my negotiation skills are still in their place. its almost like (drumroll please) i've lost my mojo. no, people, seriously. it not be good. and i've got to forc.. i mean, in my current condition, persuade and coax, this fellow to come to a party on friday night. and i've got lots of a math to catch up on. cutting class is the least of my troubles now i guess. this feels like getting a barbie doll for christmas. i'm writing in short sentences again. urgh.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      got your attention? no? didn't suppose so. haha, going to skip school on thursday and friday. why? cause i don't feel well today so i'll drag it to thursday and friday(which i quite hate) and it'll be four days of holiday for me! hah! and a couple of friends and myself have to go shopping! yay! (hence the title). time to blow my allowance on four non-stop days of shopping(and a party in between). damn shopping i hate it but i love it. crap... so much work, so little time. i feel like a work-a-shop-a-holic. argh... nothing to bitch about today. maybe i'll bitch again later, or maybe i'll get into trouble in school tomorrow then bitch, who knows? rat-tat-tat-tat-tat!damn that was childish.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      friend just told me that some guy whose stuff this ass-clown friend of mine wrecked was really pissed about it. when i said stuff i meant skateboard. now, it was wrong of my little friend to wreck your stuff, but it wasn't the group's fault yeah? and like if you hate backstabbers then why don't you tell it to my dwarf friend's face? huh? punk.( you can see i'm getting worked up because i start to be talking like a african-american). i'll cap you bitch...(now now, cool down. listen to some kagrra.) look, as i said, dude ,go settle it with the short one eh, but don't say that my best friend's (now i'm going homosexual, scared yet?) group makes you sick. you know what makes me sick? no, really, you want to know what makes me sick?  really? pretty please with a cherry on top? ok i'll tell. skaters. well, not all of them. some of them are quite alright. but not those with clean boards. dude, if you let your board get dirty and scratched, you'll look cool. trust me. i'm good. you skaters should stop listening to stuff like alkaline trio and breaking benjamin... listen to kagrra.... you'll feel much better and serene, then you won't get so worked up yah? ahhhhhh.... daikirai, daikiraiii, daikirai...(you know it means f*ck, f***ck, f*ck already eh....)
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      people actaully read my sh*t. is that cool or what!(note to self: no, that's not cool. you'd better restrict your comments or be beaten up by angry lynch mobs waiting outside you school.) portobellos rule! 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what a shitty week. yeah ok, news is out that baroque's first album is gonna be out 01/09/04, and i got more people to like yellowcard and merry... and,and,and...damn. you know what,there is nothing not-shitty about the week 5/7/04 to 10/7/04 (ok it's not really a week but...you get the point.) underlining the shittiness is my brand-ass-spanking-new...haircut. I look like that kid from the little rascals now. alfalfa or something like that... and it's all thanks to swanky and posh discipline master Mr Denis Koh C.H.. Its all thanks to him that i have this new suave and manly new haircut. it's, like.. you know... indescriptablly(is there such a word?)..like...how you say...shit. give me a few days and i'll be affectionally known as "bowl-head"(unless i can salvage the situation). you know what, if there's anyone who can look at my crap hair and not burst out in fits of laughter, i'll give that kind soul 10 bucks. how bout that?  but anyway, today was kinda cool. met some of my old sunday school friends in the morning after the 6 a.m. mass in church. then we went to drink beer at the kopitiam at around 7 plus. you know what i'd like. to sit at a coffeeshop eating hainanese chicken and drinking beer like lao ah pehs. ain't that cool? i feel stupid, drinking beer at 7 in the morning. hah, i remember that time at my class chalet where all them dumb f*cks drank diluted vodka and got high. sanctimonious sons of bitches.  i learnt that from chris jericho, cool huh. ugh...feel bad...maybe i'll go to school tomorrow and pinch someone's nipples or kick him in the testicles (you know who you are... mwahahaha.)off to practice on my sister's life sized lindsay lohan poster. take that you implanted bitch! boo-yah!
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      why do girl problems always happen to me? is it possible for a guy to develop feelings for a girl if he's only known her for a week and talked to her twice. i say no. damn it why does the average male always asssume that if a girl is talking to a guy, both of them MUST have feelings. look, i have gal-friends who i drink with and we're seriously like "brothers" (they're not butches, by the way). damn that stupid misconception. if that were true, MUCC would be millionares by now. hah. practically, i'm bitchin about this because i'm in that very situation right now. damn, you say? yeah, damn. and the poor innocent young thing involed already has millions and kazillions of suitors. and i'm no brad pitt. this is so totally crap. my sentences are short. dammit i know my limits and i won't jump at a hot babe to try my luck. i'm down-to-earth, and don't need a woman to complete me. life is good without sex and women and making out and nude women and nudity and love and sex and... ah f**ck it. damned if i do, and damned if i don't... maybe i'll give it a go...(haha. got you there).ta-ta, happy public
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      crappy computer took 2 weeks to load back up again... now i can finally go back to ranting and raving again... hah, didn't get into trouble with the cops anyway. and school's actually going quite well for me. not much trouble, new dorky haircut... i guess its going to be a looong term again. back to the topic of drinking, i guess it wasn't that bad. sure, i know of many 16 year olds who get drunk on a shot of diluted vodka (especially the weaker sex, if ya know what i mean), but i was drinking with -17- year olds. one year makes the difference y'know. going all light headed really made me happy and we had fun running from east coast to kallang. and back to bitching, i seriously wonder what is it with some hot gals and ugly guys. what? you want them for what they are inside? what? you're not after their money? what? you're not some insensitive bitch who's trying to prove to her girlfriends you can get a man to eat out of the palm of her hand? what? what? what? you damn bitches make me sick. so go on, call me ugly and fat, its what i am. but i hate hot girls! (okay not really, some of the, are quite nice, but hey, you never know) ..end..  
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lots of crap to get off my chest today. first, about the day. today was a monday. 'nuff said. bored my way through it. math? sleep. physics? do test. THEN sleep. recess? made an udder and stuck it to my crotch. close to sleeping then. geog? stoned my way through. social studies? made fun of boss. lunch break? did nothing. history? slacked and talked crap with brandon and juanjuan de juanjuan like hell. i think i am sexier than him. no doubt he has a french sounding name, but i have my dry wit, solid one-liners and triumph the insult comic dog's retarded-ness to back me up. juanjuan de juanjuan and goy can NEVER hold a candle to me, let alone a cricket lighter. mwahahahaha. then stayed awhile to play abit of magic. i love magic. magic rocks. nothing can make me stop playing magic. magic is the coolest game EVER. then ridzuan broke his pants. haha his zip broke and he sent short to attempt to fix it. then he started walking around in class in his undies. everyone agrees that he has a big schlong. he looked like a freaking male stripper, with his uniform shirt and white shoes. the most hilarious thing i've seen this week( apart from those hooke.. i mean, social escorts). then went home to slack. read this really sad article. this guy had this friend who died of cancer. and you know what his friend regretted the most? nope, not being a virgin. not saying he loved mis mummy and daddy before he died? nope. he regretted not being able to give his buds back the fags they always gave him. felt like a brick dropping down on my friggin head. to all the s.a. guys, i promise to stop taking so much from you guys and to return all your favors( seh ). that dude was pretty nice. i hope i don't end up regretting like him. TWO MORE POINTS TO GO. numero uno. people of the world, stop supporting phelps. he is only a greenhorn in swimming. i believe that the thorpedo will shine again. go ian! most of the world is still behind you. make us proud and beat that imbecile. and finally, props to randy orton. at 24, he silenced the critics and smashed that sell-out brock lesnar's record. world champion at 24. this kid has lots in store for himself. can't wait for his edge/jericho/hhh feuds. still hope that paul will still get on top though. remember this people, pain is temporary, but, the game is forever. mwahahahaha. sledgehammer time! sayonara, you stupid taker marks. weehoo! 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      these works were garnered from the bowels of sgforums.com. they belong to baka gemu co. anyway, so i'm not stealing anything. read 'em, and have a good think. actually, read mazohyst's one and have a good think. the one by ain't afraid to die is just there for the inner dominatrix in all of you. back to the day, then. pendek sluts attack! me and my friend were at this shop eating when there was this bunch of sluts from church. they freaking waved to us and we didn't wave back. then they started kao-peh-ing because we were damn ignorant about them. what? since you're hot you expect me to feel the urge to respond to your calls? men aren't shallow anymore. well, except mark. mark is as shallow as a cd case, or even shallower. then the whores came over and kao-peh-ed even more. we gentlemen politely excused ourselves. then they followed us. then we turned a corner and ran. felt like an episode of heartlanders. we ran away laughing like madmen. he still had a hard-on, but didn't want to admit it. mwahahaha. excuse my punk-ish friend, for he is shallow, unlike moi. bottom line is, not all hot women are good. some not so hot ones may be better. depends if you're shallow or not, i suppose. then went home to waste my life in front of the tube and the computer. it then crossed my mind to go look for those 2 pieces of missing literal art. when i found them i jumped for joy. there was also this psycho's poem about how he hated the butches in a certain school. that guy was one sick freak. he should have been condemned to an asylum. hah! then went around the net looking for taking back sunday stuff. they're pretty good. too good, in fact. thanks mark. i owe you. you have saved me from the recesses of blink and busted and mcfly and blahblahblah. thank you. off to sleep now. tired as hell. then i'll wake up at 10 to come back to bitch. either that or i'll be dead till tomorrow morning. sayonara, hot women. you suck like hell. 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Disinfectant by Mazohyst   The old man, lying in his hospital bed,  Waiting for death to carry him away.  The smell of the disinfectant, piercing the senses of the waiting relatives.  Waiting for the moment, waiting for death to carry him away.   Do you regret now?  What you should have said, but have not done?  What you should have done, but have not done?  What awaits you?   The gaping black abyss of the unknown, the place we all go...  When your mother died, you wondered what she felt...  now you feel it yourself...  Is it nice?   The moment approaches.  You see it on the faces of your family.  They stand around the bed...  Looking at you, you, with those tubes sticking out your body.   The young ones, watching in fascination as the heart monitor beats...  Even now, you feel the strain it takes to keep it beating,  waiting for that final moment,  Waiting for death to carry you away.   There... you hear it now  The call to leave.  Your family stands, helpless begging you to stay.  You can't hear it anymore  Your mind, your consciousness, your soul, drifting away into nothing   The droning beep...  heralding your departure  heralding the moment,  that death took you away. 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Violet by Ain't Afraid To Die    Violet wants to play a game. A game where we can all have fun She strips out of her clothes and ties me up And whips me into submission  Submission. Cold cruel submission I enjoy submission, Do you?  I play along with Violet We delight in the flow of our blood The pain is excruciating How fun.  The pain brings pleasure, Pleasure beyond words. Pleasure which is brought by open wounds, Wounds of a masochist  She, the sadist I, the masochist We coexist in this romp We need each other  She hurts me I feel wonderful I receive punishment from her, I'm sure she loves it too  The chains and the toys, Glittering prizes in our eyes. We play with them like school children Hurting each other with them  Our tears and wounds bring joy, Not pain. But the laughter brings pain, Not humor  Once again the game is ended, To continue another day But next time I'll get Violet, I swear For the castration she gave me today. 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      part 1 got its title posted. i clicked publish post for part 2, but it didn't come up. i highlighted some words from part 3 and the whole post got wiped out. i hate blogger. now i have to post about the previous day on the next day. i feel like a cow. but never mind. my endurance is god-like. here comes part 4. stupid tuition teacher woke me up in the morning by calling me and asking me to go for tuition at 12. forget it, i said. watched my usual saturday morning shows before making my way down to changi airport to meet flor, drey and brent. they were going to be late so i made my way down to pasir ris to fool around at the arcade. read FHM too. what a brutal waste of money. full of retarded western girls with giant boobies. yuck! daikirai desu. note to FHM: feature more local girls! then went to terminal 2.. SALAH! flor and drey were at terminal 1. so i walked there. walked. walked. met up with them then went to eat while waiting for brent. then studied. yesterday i stayed awake in class and today i studied. what's going to happen tomorrow? belinda lee coming crashing through my celing? nah. didn't think so either. then went on 24 to paya leber when it happened. the big smelly rotting unfair vagina came up at one stop and plonked itself down next to me. and sat close to me. bloody freaky. and i leaned away, hoping that it would take the hint and f*ck off, but it didn't. and even though there was an empty seat next to it, it still stayed next to me. i wanted to kill it so badly. i wanted to kill it till it died. when it finally retreated i could then breathe easily again. next time i see one i will f*ck it ( not literally ). then at the shop etmun was sorting cards again. neat freak! haha. oh yeah. got the news about you. you know who you are. eh, cheer up lah. i'm sure the both of you will get back together somewhere down the road. live for the moment, yeah? i am such a hardy mark . chew and me sat outside on the grimy floor like derelicts. then we decided to upgrade and sit on the long john silver chairs. went back in after awhile to talk cock with alex about star wars, james lye and unfair corrupt singapore cops. hope hsien loong takes care of that problem( the cops, not james lye or star wars). then after that we went to tampines to play lan. whooped the asses of unfair guys, as usual. obviously while spouting clever one-liners. then we saw this guy who looked like a klingon. freaky sighting #2 of the day. then chew went back to kembangan to entertain his "guests". while walking home i saw these "convent girls" sitting at this ulu void deck. convent girls with dyed hair and long socks with davidoffs between their lips. these girls weren't only smoking davidoffs, if you know what i mean. freaky sighting #3. nice phish moment, though. how sick can some clients get? not as sick as sexx, that's for sure. urp! blogging about the previous day on the next day again. yes, as much as i would like to deny it, i am everything but the seh. at least i survived saturday without the crack. weird. mucho weirdo. ooooooooooooooh. 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      japanese modernist by MERRY lyrics: gara music: yuu   JAPANIIZU MODANISUTO  go mad JAPANIIZU MODANISUTO   uooo~ naze ano kuni dake ga tsuyoi  uooo~ naze ano kuni dake?   ano hi tonda GAREKI no ue eikyuu fumetsu no HEDONISUTO  SUICCHI ON de kyou mo tonbimasu yowaki jibun ni "SAYONARA" BAIBAI  shounen yo ima, mae ni susume, shounen yo ima, taishi wo dake  shikkari to mae dake mitsumete  minna SUKAIHAI de ima oyuki nasai   go mad JAPANIIZU MODANISUTO  go mad JAPANIIZU MODANISUTO   ume yo, taiyou yo, chi no hate, ano sora yo  kikoeru ka? koe ga   ume yo, taiyou yo, chi no hate yo, ano sora yo  kikoeru ka? koe ga   chichi yo, haha yo, imouto yo, otouto yo  kikoeru ka? koe ga...   ume yo, taiyou yo, chi no hate yo, ano sora yo  kikoeru ka?   
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am joking. who in the blue hell would be sick enough to do that? not me. but it sure was a freaky friday. i actually stayed awake during geography. and did the test properly. and stayed awake for the rest of the day. and also staying awake during grandma grace's lesson. i feel bad. feels...funny. then i felt like not paying attention during edmund goy's lesson. but at least he was nice enough to let us opt whether we should do work. then after that me, lionel, aloy and alex went to tampines. aloy had to pick up this pair of shoes from this tampines junior college guy. we reached there at 130, but the fellow was coming at 2. so we went to burger king to eat. stupid new incompetent staff didn't want to give barbecue sauce. pfffft! talked cock while eating. too bad lionel didn't bring his camera. or else we could take some pictures of unfair people. then aloy reminded me of pranking people. the good ol' this-number-is-for-sex-online-spamming. utterly evil. complete genius. however, i prefer the subscribe-to-a-lot-of-gay-or-transexual-newsletters trick. irks the person EVERYTIME. but i haven't done it in a long time, though. maybe i should do it to a random person. but at least i'll admit to it if i did it, so if any of you get gay porn, its not me unless i confess. and here i am blogging and watching outlaw star. harry and ron kick ass! no not potter and weasley. those two can go suck eggs for all i care. harry and ron MACDOUGALL. the most fearsome gay guys in the whole universe( well, except fred). i shall bitch again later. wank time( maybe )! 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      'tis not the end of the world. or so they say. crappy chinese o level results? fret not seh. retake lor. ok lor. chinese is just like english. why they never formed a china council, don't ask me, i'm still asking myself the same question. english is basically like that: either you know it, or you don't. no such thing as studying english. just like chinese. so stop studying chinese. you should probably live chinese if you want to be good at it. go talk to everyone in chinese. i guaran-damn-tee that your chinese will improve. screw language tuition its useless!   in other news, wearing a hairband does not certify that you are gay. well, unless you look the gay sort. there is no evidence provided to my parents that i'm gay. just this evening, as i sat at the dinner table with a hairband on my head, my dad exclaimed, "are you gay? why are you wearing that turquoise hairband?" to which i responded, "f*ck you, dad!" okay, i lied. i opted to keep my mouth shut and fill myself with chestnut water, and responded with a quick and rapid shaking motion with my head. parents, your son will not be gay if he likes wearing hairbands. however, if your son likes trying on pretty frocks and faints when he sees fake louis vuitton, then by jove i'm sorry. he is a complete faggot.  and on the topic of sexuality, i have learned that doxy means a person who is like a wife, except that the poor woman isn't a wife( out of point ). i think i've gone perpetually bonkers.  aaaand, to end this newsflash, thank god for macguyver-ness, as now, every dumb inclined fool can make like him and build his own taser. bzzzzzzzt! fear rape, snatch-theft, molest and other crimes no more. with this new hand-made taser, all poor and innocent singaporean young ladies can now protect themselves with a originally banned-in-singapore gizmo! fear not the dark alleys of geylang no more! best of all, this taser'll make 'em BLEED. jam it into their genital area and say goodnight. if only i was bothered to tell you ignoramuses how to make it. i suppose that's for another day. *end*(!) 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      baroque's ila rocks! although i thought little of it at first it makes me sad sometimes. heeheehee. but that's another story for another day. anyway, back to the usually boring thursday. slacked through chemistry outside the lab. marked boomerang-like thingies during physics, lifted weights during p.e., ate during recess, slacked through chinese( weehoo i got C6! ), slacked through social studies with the unfair relief teacher and actually studied at history. then i decided to skip math. grandma have mercy. end of blog for today, maybe i'll bitch again later. in the meantime, check out there circa-2002-2003 pages which rock!   urlLink http://www.angelfire.com/pro/mp2002/sex1.htm   urlLink http://www.angelfire.com/pro/mp2002/sex3.htm  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      went to another boring day at school. urgh school. school bites like hell. got punched in the cock by ben loh during math. sneaky bastard always gets me. however does he do it.. i wonder. i must be stupid. then was stupid aida's lesson again. aida had this new spunky haircut that screamed, "I'M A PENDEK". but, i be considering whether i be wanting to get an aida haircut though. then during english we did up posters saying what we would do if we were Singapore's education ministers. i wanted to abolish uniforms and racism. and to promote the use of vulgarities to in turn promoto good speaking. bottom line was that if i was the education minister, all of you could just say goodbye to the education of your children. then history was an hour later. chin was at her usual sarcastic self again. hinting that some people just came to class to slack and sleep. it was ME. and i sure ain't proud of it. then went for physics where sor hoon was her cool crazy self again. then went home to sleep before tuition. then i went to learn how to make a taser. AND I'M NOT TELLING! time to go kill some people. like hai kiat. burn baby burn. after tuition was singapore idol. at least we can take comfort in the fact that we're not as bad as malaysian idol. what is it with people and their 15 minutes of fame. go strip on the streets. or have a wank in the middle of orchard road. or castrate yourself on the field during the next national day. if you can't sing and you know it. DON'T GO TRY OUT FOR ANY AUDITION OF ANY SORT. don't waste the time of musically talented people( i.e. me ). but i'm not going for singapore idol. i'm going to play in a lounge! hopefully. damn those eurasian chicks were good. by saying "good" i also mean "HOT". phiisssssssh! that's about it for today. off to watch outlaw star for the #2853rd time. i still cry when hilda dies after saying "an outlaw doesn't go down easy". *sob* why did hilda have do die! damn you kei pirates. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hiza wo kakaeru  hibi yo SAYONARA  nandemo ii kara kowashite mae!! moshi yume ni yabure tsurai toki ni wa  "MAKKU" de TADA no egao wo kae ba ii  somaru koto naku  hibi sugoshiteta hitori furui PANKU wo kiiteita  hakidasu koto de subete ga kawaru to nakayubi tate mou...  MAYOWANAI!   IKE IKE WAKAMONOTACHI YO  IMA, TACHIAGARI HATA WO TE NI TORE   jibun ni jishin  hoshii nara ima fudoukan mezashite hashire ba ii  moshi tsukarete kujike sou na toki wa  "makenai de" utatte mo rare ba ii   IKE IKE WAKAMONOTACHI YO   IMA, TACHIAGARI HATA WO TE NI TORE  ushiro wa furimuku na mou,  akiramete owari ka?  ushiro wa furimuku na  ima, tachiagari mae ni mae ni susuME!!   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      2 all those ppl whu lyk 2 tok liddat. plz stoppit. typin liddat in short form or in broken engrish is veli irritating. it pisses mi off. if u lyk to tok liddat, think of all de ppl whu cum 2 ur blog or site 2 read ur stuff. they will have a veli hard tym tryin 2 make out what u r tryin 2 say. n it osso make u seem like an imbecile. lyk now i feel lyk a stoopit beng whu can't read. so plz, for de sake of better engrish, stop usin crapy short forms and broken engrish. thankew.( i am now going to shoot myself. or hug a gay man. which ever i can get to first, the gun or the gay man. i think the gay man. ) 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah. i learned stuff today. the first lesson being that i am a beng. as much as it hurts me to say that. no one could endure 5 hours of tiao kah while playing cs and drinking canned coffee. except a beng. and an elite beng, at that. 5 freaking hours. my eyes are leaving me. courtesy of dogshit and ji(bye)wei and the fish. nice to see them after like a few months of not cs-ing together. they still looked the same, save for fish who had this rocking new long hairdo.  was also nice to see that jiwei improved and so did fish. and dogshit was phenomenal. urgh. and i was still the same usual retarded freak. wonderful rape reunion. 'cept for mui and chew and... urgh we're a small clan. but we rock ass. then later we went to marche to eat. now i feel like dying. ate rosti with this penis-like garlic sausage, 2 plates of salmon sashimi, a bowl of calamari, a plate of soft shell crabs, a cashew( which kaoru likes to get ) brownie with movenpick vanilla ice cream and a OREO CHEESECAKE. oreo cheesecake. 0r30 ch3355c4k3! killer oreo cheesecake. urgh i have sinned. then dogshit wanted to smoke. bloody hilarious because jiwei needed to do this survey on underage smokers. but being the unprepared fool that he was, ji-balls forgot the voice recorder. ah well, that's life i suppose. then we went to beng at the arcade in bugis. saw johnson again. idiot always asks me for etmun. went to play pfreaks, and hlafway through my wrists acted up again. at least i got to play sobakasu! BENG SEH! then played guilty gear. BENG SEH! then play KOF. SUPER BENG SEH. then played time crisis. QUITE BENG SEH. but the bengness wasn't over yet. after arcade-ing we then decided to do something else. play cs. BENG SEH. played till 830 then dogshit gave me a cab home. thanks lots canine faeces! till the next rape reunion. then i went to tampines mall to meet a friend for coffee bean. talked crap for awhile about old times. haven't seen her in a year i suppose. hot coffee rocks. can't feel my tongue. then i did the bengest thing in the world. i went to play initial D. someone shoot me now please. of ambush me tomorrow in school and beat me up. stop this bengness its killing me. haha was quite funny how the game worked. no wonder the bengs like it its so much easier than daytona. thank god there weren't much bengs there. or else i would have died a horrible death. ran out in cold sweat after losing at some stage. then talked cock while walking to the mrt before i walked home. now here i am f*cking around at the computer. school tomorrow. i suppose i had better sleep early then. sayonara, you nice non-bengs. i envy you. help. tolong. jiu ming. tasukete.  
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finish the sentence  I should warn you...: that i'm crazy  I wanna be the....:kaoru of what ever i do  All I need....: is friends i can do shit with  I love...: visual kei and friends who do shit with me  I hate....: too many things to mention  I give....: advice and other unmentionable stuff.  I take....: hk, booze and a little bit more of some other crap  I can't stand....: mature people  I felt alone....: always  It was so painful when....: i fell on my head on concrete.  I think...: of not studying and fooling around all day  Life is... : good when you have crazy drugged-out friends and when you're drugged out too  Love is....: crap.  My family....: is good, but bad at the same time  I wish...: that everyone would be happy and not fight  My biggest mistake....:is  not saying the things i was supposed to say  When I am alone I....: have a wank  Will someone please....: let me beat the hell out of him/her  I fear....: birds, other than that, nothing  I have...: everything important  I want... : nothing.  I regret....: not saying the things i should have said  I ache..: when i go crazy and hurt myself  I always...: am happy  I am not....: heterosexual  I am confused....: when i am drugged-out or drunk  I cried....: when people f*cked with my family. then i will stop and kill them  I am afraid....: of nothing, except birds  I need....: sexx. i already have family, friends, drugs and music.  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what a title. explains what happened to me a few years back, but i will not delve into it. basically stayed at home all day long watching tv. then i decided to watch outlaw star and trigun again, just for kicks. then i realized that after seeing stupid characters from shit animes like rave and naruto, trigun and outlaw star still kick ass. i bet legato could mind control all the naruto losers to f*ck themselves and do the hokey-pokey at the same time. and who could forget good ol' fred luo. fred. my gay inspiration. the coolest gay anime guy in the world! who could just look at a hot woman and say hi, while he goes to hug his male friends? 2 people. me and fred luo. BROKEN. and of course not forgetting gene and jim and melfina and suzuka(BROKEN) and everyone's favourite ctarl-ctarl, aisha clan-clan. my advice to all you naruto and rave and whatnot losers is to watch outlaw star, trigun, rurouni kenshin, get backers, and of course, for those who are 18+, bible black and wicked city. wicked city=lush and beautiful. bible black=the best hentai anime so far. if you haven't watched bible black, you are a fool who only looks at lousy hentai. and of course, being a secret plot "mark" i advise all of you to go read it. secret plot is horny and rockin! aaaaand back to my day. urgh. stupid sister took my phone and red all my messages. you know what that means. child abuse time! and got forced to watch the national day parade. urgh it completely sucked rocks. as usual. but nice to see them pay homage to the goh-man. goh-man rocks! weehoo tomorrow its going to be 6 hours of unadulterated cs( i hope ) at cineleisure! haven't seen dogshit in a while. and jiwei too. and those graduated guys. urrrgghhh now i feel bad. should have studied hard. end of blog i suppose. all you f*ckers "in love" please line up to get your spoon. (so you all can eat my ass) 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      saturday was rather not-so-cool. in the morning i went to pasir ris to spend 10 bucks on percussion freaks. felt REALLY bad. but the 5 games busted my wrists up so no vigorous activity for the next few days. boo! then later went to kembangan to spoil my eyes again with an hour of cs. saw some old "friends" there. then went to meet up with chew to go to suntec to watch this apparent j-rock band play. all i can say about them is F*CKING COOL BASSIST. he freaking played damn accurately with his fingers and swayed to the music with this toshiya-esque vibe around. talent+showmanship=really really good. the other guys in the band were really cool too. just that the bassist was the coolest. hah! then went to marina to play guitar freaks and irritate bengs. after we had enough fun with the bengs we went to the esplanade to meet brent lionel shijie drey and flor. but stupid place was so crowded. and this idiot complained about smoking. you stupid fool. there's no law about smoking in an outdoor public place, so there. then after the crappy fireworks and busted-up handphones i FINALLY met the gang at marina. went to eat at cafe cartel at plaza singapura. ordered some seafood platter and some other crap like potato wedges and crab claws. ate a bit and was quite full. late night food is bad. then when all of them left i went to meet chew to go home. haha he said there was this lolita-ish girl who he bumped into. then he felt bad. ah well that's life. then he gave me a pep talk on XXXX in the mrt station and kept telling me crap which i think was quite rational. hmmm.. maybe i'll go with his advice. but you never know the real reason, eh? sayonara, you attached losers. bleeeuuurghhh! 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha. stupid gazette song where some guy at a new year's party keeps saying banzai out of rhythm is stuck in my freaking head. today went to chewguy's house in the late morning. jammed crap acoustic songs like san dimas high school football rules and stuff by dashboard confessional( NOT VINDICATED ) and like, acoustic pierrot and stuff. then went to paya lebar in the late afternoon. talked crap and jammed some more. then we attempted in vain to busk outside the coffee bean for free coffee. then most of the group suggested that we camp outside this spa/salon to look at women. then ryan chased nester and stomped him. then nester got all moody and acted like a 6-year old. rather funny, the sight of him sulking in a corner. then went to eat at the mcdonalds while one of them( i won't say who ) ogled at this "cute" malay girl. urrrrggggh. sam went missing so we had to wait awhile before he contacted us. went to visit him beacuse his mom passed. but he was really strong though. still able to laugh and make jokes. tough dude. we were then reminded about how hai kiat said that he didn't care about his mom while his mom was suffering. damn you hai kiat. your throat is mine. i will make your life hell for the rest of the year. no, i'm not going to beat you up. wait and see. yay i can't wait for the concert and fireworks tomorrow! hope by some sudden twist of horrid fate hai kiat gets fried by haywire fireworks. yummy crispy fried boy! sluuurrrp! 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      school ended at 10 like that today balls. then in school just did a hell of a lot of crap like watch people compete for movie passes. then in the end everyone had to enter the hall to watch david( who is very popular in the school's gay community ) and matt and bedick and two other fellows sing a whole load of songs. then during the last song aloy went on stage and rubbed his shirt on his crotch. the gay community gave the solo act a thumbs up. however, dk the party pooper obviously gave aloy's demi moore attempt a thumbs down. dk then proceeded to give aloy a dressing down. he also saw me going to the toilet and i had to persuade him for a whole 5 minutes that i wasn't going there to smoke. you stupid pendek i had nothing in my freaking pockets, how was i going to do the dirty deed? anyway there by the grace of god aloy got away scot free and him, me lionel and randall went to central. then randall later ditched us to go meet his "dardar". that word gives me goosebumps. aloy's other half came to meet him around half an hour later. drank some 100 plus while waiting and told the stories of my secondary 2 neighbour and another about sticks of happiness. then aloy sent his girlfriend off at the mrt station and we went off to get buses. aloy and lionel took 53 and i took 22. goddamn stupid manjustri lians piss the f*ck out of me. fancy singing jay chou songs in public. you don't see me screaming like gara in public, do you? no you don't. all the way from serangoon area till they dropped at bedok they were full of praise for schlocks like jay chou and 5566 and energy and other fag-guys. i hope i don't see them this sunday at marina or i will have to kill them. viciously. couldn't get out of the house cause of this horrible headache which i think was caused by the consumption of too much isotonic drinks. then couldn't go down to central to play arcade. awwwww... if i did then maybe i would have given her a surprise by waiting below that dumbass building. hmm i forgot to ask etmun if he was still going to the council. i remember how this teacher asked him to pick up a pencil the same way a gay convict asks the new inmate to pick up the soap in the bath. laughed my freaking ass off. ooh can't wait for suundaaaay! visual bands and fireworks! woohoo! 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fami Resu Bonbaa(Family Restaurant Bomber) lyrics and music by Sex Machineguns   Welcome, how many in your party? Two people?  Someone will be joining me Will you be smoking?  I'll seat you. When you've decided on your order, just call me over.   Today is my first date with her.  She hasn't come yet 30 minutes pass and she hasn't come yet.  She hasn't come yet   You idiot, you idiot, you waiting idiot   Welcome, have you decided what you want? The Japanese hamburger?  Yes, the Japanese hamburger. You ordered the Japanese hamburger right? Here are some hot towels.  Don't wipe your face   My order hasn't come yet.  It hasn't come yet The girl I love hasn't come yet either.  She hasn't come yet   You idiot, you idiot, you waiting idiot   I've been kept waiting too long. Family Restaurant Bomber, family restaurant bomber I don't smile. Family Restaurant Bomber, family restaurant bomber An explosion of anger. Family Restaurant Bomber, family restaurant bomber It's unforgiveable. Family Restaurant BomberBomber   No that's not all, how long will I have to wait, with this clerk I'm very sorry about your wait.  Here is your onion ramen. What? I ordered the Japanese hamburger... Really, the Japanese hamburger? I'll check up on it for you. I'm very sorry, it was the bibimbap right? Oh oh oh, I'm going to kill you! You asshole!   Welcome, nice to see you tonight. From morning to night, the greetings continue. That girl that I love probably won't come The coffee that I didn't ask for is here   My order won't come. It won't come The girl I love won't come either.  She won't come again.   You idiot, you idiot, you waiting idiot   I was rejected. Family Restaurant Bomber, family restaurant bomber An explosion of anger. Family Restaurant Bomber, family restaurant bomber A small bomb. Family Restaurant Bomber, family restaurant bomber It's a massacre. Family Restaurant BomberBomber Enjoy your meal   aloy, here's the translation. enjoy.  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      school was slack again, as usual. today aida was absent, so no chemistry. physics was all blah, and so as p.e., and chinese, and social studies. then it was going to be 1 1/2 hours till the next period so i decided to skip class! sam the truant strikes again. followed et-mun and boston rob next door where many people lived where they had some sticks of happiness. stupid emmanuel why did you have to implant that phrase into my head. now happiness can bee bought. bloody geniuses, them. people only come to visit in the afternoon so we were safe. then went down to soulcraft with etmun to fuck around with magic. in the small course of one hour we saw around 20+ female smokers. females, if you smoke, you will have genitial problems and maybe birth deformities. leave the lung-destruction to the men. then etmun gave me a lift back to tam-penis. then, when i reached home, my china neighbour called me down to his place. turns out some of the girls who lived there had some sticks of happiness. we stole the sticks of happiness and rewired them like hell. thank god he remembered the wire order, or else later they wouldn't be able to get their happiness back. then at home i decided to act smart and play heavy metal with my acoustic. say goodbye to the bottom 2 strings. one was gone a few months ago and i didn't bother replacing it. then i snapped the other one today. now i have an acoustic bass is that cool or what. not. argh i've seen so many sticks of happiness that i feel like vomitting. bleeeeeeeeeeeeeeuuuuuuuuuuurrrrrrrrrrgggggggggghhhhhh! 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha today at school we witnessed yet another fool who didn't know how to commit crimes well get punished for his insolence. obviously he got the fact that stealing was easy into his foolhead. dumbass was caught for stealing canteen food. what is he, a tramp. two strokes, end of story. therefore, what i've learned from eddie and chavo is this. if you want to lie, cheat and steal, do it well. don't go around doing shit only to get caught. that's ignorant. in other news, i slacked through the whole day. in fact, the day at school was so fruitless that the only thing i remember is the public caning. and the fact that the guy who punched chewguy was being suspended. urgh yesterday was also so fruitless that i forgot to tell the story of the evil-ness of chewguy. yesterday some asswipe punched him in the face because mr. asswipe thought chew was going to call someone to beat the piss out of him. then chew called him a motherf*cker. but that guy's mom passed away already. then mr. asswipe got mad and attempted to attack him again but the fight was broken up. you see. this proves that sometimes, your words may be stronger than your fists. can't say the same for kj and gang. i suppose in a verbal and physical fight they'll get beat like pusses. thanks for chew for his flaming help, and i suppose i'll leave those guys alone now yah. now to go look for new prey. no cortamos tu prado, suckers.( i not knowing what that means. )  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      urgh... feel so shagged after that first post. that fellow deserves anything that comes to him. except joanna and belinda lee in a box smeared in hershey's chocolate, but that's another story for another day. today school was a complete fuck. completely didn't learn anything today. after reminiscing about illegal stuff, i think its time to look back at this time last year and to see what the hell i was doing. last year, i was a single-chain-smoking-alcohol-drinking-vandalizing-cyber-criminal. is that cool or what. now i'm just a not-single-clean-nice-guy. (*pukes*). i seem to have been out of trouble for a long time and i'm itching for a nice standing session outside denis' office. and we're planning outings on friday and saturday on a tuesday! wheeeee~! urgh i feel gay i haven't used tilde for a long while. ah well. that's life. more on outing planning. end of blog. and send me your comments on how to get my ass outside square-head's office. i will commit myself to the best request if it's rational. damn suicidal tendencies.  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      people. prepare yourselves for the gayness that is... oh well i suppose i'll spare him the humiliation of telling his name to the whole internet. this brave young man actually told sexx that sexx should go learn vulgarities from talkingcock.com. is that funny or what. sexx (and all other intelligent people) do not use dialect to insult. what, my brave boy? do you think i'm a gangster like you? hmm? and what now? he says meri is a name of a girl from bangbus.com. ahh... i suppose that's the only site he goes to. hey, please go support local porn at sammyboy.com. i already have a subscription. stop going to sell-out mainstream porn sites like bang bus, you make me sick. and oooh. and now he says he can't call me a crackhead because i haven't smoked before. and what makes you so sure, mister i-smoke-and-you-don't-so-i'm-cooler-than you? sexx smokes alright. sexx is a freaking chain smoker, for crying out loud. fine, maybe you're a smoker too, but for the love of ryou stop using that fact to establish that you're ranked higher than me in life. last point, you stupid mainstream posers all share the same poser fact that all sarong party girls are bitches. so the papers and the books say so you must follow lah? idiots. think you're all so great with your beng vulgarities and porn sites and being smokers and hating sarong party girls. go on, ask anyone who knows me about my relation with vulgarites, smoking and porn. i've been through more of those than you, i'm sure of it. you want a fight? you've got it.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today at school was interrogated all day long about me and her. at least i didn't get physically abused much. i suppose that love IS a many splendored thing. funny how love feels. it feels like... ah f*ck it i won't bother describing. after a complete waste of time at school, me, lionel and aloy decided to go to the city hall area. lionel had to buy some crap for his woman. not that the things he bought were crap, but its just that i like to say crap. crap. hah! then after buying his crap, we went to the raffles place burger king to eat. damn fool lionel almost ate some one else's cheese nuggets. ate for like, half an hour? then took pictures of random people. hope they don't find out and report us to the cops. life is good. there was this woman who looked like shinya, i'll load it up when i get it from lionel. then aloy the dumbf*ck thought it was fun to make me miss the train. held him captive for 6 minutes, then took the train all the way home. saw her online and chatted for awhile then she had to go study. argh why am i helping you stay online? i shall kick myself again for depriving you of education. then the icing on today's cake came when i saw the sea hum gang tag again. utter bliss. and that kyo guy doesn't even know what a mormon is till he checked it out. can you say "idiot"? i sure can! now, i'm ahppily waiting for them to reply to my tags. unless those poor kids are all tucked into bed now. altogether now, awwwwww.... how sweet. but hey, i guess it'll be sweeter for me you kick the asses of three gangsters in a verbal fight. i wait patiently for their un-profound replies. time to flame like the human torch! flame on! (okaaay that was lame). 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      time for the usual less-than-a-page sunday blog. maybe i should just cut and paste my blogs for sunday. as usual, stayed at home watching tv, playing computer, and running around my flat's corridors. why the hell do i actually like watching one piece and fastlane so much that i can't miss them every sunday? as i said, the world must be ending. then spent the whole afternoon on the computer. msn abit f*cky today leh. sometimes they state i keyed in the wrong password... only got in after keying in the password like 50 plus times. then went all round the net looking at the blogs of bengs and lians. double urgh. at least now i know that sexx isn't the craziest person this side of the internet. i saw blogs of lovesick bengs, lians deep in love with their beng, and of course, my favourite, female-stalking psycho freaks. i think all stalkers should be put in prison and caned every 4 or 5 hours. that'll teach them. or you could just send them to sexx. or castration, even. and finally, to end this crap. drey, stop mugging at the computer. it be bad. then you will be tempted to drop your books for awhile. in this case, awhile being an hour or so. then you will be knowledge deprived. that be worse. good luck for the prelims! and sayonara to all you other suckers. haha. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so, you want to rant online eh, douchebag? here's what i think. you are a complete douche and i am one hell of a crazy sonofabitch. therefore, u are a gay man and i am sexx. people like you really drive me to the point where i have to write essays to stop myself from breaking something. or killing you, which ever comes first.  so you think it's cool to go tag retarded comments on the blog of someone who rejected you? and your great friends even have a link to the blog that has the label "(spam)". how cool is that? not at all. you're all just like sea hums. disgusting, smelly and useless. rule #1, never send sea hums to do a man's work. if i got some real people who could REALLY insult you and your hums, i think the whole group of you would be lost for words, you douche. plainly because we're men and you're all pendek hums.  and, if the last miyavi cd is sold out, what's the point in longing for that nice handsome man. get some kagrra shit. sure, its not the best but its still second best. and what's the point in getting worked up when you find out that someone has been avoiding you? so what now? you want to lock the person in your house and make the poor fellow be at your beck and call? you think too much for a walking tampon. i say you should go home, sit in front of your computer, go to a porn site and have a wank. you'll feel much better. and if you don't, you can always just turn gay or get a castration.  the point of all this is, you are just plain stupid and infatuated with this "love interest" of yours. not all people want others to wait for them everyday constantly. some may even find it freaky. however, if you keep this up, then sexx will have to come look for you. better sexx than the police, you know. in jail, people will just make you pick up the soap everyday and give you a sore rectum. sexx, however, will smoke a whole pack of fags in your face. then he'll drink a whole bottle of black cat and puke all over you. then he'll show you the finger and a)beat you up and break you up, or b) castrate you. better hope its a.  finally, just on a more sensible note, if you love a special someone, give them what they want. they want manolos? give. they want this other guy? give. they want you out of their life? give. okay i admit i said that for fun. you are still a complete gayboy and a moron. take a good look in the mirror can? then please proceed to bash your head in to mirror till you bleed to death. or sexx can just come over and make it quick. till i see your next testicle-less ranting, loverboy. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woke up feeling like crap. but hey, it WAS a saturday. saturdays aren't meant to be spent lying around at home like a sick dog. went to go get a haircut. yes the mullet is -BACK-. then went home to try and sleep it off till noon. then went to meet drey at cafe cartel. we both ate the carbonara( which is like, the best thing to eat in cafe cartel, to me, i suppose ). then got this stupid rude waiter, ask him for things then he ask us get ourselves. i should have slapped him over his fool head. imbecile.  ate for an hour and talked like crazy people. then went off for a stroll in TM for another hour plus. really got me tired there. i think we must have went to all the shops.  time really flies when you're having fun. then she had to go. one of our first lunches and it had to end so quickly. blah! saw her off at the station. never mind, there's still next week and next month and next year and... you get the point. heeheehee. so later i decided to make my way back to paya lebar for another cock-talking-bull-shitting session. talked crap till 6, then et-mun was kind enough to give me and chew a lift back to tampines. then headed to the arcade to freak around before going to play cs with bengs. bengs suck. we rule. then talked cock for awhile more before going home. urgh i feel bad for spending more time with my friends than with her. i shall go kick myself now, because i deserve it. sayonara, single people. 
    
</post>


</Blog>