<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How does one attain the level of performance/ maturity that we expect from ourselves? More often than not, our expectations will rise as our abilities improve.  So how do we ever feel adequate? By measuring ourselves against others? I don't believe in that, it only enhances our own insecurities and pessimism. Or by accepting ourselves as beings that constantly need progress and advancement. I think the latter sounds more reasonable and more in tune with how humanity works.  But...why do I get the occasional feeling of inadequacy? Is this inherent in our workings as logical human beings? This I have no answers to. Anyone care to shed light on this?
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mondays...are they merely invented just so that we can experience the joy of fridays? I always manage to crawl out of bed on mondays, and rarely make it to work on time (not that I have fixed working hours). On those days that I can't manage to do that, it will usually result in me calling up to work sick :p or taking leave.  This is one of those days when I manage to discipline myself. But I'm just wondering, are there lots of people out there like me? People who get so sick of the routine occasionally that they just don't feel like following the rules set by god-knows-who.  till thursday n friday, sze lin
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That was  totally  misleading.  I actually came on to post another bit of thought, and was really excited to find out I had received my first comment.  Guess what...it was my younger brother!  Enough said...  hahahaha, this is totally depressing, he spoilt my 1st experience of a comment!!  oh well, I gotta live with this for the rest of me life, better get used to it huh.  :P 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh wow! My first web posting!!  haha, feels good leaving my mark on the net for the world to see.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Does everyone have their own soulmate out there somewhere?  Living in a city and spending my pre-adulthood in buzzing cities like Kuala Lumpur, Singapore and Manchester has had an effect on me.  Sure, when you're young and unawares, caught up with study and relationships, life was so easy then. The city was the best place to be in for a young person. Lots of variety and choices. We could get whatever we pleased, whenever we wanted, with the people we want to be with.  However...after working for some time now, and after leaving my school life and all its luxuries, life to me just feels so dark sometimes. That nagging feeling I carry with me throughout the days. Yes, it is there all the time, albeit in a form that isn't easily "seen" or felt.   Only when I've got time on my hands and am alone at home, then will that darkness surface. Yes it is a darkness. A darkness of the mind and soul (shit, I'm starting to sound cheesy). But yeah, it is exactly like that.   Why is it that I'm getting this now? Is it because of work? Or of my exposure to society? Why has this never hit me when I was still studying? Is this part of adulthood? I don't think so and  refuse  to believe that!! Meanwhile, I will be working hard to attain the wholeness of happiness I felt when I was still a kid. And no! To whoever tells me this is part of adulthood and life!! I strongly do not believe in that. Not after tasting the goodness of freedom previously......
     

    
</post>


</Blog>