<Blog>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ~Current Music~ 'When It Goes Down' by Something Corporate ~Current Person~ Sam  Today...hmm....today, I got out of school early at 12 again. Barbera (my bryce teacher) and I talked today about the E-Zine thing I'll be co-directing next year. (I'm excited :) ) He gave me a bunch of books on Flash...omg...they are huge...and long...and fantasticly kewl. *yay*   Oh, and lots of people are still complimenting me on my art in the art show!!! It's so great getting the positive feedback!!! Makes me feel all warm and cheesey inside ;).  I WANT TO GO ROLLERBLADING!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! My foot is mess...I think the blister is going to eat me alive...it looks kinda infected and crap....I need to get it to heal by Saturday...yeah good luck....I want to be able to dance  at prom!!! *rolls her eyes* That was the whole point of going... But anyways, I have had the urge to go rollerblading every day this week, and now I can't....bumms me out man....  I'm also working on Rachel's picture, I'm not sure what I'm going to do with it...I kinda want it to be done, but it doesnt look done. *shrugs* Ah well.  Oh, and Chris and Anil and Sam and I went out to lunch at Mirsch Mirsala today, it was great, I love that place/food. YUMMMM. Cept my stomach was kinda hurting, so I hope I'm not getting what Smauss had ;) It would serve me right though. Chris still seems a little sore about my "breaking up" with him. We weren't technically going out so, it doesnt really count or anything...but...I don't know. I still feel like shit about it..and I think it's starting to come out in my giving him crap about stuff...I rag on him pretty hard, and I keep biting my tounge every time.....I'm going to get myself to knock it off if I have to swollow my tounge to do it! Chris kinda makes me feel unwanted in the group...but thats not unlike Colin, so I guess I'm sortof getting used to it...*winces* If it weren't for Sam, I don't think we would even be on speaking terms.  I also feel like painting...and drawing....or something....I just ...don't have anything to do.....sux moose man..;) 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So I'm at school ....I'm "working" in my Bryce class...its a digital animation and rendering program...its _quite_ exciting. Yep....cept I don't have anything to work on....*is bored* Our schedual is so freaking messed up...Smauss!!! The one day we could have officially had class together you're sick at home!  Both third block classes were together today....it was sorta a slver day, so I couldn't get any of your h.w. . Sorry, dearheart.   So school gets our early at like....uhmmmmmm 12 something, so I'm going to rollerblade (YAY!!!!) up to your house and visit you. Hopefully your stomach ache isn't contageous....;)    .....*is still bored*  I think I'm going to go to 'hold the button.com'.....that sounds like a good use of my time.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      (I'm going to borrow this idea from Colin's Blog)           ~Current Music~ Aerosmith           ~Current Person~ Nobody            I'm supposed to be working on my chemistry homework...but its pissing me off...so I'm procrastinating.   I'm so excited about tonight!!!  Nate(ive known him since before kindergarten, he's one of my greatest friends) is coming over tonight and we're going to play with Premiere, Flash, and Bryce! And I get to drive him home at midnight! ooooo...;) I think my parents are actually starting to loosen up on the driving restrictions....I drove them around almost the entire day today, and we weren't yelling at eachother, so thats an improvement :).   Oh and my dress and jewelery are finally all taken care of for prom. My mom is kinda annoyed, she thinks Matt should pay for something, cause hes just been saying we're going to pay 50/50....even though I have to buy a dress, jewelery, shoes, hair-job, makeup etc all for _his_ prom, now i have to pay for dinner and my ticket?....I dont know, I dont need him to pay for everything, but honestly, _he_ asked me, I think he should pay for _something_. Lol, oh and I also have to get him a boutonier (sp?), and I have no idea how or where to get one...my dad said he'd help, but presently is ripping apart my bathroom....*sighs* my parents are always fixing or remodeling something around  our house...  Ah well. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A part of you has grown in me.  And so you see, it's you and me  Together forever and never apart,  Maybe in distance, but never in heart.  ~ by Anonymous ~ 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      (For anyone who doesn't know me)     I'm a 5'4 girl with short blonde hair and blue-green eyes. My passions are swing dancing, drawing, some writing, telemark skiing, hiking, biking, reading, camping, rafting, water skiing, playing in the ocean, hanging with friends and painting.   (Told you it was short) 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So I'm getting ready to go swing dancing right now...Matt's over, he and I have been carpooling down there and he leaves his car at my house. So after the Charleston lessons, we drove back up to my house where we had dinner, laughed a lot, and now he's working on his Calculus homework and I'm...ermm... "studying" for my grammar test...with none of the things I actually need to study...I'm gonna fail, yeah. But he lets us retake, so I suppose thats okay, it's just gonna be a hassle.  Everyone keeps asking Matt and me if we're going out. They all seem to _know_ that we are...no matter what we tell  them. *rolls her eyes* Cause, ya know, they would know better than the both of us. *Sighs* He's taking me to prom, cause the girl he asked said no ;) Its alright though, cause we're just good friends, and he wanted to go with omeone. So I've got a cute dress (god, I just said  the word _cute_..someone shoot me...).    Of late, I just got dumped by Colin...not sure why, we were dating for what...two weeks? Not even? I don't get it, he really didn't give me a reason, and that ate away at me for some time, but now...I'm over it. Or at least, as over it as I'm going to be. I liked him a lot, yeah, but whatever his reason, I have finally realized that it just wouldn't have worked out. The good thing is I've come to terms with that.   Uhmm....So I'm going back for the social dance in about ten min, and I'll be home late again, sweaty, tired, and happier than I ever am with anyone. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just for your information:        All the posts after this are from my old Blog at my other site, their titles are makred with a:    ~      . 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ~Current _People_~ Without a doubt: Sam, Smauss,  Rachel.  ~Current Music~ It's only a few lines of the  song 'Night Moves' by Bob Seger:             I woke last night to the sound of thunder       How far off I sat and wondered.      Started hummin' a song from nineteen sixty two      Ain't it funny how the night moves      When you just don't seem to have as much to lose.      Strange how the night moves      With autumn closin in...  School's coming to an end. Finally. It has tried to eat me alive this year. Sometimes I think it actually did, and I'm just a faint memory in another surviver's hysterical nightmare.   Yeah, I'm one of those girls who lose themselves in their memories....but I'm not one of the ones who dwell on things long past...I dwell on the here and now...which isn't any better.   It's the fires that burn in our hearts when we're young that cause us so much anguish. We want to become so much, we want to succede, we want to live up to expectations, we want to be unique, we want to be ourselves, we want to be so much...too much...it isn't who we are, it's who we aren't.   There are lessons we learn in life, and we don't always learn them the first time. Sometimes it takes making the mistake a third time...sometimes it takes ten times, and sometimes it takes being assulted to get it into your fucked up head that there are some people you just shouldn't god damned trust. There are some people whose motives you can never really know. Those who keep betraying your forgiveness...the ones who take your power away.  There is so much good in this world, like friends who listen, friends who care, who love, who won't let you keep blaming yourself, who hold your hand with that angry fire in their eyes, that fire you used to have... and yet no matter where you look, it just doesn't seem to want to be found.  3:00 Monday morning, I woke up feeling so alone I might have screamed and not heard a response, 4:00 Tuesday morning, I woke up crying, and I couldn'tremember why... 2:45 Wednesday morning, I woke up shaking, I had been running from something, 3:25 Thursday morning, I woke up with a migraine-level  headache, 4:15 Friday morning, I woke up aching everywhere, mostly in the places drugs can't reach to deaden, 3:55 ~ Last night I woke up shivering, I was cold in a 70 degree room. It's rather like being alone in a room full of people.   It's been a great week for full nights rest...*rolls her eyes* I don't want to be here, all I want is distraction, something to take my mind away. It's people like me who should be being offered drugs, the half dead are likely to take anything. But no, of course not. I'm too good for that, right? That's what they keep telling me, but since when? I used to be too good for that, but now? What am I now? When did I show resolve? Don't I have any willpower anymore? Where does your honor go when you lose it? Does it melt away into the afternoon sun? Or does it just hide beneath the covers, trembling for fear of the monster it sees when it pulls down the sheets?  And when you look in the mirror, you see all you wish you weren't, but have no idea how to change. It's society that's distroyed who you were, when you were young your fire burned so hot you were like to outshine the sun. But you grew up, and so many things happen...and when you think you are the most weak, thats when the fire startes to flicker, and fade. You look at everyone else, and there in the smiling faces you start to see the mask. You always knew it was there, but when it becomes visible...you begin to understand why children hide underneath their covers. There _are_ monsters in this world, my child, but take care, they are all around you; take care that you do not become one yourself. Fire is what they feed on, and only you can fight them.  But I have a question for you all, when is it too late to fight them away? When they're in your heart, or in you're soul?   Ain't it funny how the night moves      When you just don't seem to have as much to lose.  Yeah, hillarious. I dont seem to have as much to lose anymore, and that's the sad thing.  Of the things they tell me are important, I've got my virginity (oh good...Im so fucking happy about that one), I've got my family, and my friends. Can you lose yourself? I have no doubt. Question is, where do you find you again? If you could get away, where would you hide? Hate to say it, but if I could, I'd hide in someone's arms. Haven't I learned that's just a tad bit dangrous? Heh, but since when has learning something's wrong stopped me? If you like someone, and you've got no problems with being with them, why not, eh? Psh...yeah, really. Why.       So I know what I need, I think. I need a safe place to heal. I reread my entries and I'm obviously not in a good environment these days, to put it lightly. 'When I was young, I thought that I could fly, I believed what I hoped for, I had wings and dreams could soar, I just don't feel like flying anymore...' I want to fly higher, but how do I when I haven't got wings, a wind, a sky, or even a ground. So where do I find this safe place? Psh, I bet it doesn't exist. It's inside of me, like so many things these days. The thing that needs healing is inside my head, so that's probably where I'll find the cure? Right? Sure, if there is a 'cure'.  'You can't run, so you might as well hide... Open up, we're coming inside,  What's it feel like to know you're going to die?  So they took me down to the gallows, And this boy he say to me,   Why do you smile when the rope's around your neck? I said I tell you boy when I get back...  I, I, I ain't opposed to seeking justice,  but you're going about it all wrong, the man you're looking for does not exist, he's just a figment of the higher man's tounge...  How are we to know that your not a liar? Don't you see we have a job to do? And our job is the law You fit the description of a criminal crosser We believe that he is you and that is your flaw that is your flaw... that is your flaw...' 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So I was contemplating things while I was driving to and from swing dancing yesterday. I discussed with myself into great detail how when some one gets beaten (mentally) by so many things over such a long time, the "skin of their mind"(forgive the odd metaphor) becomes so intensely bruised underneath the skin that any exertion or pressure can make it break and bleed. Even something as benign as joy or laughter can separate the weak scar-tissue. Because the blood pools underneath the skin and heals so appallingly slowly, these cuts bleed profusely. This, in turn, makes more bruises, scabs and scars, which make the healing process longer. All is never hopeless it seems, because there are some things that cause rapid healing; six steps forward, instead of three, for ever ten taken backwards. One of these things is music. A song that brings you back to another time in your head, a time where life just felt better, a time before the beating. At least, one helped me. The only other thing I know of that helps doesn’t heal, it’s a distraction. Just like when you get a cut, but your mind is busy doing something else, and you only feel the pain when you look at it, the same rule applies: if you can distract yourself from the pain, I think it gets a little more time to heal. ‘Cause it seems like when you stare at the wound, it doesn’t heal. Your attention only digs it deeper, or turns it a nice infected pink color.  Those are the only ones I know of, but I’m confident there are more…I just haven’t found them, or felt them, or cried enough to have earned them I suppose. I’m not one for crying, so if that’s the trick, I’ve got a long way to go. But all this torment is in my mind, I know that. I just haven’t found the place in my head where I can let it all go. It’s like when someone gives you this gift you know you have never liked and never will, but you just aren’t _ready_ to let it go, and after a few weeks go by, you decide to throw it out. I know that’s all it takes; I just have to find that state of mind where I can ‘throw it out’.   ~Even though the actual instigator of the hurting is gone, it will still haunt her nightmares every night. It took her power away, and the only person who can get it back for her, is her.~   Lol, so I've been enjoying myself making designs all over my body ^_^ *grin* Henna is awesome fun, and an awesome _distraction_. The rain has helped too…rain has to be one of the most fantastically wonderful sounds in the world. The thunder, the lightning, the drops falling on the tin roof over our deck…the smell…oh god and the smell….if I had to choose to be deaf or blind, I’d choose blind, I  doubt I could live my life without the sounds of rain. Of course, I’m being melodramatic….but even so, it _is_  amazing.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ~Choice~   And there is a loud cry, “I am!” 	A self assertion that we are more 	Than they say we are. Where we fear an unseen enemy      More than an Auschwitz; Where we risk war to know an adversary      Rather than to know ourselves. When the world drowns in veils and masks      And runs from the vigilante unmasker: 		The philosopher.  		The writer. 		The dreamer.     We murder them,  The ones who doubt the rules of right and wrong Set so assured in blood-spattered stone.      And we murder them: 		The artist. 		The lover. 		The questioning child.   To honor every achievement, To applaud every kind act, To love the face beneath the façade.  And when the child questions     Why we have separate countries,         Why we have boundries,             Why we wage war,               When after all, Aren’t we all humans? 	...and what is it to be human?     The lesson is not to listen, But to hear. The hearts of the untainted are as ingenuous  As they are naïve.  If one voice doesn’t rise up Against the raging flow of society There will be no one to patch up our wounds, Everyone is available But no one does a damn thing. Between morality and self-preservation, 	Take the higher moral ground. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ~This is the Time~   This is the time, This is the dance;  Face it, that question,   What can you be?  Too bad this isn’t your time,  This is a time Where honesty digs you a deeper grave, And lies send you to heaven.     But Hell still costs a heart, a body, and a tear. And you give up everything To pay a debt You never made,  To the hate too deep within you. It’s not knowing who you are, Its knowing who you aren’t. It’s when knowing knowledge that never lasts Is more important than thinking thoughts That make you care.  This is a time where You can bleed to death from a promise broken, And survive in a lifeless body In a world being suffocated by its own hands.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Current Person: Mr. Kipp Current Music: Guns and Roses and Aerosmith: Come Together  Awww Mr. Kipp was so nice today!!! It was SO FREAKING COLD in our w.s. room today, and he let me and sam borrow his sweater and fleece in his closet. It was sooo nice! Smauss and I will be making him a cheesecake, just cuz hes so awesome. Sam! You should help!! We need your spring form-pan too.  Sam, Smauss? I have to talk to you guys, we should have a sleep over, I have to talk about Greg. I don't want to, thats why I havent yet, I need it pried out of me....I just can't bring myself to say it at school, I feel like it needs more time than that. OH, and don't worry, I dont like him again.  "Just like every cowboy sings a sad, sad song..."  I miss herding cattle. I should go become a cowgirl and leave this stupid, depressing life behind. Only thing stopping me is the feeling I can make a difference in this world, and I shouldnt waste my chance. *Rolls her eyes* The one part of me that decides to be an optimist....lol.   N E ways, I'm off to bed. I'm going to sleep for three days straight when school ends, just you watch. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      http://students.washington.edu/moyn/china.html   Yes, I know, I'm insane...but you have to admit, this is freaking hillarious. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ~Current Person~ My mom and dad (yeah i know, two today) ~Current Music~ Fly Higher by Five Iron Frenzy  So I'm feeling pretty lost and confused. Why? Hell, I don't even know why anymore. I have no confidence, no strength, no passion, no joy; all I feel is annoyance, hate, frustration and anger towards everything. School's almost out, and finals are coming. I need to get my mental state under control or I'm going to have another break down during the test week.   God damn...It all just hurts so bad. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Her: "And why are your toe nails neon yellow?"  Me: "I got the urge." Her: "What the hell were you doing to make you want to do that!?" Me: *shifty smile* "Uhhh...well....." 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Current Music: "Every Rose Has its Thorn" by Guns and Roses Current Person: This one goes out to poor, overworked, wonderful Courtney; hang in there girl!   "I'm going to manufacture an injection that shoves joy up your pathetic, melancholy ass until you're so fucking happy you levitate."  LOL, I had a dream and my nonexistant twin said that to me. I think my subconcious is trying to tell me something. I'm sorta depressed, but not really. I just get moody and write to get it out of me. I don't really brood like this in normal life. *sighs* so anyways....I need softer hemp for my necklaces, this kind is too rough...it makes my neck all red.      Hmmm....ran out of things that aren't depressing to talk about. Lol. So I'll just end here to try to get a few less pathetic entries. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ~Music~ Offspring and Rolling Stones  ~Current Person~ The Cheese Fairy  So I think the heat is going to kill me. There is heat at school, heat in my head, and heat in the weather. I'm so tired of school, I just want to leave.  I need to sleep too. I'm exhausted in my head, my body is slowing down, but it can get better with sleep. My head..I dont know what it needs to get engery, but I need it bad.  I'm excited about getting Smuass's pup with her tomorrow. I'll be sleeping over for two nights in a row, I'm really excited, but I'm just so tired its hard to be happy. You know its bad when its hard to feel joy.          Love and hope and sex and dreams        Are still surviving on the street        Look at me, I’m in tatters!        I’m a shattered        Shattered  I'm burning out....this year has been so long and so hard. Next year will be worse, I'm afraid, but I just keep hoping I'll recover over the summer.  I'm excited about going to Egypt too. It will be one of those memories I'll never forget....I'm sure. I've always wanted to go there, but, lol, its hot there too. Go figure. More heat.  I feel weak, drained. Mentally and physically. Each day is a struggle, and I'm getting more and more easily angered. I just snap at sam and smauss a lot, and my anger lasts so long I cant even appologize. I need to find a way to smudge or something to get this nastyness out of me.          Don’t question why she needs to be so free        She’ll tell you it’s the only way to be        She just can’t be chained        To a life where nothing’s gained        And nothing’s lost        At such a cost         There’s no time to lose, I heard her say        Catch your dreams before they slip away        Dying all the time        Lose your dreams        And you will lose your mind.        Ain’t life unkind?   What is the first thing you think of when I say the word:  Rain ?  ~I think of the old black and white movies, where everything is cliche, mysterious, and .....simpler? But are they really simpler? Or is it just our subconcious want of something more romantic, controlled, something where we can expect certain things to go certain ways? Something to rely on? 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ~Song of the day~ How You Remind Me by Nickelback   ~Person of the day~ Smauss          Never made it as a wise man        I couldn't cut it as a poor man stealing        Tired of living like a blind man        I'm sick of sight without a sense of feeling        And this is how you remind me        This is how you remind me        Of what I really am        This is how you remind me        Of what I really am  That's the part of the song that makes it my 'song of the day' I guess. Today I had a terrible day, everything seemed to just be shitty in general, and yet...at the end I seemed to pull it around. One of the hardest things today, for some reason, it was as if I let my guard down and all the hurt I felt about the Colin event tried to drown me. I just kept being reminded of how much I was sad that we broke up, that we weren't friends anymore, how we didn't talk, how I felt like an outsider, how much I didn't want that to be like that, and how helpless I felt to fix it....on top of it all, I had a chem. test, I need to redo half of my Bryce project...which I swear hates me, it keeps getting deleated for random reasons.....God, and I just plain _woke up_ feeling low as Hell. *shrugs* But  today, well...after school, I was riding on the bus with Smauss, and I knew she was tired and was worrying about her own problems, and was just listening to me fume about how I was feeling....but even so, her listening was the best thing she could have done for me. She let me rant and I eventually ran out of steam, and we sat quietly for a while...and I just thought. I thought for a while...and just before my stop, I decide I'm not going to allow him to do this to me..to make me so unhappy. It's _not_ okay, and I _won't_ be sad because of the Colin thing. I refuse to.          And this is how you remind me        This is how you remind me        Of what I really am  That's for Smauss and Colin both. Smauss in a good way, and Colin in a bad-ish way. Smauss reminded me though her support and confidence in me who I am inside, and how I always fight it when people control me like that. Colin reminded me through just plain making me feel like shit, that I won't take that from him, and, more importantly, I won't allow myself to feel like that.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    So much rain...I feel like I'm crying all the time, just never sheading a tear.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink      Your heaven is a lie . 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Yeah. I'm right there.  *Breathes*  Visualize your happy place....
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Pretty Corvette *stares for hours*....
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ~Current Person~ Tony ~Current Music~ That one song I keep calling Fly Higher by FiveIronFrenzy   Yo. I'm at work right now...Ashley told us to go back to the Admin building, and she hasn't showed up...so we're just hanging out. Matt's playing on his new pretty lap top. 'Tis kewl. I've been learning a lot of interesting things about comps these days though, that and doing a lot of grunt work. We've moved over 250 computers by now *rolls her eyes* all over creation, too. Lol, Matt's sorta talking to himself, sorta not, so I never know when to answer. So I just kinda look at him to see if he looks at me for a response, lol, he's an odd one (like me, right?).   SOOO hopefully I'll be able to get my freaking license today, Dad's picking me up early today and we're going to go try to get it at one of two places. I still can't believe I lost my wallet, but it seems like I've been loosing everything these days, shezzz. So has everybody else too, I guess. I'd almost guess Mercury was in retro, but it's not...so I donno, maybe Smauss can ask her mum what she thinks. *Sigh* Well...we're getting paid to sit around I guess, cause I dont know where Ashley is.....Tony is going to beep her on the beepy-phone (nextel). Tony is kewl. He's nice and oh! He told me what a style sheet is!!! Yay-ness....so now I can hopefully figure out how to use it/ if I need to use it for next year's online journal thing.   Yep...   *nods*....    mhmmm.....   So I'm a little lost on what to do now... guess I'll just resort to holdthebutton.com again...lol.   Peace Out. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Current Music: GooGooDolls Current Person: Sam and Nate  I’m home now! Missed it a little, but mostly Sam (and of course you Smauss…but your not really “home”…) Mom made me clean my ENTIRE room, but its pretty good looking now…Sam and I went out to an acoustic coffee lounge, it was really great and we just talked for about an hour and a half about our trips, and then just reminiscing and discussing life and how lucky we were to be such close friends. Then we picked up Nate and drove to another coffee place, The Mug, and Sam got me a biscotti lol. Great time.  I need a pic of you dearie for my wallet. I visited your mum too, helped her w/ the snakey pictures.  Sam and I are gonna take her out for ice cream  some day soon too, cause she’s lonely and misses you. J’kar misses you too. It’s 12:30, I’m tired, so I’m off to bed! Talk later dearie, and if you want, reply to my post on the guild! KissKiss. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey Smauss! (I’m guessing Sam won’t be reading this…) I’m having fun out here in New Jersey, we’ve been fishing a lot, and I’ve caught some gargantuan fish….hehe …that’s a weird word…gar~gan~tu~an… *groan* I lost my sunglasses, and my head is eating me alive…..stupid headaches from sun are the worst. Blue fish taste really good, especially when you catch them yourself and they are really fresh. Yummmm. We went out fluking (fluke is a kind of flat fish, they taste pretty good, but most of them are too small, you can only keep a certain size) and while we were fishing the whaler (a kind of boat) kept making this annoying beeeeeeeeeeeeeee~ing sound, and it wouldn’t fucking knock it off….it goes off when the motor is getting over heated, and we thought we got it to work, but a while later it started up again just as we were about to go out on the ocean! (can you imagine how much it woulda sucked if we were out on the ocean and the engine died? Bummer~uhm~Jim…;) ) So anyways, we went back to Uncle Don’s house and swam in the pool the whole rest of the day with Donnie (my cousin), Tim, and Donnie’s friend Katy (she’s really nice) and she’s inclusive, unlike&nbsp;when&nbsp;I feel like Donnie hates being around me.... . Tim taught me how to play ping-pong, I suck massively, but I was getting better. He is spastically good at pool too!!! We need to go to your grandmother’s house and play, and jump on the tramp and eat ham and drink sobe tea. &nbsp;So now I’m recovering from my head ache and looking out at the sail boat races on the river. You would love it here, I know it. It’s warm too ;). How is the weather out there? Good I hope? I keep looking at the weather for New York on the TV, but I’m not really sure where Buffalo is…&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I’ve been having issues getting on the internet…but I’m doing my best to get on. I have about ten min at a time, and I can never finish what I want to do! So it’s taken me about three days to get the rp post up *rolls her eyes*, just a little frustrating. Well, I’m thinking about you!!! Have you been motorcycling much yet?And have you gone to that one place with the buffalo wings yet?? I miss and love you!!! If you talk to sam on the email, tell her I love her and miss her a lot, and I can’t email her back because I’m having such trouble getting access to the internet.  &nbsp;  It’s very peaceful too, we’re listening to this calming music, relaxing, its not any sort of a rush-around atmosphere like during school. I’m going to miss summer again I know. We have to play our video games, jezz we haven’t gotten anywhere on it. Tim rented this game called Drakenguard, it looks really fun, I think we should play it some time.  &nbsp;  We’re prolly going to go up to NY and see a Broadway play! It sounds kindof fun to me…I wish I could see Victor Victoria. If you ever need to get me a gift, I’d love to have a DVD or VHS of it.  Pop-pop slow dances with me *Grin* ; ) It’s fun, he’s really good. Well I suppose I ought to go do some homework or some odd thing….*rolls her eyes* how about not….you enjoying our reading or anything? Ah, well I miss you.  &nbsp;  We are close in heart,  Step    
     
    
</post>


</Blog>