<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The pain in my heart is ridiculous....I cant take it anymore.  I dont wanna go home and I dont wanna move outta my chair.  He called saying he was waiting for me to come home, but I didnt go home...I went out and stayed out...I need time to seriously clear my head, why do I attract these shady characters?  I can't wait to go and see Steve...I need to get outta NY for a min, I dont think I wanna come home.    I feel like no one understands what I am going through...am I making a big deal out of something really small?  I wish I could hang out with Sikeem after dinner in the city, but I probably shouldn't.  This pain hurts so bad...bad because I let myself become vulnerable....vulnerable for someone who doesn't love me or care about me and it hurts like hell.  Right now i just need time to heal and I dont wanna talk to anyone, I am just hurt.  Leave me alone.............
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This pain is crazy...it's not like a pin where you miss somebody or you feel resentful or you wanna cryyy..its just hurts and it really hurts deep.  I cant explain it at all or anything, I just really want it to go away.  I understand the saying kiss a few frogs, but I think I have kissed a whole stadium full of em and I am just so  tired of this crap.  I am glad that I am going to see Kim and Tori tonight, because I dont wanna be alone tonight.  Why do I act the crazy ways I do?  I am slightly psycho.  Why did I have to go up to his house and ring on his doorbell like I am some ghetto chick without any common sense or up bringing.  WHat has this man brought into my life so necessary for me to act like I have completely lost it?  the answer  is nada and the answer is I wish he would just fukkin dissapear. I dont want him to call me for his bag, dont want to see him in my eye view ever again.  He hurt me.  This whole sh*t was a big lie once again.  And it seems that no matter how much I put up the wall of defense, it always seems to get blwon up with a bomb...it's just too much.  If i can help it, I refuse to sleep at my house again for the rest of the week...or even ever....I wish I could shack up with a friend somewhere in Jersy for atleast a month, the pain and the memories are too frikkin annoying!  God, I know you see me typing this...And I understand the lesson and no, I am not mad or remorseful at you because I can handle it all, you bult me like a mac truck and I am truly grateful....but please, show me what I need to do next time...and please right now just cover me with your love and your knowledge....take this crazy aspect out of my soul....I wanna be a rational person...although Trev isn't perfect, I totally see the same imperfections from 6 years ago that messed up that relationship as well.  God, please tell me what I need to do.  I wanna be marrried one day, I want that man to love me and I wanna treat him right, not push him away like  the rest.  I am just scatter brained right now, God please, whoever he is...let him have a kind heart, because you know how frail I can be....and the heartache is becoming so unbearable...but like the others....3 months from now, I will look at this blog and laugh and reminisce about the stupid shit I did...every day I get stringer and smarter.  I remember my lowest point, sitting in that basement in Ms. Edwards house, no job, being disrespected by that dude, no car....and look how the Lord has blessed me.  I am truly happy, I just gotta cut the uneccessary baggage outta my life, I will make it.  Back to square one...
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How do I feel today....it really goes up and down.  I am feeling positive about a few things and uncertain about others.  I can honestly say for the first time in my life...my self-esteem is at all time high....even though I have gained ten pounds...I look in the mirror and I actually love what I see.  I have the prettiest eyes and the cutest smile.  When I was younger...I always felt so UGLY and awkward....but I know for a fact that all of the stress I went thru as a child...it was never in vain, all of that stress I went thru in HS...NOT In VAIN.  My life is actually happier...and although disappointing things still do happen, I guess I deal with it better.  I guess I am just in a better place in my life right now.  But as usual, since 2000, my love life is just rocky.  I am just starting to realize that it has something to do with me.  What am I putting out there, how am I behaving in these relationships?  I am not gonna lie, I am sometimes envious when I hear that women have been with their boyfriends for like 4 years and I cant hold a relationship down for more than 6 mos at a time...whatever.  I basically just have to re-evaluate a few things.  I haven't spoken to her in a min...and I cant front, I don't think I miss her that much....or maybe I do...we basically grew up together...we saw each other at our lowest moments.  I think she has seen me cry more than my mama has.  I called her, but didn't hear back from her.  I left her a msg about VA, lets see if she calls back.  I am just so excited that I will be hanging out with my homie for July 4th weekend.  He is someone that will be in my life forever.  We are weird just alike and also very expressive and appointed.  I love him...I don't think there was ever a time he hasn't been there for me.  Tonight...going to da gym, then heading over to Loci's for a quick BBQ.  TMW, BBQ at Garys then Shanis b-day party...Sunday is wit mama.  Who knows what  the weekend will bring?  Will I see him...do I secretly want him to fall to his knees, cry and tell me he loves me...he is sorry and wants to marry me and would I do it right on the spot....YEAH, cuz I am crazy...but I know it wont happen...just my crazy thoughts I tell ya...LA LA LA
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just wrote mad stuff and I am so mad that it got erased!  basically, Trev called mad times yesterday and threatened teh kid!  Why do I deal with these losers?  The crazy thing is that I was falling in love with him.  He was cute and cool.  But it's not like I dont know his pat with Courtney and Raine...he likes to use girls in  this sick sadistic way.  Let's just say that sometimes I am glad that it is over....What I am really glad about is that I dont have to spend my day wondering what the hell he is doing? Was I alwys this paronoid?  I can't wait for the day when I meet my soulmate and everything just feels right - the only person that it ever felt all right with was Kyle.  I love him and I still do!  Work was crazy today...preparing for the MAs.  I have so much work to do...but that is a good thing, I am in a much better space than I was in last year around this time.  Thank you God for answering my prayers.  I sent Anthony and Trev Fathers Day cards today, I  thought that was a nice gesture.  Today, I am gonna gym it up then rest.  I really need to go and visit my mama...I haven't seen here in a hott minute!  I will go and see her Sunday.  Life is so crazy, you never know what it has to offer you around the corner...
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's amazing how you can go through the same thing like 10 times abd take something different away from it each time.  I am 25 now, and I turly believe that I am stronger than ever now in my life.  I think that incident with Trev taught me so many things about life and what I will and will not accept.  I have seen my mom go through so many things with men and wondered while she dealt with it....now that I am a woman I kind of understand what she was going through at the time.  Today, he called me.  And even though I have been day dreaming about him all day and I shed a few tears on the subway....I realized that he is not what I want in my life.  I have alway sbeen attracted to the under dog...the people who are going thru teh struggle...the guy who is rough around the edges....  They usually don't make as much as me...don't speak the best english and probably dont know much about culture.  I have realized that it is definitely time to change the game up and deal with a brother on my level...I deserve better, I wanna arry better.  This day is the beginning of a new life for me.  I wanna get my head right, my body right, my relationships right...  Also, I am not focusing properly at work....surfing th einternet too much!  Wendy, it's time to perform for the job and life that you want!
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God is good all the time, not some of the time or on the weekend....but all the time.&nbsp; These anxiety attacks that have been killing me since a teenager have gone away....thanks to the help of Xanax.&nbsp; Like actually, nothing really gets to me emotionally anymore and I prayed to God for that solution...and he gave it to me.  As for Trevor, it is a wrap.&nbsp; He played me so bad last night that I am convinced I would have had a nervous break down if my good friend Xanax wasn't in my life....then has the nerve to type me this email this morning:    No disrespect, but I would appreciate a great deal if you allow me to see you on Saturday and da following weekend! Please advise       &nbsp; Okay, now is this fool crazy.&nbsp; Does he realize what he did to me last night?&nbsp; Does he think I am a sick, weak fool....no homie, you were mstaken and I am on to you!&nbsp; Your never deserved me in the 1st place and whoever she is can seriously have you.&nbsp; It's a wrap.&nbsp; Then the fool has the nerve to call me and leave me a voicemail with the same question....HA HA...fool, I got your message and I will never respond to you nor do I ever wanna see you again as long as I live....beat it!  I entitled this blog "restoration" because this is the beginnning of getting sh*t together.&nbsp; When I was with Trevor...it's like I was in a serious daze and I forgot about all the important people and details in my life.&nbsp; Especially my best friend Roxi...I love that girl and I dissed her for him?&nbsp; What the heck was wrong with me?&nbsp; This has taught me such a valuable lesson.&nbsp; Never put any body especially before God and the prmises you made to him and especially the beautiful people that he blessed you with in life like your mama....never again.&nbsp; I will take this time to be a strong person, get my life together....finances in order...complete my therapy...so when "he" comes along I will be ready....so really ready.&nbsp; Vera is right and is always right...I just didn't want to believe her. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally did what I always wanted to do....I spoke to a therapist today.&nbsp; Her name is Ms. Janice Packer.&nbsp; It went well and she diagnosed me with Anxiety Disorder and prescribed Xanac to me.&nbsp; Let's hope it works...  Today is the talk with Trev.&nbsp; In the beginning, I wanted him back and my anxiety order also encouraged that.&nbsp; Who knows what he will reveal to me today...but as the therapist said, I am a strong woman who has endured so much.&nbsp; If I can conquer those things, then there is nothing he can tell me that will make me wanna die.&nbsp; God is accompanying me on this talk, so I know in the end I will be fine.  Details to follow................. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have triggerred those anxiety attacks again...the one that I found I had when Greg did what he did to me.&nbsp; My whole body is in pain and I dont know what to do.&nbsp; I speak to Trevor tmw and I dont want the situation to get any deeper than this...because if it does, I may get very ill.&nbsp; If I keep feeling like this, I am gonna go to the emergency room...  I am asking you Jesus Christ, please save me.&nbsp; I am dying, I cant function, it hurts all over.&nbsp; Who am I, where did I go....I am shaking now and I am getting scared.&nbsp; I better go... 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      out there somewhere or have I already missed him.&nbsp; I knew the break-up with Trev was gonna happen eventually, but it hurts a little bit now that he is gone.&nbsp; I loved him, even though he didn't love me and I am realizing that now.&nbsp; Is it that I am such a bad person that I will never have a successful relationship?&nbsp; yes, I was paranoid with him, but look how the relationship started off on shady grounds.&nbsp; I should have let him go in the beginning, but I just felt this connection with him....damn, I love the man, but there is so much "stuff" to him! His baby mama....he refuses to share, his daughter...wont really comment and then RAINE....c'mon.&nbsp; How much can a woman take...love aint suppsed to feel like this.&nbsp; I let you drive my car, live with me for like no money and you wanna gimme drama...well Mr. Gilmore, it was fun, but now I must let you go...because I come first and I am&nbsp;soooooooooooooo NOT happy and I was tired of feeling that way.&nbsp; VERA was right, right, right!&nbsp; Now I have to drop his sneakers off to him, which is gonna be painful, but well worth it.&nbsp; I want him to go away, and now it is time for me to raise the bar in my life and not deal with people who would treat ANYONE in shady ways as he did.&nbsp; I got the phone call from that girl for a reason and I should have taken heed to it.  I want a man now, NOT a liitle boy.&nbsp; A gentleman that will hold the door for a woman, give up his seat for an old lady....never curse or disrespect his woman.&nbsp; I know he is out there somewhere, vera said he is there too.&nbsp; ANothing in my life that I went thru and shed tears for was in vain.&nbsp; I learned from it and always workedout better for me in the end.&nbsp; When I meet that man I will cherish him and tell him he was worth the wait.&nbsp; So although I was hurt in the begginning of the blog, I AM FREEEEEEEEEEEEEEE.&nbsp; He just wasn't the one, even though he appeared to be.&nbsp; I still love him though.&nbsp; By next month, this shouldn'thurt as much.  So right now, I will cure myself of this hurt, go back to school, get this weight off, start volunteering again...so when he comes along I will have something to put on the table...because Vera already told me he was a gentleman and that is exactly what I am looking for.&nbsp; All I have to say is that God is good and he gives you the truth when you ask for it...al you have to do is see it for what it is and believe!  Where is my friend Steve?&nbsp; I have been calling him all week and I have heard NOTHING from him at all!&nbsp; I am getting worried.&nbsp; Stay tuned... 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's finally over.&nbsp; That confusing state in my life has finally come to an end.&nbsp; Although before when we broke up, I would want him back secretly.&nbsp; This time I have finally made up my mind.&nbsp; I was tired of crying and tired of feeling that pain in my belly that just wouldn't go away.&nbsp; I loved Trevor, but I hated certain thing about him.&nbsp; I hated the fact that he treated Rain so purely.&nbsp; I hated the fact that I would see him peer over at other women occasionally, I hated the fact he refused to go out of his way to do anythig kind for me.&nbsp; I just basically did not feel loved and I honestly felt that he was a con artist.&nbsp; My gut feeling may be paranoia, but I refuse to live my life feeling uncertain about somebody that lives with me and who I trust with my vehicle.&nbsp; When I saw Levar do what he did with my car...it was truly an eye opener.&nbsp; That girl could be me.&nbsp; Right now I am just trying to focus on me and breathe again.&nbsp; Although I miss him, I refuse to put myseld in a situation so quick.&nbsp; I love Trevor yes, but I sure love Wendy a lot more.&nbsp; And rather than reflect on this situation, I am gonna just move forward and do my thang.&nbsp; Good luck to you Trevor...I wish you the best in life.&nbsp; Hopefully, you get your sh*t together, take care of your daughter and getto know God! 
    
</post>


</Blog>