<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey*  We just arrived at Mandys house safe and sound! Right now she is going picture crazy!!! (Nice ones of Uncle Larry)There was alot of Traffic on the way because a tractor trailer toppled onto its side! *Uh Oh* Im staying here...In wincheseter for a week! SO Have fun what ever ure doing!  -Marisa-   
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hey! Tomorrow morning I am leavin to go stay a week w/ my cousin at Winchester :-) Its gunna be fun!!! But Im going to miss everything about this tiny little place!!! All the Avalanche Games I'll miss and all my friends KRIS MOLLY KELLY TESS RAT EVERYONE ( I left out about 5 gazillion )! For *you* I hope you have fun at camp be a good kidd!!! I love ya lots and Im glad that we started talkin again!! U mean lots to me, and whatever u decide to do about your *situation* Im there 4 ya! I kno yall probably wanna know who Im talkin about but I aint tellin you! Cause it my secret. And tew Grey Im sorry for the ~5~ times that I have turned you down! Maybe u should let me ask u to go places instead! But ure cool w/ me! Anyways its off tew packing!  Luv,  Marisa  
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hey*  Just got backform gymnastics and I am exhausted.Im talkin to Molly online! MUAH GURL! Anyways, this week has been alotts fun Sunday mandy got in town and I finally got to see her Monday afternoon. We played all day (shes done stuffed her self...with cantoloupes!!!)And then there was the nightmobile with the flashligh on the end. Great times, OMGOSH MANDY THE DEVIL ES CALLING ME NAME AND MY PARENS DONT LIKE IT!!! ( Raindrops keep fallin on my head *drip drop*) Great Great Great, congrats on gettin farther w/ the Daniel situation. Then after a whole "Fat Peeg" saranation we went to bed at about 4. AND DIDNT WAKE UP TIIL 12 CUZ THE EVIL RATS!! Then it was of to mommy ruthies (Ba Ba Ba Ba Ba IM Loven It) Then we swang...high in the sky...untill I toppled and rolled off. Then we got online and took pictures hahaha man look at the DEMON BABY and the EVIL KANGAROO!!! Penguins go EEEKKKKK. Those slippery little varmits swell up fast! QUICK HIDE  EVERYTHING  jajajajajaja ( as the......) And he wasnt even half way down the steps. OMGOSH MY BOOBS!!! MAN! Well mandurber had fun!  -Marisa-  AKA- Rissafer  
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hey*  Im sitting here waitin for Mandy to get here, who knows where she is. This weekend was fun. The original plan was that I would go to Alex's on Friday at about 5 but then...someone i/m'ed me and was like wanna go to the Avalanche Game? SO I picked up Ali (Alex) and it was off to the game. It took us like 30 minutes to even see a person we knew and it was **** (HEHE Im not using names just to keep ya on ure feet) and I dont think he remembered me so I was like AAAA what the heck. Then I saw Walters and there was this guy with him that looked sooo familiar but Ic ouldnt quite remember who it was, so eventually he came over and *re*introduced him self as ******* and i was like ooooooo and we talked and all that Jazz. Then **** came back over and he was like hey ( i guess he all the sudden remembered me?) we talked and then after a while decided to go sit down. We wanted to find ******* so we kept leavin ****. But I always came back to ****. Anyways Im not givig all the juicy details. I'll tell you more if anything happens out of that. Last night (Saturday) We went to Thunder Valley and well well well if **** wasnt there! But we didnt tak like at all. But it was still there. And today we went to The Creek, me ALex and Kelly! KELLEYFER!!!! My love. I love that girl sooo much and dont worry about Jim things will work out like u want theem to and if not Im always here 4 ya! ALI he so much fun w. ya thanks 4 tht great times. Kell we can go fishin' wheneva u wanna just call me up and we can catch the "golden fish" haha nice  Luv,  -Marisa-  aka-Rissafer  
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       HHEEYY*  Nothing better to do than sit here and talk to my crush!! HEHE u knew I was feelin it on the couch hahahahahah insider u wudn understand!  -Marisa-  aka:.:.:.:.rissafer.:.:.:.  
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey*  Its about 10:56 AM and I just got up. I feel like CRAP, so I will probably have to go to the doctors. Mandy comes in like 3-5 days Im not quite sure btu Im excited!! So...Im talkin to this guy online that I talked with 4 a while and then kissed, and then he was like I DONT LIKE YOU, and so I go to the baseball game and he comes up out of no where and pushes me and Im like UM OK! But that doesnt matter b/c theres this even hotter guy! And my modo is what happens in the past stays in the past! Well In out Peace*  -Marisa-   
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am waiting for SOMETHING to happen in this boring day, I refuse to go outside its muggy, and wet, and hott!!! So i'll sit here and wait for possibly nothing. Im wondering (randomly) why should you fear death. . .I mean its not like anything bad will happen to you AFTER your already dead! And you will probably most likley go to an even better place than here! I doubt heaven has pollution, crime rate, and drug trafficking!! Anyways. . .Im out of here!  luv -Marisa-  
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hey There* Well It has been just a DELIGHTFUL day! I have only been to 4 doctors appointments. Yeah, well Im just estatic about my cousin (Mandy) coming! Hasnt really been much to do today if you know what I mean. But I am excited because i get to start back at gymnastics tonight! I did it for 6 years and then. . .stopped! But I cant wait to finally go back. Right now there is nothing better to do in my life than talk to guys on i/m. This year was interesting for guys, I only had 1 real relationship and even that only lasted for um. . .4months!That was Kyle and, im not the type so sit and yearn on him because it was I who dumped him and moved on! There were other guys, Ben ( 1 week ) Keegan ( 1 Day )Yes, I have realized that in relationships I dont even see a reason to *go out* in middle school. I mean honestly what are you gunna do...go to a movie. Even thats a waste of time because your PARENTS have to take you. But Im in Highschool now so that doesnt matter! I only date older anyways. Well I hoep you have a great day! .:.:.:.Love Always.:.:.:. -Marisa- 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey Ya'll***   Okay heres my weekend so fa...friday we ((me and Jess)) went to Salem after 5 which was quite eventful :-)...WHen it was over we ((me,jess,sam,maddie,morgan,cody,and shane)) Decided to roam the streets of Salem in search of a resturant!~~ I saw JayBay ((Jason)) hes been in the Navy for a while! ANYWAYS we ended up going to the Mill Mountain COffee shop where morgan and Maddie hooked up :-) tehehehe. Cody boy!!! YOU ARE A FINE PIECE OF MEAT!! Anyways then it was home to Jess' man we locked ourselves out at like 2 in teh morning~~ It was great tho but ill be out now!!!   Love yOU!   Rissafer  
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Howdy :-)   Yes Yes I know its been a while but o well! Im sitting here at my house bored as ALL!! We go back to school August 25th woop woop Im goin to highschool! AHH Im kinda nervous but at the moment thats the least of my worries! I havent written latly because well I havent exactly felt the happiest about my life or anything about me. I know right. . .Its a "teen stage" but Its really not and I dont know what I would have done with out Kristin, Mollz, and Kelleyfer!!! Thank yall soooooooo much 4 listenin to me thru everything! Kristin went on a cruise and got me a music thing!!! WOOP WOOP and Kell babes CONGRATS on you and Jim back 2gether! Mollz congrats on "talkin" with you know who!!! I have a b/f now too! Spenser...MUAH, but my lil buddy! I will ALWAYZZZZZZZ Love you cause you live under Risa's bed!!! HEHE Well I'll write more when theres more to write about!   Luv Ya Dearyl   ...:::Risa:::...  
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey*  Sorry its been so long but Im at Mandys. Its really fun here, yet so different! I mean everything about the two places is opposite...they like punk we like rap...they dress sooooo different than us!!! Some guys were even wearin girls jeans! Its crazzy :)...But anyways most everyone went off to camp this weekend, yess Im talkin about u Kelleyfer!! I hope that ure having a blast! But Ive also been missing ***** this week while ive been gone! But we'll see what happens with that! Ali baby is going out with Brandon... wonder if it'll last! Well Im out, more later PEACE!  -Rissafer-   
    
</post>


</Blog>