<Blog>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Football (or Soccer to the uncouth north Americans)  England's playing Croatia as I sit here at work, England lead 4-2 and might actually win a vital game for a change. I am sure all my colleagues think I am in sane, I sit here groaning and sighing, cheering (not too loudly) at every chance missed and foul, every close call.  I don't follow football all the time (rugby's my game) but this is England, my home my land. I don't know how can explain it any better. I am sure others love their homeland too, but there seams to be something about England that green and pleasant land. An Englishmans belief that God lives there, that almost certain knowledge that whatever happens England will be there.  I know many who might read this will no doubt disagree or even cuss at me. But these last fifty years something has remained dormant, sleeping but if it ever awakes then the world I fear will be shocked. English nationalism.... Many think England a spent force, an empire in decline or gone.  When the English awake, with dreams of empire, then all should worry, all should tremble, for these peace loving English can still bring to bear that mighty sword, bringing down all, be it Hilter, be it Neolpeoan .... England did bring them low in their hour of victory.   I know the above may be pompous but remember well June 18th 1815..... Come on Ye noblest English...
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Feeling sorry for myself today....  Got a property tax bill and a car insurance bill yesterday some $7500 combined. They really know how to sick it to ya!  On another note... The Canadian elections are getting closer and I get to look at all the parties as an outsider. I can't vote (not a citizen yet), but I read the papers, watch the TV and have to say that Canada has some of the most incompetent politicians in the world. More concerned with telling you what the other canidates are going to do rather than there own policies.  I watched the televised debate on Tuesday evening, I have never seen such a rude bunch of people, this was not a debate be a yelling match.....  Well Goto go...
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Has anyone ever noticed that the harder you are forced to work, you achieve the least. But the converse is not true, when you are not pushed to deliver, then you don't.  The thing is, is there a happy medium?  Another thing how do you describe a multi node supply chain network in terms sinks and sources, that makes sense to someone who can only think in terms of warehouse and store
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I really don't what a BLOG is.... But everyone seams to be creating one, so as the band wagon rolls along I decided to jump on.  Just to introduce myself...  I am recent arrival in Canada from the UK. I work for a medium sized food retailer in western Canada as a systems analyst.  My hobbies include wasting time, drinking beer (or wine if there is no beer available), Reading just about anything (I've been known to read cereal boxes when I can't find anything else). Oh and annoying people on the internet by publishing a random collection of thoughts. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>