<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink stuff is everywhere     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     A vorpal mass of swirling chaos slowly begins to spin into neater pockets of relatedness, lists lengthen and are checked slowly off. Contents of emptied drawers are slowly sorted and compacted. Emotions and plans and uncertainties slowly pass into one: it is almost time, I will soon be sent forth. Slowly! Slowly, I am getting ready for the next phase of my life... 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this blog coming soon!!!
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well that thing where you start to realize you're actually leaving is actually happening to me now. We went to eat Chinese Food last night. I love that in America, when you want to enjoy some American food before you leave, you go eat at an Italian place, a Mexican place, an Australian place. And Whataburger (several times).  Today I will say bye to many people and spend this evening doing the last bits of packing. Dad is going to grill something for dinner.  Anyway, I got up kinda early so that I could start getting a bit closer to German time. I am going to eat some Honey Nut Cheerios. Maybe I should put a box of those in my suitcase. I keep thinking "I should bring this with me". Also that cookie cake Becca and Mom made. They need to make me some of those to take with me. But the suitcases are packed, and stuffed quite full! So I hope everyone enjoys all their AMERICAN STUFF a little bit extra on my behalf this year.  Breakfast time.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink my room and our homeshrine     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Can I put our living room, couches, homeshrine, and room into my suitcase? 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink missing the sound effects     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Can I put Zach and the playmobiles in my suitcase? 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink Weirdo and Birthday Girl with Family     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     this is just a really swell picture of some really swell people who agreed to let me take a picture next to them. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink WE LOVE GRANDMA MINNIE!!!!!!!     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Having a bit of birthday cake, made by Becca. Do they have cookie cakes in Germany? Saurkraut cakes? 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink mom packs, i take pictures     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     we're working on it. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was super nice to see everyone who came. Thanks for coming, people who came. I am lucky to have so many really good people to support me and see me off. And bring me presents.  Below are many photographs of the weekend. There are many more at http://flickr.com/photos/andrew_/. I did not post a certain picture here, because Dad didnt want me to spill the beans... about why the beans tasted so good! Everything else tasted really good, and not because it was spilled all over the floor (oops! sorry Dad), and I hope everyone had as much to eat, and as much fun, as I did.  At this moment there are stacks of clothes and a few other piles of things assembled upstairs in the computer/school room. Things are coming together, but there's a lot more to do to be ready for Friday. And its still just beginning to dawn on me that I will soon be in Schönstatt. Everyone being here at our house made me realize more than ever that home is with the people you love and are related to. So going to Schoenstatt will be the biggest homecoming of my life. So right now the main part I'm worried about is getting from Frankfurt to Koblenz, and then being sure that I have enough underwear and Advil to last a year!!!
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink Molly, Polly, St. Paul, and Me     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Circle the one who doesn't belong!  Hint:  The weirdo in the middle who still has to go earn his halo. (ME) 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink Too Much Hair     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     My godson and his godfather. (This is actually the best of about seven similar photos.) 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink Joey and Weirdo     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Bye Joey! Bye everyone! Smile and say SAURKRAUT! 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink Irina likes this kind of beer a lot     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Yes, Mr and Mrs Rakalina, the girl with the Miller Lite is your daughter. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink Setting up     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Lovely decorations! 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink People get here     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     there were lots of nice people at my party. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink Esteemed Guests     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Nice party. :-) 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink Flashy Room     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Some of the wonderful young people in attendance. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink I need a Haircut     Originally uploaded by  urlLink and_rew .     Nice new blanket. 
    
</post>


</Blog>