<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Got this offa pcsphonetones.com... I could not have said it better, Thanks Jason..  Message: Everyone, I believe is entitled to their own opinion. I don't think the best decisions have been made (but I don't think they have been in any administration). Hindsight's 20/20, and I don't envy anyone who has to make decisions on a global level. There are thousands of people involved in the decisions for which Bush is commonly blamed, but since he's the final word, he gets the finger pointed frequently. In my opinion he's doing a fantastic job. Gore would have been sending Jimmy Carter to Afghanistan to try to peace talk to the mountains. Do we need to police the world? No, but the UN's not going to do it. Would diplomacy normally work? Yes, but not with Iraq or North Korea, rational people have to deal with other rational people for diplomacy to work. Does a large portion of the middle east hate us? Yes, but when did they not? Are gas prices high? Sure, but Kerry wants a 40% federal tax increase "to curb your usage", yes, like taxing tobacco has curbed it's usage, meanwhile SUV sales are as high as ever with $2+ gas prices, and Kerry's flying around with two passengers and a crew in a private jet, sucking down gas like a 1972 cadillac four door riding on the rims, and towing a tank. Conspiracies abound, and I can only ask that you not put your approx. $8 in the hands of Michael Moore. I mean, hey, that's 4 gallons of gas.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Seems like most businesses these days are starting to follow a new operating model. It appears to me that customer service and integrity are declining and this is due to this new operating model. This new operating  model of which I am speaking is the tendency of companies to let the accounting department drive the business plan (especially publicly held companies). I believe that this, in major part, is responsible for the negative (IMHO) downturn in the practices of corporations. When you let a person who's sole concern is  for the financial well being of the company dictate how the company is to operate, then there is no doubt that customer service will decline. An accountant is not employed to look out for the customer, he is employed to make sure that the books and ledgers of said company are complete and correct. In this task he is  invaluable, but the same accountant wondering how he can save the company money this quarter, can impact the product/service of the company. Follow me on this: If a company that is producing a taco pizza, (you can imagine which) is told by the accounting department that instead of putting 10 olives on the taco pizza, we can put 9 and that change alone will save us $100,000 world wide this quarter, then you can imagine that in a couple years the accounting department will 'nickel and dime' the value of this product down to something that is not very pleasant to eat.  This phenomenon is widespread and in most every field of business. I would say however that there is another culprit in this downturn in customer service: Volume. These days with multinational corporations and huge companies that are servicing millions of customers, it is a logistical and managerial nightmare keeping things together, offering good value for the product.. let alone good customer service. I venture to guess that it is just the path of least resistance to let the Accounting department drive how the business operates.. after all, they keep saving the shareholders and or owners money.. Right?
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Unions are outdated. Auto Unions. Gov Unions. Teachers Unions. There arn't any 10 year olds working 12 hour shifts anymore.. Anywhere you get a bunch of people together for the express purpose of blackmailing an industry into giving its employee's (union members) things that it cannot afford, and thereby risk its ability to compete.. Well, I don't understand how anyone can think this is helpful to the country.. You have this huge outcry by the  Workers in this country, "NO MORE SENDING JOBS OVERSEAS" "NO OUTSOURCING".. Well Smart People.. You are pricing yourselves right out of the market.. Do you think that a company which cannot afford your high rates and all the taxes in this country wants to go out of business? No, so what are they gonna do.. Go where labor is cheap, and the taxes are light.. Unions are a victim of their own success.. DOH! You cannot just VOTE your way to being rich! It does not work.. You'll see, SUCKERS..  BTW: SURPRISE! I am not a union member, I make good money, and oh yea.. I have not had nor asked for a raise in 2 years.. I know that my employer cannot afford to give me a raise.. so guess what? I am tightening my belt, and sucking it up, working overtime without asking for compensation so that my employer will remain competitive and not outsource.. You gotta give a little to get a little, and give allot to get allot.. Cause and Effect. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So Mr. Rumsfeld is catching hell because he kept a terrorist incommunicado for 7 months.. or a year.. or 10 years.. whatever, you can tell it's an election year, and the Democrats are workin it. I mean face it.. if you let the enemy (terrorists) know that you have an important prisoner of theirs, then they will change any plans that that prisoner might have known about.. so as to make having the prisoner worthless as an intelligence source... Isn't that what the press has been whining about?? That we did not have the intelligence that we needed to avert 911?? And by the way, wasn't the Left side of Congress giving the President all kinds of grief about not having good intelligence.. You Can't Have It Both Ways..  --> Me
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Big Fan of Robert Heinlein.. got the title for this blog, from a character's description in his book "The moon is a harsh mistress".. Here is the full quote: A rational anarchist believes that concepts such as 'state' and 'society' and 'government' have no existence save as physically exemplified in the acts of self-responsible individuals. He believes that it is impossible to shift blame, share blame, distribute blame.. as blame, guilt and responsibility are matters taking place inside Human Beings singly and nowhere else. But being rational, he knows that not all individuals hold his evaluations, so he tries to live perfectly in an imperfect world... aware that his effort will be less than perfect yet undismayed by self-knowledge of self-failure.  My (and RAH's) brand of thinking is not quite politically correct, but it is usually backed up by common sense, and or facts.. In other words I try to keep my mouth shut unless I have something worthwhile to say.. We'll see.. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh.. Right.. I'm the only one here..
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I would like to know how anyone thinks that John Kerry is going to get anything done.. I have listened extensively to this guy, and he speaks only in the most vague of terms. He offers no solid plans, makes veiled references to what he thinks, targeted at what ever constituency base function he is at, and never-ever says "HERE: this is how it is going to work". Gee.. I don't know maybe he is SO smart that he will just sort of wing it - but that makes me uncomfortable, we are at WAR, or at least we have a major anti-terrorist effort underway. John Kerry and his little buddy, what's his name, are both lawyers.. perhaps they will sneak into the enemy's camp and litigate them to death, or if that is not what the pollsters say they should do then, well, whatever will get them another 4 years.    In a Democratic Society: Why are democrats called democrats, and republicans called republicans.. MMM Perhaps a definition is in order:  The United States of America is a Federal Republic:    1. Federal Republic: A federal republic is a republic constituting a union of constitutionally recognised self-governing sub-units called states.    The Democracy part is that we have elections:    1. Democracy: A democracy is a form of government in which ordinary citizens may take part in governing, in contrast with a monarchy or dictatorship.    I believe that a republican is interested in the Republic, meaning that the individual States are of paramount importance, and that they should be able to decide what is good for the people that live in them.. The idea is: Minimal Federal Government..  To contrast this:  I believe that a democrat is interested in this grand democracy that lifts up the common man.. Why do we let these states have any autonomy at all? We should run it all right here in DC! In fact we should just employ all Americans in the government regardless of worth or value.. and then this grand experiment will come to fruition. We are half way there already: check out the statistic on how many government employee's there are.. Along those lines check out this definition and see if you make the connection yourself. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Communism    So you can see the fundamental difference here, and for that reason alone I mostly vote Republican.. but also caring about our country, I do not want to see it go into the hands of two lawyers, who are democrats, who cry about coming from poor beginnings, but who are in reality are both - each much more wealthy than Bush.. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>