<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dont stop the feeling in the shin dig.....guuuuuuuys...wuts going on in ur lives..the only way i can find out is if u post....cuz im too lazy to ask in person....soo..basically...post...bye
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yo yo. sooo today was pretty fun. started off reeeeally boring but in the end it was grand. my mom woke me up at like 9 tis morning so i could get ash with her. (even tho ash wouldnt be done for another hour or so.) finally the time came to get her. we got her, droppped her off, then went home again. i sat on the freakin couch for another 3 hours. no wait...4. then my mom and i walk out to get aumt barbara only to find pat and jesse in my driveway. which was good cuz we planned to go to the mall and see a movie. which we did...went to the mall...then went to pat's house to watch 50 first dates. it's a funny, yet depressing kinda movie. so all in all it was a pretty dern fun day.   so Brad and Christina r comin up tom proooobably around 1ish. its pretty cool.   oh man...yesterday...the kid at the concert. wut was his name? Richy was it? w/e...ne way that was kid was craaaaazy. he never eftus alone. ok..maybe like...twice he'd leave only to come bac in 2 min. ugh! but he was nice. then there was--aww man..i didnt get his name--ne way the band manager. he was cool. Christina pushing that skateboard into his head. oh man...thats was great. GREAT.who else...oh yeah! the kid in the star shirt who gave me all those waterballoons...he was cool. the the kid who broke his leg/kneecap/arm. w/e the crap it was. i caaant seem to think of ne other "friends" we made. i think thats it ne way. man, some of those kids were jerks tho. they were soo...sweary...and they cussed a lot. "cussed" its a new learn i word today. (lol ash) well thats mostly it...i say mostly cuz i kno there's sumthin i missed. but ne way...c y'all tom. leeets go to the pool. it's supposed to be nice ne way...see y'all! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Mmmm.....the skin on Nicole's baaack...  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm totally taking a break from Blurty...I can't type anymore about my day on there...the memories hurt too much. So I'll juss do it here.  Yesterday was fun. I'm trying to think of what i did in the morning but nothing's comming to....I was prolly sleeping...nah wait i was....till like 1 o clock. Then I wondered about the place in which i call home till I found the phone to make human contact. Nicole was my first victim.   Nothing happened over the course of the next 3 hours. Around 4 tho (DANG IT I MISSED MEN IN TIGHTS!!!) my aunt picked me up and Nicole and I went to this concert thing at FBC. No one showed up till an hour after we got there and nicole and I juss spent our time being intimidated and quiet. When we first walked into the church there was this AWESOME band playing...they were ska I guess cuz they had one of those trumpet player guys...oh man...they sounded soo cool and I'm regretting not trying to find out their name.   Umm....the rest of the night was cool. Met a lotta ppl...sum people I didn't wanna meet....I saw Namesake play again...they did good.   Erm....I can't think of much else to say....I had my spanish regents again...one word...FAILED 2 the EXTREME. I did it to myself though....I didn't study much...I'm pretty sure i didn't pass though....anyway...thats all for now...I wanna go take a nap or sumthing...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So i wood juss like to say hi to everybody aaaand say i love you all and I'm trying to keep my fathers day fun. Here's sumthin fun....  F is for Failing to Fail  A is for Assasination T is for your frequent Tooth aches H is for Hearty vegetables E is for the EXTREME dad you are R is for the way you take out my Robust brothers  I love you dad.   I hope you all enjoyed a nice fathers day. I didn't even spend half of it at home. I went to katy's after church which had a church picnic. I went swimming though which is cool...and in the end my dad loved me for the junk i put together to look creative and cute. I was broke.   I'm gonna continue to watch Happy Gilmore now so if you'll escuse me....please..Im serious tho...MOVE!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      suumthin
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well...its 10 00...juuuuus got home form YG...my day was pretty bad. mooostly cuuuz of my mom. (but lets not let that get out...)   it all started this morning in the car on the way to drop hargraves off. some how we got into a convo where my mom went on and on about her past jobs. "worked here then i worked...no wait it was there. theeen i work blah blah blah" i look back at ash and i could tell she DID NOT want to hear it. so i go "mom...im preeeeetty sure ash doesnt exactly care where ur past jobs were" and then she got all mad. then we got home. things were goin ok...until she saw my room. now it wasnt THAT big of a mess...buuut w/e. my dad was gonna put in my AC today so i hadda get things off the floor and away fromt he window. i do...she comes up and starts to yell at me "this isnt good enuff...ur dad and i pay morgage and we dont wanna seeur room a huge mess!!!!!!!!" i told her that she had said juss to get things outta his way and she goes "no i didnt! when did i ever say that!!! i told u to get this room spotless...somemore blah blah blahs" she had been annoying me this whooole week...she even got to gibson for cryin out loud...sooo that juss made me snap. so i walk away (which she told me to do if i snapped) and she flips out even more! im like "mom u told me --" " no i didnt its rude to walk out blah blah blah" and finally gibons and her dad showed up. juuus in the nick of time too. then i went to YG and things were great...until it was time to get int he car. she asks me wut i told everyone y they couldn come over. so i say "u were stressed." sure thats not exactly wut i told u guys...but thats y she flipped out on me. and again she starts to yell...ugh! i juss cant take it ne more!!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! *pants* ok..im think im good...well i g2g...i can only be on till 10 20...ugh!!!!!!! bye guys.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It seems as if this blog was a mistake...so im thinkin about deleting it just to save us all from a lil aggraviation and crap. I don't wanna be a jerk about it...idk wut do u guys think?   Today had been ok so far. Washed my dog aaand watched this projection from my parents wedding. No sound or anything and it was only like 5 minutes long but it was cute and I got to see a lil of my folks wedding. Then I juss looked at sum pictures from forever ago with my mom and dad and here i am now about ready to go to youth group. I'll write more later k? 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well...its 1:52 AM and yes...i am still online. You kno those nights wen u juss cant seem to fall asleep no matter what you do? well...this is nothing like that. im juss to lazy to actually turn my computer off. plus...im not tired and rather bored. that said...im gonna tell alllll baout my my lousy...yet exciting day. started off as any ol' day...wakin up...gettin ready....then i got o school and take the bio regents. it was ok i guess...juss stressful. then i got to come only to get get ready again so i could go to a concert w/ YG which was then sold out wen we got there. y they didnt buy the tickets in advance...idk...buuut w/e. then laser tagging was pretty fun. so there ya go...everyone who joined so far probably knos bout this day. but hey! wut better way to kill time then type up stuff bout ur boring life right? right. hey...i already killed 5 mins. thaaaaats not to bad. course that juss says im a slow typer but w/e. my excuse? its late. well that wore me out so children im off to bed. bye now...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it was rainging and i jumped in puddles and get this...i got wet!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Actions were taken into the hands of one ashley Gibson today as she surprised the media and friends with a brand new blog in competition with Mr. Jason Sumthing Or Another.   Perhaps competition is too much. I don't wanna be mean...juss...forceful and loving. I only want the best for my members and their children. HS YG Extreme even offers face to face communications through your computer. (Comments on posts) and allows you to tell the world, especially this blog, what you really think and how you realy feel. If you are interested please contact me at Goldenrose....***@aol.com. I'm sorry to inform you that this HS YG Extreme will only accept members that know one Ashley Gibson's SN.   Meanwhile I'll be catchin ya and dragging you in here if I must.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello all yall, tis me, allie, and i feel like i jus won an award....its like i go to check my mail...and i see this crazy lil e-mail bout joining another blog...o, happy day, ash g i mos deff think u should keep this one.  i like it, and thats all that counts.  well, not really....but if i had my way this would be staying...not that im actually gonna post much cuz...well, my comp...blew up again...yeh i have like this weird supernatual ability to kill any computer i touch.  this isnt mine...the one im on now...im baby sitting...crap, i gtg...sum kid is messin wit the TV...annnnd now the dog jus went.  snap, if this job didnt pay well i wouldnt be here.  actually thats not true... i need all the cash i can get.  not that i get alot...and now im rambling...see ya'll!        L.A.  sidenote: did u guys kno that u can change the post to any day you want? thats crazy...ima make this like...before the blog was even started...so now its alyshas bday all over again  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello all yall, tis me, allie, and i feel like i jus won an award....its like i go to check my mail...and i see this crazy lil e-mail bout joining another blog...o, happy day, ash g i mos deff think u should keep this one.  i like it, and thats all that counts.  well, not really....but if i had my way this would be staying...not that im actually gonna post much cuz...well, my comp...blew up again...yeh i have like this weird supernatual ability to kill any computer i touch.  this isnt mine...the one im on now...im baby sitting...crap, i gtg...sum kid is messin wit the TV...annnnd now the dog jus went.  snap, if this job didnt pay well i wouldnt be here.  actually thats not true... i need all the cash i can get.  not that i get alot...and now im rambling...see ya'll!        L.A.  sidenote: did u guys kno that u can change the post to any day you want? thats crazy...ima make this like...before the blog was even started...so now its alyshas bday all over again  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just want to make sumthing clear....right here...right....um now. This site was created for entertainment purposes only. Anyone who wants to join can. I really don't care. So anyway...onto my day  I've been sleeping so deeply lately. I keep having dreams and forgetting most of them an hour after I wake up. I do remember one from last night's though. I was at casperkill and I was hanging out with someone...it was someone I didn't know though. Like I guess I created him (it was a him) in my imagination or sumthing. And he was driving my places and we ended up at casperkill and we went outside all around the building. At some point we stopped by those hills right next to the tennis court. And we just layed there looking up at the sky and it was a beautiful day. With fluffy white clouds, deep blue sky with a light breeze. I remember the way the day was because its like ...my favorite type of day. It wasn't romantic or anything...juss...peaceful.   And lets see...my aunt picked me up around 1 i think. We went to...geez where did we go? I guess we went straight over to the mall. I got sum junk...a book, "Jenn Eir or sumthing. Um...sum earings...aaaaand also....I got stopped by some guy doing a charity thing at the mall. He asked me irf I wanted to save animals and children and I answered I'd ratehr save the children, thanks. He said oh not an animal person...no children r juss more important....ok, well do u wanna help children...Im like...i do what i can already but i'll see wut u got...so after exapling this crap to me I give him 5 dollars...I wasn't too smooth about it. I shood hav said sumthin better...but oh well..he gave me sum sewing kit however. Its actually pretty nice.   We got to the pool around 4 30 or sumthing. We planned to get there around 2 but wut r ya gonna do. Peeps were there, we went swimming, bowling, eating....the usual...I had a good time. All and all it was an aight day. Smells like burgers on the grill right now..I thiiink I'll go check it out....
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I cant get on AOL...but i can get on AIM and explorer....so the night's not a total cry. Garsh I'm tired. Now I'll recap the day's events.   *sigh* First lets see...I woke up at coley's house. I slept really well and all that junk and we headed over to Jordans around 3 with brad and christina. Umm...the party was fun. It was smashed with food, cold beverages, volleyball and a trampoline....but alas! The party ended for myself at 6 when i headed over to the church. Dont get me wrong tho...I love singing for the youth group....but i was ready to hit sumbody when i found out everyone went over to Nicoles house a lil while later...and even tho its 11:30 right now....theyre still there...grr...oh well...It was juss jesse, pat and I at the youth group today but as Im sure u all kno theyre MORE than enuff for a girl like me *wink*    Singing tomorrow for church *hissss* Wish me luck whoever u r....yah u kno who Im talking about...  And remember..."Dont waste another daaaaay!"  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh man! Do u know what its like to wake up...and find your kitchen and half ur living room SWIMMING in dog urine. I do...and it sucks...  However, the rest of the day wasn't too bad. I went to the pool around 1 and most of Da Gang showed up eventually. It was cool...did a lil swim swim...lil eat eat...a lil...no thats it. We got picked up around 6 and went home..only to leave around 8 to go to charlie Brown's for my brothers bday. My folks wont be here next week for it cuz of their cruise so there u go. Oh man, it was bangin. I never knew there were so many types of steak in one place. I had london broil or whatever in the end. I was too afraid to get a plate of sumthing new. It was cool tho...  Aaaaand now Im over nicoles house for a...SLUMBER PARTY!! Actually shes sleepin now...but its cool...she's still a growing boy afterall. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The movie....for all those that didn't go...wasn't too bad. Infact, yesterday was pretty good all together. I was supposed to go to the pool with nicole but we were too lazy to go anywhere till like 3 or sumthing when our moms + Christina picked us both up to go to the mall. We ate lunch at Ruby Tuesdays (slight mmmm)but I wasn't that hungry. I haven't been very hungry lately. I keep feeling really down about myself...its really irritating. We hung out around the mall for a while. I got a new bathing suit and sum church clothes, including a matching outfet to Nicole.   Then idk...they drove us over to Matt and Juliets where we had dinner. It was cool, their house is REALLY nice and so is their pond....great for spontaniously(sp) jumping into..pretty sick stuff...but it was worth it cuz matt paid for my movie ticket and gave me 7 bucks for snack foods.   Then we got to the movie juss on friggin time...good movie i gotta say. The first one is always better and stuff but this one was different. It had more laughs...yet more drama....the whole thing was pretty much drama....infact most of it juss made u wanna feel sorry for the guy...perhaps thats y i feel so weird today....naah...  Have a nice day everybody...especially u so and so. 
     
    
</post>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so....since we were 2 men short...aaron and i had practice anyway today..and im so glad we did..it was actually pretty fun...we have two songs started....and it was cool..cuz ideas i would have..aaron had ideas to add on top of it...he was really playing creatively...totally psyched me up to practice again..first day of work today...boring a mundo..er sumtin...buuut..i think it'll get better once i start working for real...plus i get 12 hourse the next 3 days...so thats like....$113 minus taxes for 4 days work...not too shabby...i guess i missed the movie the crew went too...which sux cuz now im home..and bored...and they're not on to listen to my endless stories....so sad...so in the words of rob..."my stomache is in my throat strangling my heart"....p.s.....its only cheap cuz u know im a sucker for it
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so very much has transpired..sorta since last post..oh well...lets skip the formalities..they always were ur weak point(?)...wednesday i gotta job at target..so ka ching there...cashier/sales dude works for me..i work for them..er sumtin..jesse and i also hit up a practice...which was desperatly needed....afterwards we went to nicoles house...then to be sent to ashleys house...we went there..picked up her trash..and waitied around for a couple hours..i felt kinda bad cuz im so boring and the girls were gettin lamed out...finally we went to the mall...picked up c money on the ride over..ate dinner there..then went back to my house to watch 50 first dates...more like 50 last dates if u ask me..i dont' know why..it just sounds creepier...then every1 went home...and i was left...thursday through now seems kinda hazy...worship at yg was garbage..even though ash and nicole sang awesome..i garbaged everything up...sunday we went to christina's grad party...it was cool..even though i never said like..one word to christina...it was wuts unsaid that means most i hope...so we were the last ones there...as expected from me..always late....tomorrow i start work...fun stuff...and maybe a movie afterwards..but thats for tomorrows entry...kim..even though u prob won't read this..i hope u have an amazing time in germany...bring me back a luger...and jesse...if u read this...bailing is garbage sister...anywho...dust ur shoulder off
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nothing happened yesterday..heirgo...no post....today was cool....went out to lunch with the family...went to a concert at fishkill baptist..ash, nicole, aaron, jesse, and ash showed up (in order of appearance)...tran came later...it was a pretty cool night filled with half naked asians running through gyms and kids breaking their legs....so great..anyways...my chest hurts for some reason...i think i got the black lung..dag yo...48 years from retirement 
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so my plan this summer..not go one day without doing sumtin...its gonna be hard...im gonna do it though..so today was aight..got up...showered..went up to the mall and got a bathing suit..so now i can hit the pool on monday...got home..waited for my dad to show up..he finally did so i took the truck up and picked up jesse..we hit up mcd's and then church...worship was aight..though i can't get the guitar right..and power chords on acoustic is HARD...i just gave up towards the end....dave did a good bible study...i need to read the word more..seriously..but after jay and i chilled mostly..along with the other folk...jay..i have ADD..i try to pay attention but its hard...coasted home on lil gas...annnnd...here we are now...i got my dads cell phone back water logged..and he was totally understanding...he can be really rambo sumtimes..it makes up for all the grillages...soooooo....bye
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today was weird...finished up regents today..and i am done..then i went to the gym deal at casperkill with my dad and signed up...we put some infinity speakers and a new cd player in the subaru..ka ching..and ate lunch at the diner...its cool chillin with my dad like that when he's not grillin me...so i get home and pretty much head right back out to the church...we headed up to the concert only to find it sold out...having been so for 2 days..we felt kinda stupid..but no fears..we went to the mall and ate dinner..then went over to some family fun center and played laser tag...had a pretty good time with the crew...esp jason...that kiss will live on forever...and making c money jelous...that kiss will live on forever...just got home like...15 mins ago...i am tired..and thirsty broha...in the words of jesse..."i need a stiff drink...like chocolate milk"....be real
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      regents are like pickled onions....somehow...one more day and im out for summer..and not a momment too soon..it never is...after driving 4 peeps home today..i just about died..and took a 3 hour nap...missed some phone calls..i always get calls when im sleeping..i guess people like me better when i sleep...just sorta slacked off a bunch today...tomorrow im joining a gym finally..and goin to david crowder..so its mad cool..mad cool...today on the english regents we had to write this essay on griots..which are like..west african story tellers/musical performers...wut a quality job...thats all they do all day..is tell stories and sing songs...i don't have many quality stories though...but to do that for a living..hmm..that gives me 3 ideas.....
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      in the beginning of this journal there was a word...and that word was...sup...check it yo...today was ashley's bday..props on that...and tupac shakurs as well..enough said...i spent the day taking ss tests...playing guitar..and being hot...literally that is...amazingly i was allowed to go to dinner at olive garden with co minus jesse..it was pretty fun..even though i make myself look so stupid all the time..annd i sorta ate before i went..and i had to leave early..but happy bday anyway ashley...and dont' think i didnt' get u a present...urs is coming...can't wait for crowder concert on friday...its gonna be more rambo than Lt. Spears...i want every1 there...that means u...so come with me...or just show up...it all works out
    
</post>


</Blog>