<Blog>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hamid a 7-year-old kid from the country of Afghanistan lives in a village near kandhahar. He lives with his grandmother and grandfather. His father is not there he went to fight against the taliban leaving Hamid. And his mom yes she was there but one day she went out to buy some food and never returned. Probably killed by the taliban or maybe she has gone to gods house that’s what Hamid’s grandmother says. No but Hamid is sure that his mother has gone to find his father as she promised that “when we will win this battle and our government will come in power your dad will return that day if not we will go find him together”. Hamid thought that maybe his mother went to find his father to give him a surprise and he waited for the surprise. Hamid now works with his grandfather who is a woodcutter everyday his grandfather goes out in the afternoon taking Hamid with him and they return in the evening. In the evening again Hamid goes with his grandfather to sell those pieces of wood for money and after that they buy food for the next day. These days though they don’t have to bye food, as food is not available in the market they get food from the UNO. Hamid’s grandfather goes morning to the nearby camp in kandhahar to get some food. No they don’t have buses they don’t have taxis the grandfather goes on foot with few men of his area the nearest camp is 10 kms away. Its 6 years now Hamid is living like this yes once he was called to come to school in kandhahar run by UNO he went there a month he liked it but then the taliban government ordered to close the school as the taliban authority said that this school is teaching anti Islam things to the children but that was a year ago. Now he has forgotten about the school now his life is only working with his grandfather whole afternoon and then helping her grandmother in household work. No Hamid is not allowed to play and with whom he will play there are no other children of his age in his village again his grandmother fears that taliban will take Hamid away as they did a year ago when they took all the children above 5 with them. Luckily Hamid was not there he was with his grandfather in another village where they went to meet Hamid’s aunty. His aunty can’t come to see him, as women are not allowed to move in Afghanistan.  For the last few days Hamid feels like some thing is changing. Yes something has changed he saw many UNO vehicles one day leaving the city of kandhahar and moving towards Kabul. His grandfather also said that these days they are not getting food from the camps. A local volunteer was telling the people who there in the camp that all the foreign groups are going back to there home country leaving Afghanistan as there is some tension between UNO and Taliban.    This was 9 days ago now all the foreign workers have left the city of kandhahar leaving the camps, now local people they distribute food in those camps. Its night Hamid and his grandfather as usual are sitting on the roof and her grandmother is cooking food. Suddenly they heard a loud blast it was not new they hear these things everyday it’s just some taliban soldier has killed some person. This happens everyday but Hamid thought that no there is something different about this loud sound and he was right just the next minute they saw a plane flying past over them and something the plane dropped and it fell somewhere far and light flashed with very loud blast sound it was new to Hamid he knew that those big things flying like birds are planes as his grandfather told him but he was not sure what those planes are doing here and what they are dropping. But the grandfather knew what is happening as he has seen the Russian war he knew that USA has started bombing raid on there cities he asked the other day a volunteer that why these foreign workers are leaving and the volunteer replied that there was some attack on USA and they are planning to attack Afghanistan. The grandfather knew that it would happen soon but this soon? He took Hamid with him and rushed inside the house he was both happy and worried he was happy because the volunteer also said that USA will be fighting with The Northern alliance in which his son is and worried because he saw what happened in the Russian war the destruction that he witnessed. The whole night they saw and heard the noises and light of the attack. The next day he went to the camp to get food he saw many houses in pieces this time he took Hamid with him too the volunteer said that USA has started attacking so they are giving extra food today and don’t come out of the house. They took foods that were given to them to use for 10 days and went back home they saw many planes in the way back home all-round the sky and heard few blasts too. They returned home safely.  10 days they passed like this staying in home not even going to work Hamid frequently used to ask his grandfather what was happening his grandfather used to tell him that his father is going to return in a few days this made Hamid happy as he wanted to see his father whom he has never seen but has seen the letters from his father written to his grandfather. He was excited, as he was sure his mother is going to return soon too. On the 10th day the grandfather again went to the city of kandhahar to get some food from the camp and returned back safely again more 6 days passed like this on the 7th day the sound of gun started to come and they heard tanks moving the grandfather knew that his son is coming back on the 8th day there neighbors came to there house and told them that the Northern Alliance forces are just half a km away from the kandhahar they heard shorts fired more loudly and here it was that night it was celebration all around the city of kandhahar the northern alliance have taken the city of kandhahar under there control. Hamid saw foreign troops landing in kandhahar but he was waiting for his mother and father to come. Two days later the day came the father whom Hamid has only saw in letters and photos has returned he was so happy that he was not getting how he is to express his feeling he tried to laugh to cry everything he wanted to speak to kiss his father he kissed his father many times. It was celebration in there house even the aunty came to there house with her two children Hamid liked there company and first time in 1 year went outside his home to play with those two cousins of his. He enjoyed the day, as he has never done that before his father gave him a magical box (radio) from which sound was coming he was very happy with it. That night he asked his father about his mother and his father also told him that she is with the god now she will return later now he believed in it as he knew his father will never lie and he thought if I have waited this many days why not a little more. In a few days the foreign workers came back to village with food and now they opened the school again Hamid’s father on the first day of the school took Hamid with him to register him Hamid liked the school the teachers he made many new friends.    After that he learned many things from his father he used to listen to his fathers stories everyday. His father took him to see movies it was new to Hamid he liked this very much he went with his father one day to the city of kandhahar and visited all the places their he enjoyed that. This way he started to study to play and to interact with other children like the children of other countries he liked his this life and wanted to forget all about those 7 years that he spent without his father    
      
</post>


</Blog>