<Blog>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       June 16th, 2004~ Today was one of those regular, not so special days. But still I had some fun. I went shopping today, and got me two cute shirts, three sexy pairs of shorts, a new purse..Because someone copied off of my other FAVORITE one...No comment on the name. And other stuff...LOL. After that I went to Kirkword Pool, for a couple hours. Once I got back I didn't do much more. Now as I am sitting here writing this, my older brother has friends over...HeHeHE! Even so, I'm bored out of my wits! SO.. CALL ME UP AND GIVE ME A RING-A-LING! LOL
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I went to the pool with my 2 pool buddies, Steph and Kristina. We went to Tropical moose too. Right now were all at Kristinas house! "Look my toe looks fat EWWW LOOK AT MY TOE!"says Steph. LOOSER!!! also we egged this guys house and then the next day (There her her neighbors)his moms like "some one edd'd us last night" AND WE STARTED CRACKING UP!!!! and then that night we did a crapy Tp job on the island on the street lol and put water on it so it was stick...the next day is was like gone haha! good times! o and kristina cut stephs hair!! its looks fabulous!! (and i cut a lil bit..like the front like one snip hahaha!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, me and stpeh spent the night at Kristinas house..we stayed up like all night haha, but we could not shut up!! haha but when we woke up...had a tasty breakfast AND I HAD MILK WITH IT!!!!!! hahahahahaha then we went to the pool for a bit, and then the pool closed kinda becuase of the strom, so then we went to tropical moose iwth ty, mitch, adam, and kevin AND THEY THROW MY FRIES AT ME (WELL ONLY TY DID) THAT LITTLE BUTT HEAD!!! ya, and then i went home and ate the rest of my fries IN PEACE!!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i woke up at 12:30...I was suppose to met my friends up at the pool at 11...OOPS!!! FUCKING ALARM CLOCK..its a peice of shit haha!well so i went to the pool at like 12:45....i walked around.....WEHRE HTE HELL ARE THEY!!!! they werent here!! then i called lauren b's cell "OH! we went to tromo were walking back now!" OOOOHHH haha should have called frist...instead of waiting an hour haahha...and my "cuz" Mark (eittoh) was working there so i chatted with him a while....then i went home...dog sat all day, I LOVE THE DOG...shes a boxer named sadie! ahhh shes adorable...and shes HYPER like me!HEHEHE...but then everything got bad!!!!!! ahhhh I wasnt invited to something that upseted me....and then i thought this really hot guys called me a bitch...turns out he didnt...(no comment ont he name...altough he'd perfer it was) haha sux 4 him!! JKJK I LUV YA!!!! but now thats over...but then i was late on taking my Acid refulx medication...which makes me get heartburn...which reminds me..i still havnt tooken it!!!!!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>