<Blog>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    smallest town EVER!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    home on the farm&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    this is a bridge in kingston&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There are places I remember  In my life  though some have changed, Some forever not for better, Some have gone and some remain.  All these places had their moments, With lovers and friends I still can recall, Some are dead and some are living, In my life I've loved them all.  But of all these friends and lovers, There is no one compares with you, And these memories lose their meaning, When I think of love as something new.  Though I know I'll never lose affection For people and things that went before, I know I'll often stop and think about them, In my life I love you more.  Though I know I'll never lose affection For people and things that went before, I know I'll often stop and think about them, In my life I love you more.  In my life I love you more.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      woke up early. went to lunch with mom and dad. chilled at home. saw fahrenheit 9/11. chatted. went to bed early.   i dread tomorrow..
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay my dream was going great, i was at a carnival with my friends and i was having snow cones and then..my subconcious fear came into play. It just totally ruined the dream, waking me up and making me want to vomit. It really was all the thoughts that I've been having played out in one swift movement in my dreams. Geez, do I hate that. I can't even escape it in my dreams. I bet a lot of people are wondering what "it" is. I'm gonna leave it at "it" for now. Not even the people who know me best know what exactly it is I bet.  So yesterday, I got up to go driving on the sunny day and I got to about down the street when there was almost an accident like 30 feet from me. I heard someone screaming the eff word litterally 20 times at the driver that messed up. Needless to say, I didn't want to go driving anymore. I chilled at home and did nothing until I said "Hey, I wonder what Cat is up to.." So I called her up and we talked a bit on the phone until it started to cut out and she to come up to starbucks (where she was) so I did. We talked and got caught up. I love those talks where she and I just let it all out and we usually agree with whatever each other is saying so that makes it even better. It's so nice to have these thoughts that no one else has and then go to Cat and she's thinking the exact same thing too! And we heard someone was playing tipsy and it made us think of Sanela-nela. Boy, do I miss her. So, more people showed up and we finally left. And everyone, I am a witness to this..Catherine was jamming to Jurassic 5 in her car!! HAHA! It was hilarious. The night was young, but I was tired, so I went home and stayed home. Chatted until 3am then went to bed. I still can't believe I'm up at this hour. Geez. I'm planning on making this a great day. Just like Michael says, "You can't have a great day unless you  make  it a great day!" 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      -camera, specifically nikon -pottery barn bed -new bedspread and pillows -new dresser -comfy chair (maybe a love sack) -record player -violin -belly button piercing (maybe..just maybe)
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The party wasn't that exciting. "Aww you look so much like your mother." Starbucks with Rach and being eaten by skeeters. Rachel and Kallie came over and watched snl and madtv. Did anyone else see the gorgeous sunset?
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HAPPY BIRTHDAY MOMMY!!   You know it really hadn't hit me yet that I was in madrigals until last night. No offense to vivace, you guys are great, but I am so excited about being in such an awesome choir. We're going to be so frikin good this year. And...we are going to Italy..that just hit me too. YES! The whole dress fiasco is driving me nuts because my mom kinda took over..but whatever. So yesterday, it rained like crazy after it stopped Navid came over. We got in the car to go to Napoleon Dynamite at the Magnolia..but after Navid almost hit a parked van 3 houses down from house, I thought "Do I really want him to drive me to a place I've never been to in DALLAS during RUSH HOUR in the RAIN?...I think not." So i cut the trip short and made him head back to my house. We played pente and he FINALLY beat me. Grr..I hate it when people beat me..especially at pente. Grrr. So after the pente I showed him my totally awesome computer game. And after my mom got home we all went to the show choir camp show. It really did come together nice, the new people rock and the girls singing is awesome. A cappella is gonna kick ace. So, after the show i avoided certain people, my stomach really can't take that anymore. After cleaning up Michael and I drove to his house where there was a party going on. I played DVD MASTER during scene it. I love that game. Then we broke out the madrigal music and I called my mom to let me stay longer. Then I called her at 1am and told her I was spending the night. So, me, Rach, Kallie, Nathan and Sterling all spent the night at Michael's. It was SOOO much fun. We talked about like everything..wow, flying "V's" will forever be a memory to me. And Kallie making up songs while i played guitar..and Nathan making up songs about kitties. "Kitty cat, Kallie wants to violate you." "Nathan, where are you sleeping?".."With the girls!"..."No, Nathan, where are you sleeping" "..downstairs :(". After serenading the girls to sleep, Nathan went downstairs to his own bed and we got to sleep. But me and Rach wanted to see Sterling and Michael sleeping so we snuck..ah, not a word!! **sneaked into his room and pulled their hair and such. After Sterling woke up and told us to go away we went to bed...at 5 in the morning. I woke up at 9:30 to the sound of Kallie's annoying chipperness. "HEY EVERYBODY! WAKE UP! LET'S WAKE UP BECAUSE IM SO EXCITED THAT I'M UP!! EVERYONE WAKE UP! YAY!" Goodness..Kallie last night was like "I am SO not a morning person." What a lie that was. Then, we all loaded up in the cars and went to donut palace..more like donut hell! If there's one thing that makes me sick, it's the smell of DONUTS! I can't stand em, I think it's because my mom took me to get chocolate milk and glazed donuts EVERY morning from kindergarten to 5th grade. Geez I know that I just can't stand the smell. Sick. So we had a pow wow like right outside of the place and I had a pepsi for breakfast. Then Sterling drove me home. That's about it. Now I need to take a nap before my mother's birthday pool party at 4, even though it's gonna rain. Poor Michael, he has to help someone move for 8 hrs today and poor Rach, she has to drive to bedford.I love you guys, good luck.   ps: Thanks ookete for leaving a comment, you rock. I LOVE pente also. BTW, are you mormon?
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I just woke up about an hour ago and have been sitting here trying to actually  wake up  completely. I went to Rach's yesterday for our snow cone party which was quite successful if I must say. It was fun until Michael learned how to work the machine and throw ice all in my face. Rach, Mal and I swam and said funny things under water and we wouldn't tell Michael so his curiousity finally got him and he jumped in the pool. So then the war of girls against boys began. Me, Rach and Mal against Michael and..Michael (Rach's bro). This war ended when Michael elbowed Mal in the forehead and eye. Nice going Michael. Then at about 6pm I had to head home for dinner. At about seven, Kallie and Rach called me to go to Kallie's church and play on the slides. I was really tired from swimming and hadn't had a shower so I told em to call me when they were just gonna chill at her house. So at about 10pm they called back and my mother was like "Autumn, you know the rules. You can't leave the house this late, you have to make plans in advance." So I just stayed at home and played my awesome computer games..and didn't get to play with Erin..bummer. Then I talked to Andrew a lot online and then he left..so it sucked. I put this test thing on my profile on the post before so everyone do it, it would make me feel really special. Then I talked to Guppy from like 1-3am about how he cut his finger on his guitar and his cable going off and coming back on again. So today I'm going to see Napoleon dynamite..SO EXCITED!! Maybe Farenheit 9/11 too. Navid, you are going down when we play pente. That's right. IT'S ON! 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1. Who are you? 2. Are we friends? 3. When and how did we meet? 4. How have I affected you? 5. What do you think of me? 6. What's the fondest memory you have of me? 7. How long do you think we will be friends? 8. Do you love me? 9. Do you have a crush on me? 10. Would you kiss me? 11. Would you hug me? 12. Physically, what stands out? 13. Emotionally, what stands out? 14. Do you wish I was cooler? 15. On a scale of 1-10, how hot am I? 16. Give me a nickname and explain why you picked it. 17. Am I loveable? 18. How long have you known me? 19. Describe me in one word. 20. What was your first impression? 21. Do you still think that way about me now? 22. What do you think my weakness is? 23. Do you think I'll get married? 24. What makes me happy? 25. What makes me sad? 26. What reminds you of me? 27. If you could give me anything what would it be? 28. How well do you know me? 29. When's the last time you saw me? 30. Ever wanted to tell me something but couldn't? 31. Do you think I could kill someone? 32. Do you think our friendship is getting stronger/weaker/or staying the same? 33. Do you feel that you could talk to me about anything and I would listen?
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      navid: I'm going to beat your head in   madison: oh please dont   kaitlin: haha someone put navid instead of david.. enless their name really is navid- and in that case, i apologize for making fun of you   madison: no thats how you spell it.....gosh you are SO STUPID....just kidding   Jessica: I thought the same thing when I was reading Autumns blog!!! [in regards to the navid comment]   kaitlin: navid/david... please tell us your real name, we are all DYING to know. heh.   kaitlin: oh poo. sorry navid.   autumn: navid is my best friend, he has a weirdo name like navid because he's foreign..foreign filth!!   autumn: also it is pronounced nothing like david. its like this, naa as in nag and veeed. say it with me, naaaa-veeeed.   kaitlin: wow, and the sad thing is i totally said it along with you... where is he from?   kaitlin: navid i mean...   anonymous: naaaa veeeed   kaitlin: yes, i got that, thanks..   autumn: iran  
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      autumndddddddddd: xanga is for computer illiterate LOSERS Midget Matt 2005: well ... BlogSpot is for computer NERDS. Midget Matt 2005: haha, j/p ... don't kill me.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I put lots of pictures on here for fun, enjoy those. Then I talked to Rach online and I told her about my snow cone maker and how it's totally awesome and she told me she might have a swim party so i suggested.. autumndddddddddd: snow cone par-tay.  And that's what we intend to do in a bit.  So thats basically the entirety of what has been going on today.  I love my computer...-sigh-
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    this is ME!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    rach and me at lotr midnight premiere!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me and michael sumo wrestling on halloween&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    this is spenser..holy goofy&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    this is me really excited about the party..and ITS NOT EVEN MY BIRTHDAY!!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ahhh I'm reformatted and all new and clean!!! YES!!
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bah! Sorry bout the total not posting thing. My computer is so sick, I gotta reformat soon. So, here I am on my parents computer posting. Are you happy? You best be. Well yesterday I went over to Dee's to make snow cones and smoothies. I had a snow cone machine but we didn't have any snow cone juice stuff so we went to target and got three flavors; margarita, daquiri and pina colada..mmm they are good. So after chillin at Dee's for a while I had to get home because mum was headed home from work. So after I had dinner at about 7:30 I met Kallie at the lewisville amphitheatre for the free tuesday night acoustic concerts. I wasn't too impressed with "monkeyshyne" and what the crap did they have a bunch of lampshades on the stage for? Kallie knows what I'm talkin about. I just enjoyed watching little kids dance crazy, the little boy with the guitar and this girl, her boyfriend and her mother dance together. Ha. Poor girl. The mormons showed up at about 9pm and we told them the band wasn't too good so we went to Al's house to watch Home Teachers!! But they already returned it so we had to go to hollywood video and rent it again. I drove and saw kit cat's car at starbucks so i slowly drove by looking for her. She later told me that she had just left her car there. Boy, did I look stupid. After Home Teachers I went home and made Navid smarter. Navid, you WILL last! Just think of Mrs. Hogan naked! Then I went to sleep. So our AC is out. Geez. This sucks so bad. It's not hot yet but I can feel it creeping up on me. So I've basically just been chilling here until it gets too hot and I have to "abandon ship" as my mom put it. But it's alright, because I've got my clapton blaring.  
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I would have had another post last night if my computer wasn't so hyped up on adware and spyware. Yes, it is true. My computer has herpes. So last night I got a call from Matt, Hollis, and Rach telling me to come over to Rach's house and chill. I went and we started watching Singles Ward, no one really got it and I had to explain all the mormon lingo to them. So we turned it off because no one really was enjoying it. Then we chilled in Rach's room which was fun because I got to look at all of her dorky elementary school pictures. Ha, just playin Rach. Well at about 5 till midnight I headed home. That was the highlight of my night. We're going to see "Dodgeball" in about an hour or so. I can't wait, "If you can dodge a wrench, you can dodge a ball." HA! Okay, so once I got home last night and saw the crappy viruses covering my computer I finally decided, it is time to reformat. So I started transfering all my files to discs. I didn't get very far because my computer kept freakin out. So thats basically all I did. Alright..off to Dodgeball i go. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, went to Rach's to swim with her, Kallie and Michael. It didn't work out so I came home and went to tom thumb with mum and we bought stuff for dinner. Came home, made father's day dinner. We watched band of brothers until Adam came over and we ate. After that we had pie and he opened his one gift, master and commander. So we watched that because my dad absolutely loves it. I've just been chillin at my house with my dad today mainly. I burned my zeppelin cds again for me because I gave my copies to someone else. Matt wanted this one song from Almost Famous, he said it was slow and nice. I guessed it was the rain song so I'm gonna take him a copy of houses of the holy. Poor zeppelin deprived child. Thats pretty much all I have done. Todays post is kinda boring. Sorry to my one fan out there. If i have one. K, later. I'll post again if i do anything tonight, but most likely I wont.    I think this is appropriate:  THE RAIN SONG This is the springtime of my loving - the second season I am to know  You are the sunlight in my growing - so little warmth I've felt before.  It isn't hard to feel me glowing - I watched the fire that grew so low.   It is the summer of my smiles - flee from me Keepers of the Gloom.  Speak to me only with your eyes. It is to you I give this tune.  Ain't so hard to recognize - These things are clear to all from  time to time.   Talk Talk - I've felt the coldness of my winter  I never thought it would ever go. I cursed the gloom that set upon us...  But I know that I love you so   These are the seasons of emotion and like the winds they rise and fall  This is the wonder of devotion - I see the torch we all must hold.  This is the mystery of the quotient - Upon us all a little rain must fall.   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Holy cow, I have been painting like all day. I am so tired and SO sore from yesterday at the lake. Ouch. I'm still home alone since my parents went to a movie and dinner with some friends. I think I am gonna watch Singles Ward again. It's pure greatness. Well, I probably going to fall asleep watching it too. Goodnight.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, it is really raining hard outside. Amazing. And wow, I am home alone. This is scary. Where are my mummy and daddy? Lunch. Well, that was stupid of them. OMFG!! I gotta go hide under my bed!!!  this one goes out to rach and mal:                 There’s a might wind a-blowin’                  ‘Cross the land and ‘cross the sea                  It’s blowin’ peace and freedom                  It’s blowin’ equality                  Yes, it’s blowin’ peace and freedom                  It’s blowin’ you and me.  
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Jessi picked me up and we drove to Alison's. We took Al's car and dropped Scott off at the Vivace swim party..didnt look like much of a party to me. Then Jessi, Alison, Heidi and I went to grapevine lake for the priest/laurell (sp?) thing. I only knew like 5 people there so it was quite a hoot. We went tubing and me and Alison went banana boating, it was tight. After it started to get dark and the boats were leaving we decided to head to Alison's where we watched "The Home Teachers". Holy moly, that is going to my list of favourite movies man. HILARIOUS! ...and Abraham begat Steve...and Steve begat..hahahaha. greatness. So after that they put on lion king 1 1/2. Wow, I'm not really into the whole lion king scene, I dont get all excited when i hear that crappy song at the beginning. So it was getting late and the movie wasnt going to be over anytime soon so I called my mum and she came and picked me up. Wow, that sounds pathetic, my car was at home okay. So anyways, here I am. La-di-da. I hope you enjoyed your friday as much as I enjoyed mine. I'm gonna go watch "Singles Ward" because I am a mormon wanna be, or Mormon Poser as Mary Weidman would say. Goodnight.   for now, rock out to this: Choose the right when a choice is placed before you. In the right the Holy Spirit guides; And its light is forever shining o'er you, When in the right your heart confides. Choose the right!  Choose the right! Let wisdom mark the way before. In its light, choose the right! And God will bless you evermore.   Choose the right!  Let no spirit of digression Overcome you in the evil hour. There's the right and the wrong to ev'ry question; Be safe thru inspiration's pow'r. Choose the right!  Choose the right! Let wisdom mark the way before. In its light, choose the right! And God will bless you evermore.  Choose the right!  There is peace in righteous doing. Choose the right!  There's safety for the soul. Choose the right in all labors you're pursuing; Let God and heaven be your goal. Choose the right!  Choose the right! Let wisdom mark the way before. In its light, choose the right! And God will bless you evermore.   heres the song to go with it.. http://www.youngs.org/mdavis/ldshymns/hymns/239.mid
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      BAH! i have to post like super fast. i went to eat a moes with matt, neither of us had eaten and we were both bored so it made sense to go together. So then after we ate i took him home and came back and made some changes in my blog. I changed the name to autumn blog instead of cellar door because Spenser and Navid both said "I dunno what this cellar door crap is, its not even a good phrase, I dunno what drew barrymore is talking about in that movie." So from now on it will be autumn blog. And i also changed the colors because it looked a little satanic and demented. Okay, so im going to lake grapevine with the mormons! SCORE! i'll let you know how it was when i get back. Later.  quote from one of my favourite movies.. "never take it seriously. if you never take it seriously, you never get hurt. if you never get hurt, you always have fun. and if you ever get lonely just go to the record store and visit your friends." -penny lane 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Navid: Autumn, my keys won't come out of my car!! OMG!! My keeeeyyys!!! Autumn: move aside! -gets in car and looks around- Navid: See, they won't come out!! Autumn: Navid..the car is drive. Navid: -long silence-...shut up.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      xjjeessiiiCCaax: whats up with david being spelled backwards? autumndddddddddd: what? xjjeessiiiCCaax: navid is david backwards xjjeessiiiCCaax: and its like everywhere in your post
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well the walking didnt really happen because once we got in the car to go to the park i was like "mam (im real northern) it's 99 degrees i am NOT going walking, i'm taking us to get snow cones!" So i drove to carrollton, barely drove, i had her screaming in my ear the whole time about my driving. yeah, remind me to never drive with my mother again. So we got our snow cones (pina colada and mango madness) and then she drove (of course). And she made me go to these stupid material stores to look for cloth and trimming for my madrigal dress, but on the bright side, she bought me a oil paint by numbers! So, ive been doing that a bit, it's of Venice! And im going there!! Woo! We saw Bob and Jeff there too, it was a party. Then we FINALLY came home at like 8pm. Andrew was all freakin out because he couldn't find Navid which means that he has a secret love for iranians. I SO almost made it thru the day being totally addiction-free but SOMEONE made me go get a slurpee!! THANKS A LOT YOU! So, I found a huge welp thing in my colar bone. It's a spider bite, i know this because Navid said it was and Navid is going to be a doctor, therefore he would know. So when Navid showed up at my house i told andrew he was here and he freaked out some more and made up lies about calling his mother and she was really worried and just made up a bunch of lies. Thank you Andrew. I was supposed to go TPing with Matthew for his birthday but his super cool mother had to say no. And when i say super cool, i mean fuckin bitch. Okay, Matt says i can only call her stupid. So i meant 'stupid'. So now im here at home. Painting by number. I finally got my book back from Jackie to give to Dee, but Navid tried to take it tonight.. autumndddddddddd: navid tried to take your book autumndddddddddd: the bell jar dee629a: Oh bam Bitch! dee629a: LOL autumndddddddddd: he picked it up off my desk and was like "this looks good" dee629a: oh did you guard it with your life autumndddddddddd: i pulled out my 38 and i was like "put the motha fuckin book down before i have to shoot!!" dee629a: BAM BAM down mother fucka! dee629a: GO angry red head Autumn   OKAY, so I have rambled on long enough. GOODNIGHT! MORMON LAKE PARTY TOMORROW!! WOO HOO!
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bout to go walking with mum..  I found this poem quite..appropriate for how i feel a lot.  Mad Girl's Love Song, A Villanelle By: Sylvia Plath  I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead; I lift my lids and all is born again. (I think I made you up inside my head.)  The stars go waltzing out in blue and red, And arbitrary blackness gallops in: I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead.  I dreamed that you betwitched me into bed And sun me moon-struck, kissed me quite insane. (I think I made you up inside my head.)  God topples from the sky, hell's fires fade: Exit seraphim and Satan's men: I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead.  I fancied you'd return the way you said, But I grow old and I forget your name. (I think I made you up inside my head.)  I should have loved a thunderbird instead; At least when spring comes they roar back again. I shut my eyes and all the world drops dead. (I think I made you up inside my head.)
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HAPPY 17th BIRTHDAY TO MATTHEW RUDKIN!  So, my plan of getting back on schedule didnt really work out..seeing as how i went to bed at about 3am and got up at noon. Oh yeah, on yesterdays post Matt wanted me to let everyone know he was at Chili's also. Even though he showed up when we walked out the door. So anyways, mum came home for lunch and wanted to go to taco bell so we went and it was yummy. scrumtulescent for Alison M. Not much planned for today, might do something with Josh but probably not. Just found out school starts Aug. 16th. SUCK ASS! i hate starting school that early. It's like a week after my birthday. Another issue: rooming in Italy. Good lord, i have NO clue who im gonna room with. I just found out it's three to a room now instead of two, so thats better. But holy cow, i honestly have no one. No one i wanna room with anyway.. So there's not much else to write about. Just this year is gonna come SO fast. School starting so early and then the feast coming right at the beginning of December and then Italy over christmas break. Sheesh... Ciao..until my next post but in the meantime..  rock out to this: oh baby, its crying time, oh baby, i got to fly. got to try to find a way, got to try to get away. cuz you know i gotta get away from you babe.  oh baby, the rivers red, oh baby, in my head. theres a funny feelin goin on i dont think i can hold out long.  and when the owls cry in the night, oh baby, baby when the pines begin to cry. baby, baby, baby, how do you feel? if the river runs dry, baby. how do you feel?  craze, baby, the rainbows end, baby its just a den. for those who hide, who hide their love to depths of life. and ruin dreams that we all knew so, babe. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was much more eventful than others i must admit. Woke up at about 10:30am at Jackie's and jumped right in her pool. Fell asleep on a float for about two hours and i got out when i really started to feel the sun burning my pale irish body. So, i talked to Matt R. about doing something and we decided to play volleyball at andy brown and we met up with Jessi and Jessica..man that's annoying to say. Well the two Jessi's and Matt and i wasted a lot of time driving here and there and just about everywhere looking for a volleyball. By the time we got to the park it was 4pm and Matt had to leave for work, so i drove him home. We remaining few decided to swim at Jessica's house and invited lots of people over, choir people. Kallie and i got out for a bit and cruised in her mgb. After attacking Michael G. with water balloons and watching Jessica's australian shepard, "Lil' Bit", puke orange muck right into the pool we decided that the swimming was over. We hung in her room and i smeared vicks vaporub on everyone near me..yeah, i am a bitch. Then, we all loaded up in the cars and headed to chili's too. A lot more people showed up, here's who was there: me, jessica, tj, michelle, kallie, alden, sterling, colleen and audrey. Yeah, I'm sure thats it, Jessi went home after the dog puking. Anyway, we drove to kid country from there and played hide n seek in the dark..oh yeah, we are so cool. So we got bored of that and decided to go back to Jessica's and chill. After some chillin, the vivace dorks all said they had to go home because they had to get sleep for camp in the morning. So the party ended and i put Matt's shoe into a vase bigger than him...yeah, i am a bitch again. Gave my car a much needed refill and then went on home. Talked to Navid online and he informed me that three more people hate me. YES! Until next time..goodnight!
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    MJ again&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Everyone at choir camp calls me MJ because of this girl&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Holy exhausted. Nothing but singing for 12 straight hours. Geez, me and Mal friggin rock. We're the best ones there..i guess it helps since we already went to another camp though..ha. Dude, I don't want to sound like a total bitch but...the rest of the girls singing soprano 1 suck. Yah, so it's real fun with Mal and Dane there. That kid is funny, Dane I mean; Mal isn't funny. Just playing Mal! I hope the carwash went well, I know you all missed me in my hot pink bikini. Yeah, I am so hot. PFF, I'm so good at making jokes. I have more camp tomorrow, 9-4 and theres a concert, it's gonna suck. Wow, negative. I meant it's going to be the best damn choir concert ever! Yah, now i have to dry my hair and straighten it and such. Gotta get up early tomorrow. Peace. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm missing the madrigal carwash tomorrow since I'm going to uta all state camp. Saw the village tonight, it was okay. My car is totally flooded with water and it smells like mildew. UGH!! I am so getting a new car. I was talking (whining) tonight about how I want a new car and Kallie goes "But I want an oompa loompa  NOW !!" and i totally realized that I am just like that spoiled girl from willy wonka and the chocolate factory. Which makes me even more mad. I am so not her! 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm..last night was fun. Really good food. Taco bell and those really good cookies with the icing on them. Oh yeah. Erin totally loves me, right when I got to Kal's house she ran to me. Who doesn't love a red head? Oh yah and since my totally crappy convertible top leaks and water gets all in my car I couldn't drive it yesterday BUT my mom let me take her tahoe, it was super. So I think I might have to go see the village with my mother tonight..I can't get in with my friends seeing as how im not 17 yet. 11 days baby! I'm almost there. That means school is in 17 days! Bah! I'm actually kinda excited and all. With madrigals and flex woo-hoo! Well, Mal just called me and told me that the movie isn't rated R so..I get to go with my friends!! yay! So my night is planned. I guess we're going with the usual crowd to the usual grapevine or marquee theatre. Well, everyone have a wonderful night! 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just got home from the movies with Jessi, Brad, Jake and Nathaniel. I actually went to see A Cinderella Story, surprisingly, it was pretty good. I really loved the kid who played hilary duff's best friend. Too cute. That's about all I've done all day long. Mom and I are about to go shopping and I'm hearing something about Kallie's house at 9. We'll see what the deal is about that.. Peace. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So the night went very well. I haven't had that much pure fun in so long. Fun where I wasn't thinking about something or someone. Anyway, the drive to olive garden was awful, me and Rach were freaking out and couldn't see the car in front of us. It was crazy weather..so dinner was excellent. Michael saying.. "These breadsticks are the bomb." and "I like salad." and rolling around in his chair made dinner so hilarious. Yah, after we didn't go bowling, we got to the place and didn't want to. Let's just say the environment wasn't healthy enough for us. So we went to Mal's and watched parts of Joseph and the amazing technicolor dreamcoat and starsky and hutch. Wow. Carmen Electra and Amy Smart. Gross. So anyway, it was short lived but so much fun. That's pretty much all I did. Nathaniel is finally home, after being delayed for a century and a half. Yay! Peace.   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone. I am at Rach's house right now. And it is raining. It is "Tornadic Weather" as Rachel says, the sky looks really dark and scary. I'm sitting right next to her window and I am scared...BAH! Rachel is in a towel and that is hot. It is green and she just got out of the shower. I just took some tylenol because I have crampers. Ouch. Yah, this entry is so entertaining. Well Rach and I went to lunch at Wendys and saw the Melville's and I said hi to Bradley and he said "I dont like you." and stuck his tongue out at me. Too bad I dont have a little brother...not. Well after that we picked up Michelle W. we drove to the dmv to get her license renewed because today is her birthday. Happy Seventeenth&nbsp;Birthday to Michelle!! So after standing in line for a century and a half we left. Oh yah, and some teenager going to pick up his license hit this car while parking. What are the odds of hitting a car in the parking lot while getting your license at the dmv?! Oh em gee man. Sucks for him. The damage wasn't small either. Bummer. Then when we got in the car to leave I looked over and saw this really cute puppy doggy. And then it looked up and...it was MISSING AN EYE!! It was just like that scene in toy story yah know. Where he looks over and sees the cute baby doll and he's like "oh hi little guy" and then it comes out and has spider legs and its like "REE! REE! REE! REE!" (that is the psycho theme incase you were wondering) Anyways, Yeah so the dog was freaky. And we took Michelle home and now Rach is drying her hair and we are waiting for Mal to come over and we and a bunch of other people are gonna go eat at olive garden and then go bowling after. In celebration of Michelle's aging. Oh yah and after the bowling we're planning on going to Hollis's house. Fun fun fun fun fun. Nathaniel comes home tonight!! w-o-o h-o-o!! I wish it would stop raining..but for now I guess I'll just have to siiiing in the rain, I'm siiingin in the rain what a glorious feeeeling im haaappy again! Oh yah, and yesterday I went to cheesecake factory and bought "the hippie handbook" at barnes and noble. Score. Okay. Later. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I woke up about 10:45 this morning because my annoying phone kept ringing my ears off. It was Nathaniel and he said he'd call me back but has yet to do so. Oh well, I have just been talking to Priscilla and Mary and Matt this morn. And listening to jimmy eat world, obviously. I feel horrible today, I am totally pmsing and I'm snapping at everyone who talks to me. My dad asked me to pick my mom up from work at lunchtime (now) and I yelled at him...stupid pms. Well I have to go to uta all state camp this weekend since I suck and need more practice. But I'm 'cited since Jing Ling Tam is running it and she's the frikkin funniest little asian lady I know, actually *second funniest, no one beats Ms. Yang! "let's rock let's rock today!" -smacks my butt- wow..good times. So I think I'm gonna have a me day since I keep yelling at everyone, I'm gonna keep to myself and just chill and such. Mom's home..gotta go eat lunch. Later. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I'm waiting for this test to end So these lighter days can soon begin Ill be alone by maybe more carefree like a kite that floats so effortlessly i was afraid to be alone now im scared thats how id like to be all the faces none the same how can there be so many personalities So many lifeless empty hands so many hearts in great demand and now my sorrow seems to far away until im taken by these bults of pain but i turn them off and tuck them away till these rainy days that make them stay and then ill cry so hard to these sad songs and the words still ring, once here now gone and they echo through my head everyday and i dont think theyll ever go away just like thinking of your childhood home but we cant go back were on our own ohhh but im about to give this one more shot and find it in myself ill find it in myself so were speeding towards that time of year to the day that marks your not here and i think ill want to be alone so please understand that i dont answer the phone ill just sit and stare at my deep blue walls untill i can see nothing at all only particles some fast some slow all mys can see is all i know ohh..but im about to give this one more shot and find it in myself ill find it in myself dododododododododododododododododododododododod  
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whenever I see someone less fortunate than I (and let's face it -- who isn't less fortunate than I?) my tender heart tends to start to bleed and when someone needs a makeover i simply have to take over I&nbsp;know,&nbsp;I know exactly what they need and even in your case tho' it's the toughtest case I've yet to face dont worry -- I'm determined to succeed follow my lead and yes, indeed you will be..popular! You're gonna be popular! I'll teach you the proper ploys when you talk to boys little ways to flirt and flounce I'll show you what shoes to wear how to fix your hair everything that really counts to be popular! I'll help you be popular! you'll hang with the right cohorts you'll be good at sports know the slang you've got to know so let's start 'cause you've got an awfully long way to go..don't be offended by my frank analysis think of it as personality dialysis now that I've chose to become a pal, a sis-ter and adviser there's nobody wiser not when it comes to popular --i know about popular and with an assist from me to be who you'll be instead of dreary who-you-were... are...there's nothing that can stop you from becoming popul-ler...lar...LA LA LA LA we're gonna make you popular... When I see depressing creatures with unprepossessing featuresi remind them on their own behalf to think of celebrated heads of state or specially great communicators did they have brains or knowledge? Don't make me laugh! They were popular! Please--it's all about popular! It's not about aptitude it's the way you're viewed so it's very shrewd to be very very popular like me! And tho' you protest your disinterest I know clandestinedly you're gonna grin and bear it your new-found popular --LA LA LA LA LA You'll be popular just not quite as popular as me! 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    i   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am&nbsp;totally diggin the music we didn't learn at camp. Especially the ludwig van. It sort of sounds like the song from donnie darko during the scene that the sky is opening up and he's having memories. I wonder..&nbsp; Anyways, I finally got some sleep today, until noon. So good. So our internet was supposed to be turned off like Wednesday, but it hasn't been. So..oh well. All I've been doing today is practicing my music. I probably won't have anything to do tonight since there's a roomies reunion and I wasn't in the room so I'll have to find someone who wasn't a roomie to hang out with. Either that or just chill at home. I need to do my summer reading anyways. So, I have nothing to write. Appy polly loggies to all. Bye. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I Gondolieri by Gioacchino Rossini  Voghiam sull'a gil vela belo risplendeil cielo la lunae senza velo,  e senza vel, e senza vel, senza tempesta il mar. Voghiam sull'a gil vela risplende beloil cielo. La lunae senza velo, senza tempestail mar.  VOGARRRRR posar sul prato; al gondoliere e da to frai beni, il ben magior. VOGARRRRR posar sul prato; al gondoliere e da to frai beni, il ben magior. VOGARRRRR posar sul prato; al gondoliere e da to frai beni, il ben magior. voghiam, voghiam, voghiam, voghiam, voghiaaaaa-am.  Non cal se brillail sole o mestappar la luna, ognor sulla la guna il gondolier, il gondolier il gondoliere e Re. il gondolier, il gondolier il gondoliere e Re. Ognor, ognor, ognor, Il gondoliere e Re! 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well I am in my room and I really should be sleeping since I have to get up and dry my hair at 6am and then go to tcu at 7:30...so I'll make it quick. I am kinda upset right now. Alden isn't a nice person. I hated him for like a year and now we're finally friends, yet all he does is say mean and hurtful things to me and he says that I'm the one saying the rude things. I don't understand him and I've tried but I just dont care anymore. I have totally given up on him, I can't be his friend. I'll be his friend, just not his close friend. I'm not going to watch out for him anymore either, he's almost 18 and&nbsp;can take care of himself. UGH! This really does bother me. So today's camp was fun..I, a first soprano (the highest part), sat inbetween the basses and the altos. It was pretty neat. We also got our shirts..but I LOST MINE. That's so typical, I lose everything. So now I have to go get another shirt, great. And I have to wake up in less than 6 hrs. Everyone who's staying at the "penthouse" hates me too. What the crap is wrong with me lately. I really have a wonderful life...and then all these little things keep bothering me.&nbsp;Whatever. Goodnight.    
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well they didnt cancel the internet yet..so I'm on again. First day of camp was fun, I'm so glad I'm commuting. GEEZ! I can't go one day without pissing certain people off. It really bugs me that I do NOTHING wrong and get bad looks and bad things said about me. Well, I like the music, it's pretty alright, I dunno if I'd say harder than last year..I guess it's about the same. So there was a dance after rehearsal but we didn't really want to stay so I called my mom and she picked us up and took us for milkshakes and chili cheese fries at Jon's Grille. We even signed our names on the walls. I've always wanted to do that. Anyway, then we dropped Whitney and Mary off at their houses and Alison and Alden came back to mine and we watched What Lies Beneath..so good. Alden had never seen it before. So after it ended I drove them both home. Now I'm home and its midnight and I still havent showered or anything and Alison is picking us up at like 6:30. OH LORD!! I'm gonna die in the morning..so..with that said, I'm off to bed. Later.  &nbsp;  *Oh and my internet is going to be cancelled (for a short amount of time) but I'll try and post tomorrow at Al's house since our carpool is having a sleepover!! Even Alden! Ha..I will  love  that*    
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm gone to TCU choir camp and the internet is being switched over or something while I'm gone so no internet for about a week. Goodbye everyone.  
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So yesterday started out with getting up at about 11am and starting to straighten my hair. Once I was done getting ready I made my way to Rach's house for madrigal rehearsal. Went pretty well except some certain people weren't there so it wasn't as fun as usual, but still it was a good time. So after everyone left, Rach, Sterlo, Alden, Jessi and I went to eat at Sonic/Wendys. After that Jessi went home and we went back to Rach's and just chilled in her room until Mal showed up! Then we drove (with the top down) to grapevine mills and ate in the food court and Alden and Rach got shoes and I got a cd. Thats about all we did there. We decided to go back to the dock and chill. Alden and Sterling are such pyros!! Geez, Alden tried to set a spider web on fire and Sterling kept spraying the candles with off. Ugh. Stupid boys. I need to stop using my card..Seriously, I spent like 20 bucks on it last night. Wow, that was random..well anyways.. Kallie, Colleen and Matt came&nbsp;later on. We were having a great time at the dock playing spin the bottle of truth..until people started saying things that were mean and not meant to be said. So Kallie's feelings got hurt and she left. I really didn't like that, I wish we could have changed that part of the evening, I'm really sorry Kal. So after Rach left to get medicine because she didn't feel well she called us and told us to come back to her house. So all of us, except Colleen, went back to her house and watched the princess bride. I can't believe Rachel hasn't seen the whole thing and Matt hasn't seen ANY of it. Sheesh, princess bride is like a classic. They made me stop quoting every line..bummer. I can't help that I remember everything. Seriously, I don't watch these things everyday, I watch them once and the lines just stick. That explains how i knew that disney movie the other night Rach. I scraped my ankle while rocking back and forth on Rach's chair thing and had to get a bandaid. It hurts. It got to be that time so we said goodbye and I drove Alden and Mal home and got home right on time myself. Yep so I was talking to a bunch of people on aim and my phone rings...and who is it..it's Nathaniel! At TCU! Yah, so I called it a night on the internet and put up an away message and talked to Nathaniel for like two hours about camp and whats been going on back here. Anyway, I got really tired and was about to fall asleep on the phone so I told him goodnight and went to bed. We went to bed at about 2:30, he had to get up at 6:45 and sing alllllll day. I could have gone to see the hockey boys at Mal's work but I was SOOOO tired so I slept until noon. Dang it. I really should have gone. It's so hard to get up for something you know you wanna do but dont HAVE to do.&nbsp;So that's about it. I'm gonna take a shower and actually do something today. Peace.     
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        try to type your name with your (one try only:P)....&nbsp;&nbsp;  nose: autumn  elbow: aujtum&nbsp; n  chin: autum&nbsp; n  feet: aasutumn  eyes closed and one finger: aitimn  back of your hand:&nbsp; ahrym n  palm: autumn  mouse: autumn  wrist: azUJYTRJY M NB  tounge: a85tumn  ear: dxop-l,om n  knee:sweujitygjui m bn     
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So I slept in my new sheets last night..so nice. But then I felt horrible&nbsp;all night and couldn't sleep at all. I had the worst headache and stomach pains..I was tossing and turning all night. I am still a bit upset about yesterday. Son of a bitch. That's all I have to say about that. I'm going to get franz ferdinand today I think. If I can convince my parents to let me leave the house. So I got up to tell Nathaniel bye this morning..11am is the morning for me. And then I couldn't go to his house because I didn't feel good. So I went back to bed then got up about an hour later to watch anne of green gables: the continuing story. Holy crap, those movies are so addictive. Then I ate blueberry&nbsp;muffins and had a fruit cup. Yeah, thats right. Fruit cup. So what the&nbsp;hell am I gonna do until school. I have wasted my entire summer away. Stupid me. I am gonna make these last few weeks so fuckin' memorable. Yeah.&nbsp;For now I'm gonna get my Franz Ferdinand and jam to that. Peace.     &nbsp;   So if you're lonely    You know I'm here waiting for you    I'm just a crosshair    I'm just a shot away from you    And if you leave here    You leave me broken, shattered I lie    I'm just a crosshair    I'm just a shot then we can die  &nbsp;  I know I won't be leaving here with you  &nbsp;  I say don't you know?    You say you don't know    I say take me out  &nbsp;  I say you don't show    Don't move, time is slow    I say take me out  &nbsp;  I say you don't know    You say you don't go    I say take me out  &nbsp;  If I move, this could die  Eyes move, this could die  I want you to take me out  &nbsp;  I know I won't be leaving here    I know I won't be leaving here    I know I won't be leaving here    I know I won't be leaving here with you  &nbsp;  I say don't you know?    You say you don't know    I say take me out  &nbsp;  If I wink, this can die    If I wane, this can die    I want you to take me out  &nbsp;   If I move, this could die  If eyes move, this could die  Come on, take me out  &nbsp;  I know I won't be leaving here    I know I won't be leaving here    I know I won't be leaving here    I know I won't be leaving here with you     
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Saturday..ahh. Thank goodness for the weekend. Pike people are back! Yay! Mom woke up up at about 11:30 today..which is early for me, so I'm tired. We went and deposited my check and went to vista ridge and got me egyptian sheets...so soft. Alright! So then we came home because I was so tired..I'm&nbsp;like the undead. I just finished watching the triathalon...holy crap. I could never do that ever, those people are so fit. Well that's about all I've done today. Now I'm gonna watch the pianist (again) with my parents. Pray that they let me go to the dock tonight. I will be so pissed if i miss&nbsp;THE DOCK. Alright, that's all I've got for now. Peace.     
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Not a good night. It was fun in itself&nbsp;but one thing just ruined my entire night.    
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Oooo so now i get to use like colors..I dunno but&nbsp;my blog&nbsp;was totally upgraded. It really likes me. Obviously. So yesterday was so much fun..besides me being grounded after all of it. It was worth getting grounded for. So after many hours of preparing to leave the house&nbsp;I, Autumn, drove to Kallie's house and picked her sorry butt up. Next, I picked up Rach and we three set off to  stonebriar  mall in Frisco. Me, the driver, knowing I was not allowed to drive outside of Coppell unless I&nbsp;was given&nbsp;my mother's consent. I didn't ask because i knew she would say no and then I'd be stuck at home doing nothing and not out having a good and SAFE time with my friends. So we drove to frisco, we went shopping, Rach got a  banana republic shirt  and Kallie and I didnt get anything. My mother called..this is how the conversation went:   "Um..where are you, Autumn?"   "I'm just hanging out at Rach's house, Mom."   "Do I need to drive over to Rachel's house to see if you're lying?"    "Okay fine, I'm at stonebriar."   "Did you drive your  own  car?"   "Yes."   "Alright, bye."   "Bye."  &nbsp;  We ate and got tired so we decided to go home. I drove myself and my&nbsp;two droogies&nbsp;back to Coppell at about 7:30. We picked up the needed essentials for the night:  citronella  candles and a blanket. Then we visited Mal at work at the stars center and watched some hoooootttt hockey boys skate around. So fine. So we told Mal we'd see her after she got off work and we picked up our other essentials: Nathaniel and his guitar and two bottles of wine..you heard me, wine. Then, we made our way to kid country at about 9 'o clock. After the longest walk ever we spread the blanket out on the dock and lit the candles all around us and talked and sang and I even played guitar. So then, Mal showed up and it was a real happenin' party. After we finished off one of the bottles we decided to play  spin the bottle , but seeing how there was only one guy there I suggested we play a different kind of spin the bottle where someone would ask a really personal question and whoever it landed on they had to answer it. It was really...educational. Now I know what Nathaniel's favourite  animal  is..ha. So anyway, we got going at about ten after 11pm. Because some people had to be home at 11:30. And the park closed at 11:30 anyway. So right as we drove outta the park this cop drives by us. Nothing happened but it was kinda weird how we left just in time. So then I dropped everyone off Rach, Nathaniel, Kallie, Mal and then I got home. Right as I told my mother goodnight she said  "Oh Autumn, you're grounded."  I asked why and she said "For not telling me you were driving to frisco." So thats it. I'm grounded. For like the first time in my life. I wonder for how long..well gotta go run errands because thats part of my groundation. I probably wont be writing a&nbsp; whole lot because I'll just be at home and wont have anything to write about. Well that's all. Hope you all have a real swell day.   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      can you sleep as the sound hits your ears? one at a time an unspoken balance here unabridged for so many years  that I should stare at  receivers to receive her isn't fair  don't worry I'll catch you don't worry I'll catch you don't ever worry  your arms in mine any time wouldn't trade anything you're still my everything  to my suprise before my eyes you arrive  don't worry I'll catch you don't worry I'll catch you don't ever worry  still breaking old habits,  habits you pulled the wool over me and I can see everything everything remembering Jinx removing  don't worry I'll catch you don't wory I'll catch you don't ever worry  no need for reminding you're         still                all                     that                           matters                                    to                                         me... 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well. My life has been crazy the past few days. And I can't even talk about it here. Suck Ass. I just wish I could let it all spill out right here. Oh well, some things arent meant to be said...
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      practice went well yesterday. i enjoyed the tight keyboard they had. tj gave me the best news of my life. might go to nathaniel's today. might go shopping again. we'll see how the day goes.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      fuck it. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Haaallelujah! Haaallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hallelujah! Hal-le-lu-jah!  1068 miles away from me forever!!!
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      good party. good movie. good people. good times.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      everyone is leaving for pike...b-o-o h-o-o. this one goes out to spensah, kit-cat and, the person i get mistaken for the most, mary.   When you’re down and troubled And you need a helping hand And nothing, whoa nothing is going right. Close your eyes and think of me And soon I will be there To brighten up even your darkest nights.  You just call out my name, And you know whereever I am I’ll come running, oh yeah baby To see you again. Winter, spring, summer, or fall, All you have to do is call And I’ll be there, yeah, yeah, yeah. You’ve got a friend.  If the sky above you Should turn dark and full of clouds And that old north wind should begin to blow Keep your head together and call my name out loud And soon I will be knocking upon your door. You just call out my name and you know where ever I am I’ll come running to see you again. Winter, spring, summer or fall All you got to do is call And I’ll be there, yeah, yeah, yeah.  Hey, ain’t it good to know that you’ve got a friend?  People can be so cold. They’ll hurt you and desert you. Well they’ll take your soul if you let them. Oh yeah, but don’t you let them.  You just call out my name and you know wherever I am I’ll come running to see you again. Oh babe, don’t you know that, Winter spring summer or fall, Hey now, all you’ve got to do is call. Lord, I’ll be there, yes I will. You’ve got a friend. You’ve got a friend. Ain’t it good to know you’ve got a friend. Ain’t it good to know you’ve got a friend. You’ve got a friend. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hmm..so I did quite a lot yesterday. It started out with madrigal rehearsal at Jessi's. Sterling called me while I was getting ready.."Autumn, the door is locked and no ones home, I've been here for ten minutes." "Sterling, she has gotta be there, she probably doesnt here the doorbell. Go around thru the backyard." "Okay, oh! There she is! She's just sitting there on the phone." So the practice started at 11am and but I waited for mother to come home so I could eat lunch with her and then be off. So I was about an hour late. It's okay though because I got a lot of nice "AUTUMN!!"'s from the guys sectional when I accidentally walked into their room. Yep, so we sang a little with just girls and then we sang together. And Alden brought his baby niece. So cute. I got to hold her a lot too, but she slobbered all over my music whenever I did. After rehearsal was over me, Travis, Sarah, TJ, Jason and Liz kinda bonded in the pool..since we were the only ones who got in. Yeah, so we got out and decided to go to sonic and get drinks..mmm mmm. Watermelon slushes are greatness. Then we drove back and played battle of the sexes, that was pretty interesting, I now know that I have no knowledge about men what so ever. I knew about tools and stuff but nothing about racing cars or budlight commercials or the president of the NRA. So, I took Travis and Sarah home and went back to Jessi's to see about our plans to see the notebook, but the next showing was too late and it would end after curfew so we decided to just watch a movie at Jessi's. So me, Jessi, Alden, Rach, Mal, Nathaniel, Jason, Jake and KALLIE went to Jessi's house for the night. We didnt really watch a movie until later. Kallie got her guitar and we played and sang. She sang her own song which friggin ROCKED while I painted Rach's nails hot pink. After that I painted Nathaniel's toe nails pink too. Thats right, Nathaniel has hot pink toe nails. The night ended with Newsies, open the gates and sieze the day!! Wow, choir people are so incredibly corny. Then I took Nathaniel home and then I took myself home. And went to bed. The End. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    so good.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well Sanela ittied back to Oklahoma at 7:30am this morn. But we got snapshots taken for her and she'll have those to remember us by. Yesterday, I picked S-dawg up and we yeckated to Walmart and met up with her two sisters and cousin, then we ittied thrift store shopping. I really liked all the sabogs but I didnt kupet any of my pretty polly I only have like ten gollies left for the week. Then I dropped her off at her house to do her luscious glory. I stopped by Catherine's to viddy her pots. They are all glazed, they look so horrorshow. So I got home and had some pischa and peets and shvatted a lie down ,and I waited for Sanela for about an hour or so. Catherine was going to dinner with Zack Visconti and some other guys, but I vareeted to stay and wait for Sanela. I ittied to starbucks and read  a clockwork orange  and sipped on a tass of chai until Sanela called. She finally called and I sobiratted her and we met Cat and the malchicks at olive garden. I met Zach Morgan, Mitch and James. Boy, they were very sladky. All musically talented too, thats so interessovatting. Yeah, so after that we vareeted to go to starbucks..again. And fillied in the parking lot. Thats where we took all the snapshots. Then a random gruppa of choir vecks showed up..it was flip. Like all of them..it was so gloopy. I slooshed this one warble that made me want to start warbling along. It was real hound and horny. Then Scott Horton and Kyle Earnheart showed up and I govoreeted with them. Anyways, after Catherine left Sanela and I ittied to Kyle's domy and we tree had some smecks and guffs until I was fagged. So I dropped her off and ittied home. Then I nazzed a little more with some dobby droogs and I finally called it a nachy and zasnooted and sneeted.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    j'adore napoleon dynamite beacoup&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wow, i have a major headache. i went thrift store shopping with sanela and her sisters and cousin. we're bout to go out again. dunno what we're gonna do. i'll update when i get home, and if i dont come home tonight i'll update tomorrow morning.  peace.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      YAY! I am so happy that Sanela-nela is in town for a couple of days! I'm about to go do something with her, put curses on people to make them fat and such. Cuz i so already have. MUAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA! So, I woke up this morning to the sound of rain. It was just wonderful... Okay so I talked to Sanela about something major that I've been thinking about lately. And she told me to carpe di em, so I'm gonna. Thanks salmanela, you rock. I was just kidding about the salmanela part..haha. Thats about it..got nothin else. I'll update later tonight and tell you all about my day. HAVE A GREAT DAY EVERYONE!
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes, it's true I was gone for three whole days. B-o-o H-o-o! Ah, I got to talk to Spenser while I was there..kinda by accident though, but still it cheered me up bunches. And my cousin said "taco flavored 'keesies'" bahaha, thats great...and no one knows what the hell im talking about. Inside joke with spensaaa. Yah, so I was at my cousins' lake house in Tyler forever. While I was there I got to see FOUR films I hadnt seen yet, all of which I liked. Saturday night: A Clockwork Orange. OMG! That is so going on my favourite movies list. It's amazing how Stanley Kubrick takes these incredible books and make them into movies that are SOOO..insendiary! So good. Sunday afternoon: Matrix Revolutions..it was  okay , I really didnt like Trinity dying. That sucked. But overall it was a badass movie. Sunday night: Ghost World. Hmm..pretty well made independent film, it's hard to like a film when you dont like the main character. And I didnt like the main character much.  Sunday night/Monday morning: Y tu mama tabien. Translation..And your mother too. Wow, I really like mexican boys after seeing that movie. It had a good plot (I guess) but didnt really teach an actual lesson. It was just like "Hey, let's make a movie with this older woman having sex with these 16 yr old boys." Which I am TOTALLY for, because these mexican boys were FINEEEEEEEEEEEE! (emphasis on the I, not the E) So, lots of good movies this weekend, clockwork orange was my favourite though. Stanley Kubrick never fails to shock the hell out of me. Bummer that there wont be anymore films of his.  Enough about movies..I got so burned on the back of my legs, my back and my chest. Geez..I can hear you saying "Autumn you are so silly, why dont you use sunscreen?!" Well, I DO use it, spf 5000 man!! It just doesnt work. I swear, the sun picks on me. He's like "Oh, there's that little ginger Irish chick, Let's make her skin match her hair." Well..yeah. Anyways, I went out on the jetskis with my cousin Graham and my aunt Jill a few times. And I went tubing with Lee-bones behind aunt Jill's jetski. Holy Mother of Pearl. She totally killed us on that thing. It was SO rough. My arms are so sore and my neck hurts all over too. AND I lost my earring..DAMMIT! The really awesome ones that my mom gave me..oh yeah like my only pair that i actually wear. Geez, just my luck. So the fire works were tight, I went with Lee and Adam to get them. Boy did we get some goodens. I liked the friendship pagodas..hehe. "Pagoda! Wheres my havolina?!" Name that movie. Anyways..the best one was the Thunder Dome, and you have to say "Thunder Dome" in a booming voice that makes it sound really super cool. We just chilled at the lake house during the day, then me and the cousins all went back to the real house in Tyler and watched movies and slept and such. I talked to Navid on the phone while I was watching Clockwork and again when i was watching Y tu mama tambien or "Porn" as he called it. Porn movies dont have plots Navid. Geez, I always hate when they try to have a plot though..I mean.... I went to bed at about 4:30 and I got up at 8:30 and slept on the way back in the car. I know how anxious all of you were for me to come back to Coppell. Hmm..then I wonder why no one has called me yet..-sad face-  All in all it was a fantabulous fourth of july weekend. I hope you had the same greatness as I did.
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sun is shinin' in the sky there ain't a cloud in sight. It's stopped rainin' ev'rybody's in a play. And don't you know it's a beautiful new day hey hey  Runnin' down the avenue see how the sun shines. Brightly in the city on the streets  Where once was pity. Mister Blue Sky Is living here today hey hey  Mister Blue Sky please tell us why You had to hide away for so long  Where did we go wrong?  Mister Blue Sky please tell us why . . .  Hey you with the pretty face welcome to the human race. A celebration Mister Blue Sky's up there waitin' And today is the day we've waited for hey hey  Mister Blue Sky please tell us why . . .  Hey there Mister Blue we're so pleased To be with you look around  See what you do ev'rybody smiles at you.  Hey there Mister Blue we're so pleased . . .  Mister Blue you did it right  But soon comes Mister Night creepin' over  Now his hand is on your shoulder never mind I'll remember you this I'll remember you this way. Mister Blue Sky please tell us why . . .  Hey there Mister Blue we're so pleased 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I went to bed at 4:30.  Someone  kept me up till then, thanks a lot. I also apologize for going to Napoleon without you, we will go one of these days. And I will most definitely drive. Well, I really have nothing more to say. Not much going on lately. I leave for Tyler tomorrow. Yay. Can't wait to see Greer, Graham and Lee-bones. Later.   Dedicated to the newest Postal Service fan, Navid:  Smeared black ink... your palms are sweaty And i'm barely listening to last demands I'm staring at the asphalt wondering what's buried underneath where i am  I'll wear my badge... a vinyl sticker with bigh block letters adherent to my chest That tells your new friends i am a visitor here... I am not permanent And the only thing keeping me dry is where i am  You seem so out of context in this gaudy apartment complex A stranger with your door key explaining that i am just visiting And i am finally seeing why i was the one worth leaving  D.C. sleeps alone tonight  You seem so so out of context in this gaudy apartment complex A stranger with your door key explaining that i am just visiting And i am finally seing why i was the one worth leaving The district sleeps alone tonight after the bars turn out their lights And send the autos swerving into the loneliest evening And i am finally seeing why i was the one worth leaving   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      holy cow, i love that place. it's so sophisticated and classy. i absolutely love it. i am so going back, often if i can. napoleon friggin rocked. oh man so good. havent seen such a great movie like that in so long.  matt sure liked it: Midget Matt 2005: my new favorite pick-up line: Midget Matt 2005: "Are you drinking 1% milk because you think you're fat? Because you could totally drink whole milk"  Midget Matt 2005: shut up Midget Matt 2005: iiiiidiot  autumndddddddddd: tina come get some ham Midget Matt 2005: lol Midget Matt 2005: I like the quesadilla part autumndddddddddd: haha i know Midget Matt 2005: good movie, good movie ... I was thoroughly impressed  Midget Matt 2005: The beginning Midget Matt 2005: the credits Midget Matt 2005: INGENIUS Midget Matt 2005: I was like, "How brilliant is that !? And cost-effective" autumndddddddddd: i know!! Midget Matt 2005: and amusing, too   So, not much more to say. I hope everyone had a good night and I love all of you.   And Kallie, I really dont think Jimi Hendrix is higher than Jesus, I was just kidding about that..but believe me, jimi is up there man. ha, jk. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am glad to go back. Yet, I am not glad that I have english first tri and I haven't even started my book yet... 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      washed my car. watched movies at kal's. got in lots of fights. got toilet water wiped all over my face and spit all in my hand. i am cranky and tired and going to bed. goodnight. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I got the eternal sunshine soundtrack and polyphonic spree and fight club on dvd. I am tired so I'm gonna take a shower and go to bed. Goodnight.  I really wish certain people would be nicer. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      obviously i dont have any pictures of that. Start from the bottom and work your way up. It's chronological..amazing isnt it. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterlings sleeping&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    sleeping Michael&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Mal and Sterlo&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Rach reading&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    aww they love eachother&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    back in the car&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    heart to heart&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    falling asleep on the couch&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Hollis's poker face&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    my shufflin' it up&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    time for some poker&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    rachels a monkey too&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me and sterlo on a buffalo bench&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    weeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    a lot of us in the tree&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    ..and again&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me in the tree again&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me in a really cool tree&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterling laughing at Michael&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Michael inbetween the fountain thing&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    moi&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Me and Rach&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterlo on a rail&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterling dancing on a bench&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Michael is pretty too&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterling is pretty&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    walking down steps&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    under the bridge again&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Rach under the bridge&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    aww its the boys&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    boys posing in front of riverwalk&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The girls posing at the front of the riverwalk &nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    hooters&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    bar&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    hey another bar&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    petting the pony&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Mike and Mal dancing to the banjo music&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    a crazy banjo player on the street "Italia!!! Muahahahaha!" &nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Mal riding the buffalo&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    One of many buffalos around Bricktown&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Bricktown!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterlo showing Michael something..&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Jessica taking my picture in the room&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me and Sterlo trying out the beds&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    in the hotel room&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    checkin out the bathrooms&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterlo and the cabinet&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterling broke the cabinet  urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    finally at the hotel&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Kallie so cute!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Rach and Sterlo dancin'&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Rach dancin'&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Mike and Mal dancin&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Michael being totally gay&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    dancing with sterlo at the sorority house&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    shooting pool&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterling playing video games&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Jessica!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Rach and Mal chillin at the tv&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    getting some grub&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterlo, Rach and Mal  urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    jessica is blurred because she was walking fast&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterling picked us flowers  urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    walking around campus some more  urlLink    
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    walking around the campus&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Mal and Rach&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    We're finally there!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Close up on Michael&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterling's so crazy&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Sterling impersonating "she who must not be named"&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Aww..it's Sterlo&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Rach practicing her music too&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Michael&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    singing in the car&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    kallie sleept too&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    mal sleeping on the way&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    loading the car some more&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    loading the car&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    before we left in Mike's kitchen&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just got back from Oklahoma! Michael, me, Rach, Kal, Hollis, Sterling and Mal decided on a road trip last minute. I got the news like thirty minutes before we were leaving. I packed my things and we all loaded up in the Gasparro van to head to OU where Annie (mike's sis) goes to school. She was doing a sorority rush thing and we all went to see it and the campus and such. It's really cool, it's always been my number 1 choice in colleges. We stayed right in Bricktown, it was sweet, we got this awesome hotel room and were upgraded to have free breakfast in the concierge suite thing. It was tight. We got there and ate and saw the end of Annie's Delta Gamma cheer. Then we saw her room and Mrs. G dropped us off in Bricktown to roam around for a bit. After all of that fun stuff we went back to the hotel and chilled there all night. We played poker and I only got to do my tarot once because Michael and Kallie think it's evil. Then me and Kal didnt go to bed until like 3:30 (after everyone else) and then we got up at 7:30 (before anyone else). Then we went back to Annie's sorority and me, Hollis and Sterlo chilled in the car while everyone else went to the music building. Then we loaded up and drove home. It was a memorable experience and I am sooooooooo tired. I'll post some pictures from the trip now. Peace. 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me and my camera&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      its all over and I have a tummy ache... 
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    party's over...&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Michael messed up face aka Satan&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Michael doing the gazelle freestyle&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me "talking to someone"&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me again&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Hollis feeling matt's "huge" muscle&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Matt pretending to be tough&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    hollis pinching his nipple&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    matt in pain after nipple pinching&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    hollis pinky swearing she wont pinch his nipples&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    rachels masterpiece&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    cake before&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    cake after&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    par-tay!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>


</Blog>