<Blog>


<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      just came back frm malaysia.. what a trip man~. the trip was awesome, its practically a bus ride to -and- fro rather than a holiday. but what's more important, is the registration for the bmat and some other exams.. wad the hell man, it suddenly turned to a futile trip. shelley got into trouble with her gf again, man~. again, ya, again. i dont know if this time the breakup is real. haha.. hope not, coz i think they are meant to be for each other. it took shelley so long to get other winnie when winne was sent back to sarawak, but now!.. winnie is back, and they are back, and broke up again.. wad complicated stuff.. it makes me think of those days with catherine back last year. i see so much of catherine in shelley, while of coz not the loving part.. probably just the physical attributes. audrey.. another love-victim. haiz, i am so tired, i need to sleep.. gonna meet shelley tomorrow, she want to go for drink, hope we dont stay out till too late, coz i need to reach home by 930pm. if not, i will get into very very bug trouble.. 
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       everytime is in a mess now. i am typing this with a cigarette stuck in my mouth, and the ash is gonna drop off. god, i just chocked myself with the smoke. damn it man, i am turning into the world's worst smoker.  i realise i cant do things as well as i used to. maybe i am indeed growing old.    there's so many things to study. and i am so much behind time. but i love the never ending task. time indeed flies. its already august. i am wondering if i am living in the past. january had exams, and those exams seemed like yesternights. and june exams seems like this morning. and soon, more exams coming up. i jus love it man. the pleasure and joy of seeing and completing everything, beautiful. i dont know anymore more satisfying pleasure then studying.   when that the poor had cried, Caesar had wept. ambition should be made of sterner stuff. how ture, shakespeare, how true.   this got to be my last pack of cigarette, i kw this is the ample time i am saying this. i gonna hav to make smoking a quits. i am running out of time here. and i cant find the full article for A case of multiple personality. any one have it?    i doubt so, except mayb OCR students frm UK. how i wish i am not in spore. spore is just so limited. darn. yah, national day just over. i am no patriot. do i have to be one?    i suspect i am suffering frm abnormal disorder, how ironical. damn man... i really got to go and find the case study. where are u case?? come tell me where are u...   Ps, Missions.. argh.. and intereacting with students at sbc, am i made for it?      Oh sure i am.. i am who i think i am. i can be who i wan to be.. how self-esteem can build u. ya..   another stick down my throat again. i cant stop smoking. wad can i do in a world so huge?    
      
</post>


<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Name : Tan MiaoShan, Rachel Home Address : Blk 439 Hougang Ave 8 #16-1545 Singapore 530439 Email : miaoshan@singnet.com.sg Date Of Birth: 1 November 1987 Webpage : zaccheus.blogspot.com   Religion  : Christianity  Church : VFC (assemblies of God)    Education   Homeschool A levels(UOL) 2003-2004 BMC Academy O levels(UOL) 2003 Bowen Secondary School   O levels' subjects  (January 2004) English Mathematics B (Pure) Chemistry (Pure) Physics Accounting   A Levels  (January 2004) (H) Biology Grade D English Lit Grade C Mathematics (P-paper1-3, Stat 1, Mech 2 &amp;3) Flunked History (AS) Flunked Economics (AS) Grade D General Studies (AS) Grade B    A levels' subjects  (June 2004) English Literature Human Biology Economics General Studies (AS level)  results will only be out in late August    IQ Score : 120     Working experience   June-Nov 2003 Delifrance Asia June 02- May 03 KFC Pvt Ltd  (Both jobs held part time)    Interest  : medicine (psychiatry)   Language  : English (Grade 'A' at O levels') Chinese (well-spoken but average writting ability) Latin (basic understanding of the language)   Other abilities  : -knows basic html -knows how to use all the main programs in Microsoft Office -basic accounting knowledge(did O level's accounting) -typing speed : 259WPM   References  : 1) Selin Lua Delifrance Asst. Store manager Tel: 92765455 2) Mrs Samuel BMC Academy 2003 English and History Teacher   More referees can be provided upon demand.    More : I am now waiting for my A Levels results, of which i did with University Of London(UOL) Edexcel Examination Board. I homeschool because i am inspired by the challege. I will be doing A levels' Chemistry with UOL in January '05, of which, i will clash my results in with the recent exam. I will be applying for NUS next year. I am hoping to get into Faculty of Medicine. But if i do not meet the Fac- standard, i will settle on Arts and Social Sci (English Literature).      
     

    
</post>


</Blog>