<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Saw "Chronicles of Riddick" on Sunday with my best buddy. The movie was a disappointment to me, actually. I mean, it was darn full of action packed stunts, cool looking spaceships, weird animals, and other stuff worthy of making it one of my favourite movies of all time. But...  It's not! The story line was lame. Seriously. It reminded me of "Scorpion King". If "Chronicles of Riddick" was shown first, then maybe it could have made it into my 'favourite movies of all time' list. But it didn't. Sorry Vin Diesel. Among the movies in my list are "Braveheart", a Mel Gibson movie; "The Professional", a Luc Besson movie; "Pulp Fiction", "From Dusk Till Dawn", "Reservoir Dogs", all three directed by Quentin Tarantino.   While in KLCC, read Whoopi Goldberg's book entitled "Book". I'm serious, it's called "Book". Anyway, it's quite funny, actually. And I spent a few minutes reading through some chapters. In "Book", you'll find out why she's called 'Whoopi'. I'm not sure whether it's true, but it's funny, nonetheless. And although I've only read a couple of chapters of "Book", I think I like Tim Allen's "Don't Stand Too Close To A Naked Man" better. Another book I like is Michael Caine's autobiography called "What's It All About?" (the title referring to his first monster smash, Alfie). He wrote the book himself, and he's darn witty.   Bumped into some old friends in KLCC. Well, can't really say friends, since I don't know them that well. They were in the same college as I was back in uni. They were my seniors. Do you realise that whenever you bump into people who used to go to the same school or the same university (although you barely knew them), they will act as if you've known them well during the period of time when they were in your live? I do. And I think it's to do with a familiar face. I mean, a person looks at you and say, "Wait a minute, I know you from [insert university name here], don't I?". Then the person will update you on people you barely knew as well. I find this flattering, actually. Since they obviously still remember me, although I've grown a beard and gained a good couple of pounds. Hehehehe...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Came to work last night. Arrived at the office around 9.40pm. Then waited for the vendors to arrive. We started work at 10.40pm. Had to wait for the main person for last night's exercise. (Note: Exercise here means the activity that needed to be done last night; and not those exercise where you have to get into darn tight leotards, although if I wanted to, I could have gone to the office wearing leotards.. but then again, the guards might actually arrest me... heheheh....) Anyway, the exercise last night was to complete the shadow image we created that evening. It took a couple of minutes, all in all, it took us roughly 40-50 minutes, this plus the discussion, the scribbling down notes, and the 'what was that again' from us who wasn't as good as the main guy.  After that, I went straight to 7-11 to get some snacks for my parents and for the birthday celebration today. I'll talk about that a bit later on. Anyway, bought two bars of Cadbury chocolates. Bought the type without nuts or raisins or whatever else they put in chocolates nowadays. I love the plain type. Fantastic. Seriously. Breaking a piece, putting it in your mouth, savouring the taste, letting the chocolate melt on your tongue, then playing around with it in your mouth, getting the taste of it all over the insides of your mouth. Then licking it clean. Fantastic....  As I was saying earlier, today in the office, we had this big birthday celebration. This party was for everyone whose birthdays are from January till June. And I was one of them. We got mugs that says "Selamat Hari Lahir", and "PTM" on one side, and my name on the other side. It's nice. I really like the mug. Thanks guys. Although I know none of my office mates reads my blog, except for one person. Thanks, this one person. Heheheh...  Am currently reading "Last Man Standing" by David Baldacci. Darn good book. Darn right it is. My uncle passed me the book through my cousin, who was suppose to read it, then pass it to me. But then she said she couldn't go on reading the book because she found it boring. Well, not to me! I can't put the book down. It's so action packed and interesting. Haven't finish reading it, though. Am taking my time with it, so I can enjoy it more. And am also currently reading Michael Moore's "Stupid White Men". It's funny, but I sort of stopped reading it the moment I got Mr Baldacci's book. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday, my ex-colleagues came to my office for a demo. They showed my colleagues and me the wonderful world of IBM. Or more specifically, IBM's WebSphere Studio Application Developer (WSAD). It was good to see them again. My ex-colleagues, I mean. I invited them over to do the demo so that we can decide on what development tools to use. So far, our boss has decided to use Java. So now it's up to us to know as many developments tools there are in the market as possible, then to choose the best. In other words, the easiest to use. After the demo, (which took about 2 hours to finish, this plus the question and answer session and the eating and drinking session... hehehe), I went out for lunch with my ex-colleagues. Just the six of us. Just like the old times. Sometimes, I still miss them, the old office, the environment, the friendships.   Alas, now I am in a whole new environment, getting to know new people, getting to know the workings of a hospital, and getting to be called 'doctor' once in a while! Heheheh... I think I should start wearing a stethoscope and a white doctor's coat and walk around wards and clinics just for kicks. Then, when somebody ask me a medical question, I'll quickly put my hand to my chin and say "hmmm... interesting question... I think you should refer your [insert ailment here] to [insert a doctor's name here], because I feel he/she is more experienced with that kind of thing".  So, what do you think? Can I pull it off? Hehehehe...  Yesterday had a chat with a friend of mine, and I commented on her blog. Well, actually, it was more a comment on the things she didn't say. And I said, if it was true, then I'm happy for her. At first she denied everything, saying it's not true. Then after a while she became defensive. And started being angry, although she did it in a joking way. After that, I logged off because I had to go home then. Then in the evening, before Maghrib, I think, she called me up and asked whether I was hurt by what she said. Of course not, said I. And we started talking on the phone. She was, at that time, driving home from work. Hands-free, of course.   Anyway, the reason I brought that up is, I don't know what's going on. With her, I mean. She's a really good friend, but I don't know why I made her angry. No, let me rephrase that. I don't know why she was angry with me. And this morning she was angry with me still. She said it was because England lost. If you are reading this, dear angry friend, I apologise. Hope we can still remain friends.  On a more cheerful note, a friend of mine just called me up. A few minutes ago. She just arrived in Malaysia from Australia. And she sounded so happy. She said she's been calling everyone and telling them that she's back in Malaysia, and she was suprised that everyone was excited that she was back. She said it made her feel like the Prime Minister. Hehehe... I was excited as well. I was darn happy to hear from her. We used to be colleagues. And her other half is my junior from school.  On a more wonderfully cheerful note, my beloved just called. She's still in bed though. It's so good to hear her voice. Although we call each other up every single day. Hehehe. Am missing her so much. She's at home at the moment, her classes starts on Sunday, since she's studying in Terengganu at the moment. How I wish she is here with me now. Don't want anyone else. She is all I'll ever need. I pray our 'jodoh' is strong since ours is a long distance relationship.  InsyaAllah . Miss you, my love.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Early in the morning, planned to have breakfast with two of my colleagues. A normal routine for us. I would usually wait for one of them to arrive to work, then the both of us will be waiting for the third one to arrive. So, this morning, we were all in the office, getting ready to go, one of us has to put on some makeup first. Anyway, as I was in the gents, my boss came in and asked me whether I've had breakfast, and he asked me to join him for breakfast. I was obviously felt guilty. So I went to see my colleagues to ask them to join us, but they declined. So it was just my boss and I.   During breakfast, we talked about work, naturally. So I'm assuming he did ask me to join him for this purpose. He asked for any updates on what I'm doing. And he informed me of certain things that I wasn't aware of. And in the end, he paid for the meal. Heheheh. Then while we were having breakfast and discussing about work and stuff, I got a call from the office. And it was my immediate boss. Apparently, there was a problem in the office and she needed me to come in as soon as possible. So, I rushed through my 'roti canai' and iced tea, and we sped to the office.  The problem was a serious one. And she needed me to liase with our vendor from Australia. As of now, around 5 hours from her phone call, the problem has been settled. I hope! Thank goodness for vendors. Heheheh. I used to be a vendor in my previous job. And I can tell you, it's sometimes painful if you have a difficult client. So now I try to be pleasant to the vendors. I try. Really I do.  Just today, we had two blackouts! One in the morning and the other one around half an hour ago. It's so annoying, especially when you are busy updating your blog, and chatting at the same time! I mean, when you are busy doing work! Heheheh...    Lunch today was provided by my department, since we had a meeting around lunch time. We ought to have more meetings around lunchtime. Then we wouldn't need to go out and look for food. And the food was suprisingly good. Because I actually thought about having seconds. It was a good meal, and now I'm sleepy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I want to explain why my blog is called Dance Dance Dance. Well, the name is actually a book by a Japanese author. His name, Haruki Murakami. I first learned about him from my brother. The first time I read his book, I was enthralled by it. I don't think I can explain the atmosphere of the book. It's just so surreal. I'm not sure I can explain it so that you can understand the intensity of what I've just said. You have to read it to understand what I mean. I like the book so much, I just bought a copy of it for myself. Before this, I would read my brother's copy over and over again. I intend to collect Haruki Murakami's entire collection. A book at a time.  "Dance dance dance continues the extraordinary adventure of an ordinary man. At thirty something, Murakami's nameless hero lives in a hi-tech, high-rise world where old virtues die fast and success is all that matters. He has shared in the glittering city's spoils, and while he has not sold his soul, he knows that something is lacking in his life.        Now, in dreams, a mysterious woman weeps softly - for him. Yet, even as he tries to understand why, the voice that beckons is not hers. And still he dreams. Bizarre dreams that propel him down byways of his life in search of ... ?    His is a strange odyssey: en route, a thirteen-year-old girl, distressingly beautiful and clairvoyant, is his constant companion; a classmate, now oozing charm on TV soaps, grapples with murder; a lady of the night becomes his guardian angel; and an eccentric Sheep Man materializes to counsel and cajole. What's a fellow to do? Dance. You gotta dance as long as the music plays. And dance is what our hero does ... in the most unexpected ways!" 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just had a discussion with a user. A little background information before I start today's ramblings. Heheh. We are currently developing the Hospital Information System for our dear beloved hospital. So, we need some information from users, naturally. Just now, we had a long discussion on the user requirements. The thing is, the discussion could be very brief. If it were up to me, it would have taken, the most around 45 minutes. And this with question and answer session. But our discussion lasted almost two hours. And I'm exhausted. Seriously!  This morning, I read in a friend's blog about user support and how the user was extremely inept at searching for things on his computer. In my case, however, he is the master of his subject, so we were in the user's shoes, so to speak. So it took him almost two hours to finish lecturing us. If it weren't for the fact that it was almost time to go home, I wouldn't be suprise if he still wanted to continue the discussion.   Enough of that. Had a rather tiring day today. I'm not sure why, actually. What did I do today? Hmmm... Well, in the morning, I had a discussion with a vendor from Australia via MSN Messenger, then another discussion with a vendor from Malaysia via phone, then yet another discussion, with a colleague, this time face to face. Have to settle a few matters before the week ends. Then, after lunch went to see the user.  On a more brighter note, a colleague of mine received flowers today. She was so excited when I told her about it, since it was I who received it from the messenger. I started to pass it to my colleague's staff, but then thought better of it, and deposited it straight into her room.    Before lunch, I went to see someone at the ICU. He just had his operation yesterday, I think. Anyway, I saw him and we talked for quite some time. He seemed bored with having to be in the ICU. I hope I cheered him up some. He had six holes in one of his lungs. So that lung completely collapse, causing him serious pain and difficulty in breathing. So the operation yesterday, the doctor stapled the holes. Then, as we were talking, a senior staff came to see him, then acknowledged me. The thing is, he looked at me, smiled and said "Doctor" while extending his hand timidly. I smiled and took his extended hand. I didn't have the heart to tell him that I'm not a doctor. Hehehehe.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today is a Monday. Nuff said!!   Am not feeling too good about today. Am missing my beloved. Today is her first day of classes, for three weeks, then off to do her practical training. *Sigh* So far away we are from each other.   Work is work. My big boss sent me an SMS yesterday to call for a meeting this morning at 8.30am. This morning, as I was entering his room for the discussion, he stood up and said he was hungry and asked me whether I was hungry as well. Before I could answer, he said "Let's go to level 7 for breakfast". So we did, with another colleague of mine. So we had the discussion there.   Didn't do much over the weekend. Just sat at home, either reading, walking around, looking for food, or watcing dvds'. Just lazed around. So not in the mood. I wonder when I'll snap out of it. Maybe it's taking longer because the time we spent together this time was longer and more fulfilling.  Saw Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban. Quite a good movie, actually. And like someone said to me earlier, it's not like the first two. The first two is, for lack of a better word, childish. This movie is quite dark and forbidding. And it's so illogical, but then again, that's the appeal, huh. I don't know, I think I like the first two better.   Saw "The Patriot". The one with Mel Gibson. Saw it alone on Saturday. Then when my parents came back from somewhere, saw it with them. In the end, my parents saw it again. I like the movie tremendously. Almost as much as "Braveheart". It's almost the same, isn't it. I mean, the hero loses someone he loves. Then he avenges their death. But darn good movie, nevertheless.  Saw "Desperate Measures". Andy Garcia and Micheal Keaton. Yes, I was bored that weekend. That's why I saw so many movies. Saw it with my mother, then my father and niece joined us. In the end, I was bored with the movie. So I started reading a book. Heheheh...  Can't seem to concentrate too well these days. Actually, I can. But when I'm not doing anything, then I'll feel it. The emptiness, the boredom, the loneliness. It's not as bad as it sounds, trust me. Just need to get over this thick sense of loneliness enveloping me.   I can't believe I actually wrote all of that. I am seldom open with people. I do sometimes, but not often. I'd rather listen than talk. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hereby officiate this blog to be mine. To be the property of eL. To be written in and to be edited however I seem fit. Hehehe. Nothing much to write about at the moment. Just that I am still in the office at the moment, and am about to leave.   Am feeling quite tired. I may be catching something. A fever, maybe. I've been surrounded by sick people all week, so maybe finally I'm being infected by them. Hmmm... Reminds me of the movie "28 Days Later". But those people were infected with  rage ... and it's a darn good movie. Go watch it!    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am currently listening to Hoobastank's  The Reason . Am liking to hear it very much, at the moment. Although I still like to hear Three Doors Down's  Here Without You . My next door cubicle mate is currently happily listening to  Can't Take My Eyes Off You  by Frankie Vallie.&nbsp;Went to the clinic this morning. My blood pressure is normal, Alhamdulillah.&nbsp;And I got my blood result today as well. The doctor said everything was ok, so&nbsp;I didn't need to go there anymore. Alhamdulillah.&nbsp;So that's that. My mum will&nbsp;be relieved to hear that. So will my beloved. She&nbsp;said she was worried when I told her that my blood pressure was high the first time around.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  After seeing the doctor this morning, rushed back to the office since I had to attend a training. The training was for Oracle's  Recovery Manager  or RMAN for short. Nothing much to write about that. I mean, it wasn't that interesting or anything. Just your normal everyday training. So tomorrow we'll be implementing the RMAN on the  Sun E3500  server.&nbsp;Now, that should prove interesting,&nbsp;and successful, I hope. After that, we need to implement RMAN on a production server. That will be done&nbsp;while everyone's asleep.&nbsp;We might start at midnight. Because the ritual needs to be performed with&nbsp;the blood of a living chicken. I mean, you can't get blood from a dead chicken, can you. Duh! Hehehehe...&nbsp;&nbsp; Just kidding.  Saw  Shrek2  again last night. My sister bought my niece the DVD. So after the credits, I asked my parents to keep watching, because I heard that there was an extension&nbsp;to the movie. And lo and behold, there was! But I'm not gonna write it here, since it would spoil everything. So, go watch it yourself! Hehehe. I've watched Shrek2 over and over and it's still funny.&nbsp;Seriously! I seriously need to&nbsp;watch other movies, huh. Can't depend on  Shrek2  can I. Well, I might watch  Van Helsing &nbsp;tonight.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My body is aching at the moment. To be precise, my arms. To be even more precise, my biceps. Yesterday it was worst. It felt like my whole body was aching. Took a couple of Panadols to&nbsp;alleviate the pain. It all started on Friday night. A very good friend of mine gave me the chance to get a free trial of a gym somewhere in KL. So I went with my best buddy. The place was seriously huge and full of equipments, and with lots of sweating bodies. Male and female. Went on the treadmill for 20 minutes, then went on to try the upper body workout. Must have exerted myself. That was the reason for the pain. But it was the good kind of pain. The kind where you feel you can't move, but after a while you develop some serious mucles. Hehehe... I wish!! &nbsp; Am currently reading Haruki Murakami's  Dance Dance Dance  and Iain Banks'  Whit . I've read these two books before. A couple of times. But I still love to read these books, over and over again.&nbsp;And besides, I don't have anything else to read. Well, actually, I do, but I don't feel like reading non-fiction at the moment. I don't think I'll ever get bored with  Dance Dance Dance . Although I have to get Murakami's other books. Maybe I'll go to Kinokuniya this coming Saturday or Sunday to get it. I think I've written about Murakami's books, but I have to say something here as well. His books are surreal. Seriously. I really can't explain it any better than that. When I read his books, I can actually feel the atmosphere of the place he is describing. I mean, it's seriously fantastic. I know I sound like a bludee nerd, but that's the truth (not the nerd part, the surreal part). &nbsp; Am planning to watch King Arthur this weekend. But I heard it isn't as good as I thought it would be. I heard they took the epic straight from the history books. So none of those magical folks or heroic deeds that blows the mind. Just your factual epic brought to life on the silver screen. Nothing much to look forward to. If I'm in the mood, I might want to see Spiderman2 again. Yup, I really enjoyed the movie the first time I saw it. Or, what else is playing? I'm not sure. Hmmm, have to check the local listing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Am not feeling well at the moment. Flu with a pinch of headache. Had a discussion just now. And it was seriously uninteresting, but it had to be done. As a formality, so to speak. A colleague of mine actually fell asleep in the meeting room. Me, I asked questions. That was the only way I could think of to keep myself from falling asleep. And it worked, for a while. After that, I started feeling sleepy. Luckily for me, another colleague of mine passed me a note, although we were sitting side by side. Hehehe. So that perked me up quite a bit. After the note passing, we managed to chat with each other without actually using our voices. Isn't that amazing! Hehehe. A few minutes after that, the discussion ended. Much to our delight. Hehehe...
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was deep in slumber when I heard my name being called. I chose to ignore the voice, since I was too deep in slumber, and anyway I couldn't find my way back to the land of the living. So I kept on sleeping. Only to be called again. This time is was more persistent. I tried to wake up but to no avail. I struggled against the dark cold place I was in. Finally, I managed to be the victor. And as I shaded my eyes against the sun light, I heard my mother's voice saying, "It's almost 8 o'clock, aren't you going to the office?". What!? 8 o'clock?! I start work at 8 o'clock!!!   That was how I started my day on Saturday. But it went well enough, since I managed to get to the office by 8.20am. Amazing, huh! And none of the bosses were asking for me. Hehehe. The big boss did a short presentation on CVS. Don't even ask. Anyway, after that, went for the department's bowling tournament. It was a fun activity for us to get to know one another better. After that, went to TTDI for a wedding. I was the  pengapit . I wonder what they call  pengapit  in english. Hmmm....  Well, anyway. Yup! Me!  Pengapit ! Hahahah!!! But I was. Seriously! Anyway, it was the second time for me. And my brother was the MC. It was the umpteenth time for him. And he's getting better at it.   Now about me being the  pengapit , we started the procession from outside the hall. There were 10 of us. The married couple, both the  pengapit s, the two flower girls, and the bride's 3 brothers and a cousin. So there we were walking towards the hall, with the  kompang  group right behind us. Right before we started moving, one of the flower girls asked me, "What are we suppose to be doing now? I didn't go for the rehearsal!" Well, neither did I! So, there we were, moving slowly towards the hall, not knowing what to do next. Hehehe. But it turned out ok, in the end. The flower girls were safely at their respective places, which was in front of us  pengapit s, and we were doing pretty ok, if anyone was paying any attention to us, that is.  I thought I would be nervous, but I wasn't. Because I knew people were there to see the bride and groom, and not the  pengapit s, although, who can resist hairy face. Heheheh. Just kidding. Anyway, after the ceremony, we stayed back to chat with the relatives. Me, I was chatting with my brother and his wife for a while, then I went on to chat with my brother's sister-in-laws's friend. After that, I took my parents for supper at NZ, the place I hang out with my friends. We had  char kuey teow ,  satay ,  ais kacang , and  carrot juice . Slept around 1 o'clock.   On Sunday, woke up early to wake my beloved up, since it was her first day at the new school. Then continued sleeping, only to be woken up by a phonecall from my beloved around 9 am. Then continued sleeping till 12 in the afternoon. Woke up, had lunch in Kl with my parents, then went straight to KLCC with my best buddy. Believe it or not, everytime we go out to KLCC, it's for my buddy to get phone numbers from girls. And he has managed to get a couple of them. But on that fateful Sunday, it was not meant to be, since he picked a fiesty young lass. Hehehe. He told me later, he was taken aback by her response, because she wasn't responding to his charms. And in the end, the girl got his number, but he didn't get hers.  By the way, I saw Shrek 2 the other day. And it was hilarious. I mean, it's actually better then the first one. And I love the first Shrek! It's about how Shrek adapts to Fiona's parents and vice versa. Throw in another cute talking animal, a couple of bad guys, a funny dialogue, and you get a fantastic movie. I love Puss in Boots. He's so cute when he does his googly eyes routine. And donkey, he's still the annoying ass from the first movie. Well, if you haven't seen it, then go watch it!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I haven't much time to write what I'm about to write. They are coming after me. They said they'll be here by 9.00 am, and now it's 8.47 am. Another 13 minutes to go. Only 13 minutes for me to tell the world about the things they need to know. It all started on Thursday night. I went to see Spiderman 2 with a bunch of my uni friends. There were 10 of us. Had a snack at Burger King before entering the cinema. The movie was excellent, seriously. I recommend it highly for anyone who loves action-packed movies. The fight scenes between Spidey and Doc Oct are simply amazing. It seriously takes your breath away. During the movie, I would find myself holding my breath till the end of one of the many amazing fight scenes. Fantastic! Go watch it!  Oh no! It's 8.51! Another 9 minutes to go! Have to continue. Then, on Friday evening, went to the Wilayah Mosque to attend my cousin's  akad nikah . It was quite a big affair, actually. The  akad nikah  took place after the  Asar  prayer. It went smoothly enough. Although the groom had to say his line twice before it was given the thumbs-up! Met up with some of my long lost relatives. It was good to see them. My cousins mostly. The mosque itself is huge. Actually, it would be an understatement to say that, because the mosque is extremely huge! It was a chore just to walk from one end to the other. Besides that, the insides of the mosque is beautiful. Don't take my word for it. You ought to go and check it out yourself.   The wedding reception was on the following day, Saturday. Now, that was a grand affair. I enjoyed myself there. The reason being, I met lots of cousins and nieces whom I haven't seen in ages. They looked good. Very mature looking. Very very mature looking. Well anyway, we had to rush through that one since my parents had to attend their friend's birthday party. I was invited as well, although I didn't feel like going since it'll be full of old people and kids. No many people my age will be there. But since I had nothing better to do, I followed. It was in Ulu Langat. Quite far, by my standards. We were late, but luckily we came just before they were about to sing the birthday song. So, after the song, we had something to eat (yet again!), and I was introduced to a very charming tourist guide which they met while they were on holiday in Sabah.  We started talking, but once they started the karaoke session, she invited me to go to someplace quiet where we can talk in peace. So, we went to the dining room which was on the first floor. But still the noise from downstairs managed to be heard. So we had to sort of shout to listen to each other. She turned out to be very adventurous and very independent. I'm glad I went to the birthday party. At least I made a new aquaintance. :) What time is it now? Oh goodness! It's 8.59 am! They'll be here any minute now! I don't think I have much time to continue with today's blog. I hope you have understood what I wanted to convey to you.    This is the last few seconds, but I need to tell you what the significant of Bladerunner is to today's blog. Well, I have just gotten a Sun server named  SunBlade 1500 . And I named it  Bladerunner . Oh no! They are here. I can see the door to my room opening slowly. I can see one of their heads peering into the room looking for me. I have no choice but to submit to them. Because if it weren't for me asking them out for breakfast this morning, they wouldn't have come looking for me now. Well, ladies and gentleman. I bid you farewell for now, for I have a breakfast appointment with my colleagues.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I haven't updated for a while. For a long while, actually. Not that anyone would notice. Except for those few people out there. Thanks guys... and girls. So where did I left off. I think it was quite a while ago, actually. So, let me start on the 31st of July 2004. That was when I went to Bukit Tinggi for a meeting. It was the  Advisory Panel for the development of the Hospital Information System  meeting. I was there to present my paper on 'Data Migration'. I was nervous, naturally. But it went well enough. I mean, they listened, then they commented, for quite a bit. But in the end, they made some decisions, which actually lightened my burden on the migration bit. At Bukit Tinggi, we stayed at  Colmar Tropicale.  To say that the place was perfect, would be an understatement. But don't take my word for it. It's probably because I haven't gone travelling around the world much. So my reference is kind of limited. So to me, it was a remarkable place, in Malaysia, except for  Pulau Mabul , in Sabah, that is.  Anyway, for those who hasn't heard of  Colmar Tropicale,  it's a resort, sort of, with a French Village theme going on. I went there with my boss. We took the official car and driver. Since everyone else drove their own vehicles. Once we were there, we pulled our luggage to the reception area. After getting our keys, we went our separate ways. My room wasn't in the same building as my boss. So I naturally assumed that the building I was heading for has very small rooms. So, there I was, pulling my luggage through the crowd, trying to find the building where my room was. I found the building easily enough. Now to go find my room. It was situated on the third floor. Key in hand, I inserted it into the lock and entered my room.  It was huge! I couldn't believe my eyes. It has a mini kitchen, a breakfast nook, a living room with a huge tv. Then, into another room was my bedroom. There, was a king sized bed, or is it a queen sized bed. I wouldn't know. Anyway, into another room was the bathroom. And even the bathroom was huge. This room isn't for me, I mean, this room can hold more than 4 adults comfortably. But I was grateful for the room. Once there, I unpacked and went down the the French village. It isn't that big. But the things they have there are interesting. They have shops, a small games arcade, some restaurants, and small shops selling caricature drawings, little animal shaped toys, hand-shaped wax and others.  Besides that, the food was good. We had breakfast, morning tea, lunch, afternoon tea, and dinner. And since it was a buffet, I took my time eating almost everything they had to offer. Everything was superb. I felt bloated after each meal. I was amazed I could stand and walk around after everything I stuffed down my throat. Hehehe. But I really felt bloated. And that's one feeling I don't like. On the whole, it was truly a worthwhile meeting. But, believe it or not, Maxis doesn't have any coverage that. At all! I was like, uh'oh. Luckily, I found two public phones, one of which wasn't working.  We went back the following day. The meeting was continued after breakfast. After the meeting, we had lunch, then we headed straight to the office. The following day, I had a training at Amcorp Tower. But that's for another day. For today, I think this is enough. :) 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>