<Blog>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last weekend, i watched this movie. After seeing the cast & production house most people couldn't have resist it. Well, everybody has the high expectations from the movie. Where the movie score goes, I didn't like the first two.... But I definitely identify my parents with Boman Irani... And the story was okay... at the end I felt movie was worth while watching once. When i was watching Hrithik Roshan, i can identify him with typical north Indian Business family guys. They make me remember my brother so much. No Lakshya in Life. Boss, till date he doesn't know what he wants to do in life.  These days reel life is much closer to the real life. Whether it is Hum Tum or Lakshya. 
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woman, Indian , Fiction Reader,&nbsp; Travel, love meeting new people, Writer, free as a bird. 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       As my last article mentioned, I am stationed in Chandigrah for next few months. This is one of the most planned cities I have ever seen. Like very city, this city has also some pecularities; the better &amp; bad the better part of the city are: Clean & neat city the Roads Traveling time&nbsp;&nbsp;& the bad part is public transport night life &nbsp;In no other city I have seen girls driving&nbsp;scooter (other than Kinetic)&nbsp;& Bikes, but it's too common in this city, and that’s reason there is no much scope for the public transport, which is virtually non existing in the&nbsp;city. And one more thing, newspaper- Chandigrah editions are too boring, not much of national coverage.  Like Mumbai, there is not much of shopping places, but those few&nbsp;Chandigrah have are really good one.&nbsp;For people of Chandigrah heart of city is Sector 17. Whenever I ask some one for some outlet, I always get one answer " Sector 17".&nbsp;  &nbsp;  This was the discovery made in last 10 days.... hopefully other good part will soon be discovered.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Most planned city&nbsp;in&nbsp;India...Chandigrah... it's totally different from Bombay.... actually it's totally different world all together.... the better part is.... there is no traffic&nbsp;in&nbsp;city&nbsp;&amp; if some one come across the red light on road.... they tell... " So much of rush" man that’s unbelievable.... &amp; worse part is city sleeps too early..........can't even think.... but no other option available.... I am going to miss the movies, the parties.... &amp; the people of Bombay&nbsp;but I am planning to visit Shimla, Manali,&nbsp;Vashno Devi &amp; even planning to learn Punjabi.... so next time when i will be back in Bombay... you will&nbsp;find Anjana speaking " Chak de Phat de" Punjabi... and makke de roti &amp; sarso da saag... and if anything more than that.... it will be there... 
    
</post>


</Blog>