<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We are trying to enjoy our last days in Colorado.  We went water skiing today at Highline lake a very small lake but one large enough to have fun on.  Angie was able to get up on the first try on only one ski (cool chick!) Especially when the boat was not as fast as it should be for water skiing.     Our friend Vicki, bless her heart, was so excited to take us out to water ski for the last time here in Colorado.  With the sun shinning and the water rippling with enjoyment, we had a blast!   We hope we will be able to come back to Colorado for my clinical rounds and it may just happen.  There are many whom are willing to take me under their wing and train me to be the best physician I can possibly be.  They are the ones who have encouraged me to become the physician I would like to be--compassionate, caring and above all understanding.  Understanding to the needs that every individual desires.     All of our friends are here and it will be hard to leave, but there is a great adventure awaiting. . . one that will instill everlasting memories upon our future generation-- my children.   Let's hope that all will be good for us and that everyone on this adventure will gain some insight to the wonders of life.   Thanks for taking the time to peruse my site and become a part of our life. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Jace and his first Trophy he earned in T-Ball&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    The Martini Gang at Aunt Nicoles in South Dakota.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    The kitchen.  These are the only three pictures I have right now.  The bedrooms are off to the left along with the bathroom.  It is cinder(sp) block constucted in case of those pesky little Class V hurricanes that tend to drop by on occasion for a little frolic on the island.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    The Living Room&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is the porch of the apartment.  The red circle is the AUC Med School Sign with the Guarded Entrance at the left of the picture with a Sheriff out front.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's 11:15pm and I am up late setting up Yahoo Messenger so I can communicate quicker with people down in the Caribbean that are helping us in the transition of a middle income family to very poor medical student family.   The families and students that I have been in contact with have been better than anyone could have ever hoped for with such a large move.   The big shocker today was we found a great apartment that when you roll out of bed you are on the AUC campus.  This is good because we will not have to have two cars and the kids and I can walk to school--it's only 100ft.  That will lower the stress on Angie, the kids, and I and we will be able to spend that ever so valuable time being together rather than commuting even just ten minutes.  Do that a few times a day and were talking a whole hour of wasted time.  I will post some pictures of the Apartment.   The only catch is that today we talked to the landlord Gil and he would like $4500 up front.  OUCH!!!!!  The rent is $1500/mo and he would like two months in security deposit.  He didn't mention anything about a contract either.  Shady?  What do you think? He seems like a nice guy and our family advisor Amy said that he is a good guy.  Well find out tomorrow when he inspects the apartment for the leaving students and see if he gives all of the securtiy deposit back. Interesting. Hmmmm.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    NautilusSmall&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Soft and Warm Nautilus&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Our kids with their long lost pal.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Angies Picture of the Maroon Bells in Aspen Colorado.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    A beautiful Sunset.  Angies sister Nicole and boyfriend Darren on right.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Smoky Sparlers on a cold winter night.  Our last winter in Grand Junction.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Angie, Adam and our Nephew Christopher on the left.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Dad and the boys. (From Left, Jace, Jim, Adam)&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Young and Happy Warlocks&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This is Prettier&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    No really, a pretty picture.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Pretty Picture&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Contrasting Colors in St. Maarten&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Sunset In St. Maarten&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Old Dawn Beach Hotel St. Maarten&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    BooBoo and My son Jace.  We will miss this wodnerful dog.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Me&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    I'm Batman&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When you get the Island Fever you do things like, have your hair beaded.  That way you feel more comfortable doing the double dutch. Angies beaded hair was done at a place called Oriental Beach on the French side of St. Martin.  My youngest son saw some pictures of the naked women (most of the beaches are European and are clothes optional) on this beach and termed it China beach.  Was he talking about the oriental thing or was he trying to say Va China?  He's 4 so I'll bet. . . . 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Angies Beaded Hair&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It is getting late for me but I am trying to figure out this Blog thing.  I was trying to figure out how to post a picture and I posted a picture of my beautiful wife Angie at Philipsburg Marina in St. Maarten, Dutch Antilles and it reminded me so much of how much I want to be back in the warm sun and listen to the turquois wavelets brush upon the beach and soothe me into equanimity.       St. Maarten a beautiful and wonderful place with so many nice and kind people who move as rhythmically as the turquois wavelets do lapping upon silicon crystals--a place where the insane rush of American life drifts silently away fading into a distant memory--a memory which becomes more difficult day by day to comprehend or recall.  You are swept up into a life of peace and slow pace, enjoying all that everything has to offer.     That is until you drive a car there and everything instantly changes.  You must be on alert a factor of 10 times greater than driving any busy freeway in the US.  It is a contrast that cannot be reckoned with by any means.  It is metaphorically a world of Dr. Jekyl and Mr. Hyde.   Ganga is smoked on a religious basis and of course as a means of slowing down, but they must all be extremely high on caffiene when they drive.  Who else would slow down for a speed bump and then peel-out to accelerate at break-neck speed to once again slam on the breaks for the next speed bump.  The only speed limit is there is no speed limit.  Safe and Sane is an understatement.  It's more like Unsafe and Insane; it is the rule not the exception.  Must get some sleep. ZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZ!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Philipsburg Marina&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here I am sitting at the computer trying not to think about work.  A place I must be within an hour.  But creating a Blog site seems so much more important and. . .cool!     This site will be a place for people to keep up on the daily doing on our (my family, Angie-36, Jace-6, Adam-4, and me--Jim 38) adventures in getting to the island of St. Maarten, in the Caribbean and my attending Medical School.     Although I do not see how I will have much time to post anything when having to study all the time but I will try to keep everyone in the know.  Ta Ta for now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      &nbsp; It is now only 12 days before we have to be out of the house and only 22 days before we leave the country.&nbsp; Excuse me for one minute, I need some coffee.  &nbsp; OK, things are better now 'cause I have some coffee!&nbsp;  I am tired--tired of a lot of moving, packing, planning, storing, working, cleaning just going, going, going.&nbsp; But it will all be over soon and well worth the awaiting adventure.&nbsp; (Please allow me some leeway in that statement,&nbsp;for I am sure there will be times that I, we, will be tried in many ways yet inconceivable.)  &nbsp; Our kids are having a hard time with the selling and packing of all of our, their, things.&nbsp; Emotionally they are spent.&nbsp; I never thought all this commotion would cause such sad feelings in my children, but then again, I guess I never thought about it from their point of view.&nbsp; I would be upset if I was six years old and someone took my dresser's leaving me void of a place&nbsp;to store my clothes except on the floor turning my world around and&nbsp;leaving me confused.&nbsp; Even with the understanding of moving to such a beautiful place and meeting new people and places it is really hard to come to the realization of the finality of feng shuiing ones life.  &nbsp; Anyway we&nbsp;have a strong family and all of us are very supportive to each other which helps tremendously with the stress and strain&nbsp;of it all especially for the children--Love goes a long way in healing emptiness and despair.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I have too much to do and must now go.&nbsp; Time for another day of "adventure".&nbsp; Where's that coffee!?   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        We had our first showing of our house on Wednesday and had an offer of $169,000.  We were originally asking $178,000 but didn't have the time to waste looking for the, "I can't live without this house, so I will pay whatever amount needed to secure this property" buyer. So becaue we are leaving for St. Maarten on August 10 we lowered the price to 169,900.   We countered with $169,500 and extended the "Get Out of Your Property" date to August 1st from July 30 (The closing date).  They accepted and we are now very excited.  However, I will be even more excited when I deposit the check!   Let's hope all the rest of the buying process goes well.    We will now start the, "Clean the crap" out of our house process and start separating the stuff into, store, take and sell piles.  This is very hard to do because of collecting so many things in our lives. And with two children it is even more amazing how much one can pile things up.     I am very excited that my parents are coming down this 4th of July.  It will be the last time we see them for probably about two years.  It will be a very fun time.    I hope I can post again soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The weather this time of year is very hot and humid and because of this we have been to the beach everyday--it's the only thing that cools us off and keeps us less irritable.  It is pointless to fix your hair and your make-up just melts off and now I know why perms and tattoo make-up were invented.    Jim and Jace (my little Cousteau boys) are loving the clear aquamarine ocean.  They are out there snorkeling for hours and have spotted eels, octipi, rays and lot's of other fish.  Adam hasn't been as adventuresome to snorkel yet but enjoys digging in the sand.   We will write more later. . . the beach is calling.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Front porch picture with cruise ship departing Philipsburg, St. Maarten with Saba in the background.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Front Porch with the island Saba in the distance.  Can you find the island?&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Front porch view with the AUC marquee sign on the bottom.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Front Porch View&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had earlier tried to post a message and the internet service here is intermittent at best right now.  Construction right next door.  Jack hammers, drills, water shutoff, power outages, but heck I'm in paradise.    I will let everyone know that we arrived safely and I will right more when I get a chance.   We have a beautiful apartment that has a wonderful view of the irridescent turquoise Caribbean Ocean with scenic islands making up the backdrop.    I will upload pics when I get a chance.  We love you all. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>