<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So last night there I was sitting on my uncomfortable futon couch waiting for the season premier of Nip/Tuck.  For any who are unaware of this show, it is a drama on FX about two 40 year old miami beach plastic surgeons trying to hold their lives together in the midst of drugdealers, pedophiles, bimbos, jealous competitors, and generally unhappy patients trying to be happy by improving their looks.  Well last night found Dr.MacNamarra back together with his almost hotty wife after they had split up last season and had brief but very intest affairs.  So with that drama over the writers needed a new twist.  Well here it is the good Dr., the one with the real talent has a yip.  A yip apparently is, like a tremmor or tick, only it is completly psycological.  So basically the practive is fucked unless he can get a handle on his personal demons.  Meanwhile Dr.Troy is fucking his new nanny who is, unbenounced to him, drugging his infant son with cough syrup so that she can pleasure daddy.  Both Dr.'s are struggling with turning 40, this is personified by a patient who botches a suicide attempt and blows away half her face.  At first she says there is no point in getting old because its all down hill after 40.  Later she recounts her earlier plea and says that getting old is a priveledge.    Well anyway it was fun, gruesome, and erotic. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Who is really a Hero???   Is Lance Armstrong a Hero?  What about Tiger Woods? or maybe Donald Trump?  Does success or domination in a chosen field make someone a hero?  I have thought a lot about this recently, and have come to a new conclusion.  I know this may sound quite mundane but the real heros in our society, aside from 911 workers, are the unsung people who manage to hold down a job, keep their families together, maintain a clean home, stay in shape, and do all this in the same 24 hour day that i flounder in!!!  A single minded pursuit of a goal borders on fanaticism.  It can only exist to the detrement of many other aspects of ones life.  You may remember Alex Lowe; he was the foremost american high altitude mountaineer until his death a few years ago.  He had a loving wife and a few kids.  He was called the secret weapon by expedition leaders, because if he was along success was virtually assured.  Then his life was cut short by a freek avalanche.  In an interview he stated that  he loved spending time with his family, but dreamed of the mountains, and when he was in the mountains was truely in his element, but missed his family.  Was it fair of him to have a family knowing how dangerous his chosen profession was?  Is it fair to expect people who participate in extreme activities not to have children?  I have really been struggling with this for many years.  I would appreciate any feedback.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well after hearing about blogging for so long i figured i had to try it.  it seems kind of like flogging without the whip...though i am guessing if anyone ever reads this and posts the abuse will be quite sharp and painful.  so anyway i am at work, hopeing that the phone will ring and i will be able to sell another trip.  my boss told me today that if i make my sales goal for this month that she will send me to France next month.  unfortunatly that goal entails me doing as much business in the next two weeks as i have done in each of the last two months.  cruel joke huh?  oh well back to work......
     

    
</post>


</Blog>