<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Hey! I'm just sittin here chillin! Been pretty bored around here lately! There's not much to do in this town. Well, unless you wanna go play in a cornfield. LOL! I talked to Zack earlier and he put me in a good mood! I'm glad he did too. Man, I needa find a job so I'll have some money saved up for when I move up there. OMG! I'm so happy for some reason. I tried to call Stacy ealier, but her phone was shut off. Urg, that annoys me. She needs to get a job. But, I doubt that will happen. All she does is sit around and smoke pot. I hate that. She's my god-sister and I love her to death. We've been in each other lives since we were born. But, she needs to grow up and take responsibilty. She's married now and all she does is run around and get high. That's just plain stupid. Oh well, it's her life! Me and larry made up last night. So we're cool now. I guess that's a good thing tho. I don't wanna lose him as a friend. He means alot to me and he's been there for a year. And I don't want him to go anywhere. Well, I'm sittin here talkin to Dave one of my other friends. I haven't talked to him in a while and kinda missed him. lol. He's such a sweetheart. He's my buddy. Welp, I don't know what to write. I'm out! Later!
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! I'm back! I'm not in a very good mood tonight at all! Me and Larry got into a huge fight tonight! It was awful and I said some really mean things! I kinda regret saying them! But, he really hurt me! I have put up with his shit for a year and I'm so sick of it. He's my friend and I do love him to death as a friend and a friend only. But, I can't believe the things he said to me. In the end I was crying and he was hurt really bad. I didn't wanna hurt him, but I don't really care. I know that sounds really mean. But, you haven't put up with the shit with him that I have. Almost all the guys I know are jerks and I honestly don't know why. It's like the only one I can actually trust, open up to, love, count on, and that's there for me is Zack. I don't know why either. I never wanna lose him. He's like my new best friend. He's starting to mean everything to me. It seems like right now he's the only thing that I've really got. He believes in me and nobody else does. That makes me feel really good to know that I have him in my life. I never knew I could ever find someone as special as him. But, now I have and I'm glad. I can't wait to be in his arms. I never wanna let him go. He's my friend and someday hopefully more. I can't wait till I go live with him. It seems like this is too good to be true in a way. This is the best thing that's happened to me in a long time. I thank God for that all the time. I honestly think he sent him to me. I don't wanna freak him out with telling him how I feel. But, I do want him to know. I want him to know that he means so much to me and I never wanna let him go. We have something, that I haven't had with anyone. He's something I've always needed. He's someone that I can be myself around. And he doesn't try to change me like everyone else does. It just really sucks that he's so far away right now and we can't be together everyday. Well, enough rambling. I'll see ya all later! 
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! I'm updating again! I haven't had time to in a few days. I'm just sittin here thinkin bout Zack! He's everything I have ever wanted in a guy. And i found him! He makes me happier than I have been in a long time. I really like him A LOT! I can't wait till we're together. I hate that he's so far away. He believes in me and I haven't had that in a long long time. I hope it works and I hope we last. Welp, I'm tryin to get ready to go out with my friend Larry tonight. He's leavin for college in a month. It's gonna be hard with him leavin and everything. But, I'm glad that he's gettin outta this town. I can't wait till I go to MD to live with Zack. I hate it here. I'm not happy at all. There's nothin here for anyone. All it does is bring me down. But, I know I'll be alot happier there with him. I hope I have fun tonight. I think we're gonna ride around for awhile and hang out. He gets off work in like 5 minutes. Then I'm supposed to call him. Man, I got into a huge fight with my mom today. And I swear I wanted to just pack my shit and leave. But, I couldn't cuz I have nowhere to go here. That's why I can't stand my parents. All my dad does is put me down and yell at me from the time he gets home from work until I go to bed. I can't take it anymore. It's driving me crazy. And everything with my mom is all about her. It's never what I want or how I feel. It's always about them. I just wanna be happy. But, I can't be happy here with them. I don't know what to do. But, for once in a long time I have confidence in myself thanks to Zack. He's everything to me right now. And I hope someday it will grow stronger. I love everything about him. I know it's not lust. I know what i'm feeling is real. And honestly the more I talk to him and get to know him the more I like him and want to love him. It's weird tho because I know he won't ever hurt me and I'm not used to not bein hurt. I think this is a dream come true. It's reality. It's something I've always wanted. And now I have it. And I thank God for that. Well, I gotta finish gettin ready. I'll write more later! 
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! I'm just sittin here bein bored out of my mind. There's not much to do since it's a sunday. I've been thinkin alot lately. And I don't even know what I've been thinking about. Today would have been mine and Michaels two year anniversay. It still is in a way. Because even though he's in Heaven he's still my world. I miss him more than anything. He always knew how to make me happy. The night he died was the night my whole world came crashing down around me. He had so much ahead of him. But, he had to go and make a stupid mistake that cost him his life. I'll never forget when I got the call. Watching him die was the hardest thing I have ever had to do. We had so many memories and so many fun times. We were inseperable from the time we met till the day he died. I think sometimes if I would've went to that party with him like he wanted me to then he would still be here today. But, I could have gotten killed in that wreck too. I remember seeing his car after it happened. I couldn't believe that was the same car that we were riding in a long time ago. It was smashed to pieces. He was only seventeen. It wasn't his time to go. He had his whole life in front of him. And it all ended in one night, because he had to drink and drive. I promised myself when that happened I would never get into a car when i had been drinking. I've lost Michael and my best friend Angela because of it. They were the ones that were always there. I miss them so much and the times that we had. I'll never forget the night at the lake with Michael, Anthony, and Ray. It was so much fun. Or grinding halfpipes with him late at night. It was always funny when he would fall. I miss tho times. I miss the way he would tell me everything was going to be ok because he was there. But, when he died I couldn't see how anything was going to be ok. But, it's gotten alot better and I've learned to move on. I still think about him every day and I will for the rest of my life. But, I can't bring him back. I wish like hell I could see him one last time before I let myself move on for good. But, I know that will never happen. I know he's my guardian angel and I know he's up there watching over me. I will love him always and forever no matter what. Well, I'm gonna go. I'll write more later!  ~~Rikki~~
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Would you call me 'dear' When I treat you wrong; Would you shed a tear When I'm far too long?  Would you need me bad When I'm far away; Would you be so sad As to cry every day?  Would you tremble lightly When you see me smile; Would you lie beside me For an eternal while...?  Would you smile for me And warm my heart; Would you let me see Your love is not marred?  Would your heart flutter When I kiss your lips; Would your eyes utter The love that it keeps?  Would your passion touch The depths of my soul; Would it hurt me much My love to bestow?  Would you be my cure, My angel, my friend? Would your love be pure Will it ever end...?
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Hey! Man, I think I'm gettin addicted to this thing. Oh well, it's awesome as hell. I'm just sittin here bein bored. Tryin to write some more poems. It's goin pretty good I think. Well, I found out that my cousin James and his girlfriend are wanting to move in to together. AHHH! I hate her with a passion. I don't really know why, but I do. She's so preppy it drives me crazy. I hate it when she starts talking about cars and she don't know a damn thing about them. Cmon if you don't know what you're talking about don't talk about it! It's as simple as that. But, she don't care. She thinks she so great at everything. Yeah, she has my cousin pussy whipped. But, jeez! What really makes me mad is when she found out I didn't like her she went and cried to my mom and my aunt (James' mom). She's like 22 I mean give me a break. GROW UP! I don't even act that childish. If she was nice every once in a while we might get along. I'm as nice as I can be to her. It's only out of respect for James. Because I love him and he's like my big brother. We were best friends until she came into the picture. I understand he's 20 and has his own life. But why does he have to blow me off like this. It's not fair. We we're so close and now we aren't. All because of her. I'll admit I'm jealous of her. Because she gets to see him more than I do and spend more time with him then me. But, the sad thing is he's blowing his friends and family off to be with her. And he told my mom that if I'm not nice to her that I'm gonna lose him. That's not fair at all. I've been there for 16 years and she's only been there for not even a year. He hates all my boyfriends because they're not good enough for me in his eyes. But, when I don't like his girlfriend my whole family is on me about it and they never let it go. Most, of the time I break up with them because of that. Nobody is ever good enough for me when it comes to him and my aunt. But, I don't care anymore he's with her. So, I'm gonna be with whoever I wanna be with. I just miss him so much and the things we did together. I feel like I've lost it all because of her. I know that's not what her intention is and I understand that. But, he could atleast call me back and come by every once in a while. But, I guess life will go on. And maybe someday I will like her and want to be friends with her. But, that will probably be a long time from now. Either way I wish them the best. I'm not sayin I don't want him to be happy. And, if that's what makes him happy, then he can go for it and be as happy as he wants. It's just I don't want to see him get hurt. Because if she hurts him I will never forgive her for that. Well, I'm gonna go update later!
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey Hey! What's up people! As you can probably tell I'm in a really good mood today. Yup I sure am! It's all because of one person. I found out when I got online after I woke up that not everyone judges by my past. That makes me feel really good. Because now I know that he likes me for who I am and not what I've done. I haven't found many people like that. He's special to me and he makes me feel special. I really like him! He makes me soooo happy! As you can tell! WOW!  I'm in a great mood. I don't think I've been this happy in a long time! I figured out what I'm gonna do with my life. It's something I've always been good at. I'm gonna be a WRITER! YES, a writer. It's my passion and it's what I love to do. I have so much to write about. I know I can get published cuz I have 11 poems published already! And I wanna help people. I really wanna go around to schools and stuff and talk to kids about my past and everything that I went through so maybe they won't make the same mistakes I did. Yup Yup that's what I wanna do. welp I gotta go. TTYLE
      
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OH MY GOD! Why do people have to be so stupid! Sometimes I think life isn't fair at all. But oh well. Guys can be jerks. It's like 12:30 at night, I'm up and bored outta my mind. My friend Marc called and wanted me to go to a party with him and I told him no. He got pissed and hung up. Then his freakin girlfriend came to my house and started bitchin me out. It's not like I could understand her. I don't see what he sees in her. She started writing a bunch of shit on paper and handing it to me. It was really pissin me off. I'm so glad she can't hear what I say, cuz I swear the stupid idiot would've got the biggest ass chewin she's ever had. But, I'm gonna be nice cuz Marc's my friend and I respect him. But, geez why can't she realize he loves her and I'm not gonna take him away from her. It's so gay! Oh well. I'm still missin Jake so much and it's drivin me crazy! How can people be so stupid. It gets on my nerves so bad. I think people like hurting me. I honestly do. Maybe I'm just an easy target. Everyone hurts me and I don't know what I ever did to deserve it. All I do is fight with my parents and my family. They make me feel like I'm nothing. I just want someone to love me and care about me. I just don't kno what to do anymore. It's crazy. I wanna get away and get outta here so bad. But, I don't have anywhere to go. Noone wants me and noone cares. I think all I have is myself sometimes. But that's not so bad every once in a while. I found someone I really like. And I hope things turn out ok. But, I guess only time will tell that. Welp, I'm gonna go I think I've bored people anough for one day! Later!
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! I'm updating again! What is wrong with the world today? Do people not care about others? Do they like to hurt everyone around them? It's sad how people can be so cruel. I seen something today that just made me wanna cry. It was so mean and I don't see how people could be that mean. I went for a run earlier today and when I was running I saw a group of people in a circle. I ran by them. I noticed there was a little kid in the middle of them. All I could her was taunting and mean remarks bein made to him. I couldn't believe what I was hearing. These guys were makin fun of this little kid because he was blind. I stopped and walked up to them and told them to stop and they took off. The little boy was in tears. I asked him if he was ok and I walked him home. When we walked to his door his mom opened it and greated me with a smile and I told her what had happened and she invited me in. I stayed for a few minutes. The boys name with Matt. He was 9. I sat and talked to him for a long time. I found out that he had been blind his whole life. He thanked me for what I did over and over. I sat and talked to his mom for a long time. And I had to leave because I had to go with my dad afterwards. When I was on my way back home, all I could think about was Matt and how he had been through so much and people did that to him. I can't imagine what he's been through. But noone has the right to treat people the way he was treated today. I'm supposed to go back over there in a few days to play with him. And I wouldn't miss that for the world. He's so full of life even after everything he's been through. I just wish people would realize he's a person too, and he's no different than anyone else. So what if he couldn't see. He's still alive and that's all the matters. So people don't be stupid. Sometimes things you say will effect someone for the rest of their lives. It may build them up or bring them down. But damnit, just be nice!! You wouldn't want ppl doin that to you or someone you know and care about. So don't do it to other people. I know I prolly sound really corny, but I don't really care. I was raised to treat people with respect and treat them how I would wanna be treated. I come from a Christian home and it's really paid off. Well that's all I'm gonna say for now. I'll update later!  *Rikki*
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Welp I'm back again! Just thought I would write today since I'm bored. I got some good news. I have gotten another poem published. I'm sooo happy. Atleast I know someone thinks I'm a good writer. I know that's what I want to do. Well, me and Jake are no longer friends. It's all because of his girlfriend. I don't like her and everyone knows that. It's pretty bad when she's 19 and going out with a 15 year old guy! I mean c'mon it's pathetic. I loved him like a brother. I guess it wasn't enough. We had a great 13 years. It was the best. We went through thick and thin together. When one of us needed help or just someone to hang out with, we were always together. He was the only person I could ever count on. But, I guess I lost that. A great friendship is now gone, because of a girl he only knew for almost a year. We were cool at first then she started mouthin me. So, of course I wasn't gonna like her. I never did anything to that chick. Much less do anything to lose him and what we had. I guess all things most come to an end sooner or later. And this one was 13 years later. It was fun and wonderful while it lasted. But, what can I say. I miss the hell outta him. But, life goes on and things get better. I kinda learned from this too. I learned that, when you go through life there's always a bump in the road that you have to cross somewhere down the line. And I guess this is one of them. I will miss him more and more everyday. But, I'll be ok. Just some advice for everyone, don't throw away what you've got. It could mean more to you than life itself and when that's gonna you won't have anything for awhile. But, it'll all work out in the end. Even when you don't have the person who has been there since you were 3. More people will come along and share all the happiness and tears with you just like they did. We had our memories. They will always be with me. Well I gota fix supper. I'll write more later! 
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey! Well I'm makin a new blog. I didn't have a very good time with my last one. And I needa place to tell my stories. So I guess this is where I'm gonna do it at. I'm a 16 year old girl. I live in Vincennes, IN. It's not the greatest place to live at. I honestly hate it here with a passion. I wanna get out of this town as fast as I can. It's literally killing me inside. I have been through a lot here and most of it I want to forget. Let me tell you about it. When I was 11 I started hangin out with a different crowd. I was always the straight A student on honor roll and I played basketball and softball. All that changed in a short time. I started smoking and drinking. By the time I was 13 I was in so much trouble at home. One night a friend came over and he brung a guy with him. They wanted to go to a haunted house since it was on Halloween. So I went. After that the guy that was with my friend raped me. I was so scared and didn't tell anyone for awhile. A few months later I found out I was pregnant. Two weeks after I found out I had a miscarriage. It took me six months to tell anyone. Since then, my life has been so hard. I started getting in trouble more and I starting smoking pot. First, it was weed then meth. I couldn't stop. By last October, I was on drugs and drinking so bad, I had to go to rehab. I was so depressed from the rape and miscarriege that all I wanted was for all the pain I had ever felt to go away. I was in rehab for 2 weeks. I went through withdrawls. I was diagnosed clinically depressed. I was always the little kid running around with my older cousins with a smile on my face. That little kid was gone, all I had left was That scars in my heart from the pain. I got suspended from school so much I never thought I would pass. When I got out of rehab I was doing good for about 4 months, then I started drinking and smoking pot again. It all went back to the way it was. It was a nightmare. After awhile I hated it again. I told my parents and friends I needed help and for good this time. My mom took me an hour away back to rehab one more time. I got out 3 weeks later. It was hard at first, but I was determined to do it. I have been clean ever since then. I don't plan on getting back on drugs. Last, June the only person I ever loved was killed in a car accident. I have been so lost without him. But I'm making it. I'm determined to be the best I can and help people and keep them from making the same mistake I did. My life hasn't been an easy one. Almost every guy that I have ever been with has hit me and cheated or yelled at me. It's not easy to live with that. Nobody should have to go through what I went through. I have lost a lot of friends becuase of the choices I made on my own to get clean and stay that way. The only true friend I have is my best friend Jen. She's been there since day one and never left my side. All the friends I did have are gone. It's all because I don't get high or wanna fuck my life up again. I know a lot of people look at my past and think omg she's still gonna be like that. I'm not like that anymore. Yeah, I dropped out of school and yeah I can't change what I did and have done in my past. But I can try to change what's going to happen in the future. I still have nightmares every night. But they get less and less as time goes on. I just hope one day I can find someone who won't look at my past, but at who I am now. I think I have found that person. But, when he reads this I have no idea what he'll think. But I hope he won't hate me now. I guess that's all I'm going to say now. I'll write more later. Bye!
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey peeps! Sorry I haven't updated in awhile! I've just been busy or sick. One of the two. I'm just sittin here bein bored! Well yesterday was the 4th. I hope everyone had fun! I know I didn't. I sat at home all day. Then we had a cookout. I didn't even go to the parade or fireworks this year. We had fireworks here at my house. SO I guess it was ok. I'm so bored! There's nothin much to do right now. So I'm just sittin online! My 16th birthday is in 13 days! So my mommma's throwin me a party. Joy joy. I just have to figure out who all I want to come to it. I just don't want my family fightin. I think I'm do something I never thought I would. I think I'm gonna ask James girlfriend if she can come. Since I want James to and I guess I can't have one without the other now. But it'll be ok. I miss Zack sooo much! I haven't talked to him in a few days and I think I'm goin crazy! LOL! I got into a fight with my dad today over some shit with me not havin a job yet and everything. I wish he would shut the fuck up. And as of today until he says he's sorry I'm not talkin to him. And maybe not even then. All he doed is put me down and I hate it. I can't wait to get outta here. Gettin outta this town is like a dream come true. And Zack makes me happy so I know I'm doin the right thing. My momma said livin with him would prolly be the best thing for me right now. So I guess we're gonna see. Welp I'm out. Update later!
      
</post>


</Blog>