<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eventually my songs turned more Christian where I like them. I wrote this one after a really tough day in driver's ed. It was probably the day I hit the basketball hoop. Anyway I was also influenced by a conversation I had with a friend last night that really upset me. And after driver's ed I felt like my will was just broken and my whole being was gone and shattered.  I lie shattered here  My will has broken Overwhelmed with growing fear Life's a minor token  Chorus The World has turned away All I can do is pray that you hear my cries send Your love to bind these lies Lift up my heart work through me loose these chains, set me free  Emptiness fills me up The Death of man lives within My desires grow corrupt I see darkness coming in 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Unlike all my other works this work could actually be a song provided I could actually write some music to it. But one day Jen S. told me I should write her a song. So I sat down and wrote something. Exactly a month later I through out what I wrote and wrote this. But I wrote this about another person for Jen. I hope she still likes it as much.  Name the Stars &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; By: Jeff Bell  It is impossible to live With society turned away When pain is all it gives And all you can do is pray  I could never begin to tell you How great you’ve always been To always see me through My woe and perils without end &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Chorus&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  You can’t measure friendship You can’t name every star Or count the footsteps of your trip Nor imagine how awesome you are  You are always first to be there When life’s burdens knock at my door To end this hopeless despair And help lift me up off the floor  I know you’ll never let me down You’ll always wish to care The day that you were found Someone heard my prayer  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Bridge&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Chorus&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  You can’t measure friendship You can’t name every star Or count the footsteps of your trip Nor imagine how awesome you are 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This was written shortly after Loveless Fight. Back when my poems were still very dark. I was probably depressed at the time I wrote this now I don't remember. However, I wrote this to portray the earlier days of my life that I lived in darkness and pain. I tried to pour as much emotion into as I possibly could. It ends on a fairly positive note. But the poem is basically my life's story.   Prideful Hate  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; By Jeff Bell  I looked this world in the eye  And tried not to cry  The only thing I could see  That bitter force glaring at me  It stared ever hard and long  Ignoring right and wrong  This world’s hate  Doomed me to a bitter fate   I couldn’t escape its call  So I let my mind fall  Into the endless night  Hating the right  And living the wrong  In one hate filled angry song   I hated this world it hated me  And I defied its evil tyranny  For years I held my ground  Loosing every round  I fought hate with hate  Refusing to see my mistake   I was a mindless pawn  Living Darkness escaping dawn  Joy fought through the black of night  Blinding me with it’s triumphant light  Brave friends then came  To put out this angered flame   Will this World ever learn  Peace and Love build not burn  Would life be this painful to live  If we had what love has to give  All this prideful hate  Will destroy what love creates   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This poem I wrote for a friend who said I actually promised her a poem long ago. But in apology to my failing memory I wrote her this. It was also a great way to freak out Moose when I told her I wrote it for her. But nah that wasn't true it was written for someone else. But you should have seen the way she flipped. *laughs evilly*  The World’s Need &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; By: Jeff Bell  Well you wanted a poem  So I racked my brain And this one will show ‘em I’m truly insane So what is it about you? That fills the world’s need That if only we all knew We’d no longer bleed Perhaps it’s the way The clouds go and the sky clear With whatever you say Vanquishing all fear Maybe it’s your smile That harnesses the sun With such brightness style And then I know my anger’s done Or your warm embrace Like a soft cool rain That comes with your pretty face Washing away my pain But I know it is that joy Deep down  True power now toy That only the the faithful found 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is one of my greatest works and everyone seems to like it. The first time I tried to write a song I sat down and wrote this. Originally the song was suppose to be about pain. But this is what I wrote and it's too long to be a song. So it's in here.  Loveless Fight  My life is empty full of void I’m a case worthy of Doctor Freud I look deep with in my mind With despair but unable to find The reason for my emptiness And the path to true and utter bliss  I’d search forever never turning back Just to catch a glimpse of that person I lack You may not know my name Or even from where I came But I hope I’ll find you And I’ll never stop until I do  Everything seemed wrong I thought it was over my life just gone But then I saw you that one day And you completely blew my mind away You didn’t even notice me But I was there, unable to breathe  &nbsp;I watched you walk by You’re grace, catching my eye You’re beauty captured me But my sorrow, kept me free You didn’t even see me but just walked away Leaving my world so dark and gray  My mind raced through day and night Only remembering the joy of that sight I knew you were the one But my misery was not undone I didn’t even know who you were But there was one thing for which I was sure 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I'm tossing some ideas around in my head right now but I'm really lacking inspiration. And my poems and songs really run on inspiration. So maybe I'll talk to some people and hope something pops into my mind. I need inspiration come on people help me. 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I just wrote this pretty self explanatory. True story what more do you want?  You want to pull this blade out of my chest pick up a spade and bury what's left it happened rather suddenly you see but she kept on going bent on destroying me clean up the blood still flowing well she's still not done come back for another round this time it'll be real fun too bad she's the one I found 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just another example of what I can do after driver's ed. And again not written for a girl or written for a friend. But you know I like them anyway. And it's kind of hard writing poety when no one is giving me something to write about hint hint. Anyway enjoy.  You feeling down What can you do look all around Who can help you  He'll lift your head high don't watch your feet look towards the sky there you will meet  If you make the choice where would your sorrow be when you follow His voice and He sets you free  He'll lift your head high don't watch your feet look towards the sky there you will meet 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wrote this after driver's ed while waiting for the first day of Band Camp. Other than that there's no real story behind it. It wasn't written for anyone or about anyone. Yeah I know dull right? I have no one to write for or about so this is what you get.  How long you've lived everyone taking running to Who gives feel like something's chasing try to run with your mind just racing  fight the darkness rebuke the night open your heart embrace the light  keep running from what's behind it'll always chase until you manage to find love ahead now there's you sign  fight the darkness rebuke the night open your heart embrace the light 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know there's two things to write about in this world. God and Girls. But when you break it down both are about love. So being inspired I decided to write about a love long gone. And forever it will be. So I look ahead to the future and the one waiting for me. The last just ran me over.  Once again I see that look But I remember what you took I can stare cold in your eyes Emotionless through your cries You say I’m not the same Well I say it sounds quite lame You start to fear and ask me why I can’t explain why should I There’s no way to really say I loved you back; yesterday I wanted to give you my heart But all you did was tear it apart And I’ve shed enough tears And I’ve bowed to too many fears You can look for me by your side But I’ll be ahead I jumped off this ride 
    
</post>



</Blog>