<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dam you brand new, you always seems to make me upset, and yet i love your o so good music. anywho, the title says it all, it also a line from a song by the forementioned band. But yes, it seems i always end up thinking about 'her' somehow. And alot of the time all my conversations end up about the whole 'situation', even if i don't bring it up, someone will ask me about it. The thing is, it isn't even that big of a deal anymore, there was so much going on in like 1-2 weeks, and now nothing is happening. I can't get her out of my head, but it's sure to subside right....i mean i barely talk to her anymore, so eventually things will just fade away and i can get on with being alone...right.  bah...that is all.
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SO, I finished my last exam today. I am confident that i passed the exam, but seeing as how i don't know what my course mark going into the exam was, that may be irrelevant. All i want is to pass. Having to take summer school will fuck up everything. I will be away, so i will not know if i failed the course until it's too late to register for summer school. Meaning i would have to take it next year. I already have 8 course next year, so my whole graduating year will basically get fucked up. Next year i will probably have to start doing my work. Which shouldn't be a problem with all my new found spare time. I mean, there isn't much to do when you don't have friends. But i won't get into that now. Well, summer is here, now for many bike trips and many days of fun fun fun work at mcdonalds.
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have come up with an ingenious solution to my silly little problem, ignore it. Now one might think of me as a coward, and i would assure them that they are right. But regardless of how cowardly this may seem, it also seems to be working. I can ignore the people that i long to talk to and it bothers me at the time, but afterwards i feel relieved, relieved that i didn't have to face confrontation. I am having such a lazy day, I turn my stereo on full, close the doors to my room, and just lay back and listen. From time to time i wander around the house, get some food, get confused when i see my reflection, before remembering i dyed my hair, and coming to the computer. I think i'll play guitar for a bit later. Basically, I'm just hanging around and paying no mind to any problems. 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      letting emotion weigh you down and hold you back in life. Like a ship at port that uses an anchor to settle itself down, emotions can hold you down in different situations in life. Knowing how and when to live in the moment and get emotionally attached is something we all must learn to do, so we can raise our anchors and move from situation to situation without getting held back by emotions.  That being said. i have an anchor, one that is nice and caught on to something. It is hard to raise anchor, but i have done it. But while going along i seemed to have come across another port, after dropping anchor i seem to have come rather stuck and i cant seem to raise anchor. So now i'm held back and i just can not seem to move on. Though i have been working on it, I geuss all i can do now is wait and see how the tide treats me.  ...that is all.
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi im jon, i had a blog on mindsay, but it got over populated by the evil citizens of oakville.
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i came on here, wanting to tell everyone about how much my life sucks. But i realize,&nbsp; nobody fucking cares how shitty my life is. Hell that's part of the reason my life sucks so fucking much, no body really cares. So my end of july plans, the ones 'keeping me alive', ya they got fucked over, so needless to saw i am slightly depressed, but more so angry. My plans for tonight were made in april or may, i was supposed to see the village with....lets call her Assface, no, not because her face is an ass, i'm just a little angry and that's all the creativity my mind can spare. Now, i know it's not a big deal that i didn't see the movie, i'll probably see it tomorrow, it's just everytime i try to make plans with assface they always get fucked over. So you can imagine that maybe i had come to expect things to fuck up tonight, you;d be right i did, but on the other hand i was thinking, no i think she actually wants to do this. Because she's always the one that reminds me, hey...the village comes out next week, or dont forget you've got plans with me july 30th.&nbsp;So you can see that i really don't know what to think, what did i do, i prepared myself for the worse, and still ended up getting rather furious. I think i'm through with assface, no more attempts to make good with her, it's fairly clear to me that she wants nothing to do with me. But before i got blocking her and all that shit, i am going to talk to her and she what she has to say, and i'll make a desicion from there.   In other news, my bike is still being fixed, that's right folks apparently it takes a whole fucking month to get a part from one part of canada to another. Fucking peice of shit cyclepath.   o well&nbsp;at least i still got...  1)anas movie 2)atreyu LoG and ETiD on the 29th of august and 3)&nbsp;FINALLY getting my fucking bike back  ...keeping me going.  july is officially the worst month in the history of terrible months. 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      now i have tried very, very hard to stay positive, but i am failing to see the point anymore. I left a small portion of people in my life, people i did really like spending time with and what not, but it seems now not even they want anything to do with me. I hate the fucking summer, i don't know why i thought this was going to be good one, well, yes i do, but that thought has long since passed/ I am so bored, and when i am bored, i think, and when i think, i become upset. I posted a few days back about my emotional anchors thing...bullshit, that was a breif period, about a week or so, where i just didn't feel anything. But now all i feel is depressed, happiness is seldom there, though it will show up on occasion breifly. Without school&nbsp;life seems so pointless, i really hope i make it to first semester, school will keep me busy for a long time with all my courses.&nbsp; As suggested i am trying to be creative with my boredom,&nbsp; and make some kind of art using an essential life fluid.&nbsp; I need my bike back so bad, it has been 3 weeks now since i have last ridden it. Well, when i get it back maybe my dad will let me keep my last few mcdonalds paychecks all for myself so i can have some money to pour into my riding.&nbsp; With no work, and no friends,&nbsp; i will have a lot of more time to put into it.&nbsp; Speaking of work, i have&nbsp; a very hard choice to make, quit or don't quit. I already typed up my letter of resignation, and was going to hand it in tonight, but as of now my only human contact is coming from the people there, and even though i hate them,&nbsp; i don't know if it is best for me to quit right now. On the other hand, it's not alot of&nbsp;contact&nbsp;because those bastards are barely giving me anymore shifts, and now they want me to get my fucking hair cut again, when there are people there with longer hair than mine, why is the owner such a stupid bitch. I'm going to hold out to next week to see how many shifts i'm getting for the week after that.&nbsp;    this is the new list im going to be keeping weekly in all of my blogs from now on, i guess as a reminder....   things keeping me alive,  1) waiting impatiently for my bike ( i think i might actually start crying when i get it back)  2) plans made for the end of the month  3)&nbsp; acting in ana's movie, despite having a small character  ...that is all   
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Your Heart is Grey    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    i thought alot about death today. I also cut for the first time in a while. I am having a great summer, i would hate for it to end...fuck.
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so, it appears my emotional anchors philosophy has kinda been working. As in, i am basically becoming devoid of feeling any emotions. I can't remember the last time i was really happy, and before i start coming off like a depressed angst filled teenager, i'll point out that i havn't really been feeling depressed or angry. The purpose to my little philosophy is to live in the moment, but with no real moments to be living in right now...i have become a friggin zombie. The only real thing i do feel is lonliness, something i promised myself i would never let bother me, and it hasn't, not really, there are times but nothing really big. Nothing to get depressed over unfortunatly. I am slowly becoming an irritable introvert. And that is the whole range of my emotion, irritable to lonely. What an exciting life i most be living. 
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so apparently im a pessimist, which is news to me. I know i am not optimistic, but i think i just stay nuetral in matters. I dont really get overexcited about the good side, and i dont get too down about the bad. But, here i am, i have been told that i come off as a pessimist, but my friend has brought up a good point. In most cases those people who are optimistic are just hoping for things that probably wont even come around. But pessimists are being more realistic. So, all in all, i would much rather believe in reality and be pessimistic, than in a dream and be optimistic.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      alas, yet another crappy day. I get up and wait around to get in touch with someone i had planned to spend the day with. Basically wasting my day, and around 6 i get a hold of her.....and to my surprise...she is unavailable to do anything. Well shit, that's just great, man we have been planning to do this whole movie watching day thing for awhile, and it totally isn't working out. maybe we are just destined to not watch movies together. Anyway, i was totally frustrated with that, but, not wanting to ruin my night, i got ahold of someone else and went and saw Anchorman. This movie was decent, there was a retarded guy in it, this made me laugh. So ya...atleast the day wasnt a total waste.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      can it be...yes, yes it is, it's an update. Well, its been two weeks, a very unadventful two weeks. I went to the thousand islands for a week, that was ghetto gay. I basically read all week, which actually isn't that bad, i do indeed heart anne rice. Now when i got back, i was already to hang out with my uber cool friends. Ya, that didnt happen. First of all, i dont have uber cool friends, and should be shot for even saying that. Secondly, both my friends decided to either be busy or not in oakville, jerks. So its been 5 days and i have yet to do any 'chilling', well i did stop by matts house a couple times. Thats about it. O and today i went shopping for some new cloths because im clothing deprived and only have two pairs of pants. So i got two new pairs of....black dress pants...hell yes. Haha, o god, i am going to be the sexiest goth kid ever. *note: some people at my school are under the influence that i am a 'goth' because i wear only black.* I figure this year i might do the whole 'goth' thing, im half way there as is, and are school is really lacking in the 'goth' department. I but 'goth' in little quotation marks, because someone may read this and get the wrong idea. Not to many people know what it means to be 'goth'. I doubt i do, but hell if it ain't got a definition it can be whatever the fuck i want it to be. o, i also got a thursday shirt, its tight and i love it. fin.  ....that is all.
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have become quite the blog whore...let me explain. So, this place has grown shitty, it continually logs me out while posting, causing me to lose my posts, which is rather frustrating. enjoy my rant, and keep on keepin on. I assume anyone that reads this knows me, so if you want the address for my new blog IM me if you care. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [Rant] I have become so sick and fucking tired of myself. I am all of a sudden this depressed insomniac that has but one thing on his mind. Sure i fucking try to get my mind on something else but after awhile it all comes back to the same thing. I sit here at 3 am now listening to fucking brand new, and not really becoming much happier. I also spend most of my late nights getting on e-fights on message boards. wow i am cool. I hate the way i interact with fucking people, i am quite possibly the worst person to ever try and withhold a social life. But to some extent it's not all me, there are just some people that i can not fucking, i call the teenagers. And, aside from a few exceptions, they are all self centered ignorant pricks that should all recieve enemas to clean out the the cum the media left up there after that thorough ass fucking. I am sick and tired these people, i am sure you know who they are, you have problem seen them yourselfs. They are divided into a few different groups, group A: higher teenage society, these people don't have to work, they're parents actually pay for them to look like everyone else does, and further widen the gap these kids have between they way they are expected to be, and any form of self identity. Next we have group B: lower teenage society, these people may not actually be poor, they might only be behind, point is, they want to be in group A, but for some reason they can not mannage it, either they are two poor to afford all the cool Van douche hats, or simply go out and buy one a month out of style, these are the unlucky ones that just can't be happy with the fact that they have clothes to wear in the first place, and are to blind to realize they hey, maybe having a large cock in my ass 24/7 isn't such a swell idea.  Group C: ANaRcHisM!!!!!111!1!!!1oneone!!!11one, yes, they are just that cool, these are the people that try so very hard to be unlike group A and B, and end up being exactly like them just with a whole new look. They feel the need to bad mouth all the cool stuff everyone else gets to wear, but end up paying the same ridiculously high prices for things. Like those fucking ramones shirts, you know the ones, everybody fucking has it, i am sure you've seen it everywhere. And another thing, what is it with this whole classic rock revival bullshit, theres a reason that music went away, it fell behind the times. Newer, better, music became available.  That music, just simply isn't good anymore. Now granted, there are some good songs out there by these bands, but they are still not nearly as good as any of the new stuff i hear.  heres a list of people i wish weren't dead so that i could personally kill them myself in hopes of getting rid of all these fucking teeny boppers that can't let them die.  - the three dead beatles* -jim morrison -jimmy hendrix - the original AC/DC singer* -that annoying fuck from the sexpistols*  now before some of you call me a hypocrite, for like Led Zepplin and Alice Cooper, i would like to point out, that i never claimed either of these bands to be the greatest bands, simply the best out of all the shitty 'revived' bands. Sure they have made some great songs, but they have also made some really shitty ones as well.  anyway, you maybe wondering where i fit into some of this, i dont, i am different then all that shit. I am not saying im unique, i just conform to a whole new idea. Anyway, i am the 'metal'** fan, with the 'emo'** hair cut, and apparently i dress like a 'goth'**. So, i am group D: no identity, these people are just happy (debatable) living life and doing what they like, with out having to make some kind of statement or fit into some kind of clique.  now, on to more pressing matters. Fuck me, i may single handed fucked up any real friendship i have ever had, with people that i have actually WANTED to be friends with, there aren't alot of you, so this says alot. First of all there was i that whole group i had hung out with till about february, when i decided i really couldn't stand there shit anymore, i dont know where i would put them, they were a mix of group B and C i suppose. These are the only people that i will have refered to hence forth that by the end i actually DIDN'T want to be friends with anymore. From that point things got really weird, it seems that i began have one really good friend at a time, and that usually lasted a month before i went on to someone else, so for april, this person was cool, we talked shit about everyone we fucking hated,  fuck those fuckers we would say....good times. But alas things got fucked, i tihnk i began to just grow tired of them, sure alot of time they were fun to be around, but there were times where i couldn't helped but get pissed off at them. Next we have may, i think am one of the only people that was able to see beyond that this person was incredibly good looking. I only wanted to just be friends with this person and nothing more. Yet, they payed very little attention to me in a group and often time i grew angry knowing that the people she talked to more were the people only interested in fucker her. So, fuck her, i grew tired of that and found myself wanting to get away from her shit. June, now along LONG while before this month, i had been um...'romantically' interested in this friend, now it was different, it was someone i could just tell how i felt, and would often times want to go to when fucking everything pissed me off. This is the one i miss most right now, but, it's gone now, with little chance of revival. Enter july, now, this month doesn't hold any real friends. but i did spend more time with someone adventures were had aslong as fun, they saved me from the worst depression i had ever felt before, so kudos to that shit. Now here we are in august, who knows what this month holds, o well, atleast i have a new e-friend, MAYBE I'LL EVEN GET TO SEE THEM, but that all depends on....  ...MY FUCKING GROUNDING. Never, ever have i had to re-evaluate my parents before, on whether or not what they are doing is indeed an example of good parenting. Yet, i here i am, they have no idea how badly they got fuck up my life, and theres. I have wanted to run away before, i really have, not because i don't like my parents, just because life is to boring. But now, now that i am actually angry with them, there is reason to follow through with my plans. My parents don't fucking trust me, i know i have screwed up before, but, differently, never bad enough to bring about this lack of trust i face now. They just don't trust me to make decisions, when i have so clearly showed that i am fully capable of making the right decisions when it comes these kind of things. It pisses me off to know end to know that they don't trust me, and my mom actually had the audacity to say that, 'i lost there trust' over the FUCKING biking incident. BULLSHIT, what trust did i have before that. There is no way you could have given me two weeks for that and not even discussed it with me, you ASSUMED something. Which is a clear example of not fucking trusting me, if you have to make fucking assumptions.  fuck this man, i write this out of anger, and for some reason i still come out as the depressed person, I AM SO SICK AND FUCKING TIRED OF BEING DEPRESSED. ahhhhhhhhhg,. 
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      after talking to someone tonight, i decided this seems to be my reason to cut.  i also thought it had promise to be a good song. however, after writting several verses and a chorus, i decided that all the verses i wrote were shit, but i was rather fond of the chorus. So, posty-posty.  'Plunge the edge into the flesh slash marked arms and bloodstained skin. But in the end it all comes down to, a cry for help that nobody answers.'  maybe i'll finish it up some time and post it.   
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dear Mom and dad,  I hope you find this.  So, i got my bike back today, hurray, and my dad was nice enough to let me ride it for a whole 15 minutes!!! what a swell guy. Now if only he wasn't such a fucking CUNT....thats right i said the c word. I am 'grounded' to the 22nd, that's two and a half weeks, for a bullshit infraction like the night biking. It's fucking hilarious how much my parents trust me, i am one of the most straight edge people there is, and yet i am pretty sure my mom thinks i'm a fucking drug addict. I love how people get smaller punishments then i do for getting caught with fucking alchohol and yet my parents give me two weeks for being out of the house at 3 am....like OMG guys. So, now that i know the punishment, i have no problem bringing about a war between myself and my parents, it's about time they realize what fucking douchebags they are.  p.s. anyone know the fasted way to bike to vancouver...please leave a detailed description. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so, i was original going to tell you about a revelation i had well going biking (with my shitty bike, not the good one) at 2 am. But something new, and actually entertaining has come up.  I'm now grounded. But it's funny though, because i'm grounded for sneaking out of the house at night... daaaaaaaa, let me think. I was able to sneak out when i wasn't confined to the house, what makes you think i won't be able to now. Now my dad is going to want to have a nice long talk about why i go biking at night. I am basically not even give him that much. I will ignore the topic alltogether. If it comes up at dinner, i will leave the table at starve that night. If he calls me down for a 'family meeting' i will totally ignore him. Also it is remarkable that he even thinks i would mind be grounded....o wait, he's under the impression that I HAVE friends. Haha, this is really very amusing, i will have to see how it turns out, and whether or not i will have to eat my words.  Anyway, on to the revelation, this isn't really all that startling, but o well. Nice guys finish last. I know it is unbelievably cliche, but it is the truth. I have been the nice guy my whole life, and it has gotten me nothing in return. Empathy gets you know where. Stop caring about others.  ...that is all. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hereby retract any statements refering to one P.W. as being an assface. I have decided to make this retraction, i guess as an act of good will... i dont know. I expect nothing to change. I already know august is going to be exactly like july until i get my bike, and how much of a difference that will make, i do not know. So, you are no longer an assface, but you may feel free to continue to keep distance from me, and i will atempt to do the same.  32 days till school everyone are you excited...i know i am.  o, and still no bike. 
    
</post>


</Blog>