<Blog>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      WeLL i WoKe uP thIs MoRnInG aRoUnd 8:30 (sTiLL SiCk n I cANt sLeEp..) I GoT uP wEnT dOwN sTaIrs GoT sOmE fROoT LoOpS n GoT oN tHe CoMpuTeR, No oNe wAs oN sO i DeCiDeD tO aDd a PoSt. mE aNd MiChAeL fInNaLLy gEt SoMe 'AlOnE' tImE 2NiTe. i DoNt tHiNk tHaT wE'vE eVeR aCtUALLy bEeN aLoNe..cEpT fOr MaYbe oNcE oR tWiCe. bUt HeY, i CaN't CoMpLaIn..ThInGs ArE gOiN' gReAt WiTh uS! I fOrGot To MeNtiOn LaSt NigHt ThAt i WenT tO tHe dErMoTOLoGiSt To SeE iF i QuALiFiEd fOr ThIs sTuDy..AnD i DiD! LeT mE eXpLaIn: YoU tAkE mEdIcInE, aNd tHey PaY yOu MonEy! I hAve tO TaKe thIs MeDiCiNe fOr a CoUpLe MoNtHs BuT i GeT  500$ ..CrAzY! iM SiNcInG a MAJOR ShoPpInG SPrEe!! WeLL i GueSs tHaTs aLL fOr NoW. I MiGht AdD aNoTHeR poSt L8r aNd LeT u KNoW How me n MicHaeLs NiGht wEnt!! L8r DuUuDeS..                           *-BaRbiE GirL-*
      
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      starting from the beggining:  *well tuesday night..me katie kate phoebe lindsey and all the juniors n seniors we've been hanging out with went to frontera for dinner..and all hell broke loose with them and our south guys..they're in this huge fight and it's really gay. they want to fight..its anoying!*  -after we went to frontera we spent the night at lindseys house, and then in the morning alex came over to go to six flags with us, we had planed to leave around 8:15..but we didn't get outta bed untill 8:30 haha. once we had gotten up and on the road it was about 9:15ish, we stoped by burger king and ate then mrs rennie dropped us off at six flags. we got there around 10-10:30. as soon as we walked in we had to get our bags checked, the people checking them were making fun of all of us because we had make up and tampons in our bags..it was funny! and then after that we started walking and a man stoped us to take a picture and he gave me a little white card..so we could come back later and see it. the first ride we went on (or should i say THEY went on..) was georgia scortcher..me and katie decided to sit out on this one..seeing how i hadn't ever been on a roller coaster i was a lil scared..after that we went on the log ride! now that was fun! there was a lady sitting in her booth at the top of the ride and she was sleeping and phoebe (being the anoying person she is..haha) yelled at her and told her to wake up! it was so funny! and the picture that they took of us going down the lil hill or w/e was sooooo funny all of our mouths are WIDE open! after we got off that ride it started raining so we just walked around a lil' bit untill it quit raining and we rode the mine train and some other lil stuff like that then we went on the scream machine and the mind bender and the best ride of all..BATMAN! yaaa that is the funnest ride ever! oh and we rode the swings! and me and phoebe and kate went and saw one of those lil shows that they have!! now that was fun.. :) the best part of the day though was going on the bungy jumping thang! idk what its called but they put you on your stomach and you go up like 170 feet and then you fly at 60mph! its so much fun!! the worst part of the day was seeing michael there on a ride with mistie..it was bad enough that he was there and i couldnt hang out with him (too long of a story..) but then seeing him on a ride with another girl.. ah! i had to act like it didnt bother me though, the last thang i need is to have more jeleosy..*i love michael alot and i dont like being jeleous of people, i just wish we could have hung out together..it was just a very akward situation that day* and then chelsie making up stuff about me..just trying to get michael to break up with me..i just wish people would mind there own buissness and worry about themselves for once and not what everyone else is doing..and she wonders why i dont wanna hang out with her..she calls michael all the time and then makes up crap! but w/e she did the same thang with richard.. :/ im not gonna complain though..i got michael and thats all that i care about! hes so awesome, and hes changed my life so much.. :)  well anyways at the end of the day we went to see our picture that they took of us earlier and when we looked at it the guy there told me that we were the picture of the day and they had named us the SIX FLAGS BARBIES! :) after we saw the picture we all raced to the car (litteraly) because we all wanted shot gun..so we run out and we see a white expodition..(thinking its katies mom) so we all start banging on the door trying to get in..and not realizing untill we looked up that it wasnt katies mom that we were banging on a total strangers doors..im sure she was a lil freaked out by us! well when we saw what idiots we were we ran as fast as we could to katies car (getting yelled at in the process by some stupid black lady)..we jumped into the car exausted and headed home. when i got home i went strait to bed i was so tired. i woke up this morning feeling worse than ever, my voice was gone, and my throat hurt..i took some medicine and went back to bed..i had to get up at like 1:30 to go to the dermatologist..and then i had conditioning at 4..i still feel like crap..but w/e..  im out. and ill post sometime tomrrow. MICHAELS COMMING OVER :) i cant wait we need some 'alone' time..LIKE MAJOR!  -*baRbIe GiRL*-
      
</post>


</Blog>