<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Proverb of the day: The lifespan of a person is based on the amount things he/her had done during that life.   Haiz...tml the hols end le...Mus study le wo...Feel a little sian but keep thinking that must work hard le...>. WILL  regret. In the hols, i did not done mus things. Everydae is play play play...hahx die le. Got  crazy  with a online game call "Ragnarok". I siao liao... play lik crazy. haha. My mum say i was poisoned....... Fine.(i was a little.)haha Anyway... tml can meet you all again...quite delighted... i got a question for you all... you all giv comments hor... Q-- Many ppl say tt China will stand out in the world market and become one for the most powerful country in the comin yrs., Do you agree??  Sorry ar...Very boring rite? Next time find a better one...Buai.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Proverb of the day: Everyday is a new beginning and you should spend your time carefully.  Haha... dunno wat to write, so i decided that i can write a proverb everyday...^^. well, todae nothing special happened la... onli playing of games, watch tv and read alittle..=X i think i spent to much on games..haha(dun follow me) den now cannot concentrate on study le...die. Therefore im stopping all my games stufs...(maybe not all ^^) so lata go school won keep on thinking about it... Btw..i think i will not be writing blog everydae...lata my brain juice no more. nuttin to  write la. so pai seh...^^ i will onli be posting the proverbs onli..haha. Buai
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haizzz... Dis my first blog, so i dunno whether is it good... Need you comments la...haha Anyway, i write dis cos many of my friend oso got write, so i join in the fun. ^^ Anyway, now very late le...so cannot write the things tt happened 2dae. haha...don get disappointed lor... tml i will write one, relax.  I wan to ask you all who hav done your hw le??? I onli do half way lor... die. Surely rush last minute one. Nvm... used too it le. Anyway, wish you all a good hols & enjoy yourself... cos after dis, it time to prepare for one of our's greatest battle!!! Good luck.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Proverb of the day: Clever(chong ming) is not equal to smart(zhi hui). The clever guy doesnt mean tt he is smart, but a smart guy is definately clever.  Hihi... Very long nvr rite le...Sorri, (too lazy la)> Anyway... i hav read the yi ren's horoscope thingy... "Scorpio are passionate ppl, they hope for a long lasting love... haha... gald tt im a scorpio... this really say out wat i wan to say..." (but scorpio are vengeful ppl... erm... there is no vengeance in my dictionary... so you all relax...) ^^
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      >>>>  Think back to the day when you first laid eyes on her, you found yourself charmed by the way she talks, the way she dresses herself to show off her best features and the way she embraces life with her laughter. It seemed as if a mysterious "chemistry effect" has suddenly developed to draw you closer to her.       You two then began to meet regularly, and you discover more things that you admire about her, her clever ideas, her healthy values and the way she stands up for you when others doubt you, you find yourself thinking of her not just as a normal friend, but a very good friend.       It is often during this period that a boy and a gal will start thinking of bringing their friendship to another level. After all, the kind of wonderful experience you have between each other can only become even better if it develops into unique… no one else seems able to replace her in your heart… so both of you agree to go steady and work even harder on the relationship, you guys "graduate" to become a couple, and are the envy of the sea of singles.       However… at some point in your relationship, you forgot how it all began. You start to take your partner for granted… why can't she laugh in a more ladylike manner? Why doesn't she dress herself more trendily? Why must she assert her views and point out your silly mistakes? Is she really the one for you?       To be fair to yourself and to her, take some time to reflect on your "love memory". The "love memory' contains all the reasons that you fell in love with her right from Day One. It contains rarely accessed snippets of how your life has changed since meeting and loving her.       Pre-steady days, did you heap compliments on her for the brave way she spoke her mind on bullies and snobs? You probably did. Did you like her unusual fashion sense that makes her stand out from the crowd?       Right-o. So why are you criticizing or finding fault with her now that she is your girlfriend? Because you have forgotten the fundamentals of love… like so many of us. You have forgotten the reasons you admired her during the friendship phase… instead… once you went steady… you put your "love memory" in cold storage…       As her boyfriend, you take up a new set of demands and expectations about her. These new ideas are not necessarily better; they could put your relationship at risk…       A healthy relationship, like learning to walk properly, follows a step-by-step development; you can't possibly become part of a couple if you aren't friend in the first place. Ok, I know some of us break the rule and plunge straight into whirlwind courtship, but how many of those couples can go the distance? Couple hood works well when there is something you like about her (and vice versa), and I’m not referring to merely the physical aspects… dun think too hard huh!       So whenever your relationship hits a rocky path, don't give up without checking on your "love memory"… rediscover the reasons why you fell in love with her, and watch your relationship flourish with a newfound vigor.       Love is to listen to the needs of the other party: giving without asking for returns… overlook the faults and find the plus point of the other party… voice out &amp; say sweet things and express your happiness and words of encouragement for the other party, just like me giving kisses to the person I like… kekekee… putting in effort, keep putting in more time to find the world of love…   Give comments....^^ 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>