<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In high school i dated this guy.  he was a nice guy...athletic, thoughful, and funny.  we dated for a couple months, then all of sudden i woke up one day and didn't feel like being his girlfriend any longer. originally, it was nothing he did or nothing he said--i just didn't want to be with him anymore. from time to time i would verbalize this thought to one of my friends, "hey, i just don't feel going out with him." and she'd say, "why?" and i'd say, "no reason, just don't feel like it."  "not feeling like it" is a perfect reason for anything in my opinion.  i've realized that "i just don't feel like it" is my life's motto, right behind my first motto in life (which shall be explained later).  I JUST DON'T FEEL LIKE doing a lot of things.  and this feeling is usually super spontaneous. like it just happens in the blink of an eye.  i could be mid-laugh, or mid-action and my brain says, "what are u doing?" the high school boyfriend was case #1. other cases have crept up on me now.  i'm beginning to think it's a sickness...a case of the "don't feelsies" if you will.  for starters, I DON'T FEEL LIKE working anymore.  i don't know why, i don't know when this happened. i like money, i used to absolutely love my job. then one day, i went to sleep and didn't wake up in time for work.  i didn't care.  why? because i just don't feel like doing it anymore.  no cause for stress, or aggravation...i don't get angry or disappointed in myself. it's just a simple fact--i don't feel like it. it's not even reflected in my work, well maybe in my tardiness or increased giggle-time, but thats ok as long as i produce the $$.  although it has some consequences, i DON'T FEEL LIKE working out anymore.   i used to love being in shape. i never liked running, but i like playing basketball, and i loved lifting. now...i love cake and my futon.  im officially a fat ass. and i don't care (yes i do), but im not willing to do anything about it, b/c....HEY, I JUST DON'T FEEL LIKE working out.    as a matter of face, i DON'T FEEL LIKE typing a paragraph for each one of these thoughts. here's a list:  I DON'T FEEL LIKE:  1. brushing my teeth at night 2. waking up on time...ever 3. washing silveware (i'll clean the dishes, but hate doing forks and spoons) 4. having basketball practice (not for a summer league anyways) 5. taking out trash 6. quitting biting my finger nails 7. losing weight 8. shaving my legs (unless i have a man) 9. drinking water 10. paying bills 11. driving anywear that doesn't take 5 minutes 12. smiling or talking to the secretary at work  AND LAST BUT CERTAINLY NOT LEAST...  13.  I DON'T FEEL LIKE POSTING ON THIS SITE ANYMORE  Yes folks its true. im done with this whole blogging thing. it is hard work and not all its cracked up to be. if you are disappointed right now, ask yourself "what kind of positive reinforcement did i offer to keep this thing going?"  and your answer would be none. (one exception, thanks Bananahead!)  PEACE AND PEACE  
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for two summers in a row i worked at the Water Pollution Control Facility in my hometown...aka WPCF...aka the Shit Plant...aka presumably the worst job on earth...aka the best job i've ever had.  my friend, who shall remain nameless at this point, but we will call her Bananahead for the sake of comedy, also worked at the plant with me.  so take me, Bananahead, and the closet crackhead secretary and u have 100% of the female population versus the 30 or so middle aged, sloppy white men who worked there. now me and bananahead didn't actually dabble in the sewers or work with shit or anything, we did grounds work, semi-professional landscapers.  with our own tools and our own pick-up truck, we took care of 13 acres of land. with two Wheel Horse lawn mowers (the kind you ride) and two kick ass weed-wackers, there was no grass too thick or hill too steep for us to conquer. but enough about that.  the best part of the day was any interaction with The Guys. it was pure comedy every moment around The Guys.  The Guys were the Honorable Men of Shit.  they climb down into sewers and unclog a city's worth of dumping on a day-to-day basis. they manned the shit presses and kept the water clean.  they were greasy. they were stank.  they spoke horrible english. but they were funny.  at the end of the summer Bananahead and i came up with a series of awards in honor of the plant.    the award for Best Use of Instruction goes to......none other than Billy Harris!! Mr. Harris better known as Billy was the only other black person at the plant besides myself.  and Billy could tell a story.  in a discussion about eating at the Nordic Lodge (a popular New England seafood buffet) Billy explained his mean skills in the art of eating.  He answered the age old question "how do u get your money's worth at a buffet?" with sheer precision.  it went something like this...  Billy (all said without interruption):    "i'll tell ya how u really get your money's worth. as soon as u start to feel yourself gettin full, you gotta switch up the tastes. go over to the fruit section and get you some fruit.  and they have all kinds of fruit. im talking every kind of fruit you can think of, they have. and if its not there, just ask and they will get it for ya. and when you get yourself some fruit, you gotta get a variety.  cuz that's what's gonna switch up the tastes. you gotta switch up the tastes with the fruit. cuz you can switch up the tastes with some peaches, or grapes, or strawberries....then you got your apples and oranges and pears...or get you some cantoloupe or watermelon...they've got the grapefruit or nectarines. cuz you just gotta switch the taste in your mouth. then you will be able to eat more.  get you a pear or kiwi or mango, and you will be all set.  then you will be able to eat more, once you switch up the tastes.  Bananahead and Me:  "ooh. so all we have to do is switch up the tastes. what other kinds of fruit do they have again?"  so that my friends is how you manage to eat a whole lot at a buffet.  and thanks to the detailed instruction of Billy Harris, I will not be a weak-link in the area of appetite any longer.    Billy Harris, we salute you!  peace and blessings
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So if i never mentioned this before, basketball has always been a huge (actually more like ginormous) part of my life. i am one of those people who picked up the rock when i was about 8 years old...and vowed never to put it down. basketball is a full-time job:  weeklong basketball camp every summer, playground courts around the city everyday during summer vacation, AAU in the spring, high school ball in the winter, and regular summer league.  Tag on being an honor roll student, volleyball, and softball during high school and you get--a nerdy jockette. live, sleep, and breath THE GAME.  inhale...exhale...  then there was the 4-year stint at Canisius College.  possibly, no, undoubtedly the best years of my life.  i wasn't a collegiate superstar, but i started and i didn't pay for my degree and enjoyed an experience that only a select few have the opportunity to do.  stereotypically, the pointguard on any given team should be the smartest, most likely the quickest, best ball handler and passer, with the most endurance.  im not going to rate my game on each of these levels in retrospect, but i will say i got a zero in the endurance category.  i mean a zero like no score...like the kid who got caught cheating on a test and eventhough he wasn't going to get a passing grade with the help, the teacher puts a big, fat, red zero on top of the paper to make an example out of him.  that was me.  the pointguard who led from behind.  i could have told my coaches during my official visit that i was never going to run a 5 minute mile, i wasn't going to get through a 30 minute sprint workout without hyperventilating, and i wasn't going to play a 40 minute game if there was any inkling of full court pressure in our defensive arsenal. i get tired.  the collegiate me was in great shape, with biceps and triceps and even those masculine little muscles ontop of your shoulders that start at your neck.  with calf muscles that were so potent they were prone to cramping and a 4-pack that you could wash baby clothes on, i was in good shape. but as good a shape i was in, and for as much conditioning and lifting i was doing...i got tired.  inhale...exhale....  which brings me to now.  i am exactly 1 year, 1 month and 6 days from my college graduation.  i am about 7 lbs. over my "good shape" weight and currently standing in my "no man's land" weight.  that's when your not fat, but softer.  not skinny or athletic, but not thick.  when people say "you put on a few pounds, but it looks good on you." when you look shorter, but ur actually just wider...im fooling with people's depth perception. im not in good shape.  inhale...exhale...  so i signed up to play in this pro am league here in Springfield.  my first game is next week (i'll update the lowdown on that). my first practice (who practices for a summer league?) was last week and also the purpose of this entire entry.  at this practice the 5 women who showed up from my team, scrimmaged against these 25 little boys aged 11-15.  i got tired.  i was the only PG and we had no subs and....i got tired. after like 5 times up and down the floor, i was in my usual position--leaned over hands on knees (but i wasn't dancing), gasping for air.  it was pathetic.  even my brand new teammates were looking at me like 'are u ok'. people trying to help me out and stuff. sad.  so finally im looking at our coach and my eyes said "timeout fool!" but my mouth said "*whatever hot air sounds like when ur tired*".  i was dehydrated b/c i came straight from work, i was almost catching a cramp in my calf, and oh yeah...i was tired.  so good thing my coach speaks the same eye language dialect as me, cuz he called a timeout.  so we're gathered in a semi-circle while he starts talking. everyone is standing up. i'm squatting. im looking up, i'm paying attention (sort of), but i'm considerably low to the ground. so mr. coach is yippin' and yappin' about us looking ok, but needing to whatever and how its our first time playing and the people we really challenge won't be little boys and that we look pretty good and blah blah blah blah blah. and mid-sentence he looks down at me and says in almost a whisper, but truly concerned voice "hey Keia, do u smoke...cigarettes?"  and you know how the english language calls for a slight rise in your voice when your asking a question...but this was a black man, with a regular black man voice...right up until he said "cigarettes?"  the "-ettes?" sounded like a white woman.  so by now my brain cells aren't responding as quickly as they do when i have more oxygen in my blood, but i manage to squeak out an unconvincing "no, i have asthma."  inhale...exhale...  ultimate cheapness.  how could someone ask me, a seasoned athlete, a D-1 pointguard, an 'if i flex the right way i still have some abs' if i smoke cigarettes?  i was upset that i didn't have a better comeback and really mad at my teammates reaction.  all eyes darted down to me...at my lowest moment (and lowest physical positioning) and waited in earnesty to see what my answer would be. i even caught someone with a ghetto-girl look like "she lyin."  inhale...exhale...  but cigarettes?  stogies?  or as R. Kelly would say--cigaRITTS?  i think cigarettes are nasty. i smoked one of my moms when i was like 10, purely experimental, just to see what i looked like. i didn't look good, especially with a New Kids On the Block pin on my shirt.  i know several people who smoke cigarettes, but not me. never will.  but i guess looking or playing like a smoker is just as bad as being one. i keep hearing my M&M-head coach's voice (who by the way is like 5'2'' so he was almost looking me straight in the eye when i was squatting)--"keia, you smoke cigarettes?"  it's like a bad dream repeating over an over--"keia, you smoke cigarettes?   NO!    inhale...exhale  peace and blessings
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cut and paste into your address bar...enjoy:  http://www.blastro.com/player/slumvillageselfish.html&artist =Slum+Village?mediatype=rm&filename=slumvillageselfish&artist =&bitrate=_128&mediatype=wmv&x=63&y=6  
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Over the past year or so, i've been repeatedly referred to as a 'Grown  Ass Lady'.  my first thought is, man i must have been really immature before and my second thought is, yeah your right!  if your reading this and questioning or if you don't know me, let me break it down for you so it can forever be broke  ...i have a full-time salary job in the field i studied (hey, i didn't say all grown ladies made a lot of $$$) ...moved into my own apartment in a city where i didn't know anyone ...suffered  my first dramatic ending to a long-term relationship ...taken major steps to revamping my spiritual connection with God ...got my eyebrows waxed for the first time ...i'm dating (notice the word tense suggests continuity) ...i'm traveling (New Orleans, Vegas, Miami over a 5 month period) ...dumped somebody b/c they were wack in the sack (i know what i want) ...moving to New York City to work and go to school (full-time) ...visit my house in CT like i'm a stranger ...dated people off the internet (this may be more desperate than grown) ...been super broke, like my money is funny-style broke, but didn't want to to ask my parents for money ...  on the flip side, my actions do not connect with my appearance.  at least once a day, someone tells me i look some age less than the age that i am.  i am 23. i look anywhere from 17-20.  that sucks. i try not to care, and i really don't, but im tired of people saying "that's a good thing". as i tell them and i'll say it again, it will be a good thing when im like 35 and people say i look younger. but if this whole babyface thing causes a delay everytime i want a drink (and i used to get carded for lottery tickets and scratch-offs), then it's annoying.  it's just annoying.   peace and blessings 
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so I mentioned that whole thing about going to see Harry Potter with my younger cousin. as soon as I got to CT, he decides he doesn't want to go.  most likely b/c he wanted to see it with his parents.  so i hate to disappoint you, but I didn't go see it, so that let's me off the hook for life--I will never see it :-)  so Sunday was Father's Day...that special day dedicated to all the men who have "fathered" a child...mind you, not "daddied" a child, but really did some stuff in the kids life.  my father and i have a weird relationship to say the least.  because i'm a nice person...and not completely heartless, I gave him a call as I usually do on this 3rd sunday in June. when i was a kid I used to break my neck to buy/make something for him, but my effort has died down from lack of appreciation.  but that's just my quasi-sad story.  I did try to get him a card, but imagine...ur in CVS, i'd say there were about 100 different cards to choose from (15 being Mahoghany cards for African-Americans). I read just about every card in that place--to no avail.  I was explaining this to a couple friends (hey guys!) and one of them makes a great point:  They need to make cards that fit all types of situations.  Cards titled, "Always My Dad" or "You Almost Got the Job Done" or "Thanks for Helping to Make Me", "Wouldn't Have Been Here Without You".  sad, but the honest truth, no card remotely fit the role that my father has played in my life.  Which brings me to what i actually did on sunday.  to make a very long story short, a guy who was friends with my mom when they were in high school hooked me up with an interview (at my current job), was very instrumental in helping me find an apartment when i relocated, hooked me up with a mechanic (when my car was broke down to the donuts), carried heavy stuff up 8 flights of stairs, etc.  you get the picture.  so he invites me to his annual Father's Day Cookout and I went and I had a great time..with someone else's dad.  now for a moment, that made me feel kind of bad. but the more i thought about it, the more i realized that it takes a special kind of man to treat someone like their own, knowing that their blood does not run throught that childs veins.  a biological dad can easily show love support--it should be undconditional, but coming from a virtual stranger, it means much more.    so i won't be one of those people who knocks Father's Day b/c my experience isn't/wasn't the greatest with my dad, but instead, I take special time to really think about those who do, but don't have to. for me Father's Day will be just as important a day for the stepdads, like-a-fathers, big brothers, uncles, and grandfathers doing someone else's job.     peace and blessings
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm babysitting (well watching, cuz he's no baby) my younger cousin today. This dude is basically a "grown man/kid".  we've all encountered them.  He is big enough to be like 13, he's smarter than some 9th graders when it comes to school work (mainly b/c he has no pressure to be "cool" at this point and kiddie homework is fun), but his silly stage knocks you right back into the reality of the matter--he's still 8 years old.  at any rate, i like hanging out with him even though he is a definite product of the 'let's market to an age group with no job or money' age.  kids these days have more pull with dough than back in the 80's.  if i wanted something (i.e a Cricket Doll, a new Lite Bright, Easy Bake oven, etc.) I had to beg for it all year, so I could get it for Christmas, play it out before New Year's, and start the next round of good behavior for the next piece of junk.   where was i going with this?    oh yeah, he asked his mom if i could take him to see Harry Potter (whatever the new one is titled).  for anyone who knows me...i hate any movie with an inkling of demonic behavior involved. sidenote: i have been using the word  demonic  since my mom used it in reference to Halloween and told me i wasn't going trick or treating anymore when i was about 6 years old.  needless to say, i have been trick or treating.  so anyways, back to Harry Potter.  I know lots of people who like these movies.  I just don't get it. It does absolutely nothing for me.  I detest the thought of spending money on it, even if its not my money, but still.  in fact, i'd rather peel bananas or shuck corn, or take peanuts out of a peanut shell all day than watch Harry Potter.  I'll tell you  how it was on the next go 'round.  peace and blessings
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was only a matter of time before I would finally succumb to the pressures of the world and start my own blog.  It's far from spectacular, and leagues away from dynamic, but it's mine.  E-mail server at work is down, so I had some extra time on my hands to get this party started--in a non MC Hammer sense.  It will take a lifetime to really learn everything there is to know about me, but who has a lifetime to waste on something like that?  The bits and pieces, the picking and choosing, the tidbits and crumbs is all you need.  So without further ado...I welcome myself into this newfound world or words and thoughts and typos and senseless meanderings and soapbox standings and all that other good stuff that comes along with personal expression.  peace and blessings
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Booyakasha!!   ( if you've seen Da Ali G Show then you realize how perfect this word is for an opening to anything.&nbsp;&nbsp;I just hope it doesn't mean anything demonic or degrading.)      &nbsp;  And moving on...have you ever had a job where you had to  punch in  at a time clock?&nbsp; I mean serious, to the minute, electronic, old school punching in, like standing in line, card in hand, waiting to begin or end a work day with the strike of the clocks synchronized stamp, lunch-box clad, before or after another hard days work.&nbsp; I have.    &nbsp;  I never realized how much&nbsp; punching in &nbsp;resembled old times. Visions of the depression, child labor, and smokestacks should be mingling in your brain right now.&nbsp; When&nbsp;I had my job at the  urlLink   plant    I didn't realize the shackles that were placed on me by being on someone else's watch.    &nbsp;  I am shackled no more.    &nbsp;  As I wrap up the last week and a half of my job at the Basketball Hall of Fame, I am realizing just how much NOT  punching in  means to me.&nbsp; The $128,000 price tag on my undergraduate diploma actually has a major benefit...salary.&nbsp; *and if you know me, then you know that&nbsp;I didn't pay the undergrad price tag, but&nbsp;you get my point* &nbsp;I know having a college degree doesn't guarantee that you will get a salary job, but it helps.&nbsp; Even if its small, salary means something.&nbsp; Even if I miss work for an entire week, my check will be there and it will be the same amount.&nbsp; Even if&nbsp;I come into work and check my e-mail, go on Blackplanet, post on my personal weblog, see what I can find on Ebay and make personal calls all day, I'm still getting said check with said amount.&nbsp;  *not that I would actually do something like that*     &nbsp;  And aside from the salary, I come and go as I please.&nbsp; Theoretically, I was told on my first day that normal working hours for me were from 8:30 am to 5:00 pm with an hour for lunch.&nbsp; I was also told that I could come in later or earlier, and in return, leave later or earlier.&nbsp; Good deal right?&nbsp; It wasn't until after a month of working perfect time blocks that I had an epiphany...this job does not take 40 hours a week to complete.&nbsp; I could be demonstrating my A game, be the salesperson of the week, no actually, the month or quarter, and I could get it done in about 30 hours per week.&nbsp; I was slow to catch on, because the other sales people had already come to this same conclusion and were acting on it. So i joined in.&nbsp;     &nbsp;  On any given day, I show up between 8:50 am and 9:45 am.&nbsp; I take my hour lunch, which easily becomes an hour plus 15 - 35 minutes bonus time. And I  always  leave at or before 5 pm.&nbsp;Usually around 4:40 pm.&nbsp;&nbsp;The best part about all of this time finagling is that A) no one says anything to me, my boss included B) I still get the job done&nbsp;with an occasinal song of praise toward me at the monthly staff meeting&nbsp;C) if anyone said anything, it would be the bumbling a secretary that has no power D) I'm black and i've managed to fool The Man and E) E is too many, no one goes that far when listing things by letter.&nbsp; So there you have it, i'm a professional slacker.    &nbsp;  Don't want to be shackled.    &nbsp;  Now I have this fear that my next job will not have such luxuries.&nbsp; In addition to all my slacking, I had full benefits, unlimited sick days, 10 days paid vacation, work related trips, and gas mileage reimbursement (not to mention the occasional NBA or WNBA tickets).&nbsp; God forbid I have to actually work for my money.&nbsp; But in the words of the Rev. Al Sharpton, "we were never given the 40 acres. We were never given the mule. So we we [I] just figured I'll ride this donkey and see where it will take me." *thrown in there for no apparent reason*    &nbsp;  well...it's now 4:10 pm, Thursday afternoon, vacation day tommorrow...you already know.    &nbsp;  peace and blessings    &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Never&nbsp;begin a sentence with the word  and .  And i...heart...you.  And&nbsp; and  is the implication that there is something else.  --in addition to,  but there is nothing else.  And i...heart...you.  And i don't love you.  And i don't loathe you.  And i don't lust, after you.  And it is just&nbsp;my heart.  i heart...my heart...is empty.  hollowed out like cantaloupe.  And i...heart...you.  the center of&nbsp;life now silenced by death.  And i...heart...you.  lungs gripped by fists and shortened breath.  And i...heart...you.  i imparted you.  And you imparted i.  And i...heart...you.  in a time now past,&nbsp;jump started you.  And i...heart...you.  And i hurt.  And you hurt i.  And i...heart...you.  Rules made to be broken,  like using  and  to begin a sentence.  And offering my heart.  And i hearting you.  And you hurting i.  And i, not ceasing.  I..still...heart...you.&nbsp;         peace and blessings       
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You can learn a lot from Chris Rock. (never thought i'd actually&nbsp;admit that.)&nbsp;&nbsp;I don't know the extent of his personal relationships with women, but I do know that he has a firm grasp on understanding  us ( by  us&nbsp; I mean women ) , gaged by the jokes he tells.&nbsp; Two statements particularly, that are just jokes on the surface, have dug into a much deeper meaning for those who really  hear  what Chris (yeah, we are on a first name basis) is saying.       "Women need 3 things to survive:&nbsp; Food....water....and COMPLIMENTS!"    "If talking was in the Olympics, a man wouldn't stand a chance."      It's proverbial phrases like these that reveal just how much a man knows about what a woman wants, what&nbsp; a woman needs, what it's going to take to survive a relationship with a woman who is worth the battle--and it is a battle.&nbsp; Even when a relationship is seemingly flawless--it's still a battle. That whole "men are from Mars, women are from Venus" crap actually exists.&nbsp;     And I have yet to find someone who specifically understands me.&nbsp; To avoid making generalizations I will be careful to state that&nbsp;the men&nbsp;I HAVE DATED do not have a clue....i'm not talking bout your man, 'maybe it's just me.'&nbsp; Maybe it's just the guys I meet that fail the same test, every single-dingle time.&nbsp; I'm not into head games or actually testing dudes to set them up for failure, but sometimes a test just comes up.&nbsp; It's accidental testing, similar to when a teacher suspects that the vast majority of a class didn't do the reading since no one can answer a question and the discussion is scarce.&nbsp; When everyone is looking at the nerd like, "say something!" and even the nerd didn't read. So....what does the teacher do to make sure&nbsp;this assumption is correct?&nbsp; They give a Pop Quiz.&nbsp;     Every man, so far, has failed the Pop Quiz. Some worse than others.    Example Pop Quiz:&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  Answer yes or no to each of the following statements.      DISCLAIMER:&nbsp; The parameters of the relationship this quiz applies to are subject to change.&nbsp; Ideally, however, this quiz serves relevance to those that are actually boyfriend and girlfriend, having sex and/or hooking up, the relationship is exclusive, and neither party has been clinically diagnosed as mentally challenged.      After a fight with your significant other, it's ok to hang up without coming to a resolution.    It's ok to use hunger or fatigue as an excuse to hang up.    It's ok to use video games as an excuse to hang up.&nbsp;    It's ok to use homework as an excuse to hang up.    You have a healthy relationship if you talk on the phone every&nbsp;3-5 days.    Your relationships is healthy if you talk on the phone once a day.    You should talk on the phone at least once on the day following a sexual rendezvous.    If a woman says "fine, bye then!" you should hang up and promptly call right back.    If a man says "i'm sorry" and it's not followed by any other words, he doesn't know why he just apologized.    It's ok to check the numbers in your significant other's cell phone and call people to learn more about their relationship.    If you see your significant other on Instant Messenger you should say hello.    If you work or are constantly sitting at a computer, it's ok not to ever send a "hello" e-mail.    E-cards are an important part of a relationship if you have access to a computer.    It is possible to use way too many smiley faces on Instant Messenger when one is attempting to be flirtatious.    If your significant other is upset and confronts you about something, it's ok to automatically fire back with your own tirade about absolutely nothing.       answers and evaluations soon to come.....        to be continued......     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of these posts was bound to pop-up at some point since it happens to me everyday, so here it is... I'M HUNGRY!   I have an ongoing mental list of things I need to ask God about when I get to Heaven--namely concerning hunger.  ok, of course there are more important things I want to know like 'the meaning of life', and why can't  some  people without color hear the music, or the purpose that men's nipples serve, and why do some women have mustaches and beards... but that's besides the point.  But I mean, seriously, have you ever been so hungry...  -you start biting your fingernails? -you drink water, but it makes things worse? -you cough to cover up the stomach growls? -you try to chew gum, but it melts away or you end up swallowing it? -you configure your mid-section in a way that muffles the growling sound? -you get weak, irritated, and mean (which can occur in any given order) -you commence to literally inhaling  some food like a monkey or dog or bear?  or am i alone on this one?  and nothing is more annoying than finally getting some food (of course it would be too much like logical to get an acceptable portion) and then realizing that you can't finish it. which only makes sense and is a catalyst for one of the positive points about hunger--it makes your stomach shrink.  I know it's not just my imagination that makes me look skinnier first thing in the morning...the time when i'm always the most hungry. me and one of my college roomies even planned around the so called "skinny stomach."  conversations like,   person #1:  "hey are you gonna wear that tight shirt, with your painted on jeans tommorrow?"    person #2:  "ummm, it all depends on what time we go and what time we eat."    person #1:  "i know.  I wish the club was open in the morning, so I could always have my really 'skinny stomach'"  being really hungry also causes greediness.  there's nothing worse than looking greedy and using the idea that your famished as an excuse.  I'm willing to admit that i've done it, how bout you? ya know, when you finally get some grub after hours of hunger...you secure a calm, quiet place ALONE to really  * monkey up on your prize. when you are barely having time to breathe, let alone digest anything that enters your mouth.    and just like that...it's over.  the good feeling of NOT being hungry anymore is what it's all about.  there is something almost sinful to me about how rewarding it is to be rescued from the agony of hunger pains, the embarassment of uncontrollable stomach growls, and the quasi depths of death (yes, i've been so dillusional I thought I would die).  if i *monkey-ed up then i usually end up feeling a bit glutton-like.  but *monkeying up is a rarity.  *DISCLAIMER: The term monkey up and or any variation of it (monkeying up, monkey-ed up), has been copyrighted and shall only be used by those licensed to do so. Thank you.  so with that said, and since the small amount of energy I did have is now used up...I'm off to lunch, b/c i'm starvin' like Marvin!!! and who the hell is Marvin?  peace and blessings
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some people receive sheer satisfaction from other people's embarassment. I am one of those people. I laugh when people trip (hysterically if they actually hit the ground), am quick to correct when someone mis-speaks, and LOVE when people just plainly 'feel cheap.'  if you are anything like me, here's your chance to have a laugh at my expense. Today I offer msyelf as a living  sacrifice for the sake of laughter.  Now that it's out in the open at work, I can safely post to the world wide web, that I QUIT MY JOB TODAY. yep, my dream job (with the nightmare salary) has received my 1 month notice.  i decided that 2 weeks wasn't enough time to replace my position. plus i like the people and i LOVE the company. so i've been attempting to muster up enough courage to actually walk right into my boss' office and tell him I was leaving. Now, I really like my boss, he's young, really funny, down to earth, understanding, laid back kind of guy. I was mostly nervous b/c i felt that I was disappointing upper management by leaving before my 1 year anniversary.     so here's the lowdown.    i was suppposed to tell him on Friday, so it would be exactly a month from my last day. but then we had cake and ice cream for some other dude who just resigned. i didn't want to mess up someone's party and my boss left early to hit the bar that day.  so i told myself, first thing Monday, you must do it.  Monday. as soon as i get to my cubicle (not office) i write my boss (Dave) an e-mail. simply put "Can we meet sometime this morning to chat." he doesn't respond for the next 40 minutes. so I go over to his office (not a cubicle) and say "hey, did you get my e-mail?" he says, "no."  then he checks it and reads it while im standing there.  he says "well i have a 10:00 am, right after that is good"...i say ok and head back to the cubi.  i sit down, a little nervous that the moment of truth is less than 90 minutes away.  so I quickly crank out a short e-mail to my friend Bananahead, " I just asked for a meeting with Dave…so 10:45 is the hour of power…pray for me! jk. im not even nervous…im just a little shaky, my hands…maybe the butt shakes as well."    send.   20 seconds later....  oh shoot, did i just send that e-mail to my boss???  yes.    ok, so how much more short-bus bound could I become?  seriously, who e-mails there own boss the an e-mail about preparing to quit.  I know you're dying to know what I did next.  the only thing i could do. i walked back over to his office (not to be confused with a cubicle) and asked if we could meet right then and there. he says, "sure, but i have a 10 am meeting, will it take long?"  "nope, only a few minutes."  so i close the door, sit down and do the do (no need for me to fill you in on all the technical, corporate hoopla bulshit that i created in my head weeks prior to the event).  he was extremely cool about it. he was supportive. made me less nervous. so then i said, "oh yeah, i just bombarded your office b/c i sent you an e-mail that wasn't meant for you." he grins and quickly turns and reads the e-mails. we both start cracking up. he  describes the e-mail as classic. and "one that he will hold on to for a while"....said he might even run off copies for the entire staff for my going away party.   ultimate cheapness.   I still can't believe I fell off that bad. my game is not up to par. i hate computers at the moment. i hate modern technology. i hate the word "sent." i hate not being able to renig. i hate it that i'm so silly i should seriously be embarrassed, but i secretly can't wait for others to laugh and share in my demise.  peace and blessings.
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We have all been subject to this super annoying untrue song (forgive me if you like it) but sing along anyways:  "i don't wanna know/if your playing me/keep it on the low/cuz my heart can't take it anymo[re]/so if you playin' me/keep it on the low/ohhh baby, i don't wanna know]  i'm not sure if Mario Winans should be slapped or applauded for bringing up the "i don't wanna know" issue. maybe if the tone wasn't so weak, i could have appreciated it.  but that's just me. not wanting to know something that occurs in a significant or ex-significant others life is a touchy subject.  the other day i sent the X-factor (aka my ex-boyfriend of 2 years 9 months minus the 1 month hiatus) a text message asking how his 4th of July was celebrated.  very simply "how was your fourth?"  I had no alterior motives for sending it, just figured we were at that holiday friendship level by now (being 7 months removed from the relationship).  no pressure for a response, no expectations of a phone call. simple.  so about an hour after the text message was sent, I receive a phone call from the X-factor's number.  I pick up. i say hello. a woman answers.   HER:  "hello?" (you can use any typical hoodrat voice for her) ME:  "hello?" HER:  "who is this?" ME: "who is this, you called me" HER:  "did you call here?" ME: "nope. i sent a text message." HER: "did you call here?" ME:  "NO, i didn't call THERE, i sent a TEXT MESSAGE to X-factor's CELL PHONE a little while ago.  i'm an old friend of his from college." HER: "oh" (apologetically) ok, then." ME: Bye. (nicely)  so there was proof. i was 99.9% sure he had a new girlfriend, but that .1% meant there was a chance that he didn't. don't ask me why i still care, considering i've already dated and been in a relationship with different people since the X-factor.  I want to know, but i don't want to know. weird.  so the X-factor calls me the next day to apologize for his hoodrats invasion of privacy.  nice gesture. but i couldn't let it end there. i asked questions. in a non-chalant, roundabout sort of way, but i asked them.   my verbalisms:   "is she a student?"  "does she have kids" "what's her name?"   his answers:    "nope, she used to be" "yep, one kid" "Tamika"  could have summed that up with one question: "is she a hoodrat?"  she is. i am disappointed. worse than that, i still care. i don't want someone that i grew to love to be with a hoodrat. i don't want to know. i didn't want to know. but--now i know.  BONUS FACT: i love calling other people hoodrats, but i'd be hurt if someone referred to me as a hoodrat.  peace and blessings
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So i know you already know this, but i might as well reiterate--i'm black.  if i was brave enough to cut my hair, i'd have locks by now, i like black music, i love black films, there's nothing sexier than a black man (some of ya'll anyways), and I don't think there is anyone (based on race catergorization) that is as cool as my people. that being said...i love Sex and the City.  my head bows slightly in shame over this one fact, but it's 100% true. i've ditched episodes of Girlfriends to watch their white pseudo-counterparts on HBO.  i accepted the 4th season on DVD as a gift (didn't spend my hard earned dollars), but I watch them religiously.  i used to watch re-runs daily on HBO, but can't even enjoy the TBS version without the bad language and sex. who takes the Sex out of Sex and the City?   why i like this show really doesn't make sense to me.  while watching an episode the other day, Carrie asked a question (since that's what she does) that rang so true...it almost deafened me. on second thought, maybe it was just some philosophical phluff (aka Fluff aka my favorite kind of sandwich) that the Sex and the City producers got me with.  "Is delayed gratification the definition of maturity?"  I don't know...is it? I think so. everything that people think they really enjoy doing, should not be done until one is "mature". ya follow me? truly gratifying acts like getting drunk, having sex, falling in love, having sex, partying, smoking weed, and having sex are things that are supposed to be indulged in when you're grown.  if you can delay doing them, does that make you mature...or maybe just patient. hmmmmm.   which brings me to my next thought...  i'm moving to new york city!! not because i want to be Carrie, Samantha, Charlotte, and definitely not Miranda. but for other reasons that concern my future.  i am not a city-girl by any means, but something about NYC fascinates me. In as much as it is filthy, fast, loud, and rude...the city conjures up a sense of sophistication, liberation, and independance.  New Yorkers claim their native borough, block, or street corner with as much dignity as a wealthy man prides in his very own name.  the wall street banker rides the train right next to the fulton street bum.  everybody eats take-out, spends beyond their means, and all sales are bargainable. i think im gonna fit in perfectly.  peace and blessings
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a major attitude while talking to my college roomie on the phone the other day.  i was basically responding negatively to whatever she said. and I couldn't figure out why. she hadn't done anything to me and I knew good and well that I was just being mean. But I just kept on.  and in the midst of my unknown attitude problem, she says, "What's wrong, are you thirsty?"  She was right.   I get an attitude when im thirsty. it sounds so petty and immature, but it happens. good thing it doesn't happen when i'm hungry b/c i'd always be upset.  moral of the story:  leave me alone if i'm thirsty.  peace and blessings
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so i still don't feel like doing this anymore...but i decided to share something instead.  I have a post-card on my desk at work and for no particular reason at all, i read it everyday. i appreciate these words, especially on the tough days.  "If there is no struggle, there is no progress.  Those who profess to favor freedom and yet deprecate agitation are people who want crops without plowing up the ground.  They want rain without thunder and lightning.  That struggle might be a moral one; it might be a physical one; it might be both moral and physical, but it must be a struggle.  Power concedes nothing without demand.  It never did and never will.  People might not get all that they work for in this world, but they must certainly work for all they get." - Frederick Douglas  to put it plain and simple, i'm going to work at it.  peace and blessings  
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        'talkin' bout good and bad hair/whether you're a darkie or fair/go on and swear, see if I care/good and bad hair' -  School Daze  (1998 Spike Lee Joint)       We've all heard the expression bad hair day, which implies that other days are 'good hair days'.  I'd like to add to that notion:   good hair lives  versus  bad hair lives .  We are all (well most people) born with hair.  Some short, some long, some manageable, some not so manageable, some straight, some curly, some micro-curly, some dry, some greasy, some full, some thin, some whispy, some blonde, some black, and most are grey toward the end of your lifetime.  Whatever the case of your crown--you've got to deal with it.        Chemicals, haircuts, curling irons, pressing devices, combs, brushes, rollers, dye, etc. can all enhance your pelo (spanish for hair)...but only to a certain extent.  Those hair makeovers are 99% temporary.  At the end of the day, or maybe the beginning I should say, your true colors always shine through.  Whatever kind of hair you have when you first wake up in the morning, is the kind of hair you really have to categorize yourself as having.  Even if you're do ragged for the night, the time it takes to get that pelo in order can be a determination factor.      Bad Hair      My name is Keia, and I have a bad hair life.  If I don't get my shit [hair, not shit literally] relaxed at least once a month, pelo is straight Brillo.  You know your shit is bad when it almost catches on fire in the hot, summer sun. *ok, there were no real sparks, but just picture thin strands of dark brown hay inches away from a tin of gas and a weed-wacker attacehd to a harness.*  I'm actually thankful somedays that I can just slap this monstrousity [thanks to dyoung for bringing this word back to the forefront in my vocab] into a  ponytail, b/c there's nothing worse than not being able do anything about your 'Do  and  you can't even pull it back.  Potentially a sad day in Pelo-ville when your shit just has to flow on its own.  When I come from the salon, I'm good.  Besides the big hole it puts in my wallet to maintain, I'm ok for a couple weeks.  But catch me first thing in the morning, when a relaxer is well overdue...I'm Don King Jr. like a summa-ma bitch.      And don't get it twisted, I've seen white people have some bad hair days as well.  I guess the equivalent of a black person's 'peas in the kitchen', would be these white people that appear to have pubes on their head.  This dry curly, mixed up stage in hair development that can't seem to find a cure.  And I've been informed by caucasian run-ins, that greaseball hair is not the 'in' thing for them unless your grunge (does that still exist?).  Personally, I think white people hair looks better when it's greasy.  Once I tried to put Pink Oil Moisturizer in Bananahead's hair.  After an hour of badgering, she picked up the bottle and in an exasperatingly annoyed voice she read, "CAUTION, DO NOT USE IN WHITE PEOPLE HAIR! MAY CAUSE URGES TO WEAR MEDALLIONS, BANDANAS, AND CROSS COLOR CLOTHING!"  As you can see, this was the 90's and she did not want the Pink Oil in her hair.      Good Hair      There are few things in this world that I actually become envious over...and hair is not one of them.  People with good hair, know they have good hair.  Note, good hair doesn't mean long hair.  In fact, the true test of good hair is cutting it all off or very low and still looking good.  Good hair doesn't mind if a man runs his fingers through it.  Good hair doesn't stay up all night before a big event so their 'Do is maintained. Nah...good hair stands the test of time.  Good hair can go swimming and shit, wash, dry, and go back to being it's good ole' self.  Good hair can usually go from a Bob to a ponytail without extensive preperation.  Only downside, good hair is rarely versatile.  Most people that I know with the good shit (not weed) wear the same style for 80% of their lifetime.       'Everybody had always thought that you had Indian in yo family.' - Martin You So Crazy        Men      If you have bad hair, i.e. little naps roll up even if you brush it, and you just can't seem to get waves, and you look like Ben Wallace while trying to grow it out-- just cut that shit low .  A simple haircut can end all this insanity.  But don't forget the edge up.      If you have good hair, i.e. water and grease and a brush have your waves spinning in circles, or you were mistaken as being a girl when you were a toddler (not a baby, I'm talking  3-5 years old)...then just take care of your pelo.  You can experiment to a certain point, but be cautious of coming out fruity looking.  If a dude is in the mirror longer than me....check the tank, cuz someone might have replaced the gas with sugar.      Natural Hair      The sole reason for this entire post wasn't to confess that I have nappy hair, but that deep down inside...I want to be a nappy dread.  I want to lock my hair about as much as I wanted a tattoo.  I don't want people to mistake me for an afro-centric, poetic, power to the people, incense burner.  It's not about being freed from the chemicals or disassociated with the assimilation to the white man's straight hair or even that I want to look West Indian.  I just think they're cute and easy to manage for the most part.  My mom has been wearing her hair naturally for the last 12 or so years, and in addition, locked her hair like 5 years ago.  They look good on her, and we have the same peanut-head.  It might just work.      This one goes out to all the bad hair people in the world:       "Bald-head skally-wag/ain't got no hair in back/Gelled up weaved up/yo hair is messed up/Need to get bout a hustle mission/Get up on loot run to beautician" -  Chickenhead  (Project Pat)       peace and blessings  
    
</post>


</Blog>