<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love to travel as do many of my friends. So inevitably, every once in a while you get an e-mail or a call asking if someone from far away can crash on the Halifamous couch.  Last night I got the call from Michael, an Irish student studying international law and a self proclaimed activist/anarchist. He's in town to speak at a media conference on "war propaganda during conflicts."  The anarchy thing intrigues me because I always associate that particular ideology with the Halifax pseudo-punk scene. A scene which I always thought was interested in anarchy only to the extent that the red A and circle patch looks good on their retro leather jackets and guitar cases.  But Michael is the real deal. He was part of the Dublin protest last week where thousands turned out to protest Dubya's visit to Ireland and Irish involvement in Iraq. You can check a story here:   urlLink Thousands in Ireland Protest Bush Visit   As for Irish involvement in Iraq all I can say is I guess it's been long enough since the Irish got their independence that they've forgot why having foreign troops invade you country kinda sucks. But, then again, the Irish government also recently banned smoking, which is like the third national sport after drinking pints and playing football. Obviously the people in charge are losing it, or maybe they're just high on fumes from the Guinness factory.  As for me, this will be an extra long weekend since I'm taking a vacation day on Friday. Unfortunately I'm totally broke. I always thought being single would be cheaper but this is not the case. I simply have too much free time.  Camping at the beach may be the only solution and I am praying to every god I can think of, including Episcopalian saints, for waves this weekend.   It's great that surfing can still make feel so good but the shitty thing is there's hardly ever surf in the summer. All I can think of is the awesome beach in Mexico where I camped this January.   The place was called Ticla and I slept in my hammock under a palapa 20 feet from water. I'd wake up early, go surf some dumping beach break waves. Then I'd hit the right point break for a few longer rides and the friendly hassle of catching waves in a crowd. When I had enough I could walk to a taco stand for shrimp tacos or go to the one corner store in town for veggies, cheese and bread. Then I'd lounge in my hammock, reading Galileo's Daughter until it was time to surf again. I have a picture of the beach taken from under my palapa. You can see my surfboard hanging from the roof of the palapa above my tent and in the distance is a perfect a-frame peak.   What's killing me is I need to get out of Halifax and right now in Ticla it is the best time of the year for surf while here it is the worst.   Mexico could make me feel good and happy, and so could a nice head high wave at my favorite surf spot in Nova Scotia, a break called Minutes. Unfortunately I won't seeing Mexico or a good wave 'till at least the Fall.  So to conclude my longest blog post I would like to share my favorite line from the Kanye West CD, The College Dropout:   "So is it cool to rap about gold if I told the world I took it from Ghana and Mali?"  Listening to this CD in my headphones as I cruise on my new skateboard is one of the few things keeping me sane these days.  Pray for surf,  k. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The election's over so let the summer begin.   In a battle of the inept and crooked vs. the down right scary the real winner was the apathy of an estimated 40% of the electorate who caried the flame of complaceny by havin' a BBQ, smokin a spliff or simply competing to see who could come up with the most convulded and pretentious, or simply down right stupid reason for not voting.   But fair play to Martin, for not totally fucking up.    Today I got off work, TuPac track in my ear/ Traded in my collar for a red and white T/ carving down the street, unconcerned/ about cracks in the pavement or road rash burns.  I sat down,read Harpers and smoked a J/ I got a call from my roomates friend from the UK/ I popped a beer, said fuck the vote  Then sat down, clicked Halifamous and wrote.  Word Up.  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The weekend in numbers:  Skateboards bought:  1 trips to the beach:  1 Waves caught:        15 Parties attended:    2 Parties in apartments that smelled like fish: 1 Beer drank:          20 Tequila shots drank: 2 Bars attended:       3 Times I thought, "Damn, I need a girlfriend": 100 Cigarettes smoked: too many Time I said, "skate or die, dude": Too many Bad dreams: 2  So that was my weekend in numbers. But the real story today, number wise, will be the number of right wing crazies we end up having in our Federal government. I really hope the conservatives don't win and in case you're thinking about voting for them here is a seldom reported fact about the conservatives: They eat babies. Seriously.  Anyway, here is my prediction for what it is worth: the liberals will form a minority government with the conservatives nipping at their heels. The Bloc will stage a comeback of sorts after last elections failure and the big loser will be the NDP. Since the NDP will have to few seats to prop up the Liberal minority the government will fall within the year and we'll get to hear and read another 200 "young voters are apathetic stories."  So in a couple hours I'm going to skateboard my young apathetic ass down to the Mic Mac Fellowship centre on Gottingen Street and participate in the marvelous thing that is a modern democracy.  K.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well this whole blog thing is turning out to be kinda cool. After replying to a contest on another Halifax Blog I have now won five dollars and all it took was a few semi-witty comments.   Here is my acceptance speech:  I'd like to thank Kristie, Blogpot.com, all my fans, all the other bloggers out there and finally Tim Berners-Lee for inventing the World Wide Web and bringing order to the chaos. But I don't thank god, because I don't think he really takes an interest in individual awards, internet-based or otherwise.  I have to admit I basically stole that last line from a comic. I forget who the comic was but he was making fun of professional athletes who thank everybody else for their performance.   The comic, imitating an athlete after a loss, said:  "First I'd like to blame the coaching staff. And I'd also like to blame my teammates who really held me back and also the fans who've  let me down all season. But most of all, I blame God."  In other news:   Who says kid are reluctant to seek help from their teachers?  urlLink Unable to convert quantity of cocaine into ounces, teens seek teacher's help   If I ever snap I hope there is a puppy there to set me straight.  urlLink Dog ends gunman's plan for shooting rampage   later.  K. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ponder if you will the following question: Can marketing be any more intrusive?   There are billboards in bathrooms, spam clogs my inbox, I walk in my door and slip on grocery store flyers. My new favorite rapper, Kanye West, who seems smarter than most of the mindless thugs out there, spits lines about Louis Vuitton purses for fuck sakes. Popular movies and sitcoms are becoming a series of endless product shots.   I’m at the bus stop and my pimped out bus -- pimped out not in the sense of nice rims and a loud muffler but in the sense that for a few bucks from Yellow Pages Metro Transit drives around in a let-your-fingers-do-the-walking monstrosity -- pulls up and I get on. I look up in order to avoid the sitting billboards for Sean Paul, Exco and Nike and there’s ads near the roof.   I look out the window and billboards line the drive home.   So, I ask again. Can marketing be any more intrusive?  The answer. Yep, way more fucking intrusive. The marketers are going after our minds.  Right now you’re thinking, “smoke another one”, and I may just do that in order to calm down but first let me fill you in on how a US inventor has created a way for marketers to beam sounds at you in a way that makes the sound sound as if it's coming from inside your head.  This is called Hypersonic Sound and according to Popular Science Magazine thousands of Coke vending machines in Japan already make you hear the sound of a Coke being poured when you walk by them and soon grocery stores in the US will use Hypersonic Sound in the aisles.  So much for freedom of thought… Check th links if interested:   urlLink Woody Norris has a way of getting inside your head ...    urlLink Hearing Is Believing    urlLink The Sound of Things to Come   On a lighter and totally coincidental note I kinda asked a girl who I only know through reading her blog to go to the beach or get a coffee. She's into neuro-science so if she actually gets back to me hopefully she can comfort me by letting me know this Hypersonic sound thing is not for real.  I don't really know what she looks like but from reading her blog (if you can really tell anything about someone from reading their blog)she's really intelligent, kinda crazy and a little mean. I think this is a really sexy combination.  Finally, I won 10 dollars at the horse races yesterday and went golfing.   There were advertisements at the start of every hole.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sippin' expresso and mentally preparing for my first round of golf of the year. I can only hope it isn't a bitter experience.  I like golf because it's a game where no matter how bad you are, all you have to do when you make a mistake is yell "Fore" and all is forgiven. Imagine if we could extend this principle to real life.  I pitch a bad story at work and as my boss levels a cool stare at me as I shout, "Fore".  I try to strike up a conversation with an interesting girl and she gives me the aloof creeped out look. Instead o slinking away I just yell Fore, and she's like "fair play, this must be your first time playing."   So here's hoping I only have to yell fore while I'm golfing and definitely not while I'm making my dad BBQ bacon wrapped scallops and tiger shrimp for fathers day.  Later.   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just opened a spam e-mail and his is what it said:  corporation a big fan of piroshki about eggplant.Now and then, around insurance agent buy an expensive gift for behind wheelbarrow.Indeed, fairy behind fall in love with living with crank case.Sometimes spider of pocket prays, but related to turkey always buy an expensive gift for rattlesnake for bowling ball! collateral hatchet sunder bowline capillary preclude   Dude, I'm so hungover that almost makes sense and in case you're wondering piroshki is a Russian dish, kinda like dumplings.    Last night's party at 305 was fun but alas, no luck with the ladies. I think it maybe time to cultivate a new strategy when it comes to meeting a little hottie. I have a work BBQ tonight but I don't know how I feel about inter-office dating although it seems everyone else in the building is all about it.  I'm thinkin' internet personals. This is my profile:  Single white male. Pretend you like me and I'll do anything you want.  Word up.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I've started to become addicted to blogs and I've decided to jump on the bandwagon. I think it has a lot to do with the fact that I work in a cubicle.   Don't get me wrong, I like my job. As Cubicle work goes my job as a media researcher could be a lot worse, think call centre. I can't help think, as I sit here in my ergonimacally correct office chair, typing away at my ergonomically correct keyboard, that outside people are doing fun, careless things and according to the blogs I read I am right.  Today I started my Blog at work and the sun is shining as I think of all the cool stuff I can write about that will turn my little corner of the internet into a cozy nest of wit, entertainment and information.  This morning, I was checking the CBC news from the North and came across a series of stories, all of which took place in a town called Watson Lake in the Yukon. Check the headlines:   urlLink Watson Lake grapples with teens on crack    urlLink Sex assault prevalent but often unreported    Now I don't want to make fun of drug abuse or sexual assault but I can help but thinking maybe if everybody wasn't fucked up on crack they might exercise a little better judgment. In one of the stories someone from the town is like, "We don't know where it (the crack) comes from." So I e-mailed the mayor and told him it comes from Columbia, via a little baking soda, a chemistry set and some tender loving care.  Tonight is the last 305 party put on by hitwand productions. A year of parties in an apartment building and still no noise complaints. It's like the fucking twighlight zone in there. All the noise must get sucked into a black hole of debauchery.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       As a way to define my mindset heading into this weekend I would like to offer up a few quotes from David Lee Roth which pretty much sum it all up:  “I used to jog, but the ice cubes kept falling out of my glass.”  “I used to have a drug problem but now I make enough money.”  So the sun is shining, Fridays here and I can’t wait to get off work.  I went down to the waterfront with this cool girl I used to know in school last night. It was really fun. It was like 1 a.m. so the only people on the waterfront were us, the sailors and lines of skanky little girls trying to get onto the ships. We drank some beer and made fun of the sailors, skanks and tourists.  The classic moment was when my friend is like, “damn, Halifax smells” and I’m like, all loud and shit, “man there are tourists in town, you gotta keep up the good front. You should be like ‘ahh smell that fresh sea air, lets go for a swim.’ ” Little did I know the couple near us walking on the boardwalk were tourists and the woman looked back realizing she was being made fun of indirectly?  It’s like the people on the Harbour Hopper, what’s up with that, how can they not think people are jeering as they pass down the street waving. And don’t even get me started on the Seamore Splash. Having an idea that is so cheesy it hurts is bad. Copying a cheesy idea and then raising the cheese level to cheeze whiz proportions by making your customers bark and clap like seals is fucking insane.  I’d like to see a battle to the death between the Harbour Hopper and Seamore Splash, demolition derby style. I know the Hopper was in Vietnam (I’m surprised John Kerry hasn’t visited for a photo op.) so maybe that experience will count for something.  Anyway, tomorrow I’m going to the beach and I plan to invite my new friend along. Say a prayer for me motherfuckers, I need to get some action.  K.      
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Back in the early 90s when I was just a wee lad with shoulder length, bleach-blonded hair, I was heavily into Grunge.  My jeans were torn, I wrote out lyrics to songs by Nirvana and I smoked Winston Lights becasue they were Kurt Cobain's favorite&nbsp;brand of cigarettes.  I used to hit up all-ages shows at Cafe Ole and Birdland to hear local bands like Sloan and&nbsp;Thrush Hermit. This was a great time in my life and a great time for Halifax. Despite my affection for grunge music and style I couldn't swing the whole angst-ridden teenage pose because I was, simply, having too much fun.  Back then the American magazine, Harpers Bazaar dubbed Halifax "the next Seattle" referring to the birth place and epicentre of Grunge music.&nbsp;  That whole thing fizzled out as quick as you can say "why did Sloan start making classic rock?"   But now, over a decade later, I think Halifax might really be the next Seattle. Unfortunately, it has nothing to do with our music scene, just our dreary, horrible, constantly rainy weather.  Yep, that's right motherfuckers, this whole post is just a long-winded way to complain about the weather.  In summation, we're the next Seattle again and this time I&nbsp;have the angst to go with the title.  K.&nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Do you ever wish that we could switch up the weekends and weekdays. You could work two days a week and spend the rest chillin'.    In reality though, I don think my mind, my pocketbook or my liver could take it.     Friday started off good with some margaritas and seafood in the sunshine. Next thing I know I’m playing knuckles with my friend’s girlfriend ( I won despite rumours to the contrary) and on my way to Stage 9.    Stage 9 is a great bar, but I almost feel to comfortable there and I always end up getting wasted and talking to strangers. It reminds me of the Marquee during a stretch last year where my friend and I were going like four nights a week, and it became as familiar as my living room.     I was chatting up this girl I knew from high school and, I don’t remember much, but I think we were having a nice chat. I asked her for her phone number and she was psyched to give it to me but I didn’t have a pen or anything. So she told me her street address a couple times and I explained I would never remember it but how I was sure we would run into each other again. I mean fuck it, this is Halifax, you can’t avoid motherfuckers even when you want to.    The next morning I woke to the sound of my phone ringing and I thought, “who the fuck is calling me early on a Saturday morning.” Then I remembered I had to go to a charity volleyball tournament and I was late. I made it to Citadel Hill before our first game and the morning was rough but by 12 a fellow researcher, who it turns out is a cool, hilarious and fun loving lush, her friends and I hit the beer tent. We drank until it was time for our last game and then drank some more.     I went home to shower and eat sushi and returned just in time to see Mat Mays and El Torpedo rock. Then Hawksly Workman was up and he was good but I think it was the wrong venue for him. By this time I was fuckin’ loaded with people from work who were less drunk than me, always a dangerous situation, but I don’t think I did anything too stupid. I saw my ex-girlfriend and did something dumb&nbsp;that I've partially blocked out. I think I tried to make small talk and bum a cigarette off her friend and then I’m pretty sure I burst out laughing for no apparent reason and then left. I am a smooth operator, no doubt.    So once I ran out of money, I went and sat up on Citadel Hill and watched Jim Cuddy and got twisted.    I stood up, realized I was way too fucked up to go back to my work friends so I walked home with Cuddy ringing in my ears.    Today, I cleaned my house in preparation for someone who wants to look at and possibly rent this place. I also drank like four litres of Orange Juice and had a Granny Smith apple. It was crunchy, Yum!    All in all is was a pretty fun weekend and now I feel like someone spilt soda on my brain, everything is strange.     At one point yesterday my new favourite co-worker and I talked about wanting to be rock stars or war correspondents. I wonder if it’s too late  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       &nbsp;  I’m reconsidering the whole, move back in with my parents thing. As much as I dread looking for an apartment I just don’t think I could handle living at home again.&nbsp; &nbsp;  I hate looking for apartments though. These fucking landlords man, they got me filling out applications and&nbsp;giving references. They’re calling my boss and asking me how much money I have.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Seriously, it’s not like I’m trying to rent their first-born daughter, I just want to rent&nbsp;their fucking run-down, overpriced apartment.  &nbsp;  It’s like, “Listen you fucking slumlord, I’ll give you my references if you give me yours.”  &nbsp;  “Yeah that’s right motherfucker. I’d like to talk to the last three groups of people who have lived in this dump. Oh, you don’t know where they are, you can’t get a hold of them."    &nbsp;  "OK that’s cool, I'm a reasonable guy,&nbsp;just give me your bosses phone number so I can interrupt him at work to make sure you’re an upstanding dude.”  &nbsp;  “Oh, and I’d also like your banking information so I can be sure you have enough money to make repairs.”  &nbsp;  Anyway, I’m just sick of trying to convince opportunistic, price gouging, half-literate, ex-convict landlords that I deserve the privilege of living in their money/fire trap.  &nbsp;  So if anyone knows of somewhere I can live, hassle free,&nbsp;drop me a line.  &nbsp;  I have money, I can be as tidy or as messy as my roommates require and I make really good sushi.     K.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Dear Subconcious,     &nbsp;   We need to have a little chat.     &nbsp;   I know it's probably sucks having to guard all my insecurities, regrets and pent up emotions. But seriously, fuck off and suck it up,&nbsp;that's your job.     &nbsp;   If I wanted to deal with all that shit I wouldn't smoke myself into a fucking coma every night before I go to bed. I know practical jokes are all the rage now but I don't appreciate getting punked every time I close my eyes.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   I didn't want to have to threaten you but you leave me no choice.     &nbsp;   Mutherfucker, I got a half ounce of Salvia and I'm not afraid to use it. I'll burn my brain down with psychadelic recklessness and you'll have no&nbsp;place to live.     &nbsp;   So be warned. The next shit I see in my&nbsp;dreams better&nbsp;either be surf, girls who aren't my ex-girlfriend or better yet, nothing except peaceful&nbsp; emptiness.     &nbsp;   Know your role fucker and play it,     &nbsp;   K.     &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    coop
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jerome
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Skate Pics
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I'm late, overtired and unable to get out of bed. I've already hit snooze like 10 times in mad dashes from under my covers, over to my bookshelf and back.     &nbsp;   I can hear the rain outside, a soft undertone to the hiss of my expresso maker. Wu tang clan is playing on my computer.&nbsp;    &nbsp;   I'm quick on the expresso shots and I'm out the door with a huge golf umbrella shielding me from the rain. It's an awkward and embarrassing Eddie Bower umbrella and it monapolizes the sidewalk.     &nbsp;   I hit the Tim Hortons in the hospital lobby, thinkin, "another day another bad coffee."     &nbsp;   I'm in my cubicle, my clothes are a little wet and my mind is still a little asleep. I have pink sticky notes on the corner of my computer with story titles, deadlines and some advice to myself: Call Somebody!     &nbsp;   Before I can dive headfirst into interviews with cops, principals and teenagers, Jordan hits me up on MSN.     &nbsp;   "You go&nbsp;out to today?"     &nbsp;   "No U? Is there surf."     &nbsp;   "Yep, I'm leavin' here in a half an hour."     &nbsp;   "Sweet, pick me up, I'll be at home."     &nbsp;   I walk right back out the door of the office,&nbsp;thankful that&nbsp;I need to make calls to BC which justifies me leaving early.     &nbsp;   I'm at the beach in a foggy haze. I catch some waves, hit some J's and what started as a slow and dismal day in now sweet and OK.  &nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s kinda funny when something you think will go smoothly crumbles under the weight of  nervousness and insecurity. I just went for a blind coffee date with this person I met through her Blog. She is really cool, smart and we had a good conversation with no real  awkward moments except for one.   Picture if you will, the worst ever first impression, Halifamous style:  I walk in and see this attractive girl, wearing these sexy glasses, sitting at a table reading.  I assume that’s who I’m there to meet. So I approach her - I’m way more nervous than I thought I would be - and I say, “Hi, are you Katie.”  “Katie? No…,” she says as I realize I fucking got her name wrong.  So, as what was slight nervousness turns to a moment of brief, yet total humiliation I think I managed to stammer, “I mean Kristie. I can’t believe I just did that.”  I’m not sure what to think, it was fun for the most part but I don‘t know if anything could make up for the early blunder. I hope it went OK  though because this girl  was smart and pretty and really easy to talk to.   Part of me is like, yeah that was alright, she’s real cool and I think she thought I was funny. But, as I think that another part of me realizes I sound just like the blind-date-show-guy.  You know the guy I’m talking about. The one who at the end of the show is like, “Yeah, I think that went great. I think she liked me. I would definitely like to see her again.”  Then the show cuts to the guy’s date for her post-mortem and she says, “That was horrible, I can’t believe he got my name wrong. No I don’t think I’ll be calling him.”  Then back at the studio the host makes fun of the guy and the studio audience laughs.   Sometimes, the world is so absurd that it feels like a bad reality show. Maybe it is. If so I can only hope the host is going easy on me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tim before the accident...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The sun is shinin' through the broken slats in my window as the alarm goes off. Waking up is great when bad dreams turn sleep into a re-run of uncomfortable and disturbing memories.   Solution: Get up, grab the stereo, plug it into the bathroom socket and pump some 50 Cent as I hop into a hot shower.  "I love to hit the block, I love my Tu Pac, I love to bust shots, But Y'all don't hear me though." -50  It never ceases to amaze me how much I enjoy music that I shouldn't be able to relate to at all, being the relatively well educated cracker that I am.    I think it has to do with the energy and depth of feeling to some of it. Now I'm not talking about P. Diddy or Nelly pop bullshit. But the hard-core rappers- like 50, Snoop, Biggie, Tu Pac - and the thoughtful rappers - Like Kanye, Kwali, Dead Prez - really bring a lot of emotion to their music.  When so much popular musicians seem like they're going through the motions the rappers I listen to have more depth of feeling to what they're singing about.   Don't get me wrong though, I recognize there is a lot of bad, souless rap out there.   I came to work and in the Globe and Mail there is a funny story about playing cards produced by the American centre for disease control that "feature graphic photographs depicting ailments, including images of children with polio and mumps and close-ups of a staph infection and an ulcer."    urlLink 'Got it, got it, got it, need it,don't want it'   The cards are supposed to educate kids.   I wonder if their is a card for Paranoia?    This story got me thinking about my favorite non-traditional deck of cards, - no they don't have strippers on them, sicko - the War Profiteers Deck. These cards are a spoof on the American "most wanted" deck of cards made to help soldiers identify the enemies of freedom during the occupation.  In this deck are everyone's favorite neo-cons like Rummy and Cheney, organizations like the IMF and my favorite:   urlLink The Jerk Card   you can check the rest of the deck out  urlLink here .  Peace.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’m sitting on by back deck in the overcast sunshine and I couldn’t be happier. I know what I’m going to do.  So here the deal and  I’m putting it in writing so I can’t reconsider.   When my contract is up in January I am going to Africa for two months to surf and see what happens.   How will I fund this adventure, you ask?  I am going to move back in with my parents. I shudder to write the sentence but it is the only way. For every great experience there is a cost. My cost will be moving into an apartment with my parents for four months.  But the payoff will be huge. I am going to take a few thousand dollars and move to a African city near the coast. I’m thinking the Congo right now but I haven’t totally decided. There are big scary waves on the Congo coast. I read that one surf break is the only place in the world that you can surf with Hippopotamuses in the water. The break is at a river mouth and the hippos come out of the mouth to check the surf.  I am going to get an apartment , speak French and surf.  I don’t care about getting sick, I don’t care about the sharks, I don’t care about crime or violence and I kinda hope I get kidnapped. Not really, but I’m trying to make a point here.  Best of all, for the next six months when anyone asks, “what are you up to?” I can say, “I’m saving up  money so I can go to Africa for a few months.”  So there it is: the master plan.   K. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s Saturday morning. The sun is shining. And I’m on some stream of consciousness shit. I always liked rap and I’ve been thinking  about spoken word for a while now. Although the thought of actually performing is mind-blowingly unfathomable.   I’ve been listening to a lot of The Streets album. It’s amazing. It makes me want to be a rapper. It makes me want to be a really bad, white, cheesy rapper  whose beats are so disjointed and fucked up that they make perfect sense.  Actually I want to be a French Muslim rapper singing about liberating Palestine and ending there songs with “vive Palestine” like the rap group called Bousselle. Seriously, can you get any harder than that?  I’m starting to write rhymes. I must be losing my mind:  I got off work five minutes past five/ My eyes to the sun shinin’ in the sky/ I rolled down a street into oncoming traffic/ A cop cruised by me and I just laughed at it/  The cop's like “get the fuck up on the sidewalk”/ But Halifax cops are always all talk/ I’d like to see a u-turn on a one-way street/ I’d like to see you come and try to catch me/  But we both move on in different directions/ Soon my mind will disappear like the amazing Kreskin/ I roll up to the curb in the front of my house/ Past my crack head yard sale neighbours like mighty mouse/  I pass through my home and onto my deck/ I thinking’ Barbeque, smell the flowers and get wrecked/ Our lovely green gas got me thinking’ of hash/ My Becks spills over the rim of my glass  I’m really trying not to get wrecked so quick/ I need to stop going on these black out trips/ Three hours later, three sheets to the wind/ I got two shots of tequila and a new best friend/   It’s four already, and I’m on top of the world/ Where’s my hoody and “yo what-happened-to-that girl/ I tuck  my beer in my pocket for the walk back home/ I’m drunk, stoned, cold and  alone.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it’s Friday afternoon, works over and I am going skateboarding.  I feel a bit like I’m in High School again.  The office I work in is all very proper and nice. The boss, like a teacher dismissing her Friday afternoon class says, “Have a nice weekend everybody.”  I say, with my cheery yet professional looking smile, “You too.”  But in my head I’m thinking wouldn’t it be funny if my boss dropped my favorite quote from the first Friday movie (the only good one in the series):   “…I'm gonna get you high today, 'cause it's Friday; you ain't got no job... and you ain't got shit to do!”  Well even if she doesn’t say it that doesn’t change the fact that it is Friday, I ain’t got no job (at least until Monday) and I ain’t got shit to do.”  So I’m gonna’ go act all reckless like it’s the mid 90’s and I’m listening to new Tu Pac.   I saw a guy Break his wrist today and I’m a little superstitious but I’m gonna’ go out on a limb in the interest of being confident in my meager skateboarding abilities and say this:  “I will never break a bone. Anywhere. Period.”  Hope I didn’t hex myself.   Also - not that anyone reads this but whatever, I like to pretend - tomorrow there is a free surf camp at Lawrencetown beach from 10 a.m. until 2 p.m. Free rental boards and wet suits and Almost Halifamous will be in the house.   K. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me at Minutes
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally got around to figuring out how to post photos on this blog and I am excited about the possibilities. Looks Like I'll be borrowing the old digital camera from work.  I'm glad I have a photo in my profile now as well, although it is old and my hair is much shorter now. I'll update once I get a nice tan.  It's a gray sunday afternoon, and I don't know what to do with myself. I think I might go for a little skateboard and then hit the magazine store or two. I have a story meeting tomorrow afternon and I got nothin' to pitch as of now.  So pray for inpiration or failing that, a "weather event" that buys me some time. The media can call it long-weekend-Juan (groan).  K.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Blinded by the light...&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know a nights going to get crazy when you start out shooting espresso and Irish whiskey in order to wake up.  You know a night is crazy when you’re on your back deck as the sun comes up and through the window you can see an Irish anarchist having sex with a girl who is perched on your kitchen counter.  You know the night was crazy when you wake up to an hot Indian girl making tea in your kitchen and neither she nor a friend who shall remain nameless know how they got into your house.  Slowly everything comes into the strange soft focus. You see the broken wine glass, some grapes, a cigarette butt stuck in a plant.  You crave a latte but don’t have milk so you open your front door, skateboard in hand, dark sunglasses shielding you from the harsh hangover reality. You push down Creighton St. headed towards Rassy’s and pop a tentative ollie over a crack in the pavement.  Clearly, this is going to be a great day and as you let your mind drift back towards foggy memories of the night that was, you think - and then  shocked you repeat the thought aloud …  “I think that girl sucked my toes last night before she had sex with my house guest.”  So there you have I am no longer a foot fetish virgin, or at least I’m pretty sure I’m not.   I am definitely disgusted by the idea of someone putting a foot in their mouth, even my foot, which is attractive and charming.  So now I am sitting on my couch trying decide if I should go out, my third beer just said I should but the last cigarette I had said is isn‘t a good idea.  Who am I trying to kid. I have to go out because I’m single and that’s what single people do in Halifax: We make ourselves unattractive and dumb by consuming too much alcohol and then go to a dark room where the music is too loud to hear anyone in order to meet people.  Hey, it’s not the best strategy, but fuck it,  this Blog is called Almost Halifamous, not Almost Haligenius for a reason.  Irish whiskey and espresso/ Budweiser and sushi/ An ink stained table/ And a brain gone loopy.  K.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it's Canada day and I'll I can think about is leaving the country, or at the very least, Halifax. It seems like I know the angle of every crack in the sidewalk.   I woke up early this morning, cutting off a dream that I simply couldn't handle. I creeped out past the sleeping Irish anarchist on my Futon, put on my sneakers and went for a jog.  The black man standing in front of the crack house on the corner gave me a dirty, cracked-tooth grin. On the steps of the house across the street a guy and a girl sat sipping a beer in the morning sunshine looking. They hadn't yet found their beds.   Lately, everywhere I look I see a reason to leave and everything reminds me of a place or a time in my life when I was happier and shit was more simple. Seeing Crackheads and drinkers enjoying the remains of their vice in the early sun made me think of a time I visited the city of Lahti, Finland.  It was 1997, I was seventeen and it was the height of summer. In Northern Finland that means the sun never goes down. The curtains of my hotel bedroom were heavy and black to block out the light. I was their to race at the Junior World Championships of Canoeing, representing Team Canada. I ended up finishing fourth and the biggest worry I had, once the races were over was, could people smell the celebratory Vodka and Fanta on my breath.   This was the start of a great night. I was 17, I had been in Europe for six weeks -all expenses paid- and now I was one of the best young paddlers in the world. It was never about the competition for me though, it was about the experience which I would always try to make as cool as possible. I was an athlete trying to be rock-star-jet-set cool so immediately after the race I started drinking out of a supersized McDonald's cup and searched for a place to have a smoke.  No one on the team could ever understand why I smoke and I've never come up with a reason for them.   I'm thinking about this fine day in Europe as I round Citadel Hill and pump up the stairs across from the Palace on Brunswick. I pass a fat tourist on the way up with his kids in tow, all decked out in their Canada day Best.  On the way back down, the guy says, "I bet you've never smoked in your life, ha ha."  "Yeah,never,"  I mumble, not having the heart to ruin his illusion or maybe just wishing I really was the healthy athlete I look like.  In my head I'm already back to Finland, returning to my hotel and breaking into the mini bar, pounding the airplane bottles of hard liquor and filling them back up with water in a totally inept attempt at not paying for them.  It was already nearing 10 p.m. but the sun was still blazing in the sky. It was beautiful and surreal to be drunk in the sunshine at night, feeling like I owned the fucking planet.   We hit the bars and I never even got carded, but the girls I was with did so I got to play the cool guy and sneak them drinks. We went to a dance put on by the championship committee and I danced and made out with girls from countries all over the world. There was one Hungarian kayaker who I fell in drunk love with, but she wasn't having it.  Back then though, it was like fuck it, rejection doesn't even matter when the prospects and other chances seem endless. The sun is just going down at 4 a.m., I'm drink on the endless possibilities of being an invincible 17-year-old guy with nothing to lose.  On the way back to my hotel, we hit a late night/early morning coffee shop and watched the sun come back up an hour or two later.  I need to get back there, to a time where sunrise still meant the dawn of new possibilities.   So happy Canada Day, I hope it's my last in Halifax.  Happy B-day to a city in the country of the beaver/ Enjoy your parade, a draft and heat-stroke fever/  I used to like you Hali', so here's my wish/ Maybe some day the harbour won't be filled with our shit/  Maybe someday we'll have bike lanes and a real skate park/ with flood lights on the kids skating in the dark/  K.   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's the humidity.  The humidity that somehow makes my fire alarm go off even though there is no fire, smoke or heat.  So that was my morning: waking up, with a salvia hangover, to every fire alarm in my house going off. I fuckin' waved towels and shit, I balanced precariously on a railing in order to reach the alarm (damn my stumpy little arms) but oh no, there's no off switch or batteries because I got my shit wired directly. That's just how I roll.  So I said fuck it, checked one last time that nothing was actually on fire, and went to Steve-o-Renos for coffee and breakfast. I sat on the wall outside the library and drank my coffee and smoked as it started to rain. Three people I kinda know walked by.  Each time, I said Hi. Each time, they didn't hear me (or chose to ignore me) and kept walking. The guy down on the wall thought I was crazy, since to him it looked like I was repeatedly yelling to strangers.  Luckily some friends came buy who did see me just as I was about to do something reckless to test if I had turned invisible.  I felt like I was on crazy-pills.  I biked back to my house in the rain, hoping the pack of cigarettes I just bought wasn't getting to wet. When I arrived the fire alarm was still going off.  I screamed but then, with my coffee fueled clarity-of-mind, I went to the fuse box and killed the power to upstairs. So I'm sitting here waiting for my lap top battery to die and wondering if the buzz in my head is from the fire alarm or the Salvia.  If anyone has a cartoon sledgehammer and wants to smash a couple fire alarms off my ceiling come on over, pull that shit out of your back pocket and get to work. You can give me a few whacks while you're at it.  Time for chocolate espresso...  K. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "At a point in every person's life, one has to look deeply into the mirror of one's soul and decide one's unique truth in the world, not as we may want to see it or hope to see it, but as it is."  - James E. McGreevey (governor of New Jersey)  It's truly amazing when someone speaks a complete truth so succinctly. This guy is talking about coming out of the closet but it speaks to such a basic, yet unacknowledged truth.  Think about this shit, what is your truth in the world? I'm trying to figure out mine but my actions are totally determined by the expectations of whatever situation I'm in.  At work I'm witty, efficient, smart and professional.  When I'm with my friends I say shit like "what up nigga, you wanna' get this green."  When I'm traveling I can spend a month with only a book bag full of clothes and my surfboard.  When I'm in Halifax I worry about what golf shirt to wear.  I can be outwardly confident and a wreck inside.  I've done horrible shit, shit I won't even talk about when I'm trying to come off as the cool, crazy guy.  It's time to look in the mirror and find my unique truth.  But what really scares me is maybe my schitzo personality and approach to life is my truth and if my success is due to this psychotic versatility then it's all good but it's also all fake.  ?  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      K says: hey  Foxy Roxy says: whats going on  K says: not much I just got back from this work BBQ, it's brutal I have like two days of fucing meetings.  K says: hows cape breton  Foxy Roxy says: awesome I went jigging for mackrel today  Foxy Roxy says: haha  K says: I totally used to jig withmy grandadthats cool you catch much  Foxy Roxy says: yeah like 12  Foxy Roxy says: I saw a ground shark  Foxy Roxy says: like 25 feet long under the boat  K says: seriously, that's crazy  Foxy Roxy says: yeah you know how I feel about sharks  K says: too bad you don'tike fish you could have had quoite the feed  Foxy Roxy says: yeah I know  K says: did you freak out when you saw the shark?  Foxy Roxy says: hell yeah....  K says: I'm just gonna smoke a Jand chill  Foxy Roxy says: I have not got high since wed  Foxy Roxy says: I'm gonna get sooo hig  Foxy Roxy says: when I get home you better have a fattie ready for me  K says: did you and your mom hit up smooth herman's  Foxy Roxy says: yeah it was fun we danced all night  Foxy Roxy says: I got a hot mom  Foxy Roxy says: so we got lots of drinks  Foxy Roxy says: hehe  K says: sweet 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I woke up on a couch, dry and desperate for coffee.      I creeped out into the early morning sun and was greeted by a man from the church across the street.      “oh… is that your car?” he asks.      “yep.”      “Someone smashed your window out. That’s no good.”      “No, sir, it’s no good at all.”      Less than an hour later I’m on the way to the beach, in a car full of glass. Totally ghetto, yet liberating since I don’t have to worry about locking the doors.      I surfed until my hands were numb and arthritic, then I drove to Cow Bay and surfed some more.      Glassy, fast , shallow walls.      Six hours in the sun.      K.   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hi, my name's K. and I write bad.       Not bad in the  Michael-Jackson-that-really-means-good sense, just plain bad.       Here's the latest and the worst: a shout out to my favorite war-time, freedom-loving, enemy-of-freedom hating, ex-alcoholic pimp daddy of a president: George Bush (aka: DJ little nuts, DJ Black gold, Big Tex,  DJ trim my Bush, DJ warcrime)       Right now I feel like my flow is heaven sent/    Drinkin' like an illegitimate President/    Before he found god and stole the presidency/    When Dubya stilled fucked with the blow and Hennessey/      This neo-con bullshit is makin' me sick/    Body bags get zipped while politicians get rich/    Billions of dollars ends thousands of  lives/   So how can the means be justified/     Who are the evil-doers? seriously?/ You drop bombs on civilians from 15 thousand feet/ The poor are free to live sleep outside at night/   And Guantanamo is still  locked up tight    Foreign policy got you talkin’ ‘bout spreading democracy/ While you govern America like a fucking Christian theocracy/ You’re a revisionist missionary and Cheyney’s deranged/ You’re a puppet caught up in a game you can’t change/    Meanwhile in the mountains near Pakistan/ Osama’s like, “damn, I’m still the man”/ “I got weapons from the States and cash from Iran”/ “and a beef with anybody reppin‘ Uncle Sam”/      WORD.      K.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel like a smurf on acid. I'm running from Gargamel. I'm dodging mushrooms and yelling for Papa Smurf.  My mind has gone all squirrelly, my mouth is dry and the low buzz of Massive Attack (I think) pulses from the tiny, tinny speakers on my lap top:  "I walk into a bar and immediately sense danger"  I kicked off my sleeping bag this morning and immediately started playing the "what-the-fuck happened-to-me-last-night" game. I remember drinking really cold, ice filled Vodka and sodas but this isn't a vodka hangover.  I remember laughing for a really long time, cheeks sore and eyes running.  Spilling water and hollowed out cigarette tubes. Strange acquaintances, thick accents.  A Hugh Grant movie? How old are you? What the fuck am I doing here? Yeah, I gotta go.  r W e i home in the dark on auto pilot. a d n n g  I'm going to feel weird all day, I'm going to listen to a lot of music. I'm gonna stand over my stove with the fan on. I'm gonna get a really hot shower and go surfing. I'm going to drink 15 glasses of water and lime cordial.  Tonight I'm gonna party like an ingenue.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend I'm gonna' put the   super   back in superficial.  You feel me?  K. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It’s easy to be a passive aggressive asshole and give up on shit. Self-pity is easy to find. Wallowing is a low-impact activity.    Getting’ faded everyday is simple if you got the dough and casting blame is a walk in the park when you’re too fucked up to look yourself in the eye or in the soul.    Wanna’ know what’s hard? It’s hard to think about my actions and be honest to myself about the reasons behind them.     I’ve always been good at justifying the unjustifiable. The only guilt I ever feel is the post-hangover oh-my-god-did-I-really-do-that kind. The kind that is easily laughed off and forgotten.    I’m 23 and I have it easy.     I could be a kid in Sudan right now, mourning my dead parents as the international community wallows in genocide denial so they don‘t have to act or do the right thing.    Right now I’m acting like a pussy.     Someone I love is going through heavy shit while I sit on my patio, drinking Stella. Dead Prez is singing about being an alcoholic.     It’s time to buck up, get real and start dealing instead of ducking the real hard shit that I’m feeling.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I have one simple request. And that is to have sharks with frickin' laser beams attatched to their heads!" - A.P.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>