<Blog>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Or at least my toon is :)   Here is my lovley bride and myself at a beautiful waterfall where we died several times. Our application has been filed with the authorities in Jueno. So... please stop back in soon for more details on the Time and Date.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I have a splitting headache, and the fact that Jill Scott Herons band in the space below me is still on the same somg they played all day yesterday isn't helping much. The file server here at work is down so I cant acess the products files I need to create the owners manuals and users manuals for the Port Authority in NYC bus terminal. LOL, like I really want to anyway :) Anyway I guess I need to find somthing to do and play with my blog and other new toys once I get home.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As a very Fameous man once told me.   Fameous man : I don't have a ponytail and I never will, Do you know why?  Me answering : No Wyane, why?  Fameous Wayne : I own horses and I know what is under a pony's tail.  I have a ponytail despite this good advice, and my profile has been posted :)  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Probably my favorite line from the movie  Blade Runner  :) And right now also true. Spent the day today in NYC solving some issues with the paging system in the NY Port Authority. Ahh It's a job ya know? New York is great but certainly not a home for me. Anyway day started at around 4:30 with a quick sprint around the block with Tedd (my dog). Then a long slow drive up to the city. Using a Compac hand held computer loaded with audio software as a Db meter, we set out to balance the many zones and over 20 amplifer channels involved in the system based with a Peavy Media Matrix DSP. A long day indeed. It also was a pretty good day with my boss Walt. Walt can make days long and rotten, or realitively fun. Today was a lot more of the latter and only some of the former :) I would have loved to drop in somewhere and meet some game friends while in town but on a Wed. it's not very convienient. As well as I was quite busy and left straight away afterward. But I realized just how close NY is to me here in Philly, and know that I will have a chance to go up to visit soon, very soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I never really thought about Father's Day much till this year. Being I myself am not one. My own father had a standing arrangement on this day with some very close friends. My dad used to take in strays, not cats (he did that too) but people. A lot of my dad's friends thought of him as a father, and on father's day he would go with a few of these adopted kids of his and spend the day in Baltimore at the shore. My dad had an extreme love for seafood, especially crabs. Ever since I was little I remember him taking me to a seafood bar called VicMars (named after the owners Victor and Mary) in Edwardsville PA. The staff knew him due to his frequent visits, and on holidays even had a present behind the bar with his name on it. (I thought that was the coolest thing myself). As my pop got older he developed some health issues (as many of us do) and one precluded his intake of the seafood he so loved. However, once a year he would cheat on this forced diet and go with 4-5 young girls to have fresh seafood in Baltimore. This was his Fathers Day celebration. My dad passed away this past year in February. Even tho I could beat myself up for not being with him each father's day, I don't. Knowing full well he was having a great time each and every year. And there always was a phone message on his machine awaiting his return from his oldest son. I miss my dad this year, and hope wherever he is, he had his seafood yesterday. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello If you would like to see my toons Stats and Gear go  urlLink   HERE   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hiya, well this afternoon we (Triss and I ) got off to a good start on my road to 25 and the ability to Raise :) She dinged 24 and Im very close to that myself. I will prob get on game tomorrow some and solo the rest. Then we will only have one more level to go. Thanks to  Elipsis  for first off looking for a Raise for us when we were jumped by that nasty will-o-wisp, then when nobody answered switched to her WHM and came herself to do it. You the best:) More soon, have fun and  stay safe!, 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Man I just wish people would grow up sometimes. I play video games. A lot of them, but especially MMORPGs lately. In these type games there are player groups or associations.  Clans, guilds, Linkshells they are all pretty much the same. A player or group of players start the group while "in" the game, many times paying game money for the right to have their group.  They get to pick a name, and sometimes a color (as in the LS bubble that flys over your characters head in FFXI). Then they set up a leadership (mostly of friends know previously to playing) and start adding members. These groups are great for finding people to play with or get help to overcome game obstacles, sometimes. Many have a lot of Drama involved. It seems that many people carry a great deal of their personal Real Life baggage into a MMORPG. Rather than using the fantasy world to role play someone they are not, they use the time to be exactly who they are, generally no-life geeks with issues. No don't take this wrong I met and enjoy the friendship of many people met in these games that are far from that description, however, they make up a small percent of the folks you meet while playing. And it's these same people who end up in charge of the Player group. Most casual players just want to have fun, reach new levels with their toons and relax. These others spend all day and night (most don't work, or are young and attend school, giving them these nice summer days off) in the game fighting monsters and eachother. The petty arguments over who gets to kill what, and just who is better than the other is quite annoying. They will steal from you, lie to you, even kill you given the chance. All simply because they can. These same people in real life no doubt would never do these things, as it really does take a coward to do them in a video game. Think about it, they spend beautiful summer days in their bedrooms, running around with names like Chaoticgod, or some other poorly spelled and even more poorly thought up acronyms for themselves. What would you expect form these guys? Well enough ranting from me for today I have a guild meeting I'm not allowed to miss, I will spill some more soon. Till then have fun, Bleah...  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey I love fireworks...  all kinds, but especially  big ones  that go high in the air.  This is why I am really happy with the "server event" going on now In FFXI.  There are fireworks every game night all night.    
     
    
</post>


</Blog>