<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Burrito Jones  1)  Have coffee with a hottie a.k.a. Notorious Lee. 2)  Dance to Michael Jackson, preferably in a car. 3)  Go to an Oakland A's game with Stan and Leang (try to catch the A's when the tickets are $2 a piece, but if not it's still can be fun). 4)  Hot dogs, get lots of hot dogs at the game, Notorious Lee & Stan both had 4.  When we went the hot dogs were only $1, but there is a 10 hot dog limit per customer. 5)  Not only are hot dogs good for eating, but make sure you bring a camera, so you can take pictures with all those hot dogs you bought.  You'd be surprised how many poses you can get into with them. 6)  Hot dogs = Farting, this may not sound like fun for some people, but I usually find farts to be rather entertaining.  So for those of you who don't think farts are fun, make a game out of it and start keeping count because believe me there will be plenty to count.  So, basically you can have fun on a wednesday night if you follow this simple equation:  Stan & Leang + Notorious Lee + Michael Jackson + (Oakland A's/ 6 hot dogs) + steady stream of farts = fun fun fun! 

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Notorious Lee  Burrito Jones and I recently finished our “Rappers/singers come Actor/Actress” movies marathon, watching instant vintage flicks like “Love Don’t Cost a Thing,” “Glitter,” “Torque,” and just recently “Honey.”  It all started when we watched “You Got Served,” which might possibly be the funniest movie I’ve seen all year, if not ever!  I’m not speaking in hyperboles.  I think they’re all pretty interesting, with the exception of Torque, cuz they all loosely have to deal with the music industry.  So here are my reviews:    You Got Served Starring: B2k, Marques Houston, Meagan Good, the girl from that crappy Damon Wayans Show 4/4 Stars  It’s like watching “Bring it On” but with a Hip-hop dancing/b-boy theme.  Inner-city Black (and a few Latino and the token Asian) “breakin’” (I use that term very loosely) crew B2k and Marques Houston go against White (and their Punk aesthetically driven) crew from the OC for the title of “Server” and “Served.”  Like Burrito Jones said earlier, this movie took itself way to seriously (the moment where Omarian and Marques Houston are practicing their dance moves in the rain…topless), which made for a very unserious atmosphere.  Hi-lights were the HORRIBLE acting, unsolved plot twists, and overly dramatic dance sequences.  Minuses: The “Real Hip-hop” and the “keeping it real” soapboxing.  Although I haven’t seen Krush Groove and Electric Boogaloo, I often wonder how they compare to the myth making You Got Served created.  While very true that Hip-hop culture is as Jeff Chang calls (more details in his forthcoming book) a “survivalist” culture originating from impoverished communities of color in New York (and elsewhere) during increasingly harsh conservative times in innercities.  And true too that Hip-hop also has its afrodiasporic roots.  But this movies goes to say that Hip-hop is a genetic function, enhanced perhaps by geographic location… maybe it’s something in that new world water…  But I doubt environmental racism can create the dance moves necessary to “serve” someone.  In the end, the Black crew prevails because they were able to call upon their “street” mentality to fully unleash Hip-hop’s hardest dance moves.  Kinda like when Rodimus Prime calls upon the matrix at the darkest hour to save the autobots in the Transformers movie.  Lil Kim takes the side of B2K, Marques Houston, and friends and tells them in the tiebreaking moment of the dance competition:  (Dialogue goes something like this)  Lil Kim:  (whispering to Houston) I want you to keep it to the streets. Houston:  What you mean streets? Lil Kim:  Straight Hood.. Houston:  Oh… the streets…  Lil Kim:  (announcing to the crowd, pointing finger in the air) We’re taking it to the streets!! (street rules… which are unexplained and ambiguous)  Of course we all know who got served.  6th man of the year again: The Streets!  Gotta have “the streets” in your posse to get your back.     Love Don’t Cost a Thing Starring: Christina Millian and Nick Cannon Rating: 2.0/4  I have to admit, I love Nick Cannon.  It’s a guilty pleasure, but everything he makes is fire.  Or maybe it’s just the Just Blaze production… well whatever it is, it didn’t translate in this movie.  This remake of an older movie I don’t remember the name of, is about Nick Cannon making a contract with Christina Millian that if he fixes her car, then she’ll help him become popular.  The movie was just pretty boring.  Steve Harvey makes another guest appearance in a teen flick (he was in You Got Served) but doesn’t really do much.  The only thing that really stood out was Millian’s ugly greased up hair.  It looked sorta like Christina Aguilera's hair when she had it dyed black.     Torque Starring: Will Yun Lee, Ice Cube, a guy from Onyx, and bunch of crappy actors I don’t care about Rating: 1.0/4  This movie is hella stupid! I pity the foo’ that paid regular if even matinee prices for this garbage.  I feel like I’m watching Britney’s Toxic video.  Joseph Kahn is no Hype Williams, and Torque is no way close to the visual orgasm that was Belly.   But it’s really all about Will Yun Lee.  Asian bro was at least casted as the sexxxy sidekick role as he hooked up with Christina Millian for more than an innocent bike ride.  He actually used to work for EBAYC, the non-profit group I was working with earlier this year.  Finally some Asian dudes in some not-so-stereotypical roles…even tho he’s got dragon images all over his biker gear.  Ice Cube rehashes his best character… oh wait… its the same character from all his movies, Friday, Players Club, Anaconda, etc. etc. (w. maybe the exception of Barbershop).  Glitter Starring: Mariah Carey and Da Brat Rating 2.0/4  This movie was a disappointment.  I was really expecting more from Carey … but she was actually okay.  Well, okay being that they limited her lines to 5 word max sentences.  The movie just had a b-rate movie feel to it, but there were no real highlights since Mariah Carey really didn’t do anything besides sing.  1/3 of the movie was a music video.  Glitter is about how Carey and producer/dj boyfriend attempt to deal with their love amidst her new found fame and attention.   I was a little confused on when this movie was supposed to take place, but I take it was in the eighties since the music she was doing sounded like Freestyle.   Honey Starring: Jessica Alba, Mekhi Phifer, Lil Romeo, Ginuwine, Missy Elliot, Tweet. Rating: 3/4  I actually kinda liked Honey.  Like you got Served, it was hella serious… probably more serious than it should have been. Honey had the slight semblance of Served, having the bad acting, being overly dramatic—which almost made it a sure fire winner.  Interestingly enough, major themes include the moral nagging like the whole “children are the future” bit, the whole emphasis on giving back to the community, and interestingly that Hip-hop should have more responsibility esp. in the development in the areas that it came from (initially I guess).    The movie and Jessica Alba gets two thumbs up for their obviously constructed attempt at imitating the stereotypical hard Puerto Rican Latina (aka J.Loesque).  Alba falls in and out of her “Puerto Rican” sass and accent throughout the film.  At one moment she plays the stereotypical feisty Latina and the next minute she’s sorority girl.  The only time she seems to consistently play her character is when she says “The Centa,’” which is the afterschool program she teaches dance at. (Center with that supposed “Puerto Rican” english accent).  Gotta Love it.  “The Streets” makes a cameo appearance in this flick when Jessica Alba watches and learns new moves from observing Black kids at play..either playing basketball and double dutch out in the streets of New York.    Lil Romeo lacks the charms and natural talent in acting that his dad Master P had in classics “The Last Don” and “I’m Bout it.”  But it looks like he might have a chance.  Lil Romeo is supposed to be some dancing prodigy (like Honey is), but all he does is a simplified Harlem shake and some brushing of his shoulders.  But Lil Romeo won me over in the movie when he went to eat (by himself) at a hole in the wall Chinese restaurant.  Lil Romeo knows whats really good (to eat).    Oh, on a side note, stuff like this made the movie great.  In the opening scene, Jessica Alba does a solo in the middle of the club with everyone watching, and she’s starts breaking and ends up lying on the floor striking a b-boy pose.  The floor is completely clean, and she’s lying there… when would you EVER touch the floor of a packed club like that, let alone with your hands?  With alcohol, dirt, urine, and who knows what else has been tracked in, I usually wear my crappiest shoes to the club, but I guess NY is a lot cleaner than it’s been made out to be. 

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Burrito Jones  I don't get it...Why are some movies so bad that they automatically become good?  Maybe it's because these movies' purpose is to convey some kind of serious message?  Hm...that could be it.  These movies take themselves so seriously that they become funny, which makes for a great time.  Notorious Lee and I have made a list of bad movies that we want to watch, basically so we can just make fun of them.  Some of the movies are Glitter, Torque, Love Don't Cost a Thing, and Honey.  You may be asking "Why?! Why would you watch these stupid movies?"  Well, it all started with the movie You  urlLink Got  Served, which was a hilarious movie, not on purpose of course.  The movie was filled with bad acting, editing, a really bad story and of course Lil Kim (who is really not so little); this is a winning combination for a really horrible and damn funny movie.  So of course I'm looking forward to the  urlLink sequel .  Now some of these movies were not as funny as we expected them to be, such as Honey and Love Don't Cost a Thing.  I would definitley say that Love Don't Cost a Thing was the most disappointing.  You'd think Christina Milian and Nick Cannon would make for an awesomely bad movie, but unfortunately both Notorious Lee and I were wrong.  Honey was in many ways like Glitter, but it had a couple messages of morality, like "do what you can to help your community" and "children our the future."  I admit these messages have a ring of truth to them, but when you go to see a movie about dancing featuring Jessica Alba you aren't expecting them to be the major part of this movie.  Even though there were a plethora of music artists like:  Jadakiss; Tweet; Missy Elliot and Ginuwine, it still did not make this movie anymore entertaining.  If you are so bold to do what Notorious Lee and I have done and partake in some great modern day classics, I wish you good luck because you are taking a gamble.  Because you could possibly watch a movie that is just plain bad and what's the fun in that? 

						
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Notorious Lee  Man… what is it about retail that brings out people’s oddest fantasies?  I have a friend who once worked at Macy’s and would tell me stories about phantom customers taking shits in a bra cups and leaving them in the dressing room.  Although I can’t quite top that story, I can now relate to the surprise or phenomenon of these customer dysfunctions.  But ever since I started working at this bookstore, I’ve always felt that it became a safe space/place for society’s awkward (ok ok, fine, I’ll use “marginalized”) to feel a sense of belonging and ownership of themselves.  So, you’re probably thinking this place is pretty hip huh?  A multicultural colorblind society immersed in an “intellectual” shopping experience since they’re all shopping for books…right?    Wrong. ****** is a fucked up place.  The place draws a weird intersection of (sub)cultures, racial and ethnic groups, class groups, sexualities, etc. etc. …the list goes on an on.  The majority in this mish mosh of minorities seems to be those of the high school outcasts groups (no no, not Outkast, it’s not cool like that or anything) who are still stuck in that mindset some 10-20 years removed mind you, customers and workers alike.  But its not so much I don’t sympathize for those with tortured teen years, cuz I too was an outcast of sorts walking the fine line of nerdiness and offbeat coolness (kinda like the neptunes), but its just the fact that the place draws some people with absolutely no damn common sense.  Folks, people don’t go there to shop.  The bookstore sits in the “downtown” of the city I live in, which is sort of the dividing line between the older whiter community and the other side of the city, where more the recent immigrant technocratic Asian ethnic groups have chosen to settle.  Besides racial divides, there are also class divides as well.  So you get a sense of the cornucopia of people who frequent this bookstore.  Yet ignorance/being stupid knows no transnational boundaries.  I mostly work in the café, but I would say what happens in the café also occurs throughout the store.  The café caters to customers who don’t really have a clue about coffee.  The Bookstore seems to know this, and exploits this.  Rather than keep things simple, with the usual lineup of lattes, mochas, and the potential sweeter drinks, this Bookstore serves liquid candy instead.  Its drinks for those that want to live up coffee culture without actually tasting coffee.  With names of drinks and snacks that sound more like they’re coming from a drink stand from Disney Land’s Frontier Land, the café is a sucker for the soccer moms and their children.  Drinks are loaded with sweetness levels that are probably three times more than your average Starbucks drink.  So the whole idea of coffee is completely devoid from the drink. Perfect for kids and moms who don’t know any better.    So you’re probably wondering “Well Notorious Lee, what’s the big deal? You’re just a coffee purist and snob.” Okay, so that might be part of it.  But it’s really the attitudes and peoples who frequent the Café (and the store in general) that got me bugged out.  Most of the people who come to the café have a complex where they think you’re really stupid, and completely doubt everything you prepare for them.  This happens quite often when those who don’t drink coffee buy the cheapest drink.  The best example would be a cappuccino, which is purely shots of espresso with foam poured over it.  Often times people will order that, because it’s cheap and because it’s got a artsy ring to its name.  But little do they know that it’s not some sweet blended drink.  And upon serving, these fools try to argue that I’ve given them the wrong drink, or that I made it wrong.  Common questions are “Are you sure this is mine?” “Where’s the rest of it?” “My friend ordered a cappuccino, and this isn’t what she ordered” “Oh, wait, this isn’t a frappeccino?”  and so on and so on…or questions about the food in the display case..  Customer: “I’d like an onion bagel.” Me:  “I’m sorry ma’am, we don’t have onion bagels, we only have everything bagels” Customer: “No, I’d like the onion bagel in the case” Me: “uh… ok….”(too tired to argue at 9:30 am)  Minutes later after preparing two bagels for her family  Customer: “Excuse me, you forgot my onion bagel” Me: “Ma’am, we don’t have onion bagels” Customer: “yes you do, it’s right here” (pointing at the everything bagel) Me: “That’s an everything bagel.” Customer: “No it’s not, that’s an onion bagel” Me: “No, we only have everything bagels, we’ve never had onion bagels” Husband of customer: “That’s all you got?” Me: “Yes” Husband of customer: “Oh my god!” (rolling eyes in shock). Customer: “Fine, I’ll take it”  So you kinda get what im getting at.  Stuff like this happens OFTEN.  I don’t know what it is, but these customers seem to lack some sort of common sense.  It’s not so much that I feel devalued as a worker (since wage labor is looked down upon in all sectors of this service economy), but I’m just shocked at what is going through people’s minds sometimes.  I seriously think that this bookstore draws the dumbest people in the city.  And really, if you really want something to eat, go down to the end of the plaza and get some real fresh food.   Here are just a few more customer follies:  -Customers getting angry when they’ve been ignored at the front of the counter for about 30 seconds, but once you ask if they’re ready they stare at the menu, mouth gaping wide open going “uhhhh…… gimme a minute.”    -A woman who once spilled her cup of ice water all over herself and the floor, and then throws attitude at me after her accident saying “It spilled, can you come clean it up?”  It spilled?  You mean YOU spilled it, dumbass.  -Customers requesting food that we don’t carry, like croissants and pies. (this happens OFTEN)  -Customers insisting that we’re Starbucks, when we’re not.  And even after telling them we’re not, they don’t believe you until you tell them that they are connected to our competitor.  Then the customer usually asks “oh wait, this isn’t (competitor)?”       -There is usually only one attendant in the café at a time, and customers (studying) will sit around for hours at a time, not wanting anything.  Rather than not ordering something when it’s dead, they ALWAYS decide they want something during the busier moments, preferring to stand in line giving you rude looks because your making them wait.  I think they just want to stand in line just so they can give rude looks, not cuz they actually want anything.        As I mentioned earlier, the café (and the rest of the store) is some sort of safe haven for society’s marginalized groups.  The lonely (and bored) people wander in finding a sense of belonging with others who live within their own anonymity.  In addition to working out their fantasies in the bathroom, middle aged men frequent the store/cafe and try to spit their best game, when they’re really looking like a JV team at best.  Other single men arrive when the store is opening and sift through magazines and stacks of cds, and as I’m leaving at around 4pm, they’re still there doing the same thing.  Middle aged men and women looking for career makeovers study in the café for hours on end, colonizing tables as if they were the Spanish empire and hardly ever buying anything either.  So you see, witnessing this every time you work can make you a pretty irritated person.  I’ve worked in several coffee shops before, and I have to say I’ve never seen anything like this before.  Its not totally the ignorance of it’s clientele to blame, since the café is thriving off of it by making drinks that don’t even taste like coffee but more like melted butterfingers or snicker bars (sounds yummy huh? But imagine the calories….).  Yet it seems like customers like to frequent this bookstore/café to let out their innermost stupidity.  People just don’t give a fuck when they step through the door, which is somewhat admirable... but the fact they have no shame in some of the ridiculous things they do shows that they also check their brains at the doors as well.  So before walking into a chain bookstore, remember the books are just a façade of the realities and horror of globalized corporatism.  If anything, it’s more like the playground at McDonalds, but for adults.  

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Burrito Jones  Music...what can I say about music?  It has been a very important part of my life from the beginning.  Whenever my parents would tell us stories about how they met, when they were married or when my brother and I was born; they always mention a song that might have landmarked that event for them.  I guess I first realized the importance of music, whenever Stevie Wonder's song "Isn't She Lovely" would play on the radio.  My parents would always say that this song came out around the time I was born and that for them this song was about me.  Initially I thought this was the sappiest thing I've ever heard, but it wasn't until I got a little older that I could fully appreciate it.  I realized that music conveys all the emotions that people may not be able to say.  My first music purchase was New Edition's Candy Girl, well technically it wasn't my purchase, but I did convince my parents to buy it.  A lot of what I listened to was basically, what my parents listened to, which was fine then, but now is another story.  In elementary school, I began to gain my own music identity.  This identity was an obsession for the New Kids on the Block (NKOTB), which I'm not ashamed to say.  I loved them, but then again, most girls did.  I admit they were not the best music artists (and I use the term "music artists" very loosely), but hey they had some catchy songs, well catchy enough for pre-teen girls anyway.    Middle school, was all about trying to fit in.  There were some music highlights and these were usually featured at the school dances that we had once a month.  The songs featured were from artists such as:  SWV, Boyz II Men, H-Town, R. Kelly and the list goes on and on.  The middle school years were an interesting time, I was obsessed (not as much as NKOTB), with Snoop Dogg's Doggystyle, interestingly enough.  At my school if you didn't listen to Rap or R&B, you didn't fit in; in fact you were made fun of.  It was unheard to be a "rocker," and if you listened to any form of rock music, you basically kept it to yourself.  When I made my way to high school, my attitudes toward music changed.  I went from listening to Snoop Dogg non-stop, to Britpop non-stop.  My music tastes included first and foremost The Smiths/Morrissey, Blur, Pulp, Radiohead, the London Suede and of course The Cure.  And in many ways my tastes were limited as they were earlier on.   Now, it's definitely all about variety...In many ways I've taken what my parents have given me;  an R&B, Soul and Jazz base and supplemented it with Britpop/rock, Hip-Hop, Trip-Hop, and Indie (even though it's become quite trendy).    To sum it all up, music is a big part of my life and so, it will be a big part of this blog.  Not only would I like to discuss my music tastes and recent purchases, but I would like to comment on music trends/fads and crappy music.   

						
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Burrito Jones  What can I say about my experiences working at a giant chain bookstore?  Well, let me begin by saying that if it wasn't for my job I might not have met Notorious Lee.  Together Notorious Lee and I, Burrito Jones, have formed a dynamic duo, who's mission is to observe, mock as well as deconstruct the actions and the psyche of the customers that frequent the store (and also the employees along the way).  This bookstore is the place for your average high school rejects and socially retarded; they overcompensate the fact that they have no lives by hanging out there for at least 8 hours.  By doing this, they believe that they are being productive citizens who have a right to complain about the way the store is functioning or malfunctioning, and since they feel like productive citizens they believe that they do have lives (it's actually a disturbing and vicious cycle of denial).  And this just describes the customers!  The employees on average, do not rate that much higher than the customers, in that they are also quite socially retarded, ignorant, and have relationships with people out of desperation.  Here are a few words and phrases that describe some of the employees:  conservative, bigot, ignorant, Wiccan, desperate, overly fixated on Asian women, dorks, goth and stinky.  Believe me this bookstore offers a cornucopia of people that ranges from slightly functional to overly dysfunctional.  ------------------------------------------------------------- by:  Notorious Lee  "Pooping in Urinals" has arrived!  It was a long time coming, but Burrito Jones' debut on the Blog scene should go down as memorable and classic as Nas' Illmatic.  But where did the title "Pooping in Urinals" come from?  Well, as Burrito Jones has mentioned earlier, her and I work at a local chain bookstore where it's bathrooms seems to be a cesspool of people's deepest darkest (and stankiest) desires and vices.    From self-love in the handicap stall to lesbian love, the bathroom has got it all and witnessed it all.  I often manage to see the East Bay Express's adult entertainment ad section opened up or perhaps some other adult magazine (say of the Playboy or Hustler genre) lying in one of the bathroom stalls, sometimes with someone(s) in it breathing heavily at the nude shots.  Yet, nothing quite captures our attention more than when some fool poops in the urinal.  It's quite a sight seeing a dark log hanging off the edge of the pearly white porcelain, almost like Stallone hanging on for dear life in his blockbuster hit Cliffhanger.  Its really a random sight to see, and you almost can't stop staring at it.  "Pooping in Urinals" describes the oddities, follies, and social/cultural products that we just can't help but stare at and talk about.  Hope you enjoy you enjoy the random ploggings (poop/bloggings hybrid) from Burrito Jones and I, Notorious Lee.    What better way to kick off "Pooping in Urinals" then with a post about the place that started it all...Our job. 

						
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Notorious Lee   One of the perks from working at the bookstore was that they often gave away advanced promotional copies of books to employees.  You could keep them, borrow them, or use them as coasters.  In the span of 8 months that I worked there, I managed to read only two books, both having to do with the politics of the music industry.  The most recent one I read was Bling, by entertainment journalist Erica Kennedy.  Here goes my review of her novel.  Bling  Erica Kennedy Miramar Books  A couple years ago, Bad Boy records/entertainment mogul P.Ditty (formerly known as Puffy) tried (twice) to recreate Hip-hop's version of "Making of the Band" on MTV with his underachieving group of rappers generically known as "Da Band."  In what could have been a smart and sophisticated look at the politicks of race, representation, "realness" and the very technical business side of the Hip-hop industry, intelligence always gives way to entertainment.  "Da Band" and their combustible and conflicting personalities became a focal point versus the music and the show merely reinforced stereotypes of rappers, Hip-hop, and urban Blackness as one and the same: ignorant, aggressive (physically), lazy, and criminal.      Providing an insiders look at the "making" of a superstar is what Erica Kennedy tries to do in her fictional novel debut, Bling.  At times, Erica Kennedy shows how the Hip-hop industry is more about selling racialized and gendered images of Blackness.  Utilizing a recycled Cinderella story of a small town girl become R&B princess, the story also offers brief looks at how this global multi-billion dollar culture has moved from hood to the Hamptons, as well as it's influence in politics, economy, and greater American culture.  Yet, the story gets caught up in focusing on similar "drama" like in "Making the Band" further glamorizing the believed "recklessness" of the Hip-hop industry.  The main character is a young small-town woman, Mimi, who is of Haitian and Italian descent.  She is signed by a premier Hip-hop label called "Triple Large" entertainment, headed by 40 year old authoritarian Lamont, who is physically reminiscent Suge Knight physically and Ditty in terms of demand and scope of his business. Mimi's dreams of being Lauryn Hill neo-soul are quickly squashed by Lamont and his label, which see her as more of the Beyonce/Ashanti type.  The main focus is on Lamont and Mimi, and their divergent paths within the industry, providing depth to this simplistic fairy tale story.  Mimi's youthful injection in the Triple Large camp is a direct reminder of Lamont's growing concerns and consciousness of his age, image, and weight (physically and metaphorically) in Hip-hop's ageism culture, where nowadays, old-school joints of the day on 106 and Park are sometimes from year 2000.  Mimi and Lamont's constant tug-of-war relationship in and outside of the studio symbolizes more Lamont's internal struggles with his own demons.  The story surprisingly starts off quickly delving into the industry's obsession and paranoia of "keeping it real" and manipulating and constructing Mimi's identity into one that fits the label's style.  Along the way of Mimi's transformation from naive and frumpy Midwesterner to Black Hip-hop diva, Kennedy shows how Blackness is negotiated when consumer demands (White suburbia) are high.      Kennedy is on point with the critiques about Hip-hop culture's conservative conscious and showing most public communities pigeon-holed understanding of Hip-hop and Blackness.  She tackles issues of sexuality, gender, race and their significance to marketing Hip-hop representation through Mimi (and other side characters) development.  Yet after the initial commentaries, which are actually contrived and few and far between, the story quickly turns into the gossip column in Source or Vibe magazine.   Bling reads quickly at Booty Bass beats per minute, and Mimi's young career moves into fast forward with few actual glimpses of the Hip-hop industry.  The focus turns towards Hip-hop's ascendance into the bourgeois status in New York's limelight.  Kennedy shows Hip-hop now older and far removed from the "streets" of the Bronx, being at the center of fashion and entertainment cliques, yet hardly more mature despite it's ubiquity in popular culture.    Much attention is paid to side characters like Vanessa (ex-super model) and Lena, Mimi's image consultants and "friends," who are not only unemployed "paid" groupies, but also constantly obsessed with making drama creating headlines in local entertainment tabloids.  While the chapter on Triple Large Korean rapper Sum Wun's homosexuality touched upon Hip-hop issues with queer sexualities, Wun's chapter was an extraneous breather between chapters of Lamont's troubled relationship with Mimi.  And also how believable is a platinum Asian rapper' and why does he have to be gay? That's hardly a plug for Asian dudes struggling with representation already.  Like Ditty's "Making of the Band," this book is made for entertainment.  I guess if people wanted to read about Hip-hop culture and politics in an academic manner, they would pick up Tricia Rose's Black Noise for some Hip-hop 101.  But why make something entertaining at the expense of Hip-hop's already marred identity?  In "The Best Part," mc J-live said, "Look how Hip-hop grew, but it's still the proverbial sad clown of music," and despite how companies are profiting off of the culture, much of America (see Bill O'Reilly and his supporters for details) continue to believe Hip-hop is single-handedly creating a deviant society.  Kennedy creates characters that reinforce an idea of Hip-hop culture that is completely apoliticized, self-indulgent, and irresponsible.  With the exception of Lamont and Mimi, the other characters are flattened one-dimensionally without any sort of consciousness: Wild Gangsta' rappers and their entourages, overly proud R&B divas, and video groupies and hos who are all about one thing: C.R.E.A.M.      With little Hip-hop literature in broader circulation besides magazines, Kennedy's Bling is a breakthrough of sorts.  Yet, Kennedy seems to bite the hand that feeds it, by offering more negative images about a culture already stigmatized for it's gluttony in materialism. 

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Notorious Lee  Thanks go out to Mark Marcelo for letting me know about the long awaited 213 comeback… and what typifies left coast like summertime anthems.  Fresh Prince’s Summertime was kind of a universal track that everyone could vibe too… Park and backyard BBQs, summer love, water fights…, everyone knows and loves summer.  But Doveshack’s “Summertime in the LBC” (1995) made it geographically specific.  It was as F called it “feel good music,” and showed a gentle side to the gangsta’ rap explosion from that era that to me sorta humanized rappers instead of getting the feeling I was watching a movie all the time.  But besides that, it was sick ass song that made you even prouder to be from the West during a time where the LA scene was solidying its place in the music scene and slowly tearing away at the east coasts rap hegemony (if only for a minute).   West coast made summers cooler than supersoaker 200s ever could (remember the one with the backpack that you filled with water?).  But some 9 years since Dove Shacks classic, the westcoast (213) is back with “Another Summer,” production creds. by Kanye West.  This song is crazy!  Summers should be the time out from drama…like snoop says is the song “remindin’ ya’ll, put your guns down, summertime, lets enjoy ourselves, we just wanna celebrate, it’s too hot for all  that… "Stresses like school, work, studying, girlfriends, that stuffs for the other seasons…  I think I love it so much in part since I’m leaving for MI in September.  I don’t think 8 mile quite has the same appeal as g-funk and California Love.  Nobody does Summer like the west coast.  Speaking of Summer…My summer has officially started.  Last Tuesday was my last day of work at the bookstore and it ended in perfect fashion.  There were no stupid customers.  No ridiculous questions about the food and drink menu.  No racial slurs from customers.  No poo in urinals.  It was the perfect way to end my stay at that place.    I have to say, that has been the most interesting service job I have ever worked at.  This job was meant to be something temporary, something to tie me over financially until I got a “real” job.  But once I got into graduate school and at least mentally committed myself there, I felt that I might as well just stick with it.  Paychecks every two weeks are nice.  It never failed that I’ve have some story about hyper customer or co-worker dysfunction to take home with me everyday (along with the stomach aches from the coffee or food I snacked on when I was bored).  Here’s a recent one:  a co-worker one day taking an order and not making it for half an hour, but I don’t know who’s dumber, the co-worker or the customer who didn’t realize it for half an hour.    And yet while it was bad, VERY bad at times… I guess it made for great story telling in hindsight.  Memories that I will… more like, I can’t forget.   It’s a place where customers exploited customer service to it’s fullest extent, and instead of asking customers “would u like whip crème on your mocha,” I started asking them “would u like me to wipe your ass too?”  I’m sure if I really asked that, I think 90% of them would have taken me up on that offer.    But in the last couple weeks leading up to my final day, I began to lose my patience.  It was time to strike back for months of ignorance.  Instead of letting customer interactions turn into MTV boiling points where I felt like I was getting punk’d instead, I just had to question customer intelligence.  Usually I would just let out a sigh when customers could never decide what they wanted… or call them out on their inquiries about how drinks I made weren’t right.  The revolution was not televised… but came in the form of  drink with my spit in it.  Just kiddin.  But if anyone has any retail experiences, please leave some comments.  I would love to hear about more disgusting and socially grotesque customers follies  On the music tip..  Dj Fuzzylogic Bowl Cutz Vol iii mixtape hittin’ the streets (and soulseek/kazaa) soon!! Title to be released when mixcd is released.   Its dedicated to all the special people in my life who have hecka shaped my music interests.  Better than Dj Clue, FMF, and Kay Slays…cuz there is no excessive shouting! 

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by: Notorious Lee  Inspired by Burrito Jones and Ego-Trip's Rap Lists*  *purchase inspired by bookstore "employee appreciation weekend" 40% off  Current Long Play   1.) Alison Crocket-"Only One" Yam-Who Remix 2.) Lisa Lisa - "Can I Take You Home" 3.) Portrait - "Here We Go" 4.) Groove Theory - "Tell Me" and "Tell Me" Remix (one after the other) 5.) Notorious BIG - "Machine Gun Funk"  (Your probably thinking, "Where's the Hip-hop?")  My top 5 favorite albums  1.) De La Soul - "Stakes is High" 2.) Common - "Like Water for Chocolate" 3.) Jon B. - Cool Relax (more r&b..sorry) 4.) Jay-z - "Reasonable Doubt" 5.) Pharcyde - "Bizarre Ride"  honorable mention:  Slum Village - "Fantastic Vol 2." 2pac - "All Eyes on Me" SWV - "It's About Time" Lost Boyz - "Legal Drug Money" Janet Jackson - "Janet"  My Top 5 Songs that I'd like to play at a party (some again)  1.) Jade - "I wanna love you" 2.) Portrait - "Here We Go" 3.) Janet Jackson - "That's the Way Love Goes" 4.) SWV - "Anything" 5.) TLC - "Creep"  Top 5 songs that White people just can't put down (from my own  experiences)  1.) Sir Mix a Lot - "Baby got Back" 2.) Juvenile - "Back that ass up" (when everyone is all over "Slow Motion, the white folks continuously dig this 1999 booty love semi-classic) 3.) Vanilla Ice - Ice Ice Baby (they love their token) 4.) Eminem - Any of his songs 5.) Snoop - "Ain't no Fun"  (misogyny has never sounded so good to the cult of domesticity promoters..they need to take a break sometime)  Top 5 songs i hate to play at a party  1.) Lil Jon - Salt Shaker 2.) 50 cent - "In Da Club" (once at a party, i was asked 6 times to play "In Da Club," and once by the person throwing the party because people were complaining that i wasn't playing it) 3.) Paperboy - "Ditty"  4.) Juvie - "Back that ass up" (for the white folks) 5.) Snoop - "Ain't No Fun" (cuz the white people always ask for it)  Top 5 things I Hate.... period (well, maybe not hate, but don't like very much)  1.) flat AND long booties 2.) freaking (the most uncreative dance move ever) 3.) White people at clubs 4.) White people at work 5.) waiting (i feel like im always waiting...)  honorable mention  White people working at the clubs trash talking on the basketball court when the players suck  

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Burrito Jones  I just bought a cd a few days ago and it's all I've been listening to.  The band is called  urlLink Keane   and they're great.  I love it when I find an album that I can listen to straight through and not even think of skipping a track.    I would definitely compare the band to a group called Travis, but Keane definitely can stand on their own.  I have read reviews where they have been compared to Coldplay, but I personally wouldn't say that.  The only similarites between them and Coldplay would be that their music is centered around the piano, rather than the guitar and of course that their both English.   More Top Five Lists  Top Five Groups/"Artists That Make Me Cringe (not in order)*  1.  Creed (The lead singer seems to have it in his head that he's Jesus Christ or something; in every video he poses as if he's on the cross being crucified.) 2.  Celine Dion (There is really no need to explain why she's on this list.) 3.  The Backstreet Boys (mainly Nick Carter...and I'm going to throw his brother Aaron Carter in the mix because he bugs the hell out of me as well) 4.  Limp Bizkit (They're music is horrible and Fred Durst acts like he's the shit...bottom line they suck.) 5.  Yanni/John Tesh (I couldn't decide which one bugs me more...well, I put them both on there because their music sounds exactly the same.)   Top Five Songs Sexually Suggestive Songs (some being more suggestive than others)*  1.  "Sexual Healing" by Marvin Gaye 2.  "Freaks of the Industry" by Digital Underground 3.  "Slow Motion" by Juvenile ft. Soulja Slim 4.  "My Neck, My Back" by Khia 5.  "Sex You Up"  by Color Me Badd   *I reserve the right to change my lists to fit my current taste or distaste. 

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Notorious Lee  I'm addicted to ABC "Ultimate Love Test."  Stan and I have watched it together the last three weeks to cheer and critique (more often critiquing) Roy, the Asian American "seducer."  I know Asians are a much divided group over the issues of masculine representation, but i just can't cheerlead for a brother when he has no game.  As Kanye would put it, "scrimmaging" is more like it.    I was surprised at first that ABC would choose an Asian dude to play the role of "prince charming" (i would have preferred something like LL Cool J... or Big Daddy Kane type), especially after the whole William Hung thing.  Im not suggesting that they cast some stereotypically hypermasculine dude so Asian American males can participate in "normal" American masculinity, w/ Roy. Nor am I hoping that Roy's "successes" would percolate inter-racial love for the rest of us Asian  American guys, cuz Asian ladies are the best in the world.. jk, i love all ladies and they all love me. But i just wished Roy  didn't suck.  But anyway...from the get go, Roy is straight up wack.  He's hella feelin Amber (the girl who's testing the relationship), but the only thing he showin is his wallet, versus his personality.  Basically, since the show started he's gotten nowhere really.  She's said that he's opened her eyes to what she really wants...without saying "Roy."  Their body language shows no sense of attraction.  Roy's a nice guy, but it was platonic at "hi, my name's Roy." But worst of all was today's episode. Plus, he wears TEVAs.  TEVAs are for White guys, lame ones, not even trendy Metros go there.  So the couples are asked to choose if they want to continue being in the relationship or not.  And the "seducers" have their last moments with those questioning the relationship.  The seducers, Roy and CR take very divergent routes at showing their interests.    Lets look at CR: He tells the girl that if things don't work out with Frank (i think that's his name), that he'll be there to support her and that he loves her (they used to date a while back) and he'll be waiting.    I think that was prettty good, because he respectfully shows, at least to America, that he wishes them the best.  And that he's the "back up" plan if all fails.  So he recognizes his role, which is to allow the women to evaluate their feelings of their lovers. Not bad CR..but did you see the girl cuddle him in her arms to console him? HAHA!   A look at Roy:  Roy did the opposite.  Instead of showing his feelings for her, he instead tries to point out the "negative" lifestyles of her relationship with Diego.  Rather than showing that something (well if anything) has developed between them in the 3 weeks (which is hasn't) to suggest he's a better fit, he just puts Diego on blast without saying his name (which is totally inferred anyway).  Roy was into some shady business, and he seemed hella sinister just the way he put things, so intrusive:  (in a low whisper) you know you can't do these things back at home...this is what you want...you can do it... your not gonna be happy at home. (not verbatim, but pretty close).  Roy was looking pretty bad, desperately pulling out the same criticisms that he's been saying every week...Not that im an expert, but i don't think merely showing all the negative sides of someone necessarily relationally makes you look better...Roy needed to step it up.. but he was just Freshmen team all the way.  I don't think Roy was being played by ABC to play a stereotypical Asian male character.   What do the readers think?   

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Burrito Jones  If a couple feels like they need to have their love for each other tested by going on the TV show "The Ultimate Love Test," and face public as well as national humiliation, then maybe they shouldn't be together in the first place. 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Notorious Lee  Here are memorable moments of the past week, in reverse order.  Monday Nite @ Bookstore:  Family of three has about 3 minutes to decide what they want in the cafe before i finish the previous customer's order.  Line is  slowly forming.  The dialogue is as follows:  mom: Is there caffeine in the Freez (blended drink). NL: If you want to yes, but we can leave it out mom: Ya, no caffeine. dad:  whats the malt freeze? NL: Have you ever had malt ice cream at Baseball or Basketball games? dad: uhh...that comes with caffeine? NL: If you want to yes, but we can leave it out, too. dad: So what is it? NL: it's like those malt ice creams, but not as thick, like a  frappuccino dad: So it's thick? NL: No, it tastes like that, but its a blended drink mom: oh no.. not that dad: no wait, i'll try it... so it's thick right? NL: (now visibly irritated) NO.  dad: Oh .. well i'll jsut have the freeze. chocolate. No caffeine mom:  I'll have a caramel one. what are your sizes (line is slowly extending.... now 5 people in line) mom: oh... ill take the large.  finish drinks, help other customer, dad comes back  dad: (shows me a half drinken drink) umm... i noticed there wasn't  any coffee in this one. NL: You said you didn't want any coffee. dad: Ya.. but i wanted coffee in the caramel one. NL: But you didn't say that. dad: oh... ya....  NL: I'll make you a new one, but you have to specify especially after you kept telling me you didn't want caffeine. dad: sorry.  i feel like im their parent or something.  like burrito jones says, i should take their hands and slap them after they do something stupid.  Plus, with all the time to deliberate over what drinks to order and the sizes, they were unable to make a decision knowing full well that the line is getting longer and longer. hella stupid.   Go Shorty, it's Your Birthday   Homie Stan celebrates his 24th birthday, with his crew thick, 15 deep in the club.  True thug style. Happy B-day man.  We first went to Suede, sorta yuppie "swankie" (stanky) bar in Frisco.  I had a feeling it was gonna be wack upon arriving their as the owner demands that i take my head wrap off. "COMB YOUR HAIR!" The owner was bald, i wanted to say, "damn you jealous?" Males are metro as a mu'fucka, and the girls are all "ethnic."  A friend says "This crowd is pretty mixed! not bad huh?" Thinkin: "you are one of 10 non-White men here." 30 minutes later we head off to DNA Lounge.  5 bucks all nite with turntable friends like Apollo, Pam the Funkstress, and other locals?  Can't front on that!  Inside, Apollo is settin it off with the current hits, juggling "Got it Twisted."  DNA Lounge has a feel of a stereotypical club that you see in movies. Like multiple levels with people hanging and dangling over platforms and ledges.  The DJ sits perfectly in the middle of the club on the ground level.  Live feed is projected onto a 20 X 20 foot screen on the back wall. But man, serious Cult of the DJ there.  Interesting thing is mostly dudes watching the dj.   Hi-lites of DNA Lounge: 1) "Got it Twisted"-Mobb Deep 2) "I Can't Wait" -Nu Shooz 3) Few White folks 4) Girl in white on platform   Best 5 bucks spent since buying Malik Yusef's "Wouldn't You like to  Ride" 12 inch.    The Library is Down the Street  At the bookstore, once again.  There's this semi-handicapped guy who comes in all the time on weekends to listen to the music and hang out. This guy loves to hangout in the music section and listen to rap @ the listening section.  He usually ends up "rapping" pretty loud, but he doesn't get the words right and really just sounds like a bunch of grunting.  He's surprisingly one of the nicer folks that frequent the store, just cuz he doesn't feel entitled to things.. like this OTHER guy.  Story time! I'm heading back from the bathroom, and im stopped in the magazine section by this 40 something year old white male looking at Maxim magazine.. or Stuff.. one of those. Here is the conversation:  White Guy: "Excuse me, do you work here" NL: "yes" White Guy: "Can you tell that guy (the guy mentioned above in the next  isle over singing) to Shut up? I'm trying to read here" NL: (blank stare of disbelief) White Guy: (probably feeling pretty rude) oh .. umm.. well.. ya know... NL: "I'll see what i can do."  After that i just walk into the cafe and ignore the guy.  Can you believe that?  What i really wanted to say was "This isn't a library dumbass" OR "Why don't you buy that magazine and read it at home, in peace and quiet?"  Whats funny is that kids will be all up in those listening sections dancing and shouting "Jesus Walks" waaaay off tune, but nobody will say anything about it..probably cuz their kids...The guy singing was Black. I'm not implying anything....but... 

						
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Burrito Jones  One of my favorite books is High Fidelity by Nick Hornby; in some ways I feel I identify with the main character Rob.  We have the same obsession:  music.  After reading this book I began doing as Rob does and making Top 5 lists about music in general, specific occasions, songs and so on.  I believe that there is a song for just about every occasion and that music can open your eyes to many different things.  Here are two of my top five lists...there will be more to come.  My Top Five Music Artists (in no particular order) 1.  Nina Simone 2.  Doves 3.  (London) Suede 4.  Stevie Wonder 5.  The Cure  Now I wouldn't carve this list in stone because I feel that my taste has changed and it will probably continue to change.  But I would like to believe that the first three artists would remain constant and the others would definitely be in my top ten.   Nina  urlLink Simone  was, in my opinion, one of the most amazing singers and pianists.  She sang with such emotion and style.  I think that a lot of the music that is around now, is definitely lacking many of the things that Nina Simone offers.  She not only sang with emotion, but she sang about issues that were relevant to many people.  I can see her influence in many artists that are around today.  I believe that the band  urlLink Doves  is one of the greatest bands.  There are way too many bands out now that sound exactly the same and really do not offer anything special, but the Doves offer a great combination of music and lyrics that most bands could only dream of having.  The London  urlLink Suede  is another band that I can listen to over and over again.  They have great lyrics and great music.  I really don't know how to describe them, but Suede's music has many different emotions and it ranges from very powerful to very fun.  Top Five Love Songs (in no particular order) 1.  "Knocks Me Off My Feet"- Stevie Wonder 2.  "You Make It Easy"- Air 3.  "Lovesong"- The Cure 4.  "Wild is the Wind"- Nina Simone *5.  "He Loves Me"- Jill Scott/ "If I Ain't Got You"- Alicia Keys/ "Reasons"-Earth, Wind & Fire  *I know you're not supposed to have a three way tie on a top five list, but hey it's my list, so I can do whatever I want.  ----------------------------------------------- On a side note I wanted to wish Stan a "Happy Birthday!"  I hope you're enjoying your birthday festivities. 

						
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by: Notorious Lee  In their classic party anthem "Hey Mr. DJ," Zhane grooves,  "Hey Mr. D.J./You can get this started Everybody's ready to party/ All night, all night/ All the girls are  ready/So we can all get to it So we can party 'till the break of dawn, ohhhhh."   This simple song's sing-a-long lyrics (and not to mention it's themes of dancing fever that are infectiously double X chromosome) really hits it on the head about the very complexities, conflicts, and pressures that a dj deals with. It also shows how djing is very much about politics as it about gettin low.  Sat. nite, I had honor of djing with the Fat Guy crew at Club Sno-Drift  in San Francisco. Preferring Hip-hop from 1988-1995, waxin' nostalgia through the ages of  afrocentricity to ghettocentricity, the Fat Guys want to reach out to people who really love the music. It sounds simple, because it really is.  People like to go out/clubbing for a lot of reasons (I will explore more later), but for these folks, they want to hit up  people who feel this style of music because of the imprints it's left on their brains and  that really set the tone of a particular moment of their life.  But back to the party... The party was a lot of fun.  Despite the fact that the place was about 1/2 as crowded as it usually is at their events, it was still a lot of fun for me (and i think for others) cuz we played the music that meant a lot to ourselves (personally) and to the whole idea of Fat Guy in general.  But the crowd there mildly gyrated to the classic jams, with quite a few of the pole fanatics asking for 2pac, Keak Da' Sneak, and as one girl requested, "Reggae.. you know the 'dancing' reggae.. not that other reggae." That comment perfectly leads into my point.  People always try to categorize Hip-hop... from the backpackers to the more radio-friendly people...they're always trying to answer "What is 'real' Hip-hop?"  This post isn't going to be part of that never-ending debate about Hip-hop authenticity because that's so Nelson George and early Hip-hop studies. This post is more about the challenges of i guess "Hip-hop djing" and how "hip-hop" authenticity can really piss off a dj and fuck up his nite when he goes to spin at a "Classic Hip-hop" party.         Girls mostly go to the clubs and dance.  "Hey Mr. Dj" says it perfectly... to get the party started, you need the girls.  Girls love to dance... and guys will only dance with girls (well, not always.. but agree for the sake of my point) otherwise they're just "leaning back." So to get girls to dance you gotta play the "dancing music" that the ladies love.  It's a domino affect.. or chaos theory or  somethin like that.  But what constitutes the right "dancing music"?  To most, this only consists of recent radio.  When i invited people to the event, some commented "well, is that music you can really dance to?" "It's the good Hip-hop right?" or "Your gonna play dancing Hip-hop right? Cuz you can't really dance to old stuff."  So comments like that assume that in hip-hop's yesteryear, people didn't dance at all....  I've been to events where the dj has been terrible, where snares and kicks are layered on top of each other between transitions that it sounds like your listening to the song in an echo chamber.  But people hella feel the dj because he played a Lil Jon superset or he played that one song that's hot at that moment.  To the average listener, a dj's "skills" are often judged not so much by the technicality of spinning but more by if he can play the right music that will make you dance.  I'm going to loosely quote from "F" "Nobody really cares what you play, because as long as people dance all nite, they'll bemhappy.  Nobody cares if your bpms are matched up, cuz you could mix off, but if that next song drives them crazy that's all that matters."  Many of my other dj friends will corroborate with this.  And that comment is very much true.. if your the cleanest mixer, but can't play the right music, then hell ya your gonna be a shitty dj.  But depending on the venue, it's more often than not, the dj is under some extreme pressures to play to the crowds taste, to get the party started and hittin till 6 in the morning.  Which leads to some other "politics" of djing.    Partying is basically business.  Well, at least for promoters and club owners. Sure they want you to have a good time, but really, they want you to spend money on drinks.. Most probably already know this, but i'll just reintroduce it anyway.  Sometimes when throwing parties, promoters have to pay off the bar tab which can be anywhere from hundreds to thousands.  So you basically owe the bartab before you make any money at the door.  For instance, at Saturday's gig, the bar tab was 5,000 dollars off  alcohol.  The first couple parties that Fat Guy through there, they made close to 8000 dollars just on drinks alone.  that's a pretty fatty profit for them for their 4-5 hours of work.   And what is it that people want to feel? "crunk"  Lil Jon's style has set off a new style of music making that involves all the sounds that just makes you want to get angry.  But to get to that next level, it involves crunk juice...y'know.. the alcohol to really set it off.  People always seem to say that "oh i need alcohol to really be uninhibited." or "I'll dance once i have a few drinks."  So in essence, its really "not" all about the music....  Cuz i think if it was all about the music, people wouldn't really need to feel loaded up on alcohol as much as say a major club party.  Well, okay.. fat guy did make quite a profit at the other parties tho... right?  True.  They're parties have been off the hook. But take San Jose's Agenda as a perfect example.  Agenda was the spot last summer for less than a minute.  The promoters on thursday nite through a party called "Stank" which would bring in some of the most famous djs and music producers in Hip-hop's past and present.  And their music sets were often the umbrella term "old school Hip-hop/Classic Hip-hop."  I went to the first one with Questlove and that one was fuckin  ridiculous.  I had to wait in line for over half an hour and every level and area of the place was packed.  I mean, damn, everyone there was having a good time, and the girls were hella coo too!  I didn't get rejected once!  But the hype slowly died afterwards.  From what I heard, even with Pete Rock and Mr. Choc, the place just wasn't packed.  I went on the last nite, and it loosely packed with b-boys forming circles and girls in j.lo hats.  It looked more like a middle school dance more than anything.  But what is noticeable is that neighboring clubs started with new parties too which played more current jams.  In addition these folks were all in dressy attire.. meaning they probably have $ or faking that they have $. Maybe "classics" just doesn't have the staying power.. but I think it's the lure of a certain style of music that really sets everything off on a larger scale...  So to be a dj on a bigger scale often means a lot of politicking.  Not just "skills" but thinking about the girls and future gigs...its the common story about "selling out." When i first started djing, i was helluva a backpacker, and when people asked me if wanted to dj their party i said "oh, i only play underground, and im not into that sort of thing."  Then of course i realized the perks of djing, ya know.. money, cash, h**, and i only bought radio compilations... but i mean, if i had it my way NOW, i'd be playing neo-soul and jazzed out Hip-hop (mainstream or "underground") all the time, playing the likes of Allison Crocket, Dwele, D'Angelo, Cooley's Hot Box, and such  Being a dj, at least in a club, is really not as glamorous as it seems.  It's fun when girls are throwing themselves at you after you play some of that "dancing" reggae (versus the "other" reggae) and when people are have a great time humping the magic stick  (the poles) too.  But djing can often mean sacrificing a lot to expose sides of your music  tastes that are usually unheard... then there is always the potential threat that the folkers aren't feelin your vibe.  Im not just talking about not getting to the club before guestlist ends, but there is always a price to pay for having fun on the promotion side of the party.  So heres my advice for you aspiring djs: Don't quit your day jobs. 

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Burrito Jones  These past couple of weeks Notorious Lee and I have seen many movies; some good, some great and some just okay.  But all of the movies definitely had their moments and if anything they were at least entertaining.  We saw Super Size Me, which was a very interesting movie.  This guy decides to document his 30 day McDonald's food binge.  You may be asking why someone would do such a thing, but basically he wanted to see what was behind all of the lawsuits against McD's for people's health problems as a result of weight gain.  I remember when I first heard of people suing McD's for their weight gain, I seriously thought it was the stupidest thing I've ever heard.  After watching the movie, I thought there was more of a basis to these lawsuits then I initially thought.  Everyone knows that McDonald's is bad for you and should be avoided as much as possible, but it's amazing to see how it really effected this guys body.  Granted, he did have McD's for every meal for 30 days, but still, he went from being beyond healthy and in above average shape to someone who's liver was failing him, as well as having other major health concerns (excessive weight gain, high blood pressure, etc.).  I would definitely recommend checking this movie out, it will hopefully change some attitudes about McD's...even about their Chicken McNuggets, which are gross because of how their made, but they taste oh so good, especially with the sauces.  -I'd watch in on video, at the cheap theatre in Milpitas and probably matinee.-   Next movie was I, Robot, or as Notorious likes to call it...I, Bot, which starred Will Smith and a whole bunch of robots.  Let me start off by saying that I had pretty low expectations about this movie and I was only willing to see it during matinee.  Since, my expectations were quite low, the movie actually wasn't as bad as I thought it was going to be.  There were some interesting twists and turns.  But the most interesting and random turn was at the beginning of the movie when Will Smith is taking a shower and they totally show his booty.  It was hella random and kind of weird.  I personally didn't want to see his booty.  Well, the basic message of this movie is "You can only trust robots as far as you can throw them,"  which isn't that far because they're pretty damn heavy.  On a side note, I agree with Notorious in that this movie would have been so much better with some robot lovin'; a little robot porn would have been great!  -Save it for video or the Milpitas theatre, unless you really like robots, but there's no robot sex, so there is no reason to really run out and see it.-   We also saw Harold and Kumar go to White Castle, which was one of the best movies I've seen in a long time.  So if you haven't seen it yet you should definitely check it out.  The movie stars John Cho (Harold) and Kal Penn (Kumar); Neil Patrick Harris does a cameo appearance.  The story follows Harold and Kumar as they try to satisfy their munchies by having some White Castle burgers; which I'd personally like to try, they're so little...I bet I could eat a whole bunch of those things.  Well, anyway, they're search for a White Castle takes them into many interesting situations ranging from a guy covered in boils, who is affectionately called Freakshow to Neil Patrick Harris on ectasy, a bunch of white dudes who are obsessed with taking things to the extreme and Kumar romancing a huge bag of MJ.  This movie is great, I also liked how the movie dealt with many different racial issues, they definitely confronted them in a very humorous way.  It was very refreshing to see a mainstream film that's two central characters were Asian American.  Definitely check it out.  -See it anytime, price is really no object.  Also, buy it when it comes on DVD.-   Next on our movie adventure was Shrek 2 which was great.  The Cinelux theatre in Milpitas is great because you can watch movies hella cheap and even cheaper on Tuesdays ($1.50!).  Shrek 2 was really funny, I actually liked it better than the first one.  The best part of the movie was the seen with Pinocchio and trying to make his nose grow.  Puss in Boots was pretty funny as well.  Bottom line it was a very funny movie and it was worth every cent, every $3.50 to be exact.  -Matinee or Milpitas-   The Village was a movie that I really really wanted to see and I was very excited about it.  I heard varying opinions on it many saying they didn't like and others saying they liked it.  So I kind of lost some of my initial excitement, but I still did like it.  It wasn't as great as I thought it was going to be initally, but it was a very interesting concept.  This movie defintely had me thinking and I have some ideas, but I would just give the movie away if I discussed them.  I would recommend this movie, but don't go into it thinking that it's going to be hella scary because it's not.  I think a lot of people were disappointed with this movie because they were expecting to be scared and to just be entertained, but instead M. Night Shyamalan made them...god forbid...think!  -Check it out at matinee, but it's not a loss if you pay regular price.-   The last movie that Notorious and I saw Maria Full of Grace, which we saw today in San Jose.  This movie was great, it was very suspenceful.  And it definitely puts a face on the plight of the poor and what risks people are willing to take when it comes to survival.  Maria is the main character who is only 17 years old and is working in a flower plantation in Colombia.  These flower plantations are basically slave labor.  The plantations were set up by American companies, which were comissioned by the U.S. government.  They hoped that these flower plantations would fight the war on drugs, but of course our government is quite stupid, so rather than thinking the problem lies within our country, they are trying to fight it outside our country.  So as we all know the "war on drugs" is doing absolutely nothing and will continue to do so, until our government realizes that it's all about supply and demand.  And drug dealers are just supplying America's insane demands for drugs...whew..that's enough of my rant on one of many problems that our government doesn't seem to have a grasp on.  Well, anywho, the movie was great and definitely humanizes the people who are exploited at the expense of drugs and money.  -See it anytime...good movie, definitely will open your eyes.-  On a side note I finally bought the movie Rushmore on DVD.  This movie is great, if you have the time you should definitely check it out.  If you liked the Royal Tenenbaums then you'll like Rushmore.  In some ways I think Rushmore is better.   

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Burrito Jones  Looking for something fun to do the last weekend of July in Fremont?  Well, then the Fremont Art & Wine Festival is the way to go.  If you go expect to see indecent exposure from women young and old, white folks nodding their heads and "dancing" to some lame second rate rock group, crappy "art," over priced food and more!  If you like to poke fun at the ignorant, white folks, scantly clad and posers, then the Festival is the way to go.  If you don't like to do any of these things then there is really no point in going.  When first arriving at the Fremont Art & Wine Festival with Notorious Lee, my expectations were really really low.  When I think of this annual festival, I think it's basically an attempt for Fremont suburbanites to feel like they have some sort of appreciation for the arts.  But in reality, it's just an excuse for people to drink in public and dress as ho-ish as possible.  After the first few booths everything started to look the same.  The "art" as they call it are basically a bunch of random-ass crafts.  I seriously could start building houses out of popsicle sticks and sell them at the festival.  We met up with Stan and Leang, not too long after we got there, which was great because we could show them all the hos and stupid folks we saw earlier.  I would definitely say that the highlights of the festivities were of course people watching, funnel cake (even though they ran out of strawberries), just spending time with friends and the kettle corn (which is worth every penny). 

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   by:  Notorious Lee  Over the past weekend, Burrito Jones and I were accompanied by Stan and Leang to Fremont's annual Art and Wine Festival.  It is definitely the "festival" season, with the now World Renowned Gilroy Garlic Festival recently passing.  Upon parking my car and seeing herds of young white girls stuffing tummies into daisy dukes and their equally White male friends overly stuffing their wife beaters with overly muscled shoulders and arms... i knew this wasn't going to be "artsy fartsy" and hardly class, but trashy.    In actuality, Fremont's Art and Wine Festival resembled a fraternity/sorority mixer more than anything.  There were several Beer/Wine fountains located throughout the festival, with fraternity/sorotity-esque types (mostly young White people) congregating in those areas being loud, obnoxious, Ho, rude, and HARDLY stylish.  Here is Stanley's commentary:  "There are a lot of ugly people here."  Stanley was on point.  I don't need to see moms walking around in tight black tops with revealing pink skirts and their 10 yr old child trailing behind with his new homemade helicopter toy.  And people wonder where family "values" and "morals" are...    In addition to the ugly Fremont company, the whole art "festival" thing that suburbia gets down to during the summer is just weird.  It's almost like a sort of turn back to clock to easier times, pre-industrialization, pre-dot.com, pre-people of color movin' up and civil rights.    I took a Literature class when i was in UCSD and in one lesson, the prof. talked about how "nostalgia" and longing for the past works to celebrate racism.  Sounds crazy right...?  I am obsessive over race to the point of paranoia...but really it makes sense.  Just think, when we think of innocence of America's past.. we think of a lot of decades.. pre WWI, pre WWII, pre vietnam war. BASICALLY pre any war.and really America was (and is) ALWAYS in a state of racial conflict, disorder and turmoil.   America lost it's innocence when Columbus set his foot here.. so really, when we get nostalgic we think of White folks havin' a good ole time... baby booming in the suburbs buying appliances for their new homes and shit. we hardly think of a colorful society holding hands on the we are the world tip, do we?  So anyway.. im getting to my point.  These festivals seem to remind us of small-town USA, of simpler times when people had their independent businesses/trade where people could earn a living off their services and selling of worthless trinkets. I mean... who really wants to or dare wears or EVER wore tie dye shirts and ties?  Who would really spend time to make shirts that they thought people would want to buy?you guessed it...  WHITE PEOPLE  Most people who are selling things at the festival are white folks too!  It's like the one day out of the year that the city celebrates its Whiteness in full force..and it's totally ok for them too.  It's like White folks affirmative action.  Maybe like a reaction to being segmented by techno-savvy immigrants in the work force or outsourcing. So all these white folks with weird hobbys emerge, showcasing their odd "talents" in hopes of making a few bucks. And all the White folks come out to party too, having a great time enjoying their "all Americaness" (aka Whiteness) together. See how the nostalgia works???   It's racist!   White pride under the guise of our appreciation for fine art and palatable alcoholic beverages.  As Burrito Jones says:  Its the one day in the year where Fremont participates in "multi-culturalism" (she said this sarcastically).  Yet, coincidentally... the Indian cultural festival later in the summer also located on the same block, is heavily criticized every year by Fremont dwellers (im assuming it's the white folks).  Though I haven't attended the festival in quite some time, every year, city officials complain about the overwhelming trash and chaotic-ness of the cultural fair.  And while city ordinance require the sound levels to be turned down after 9 (or maybe 10?) due to neighboring residential areas, only in the past year or two has there been housing built within .5 a mile from the area.  There is an unfair amt. of people of color bashing going on this city!  Partying is a past-time that knows no cultural or say nationalistic boundaries, so why not let all people act a fool?  Whut does Burrito Jones have to say about this...? 

						
</post>


</Blog>