<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can anybody tell me why the hell it takes so long to set an identity insert property to false? It is 5:30 in the morning and I am about ready to launch a server over the balcony onto the parking lot. Have a nice day.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      At the commencement of next year' s hockey season, this blog will be the source of many great Vancouver Canuck bashing posts along with praise for the fast, determined and exciting play of Espn's number one bang for your buck sporting organization on the planet, the Edmonton Oilers. Trolls are very welcome here. Bring it on Knucklehead bandwagon jumpers so we can enjoy the inevitable demise of the Vancouver Canucks together. As the number of the few quality members of this delinquent hockey club dwindle due to self chosen exportation and crimianl acts, I find it hard to contain my excitement for a year that will see the Canucks return to sub mediocrity at best. See you all in October.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      With the many big name free agents out there not expected to move from their respective clubs due to the inevitable and very disturbing lockout, one name that should capture the attention of genius GM Kevin Lowe is Jason Allison. The big Ontario native did in fact miss all 82 games last season due to post-traumatic migraines but here is why I truly believe he will be a perfect fit in Edmonton. First of all, everyone who follows this dynamic, exciting sport franchise knows that we are in desparate need of a number one centre. Moving Ryan Smyth out of his normal position at wing to fill the void at centre did without question hurt his numbers early on in the season. Allison would be a huge presence in front of the net and in the corners and is great at banging home rebounds and cycling the puck which will give the Oilers another capable body other than Smyth to provide offense in that manner. Secondly, we are on the verge of losing the services of the very talented Petr Nedved, along with all of the points he puts up on the board, especially on the power play. Big number 41 would replace all those points and more as he is definitely a 100 plus point power forward. JA was recently left unprotected by the Los Angeles Kings as they obviously felt a little uncertain about his medical condition and his future in the National Hockey League. You may ask why the Oilers would want to take a risk with an individual with such a dangerous and career threatening ailment but here is why. We have recently been taking risks with players such as Oates and Nedved so why stop now. Besides, Oates and Nedved do not possess the talent or offense of the younger, bigger and stronger Allison. Lowe could laden Allison's contract with incentives based on games played and/or point production which will produce a no lose situation for the hockey club. Things didn't work out as planned with Adam Oates but I believe things will pan out in this case. Jason has never been an injury prone player and if he can fully recover then he could be the key in placing the squad in a position to do some serious damage in the North West division and the Western Conference. So with all of that said let us as Oiler fans hope and pray that Kevin Lowe will give some serious thought and put some serious effort into the potential signing of big number 41, Jason Allison.   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man I hate this team!!!! If they take Nedved from us I am going to snap. I hope Bertuzzi gets sent to jail for life in a nice little facility in Siberia. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>