<Blog>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    We are one FINE Couple!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you ever asked yourself that question when it comes down to where you are in life? I know that I have. Shew, I use to ask that same question over and over again. I know I'm more talented than the things I'm accomplishing, I know that it can't just be this, I know that there has to be more out there. Out where I guess. So, anyway, to make a long complaint short, I run into this cat that I ain't heard from in forever. He starts telling me about all these things that he can do for me. He can heal my pain, he can protect me from more disappointments, he can help me find my purpose in life, and all this other crazy nonsense. At first I'm skeptical, but the more he talks about all these things he can do the more I'm getting into it. Now my thoughts shift and I'm thinking more along the lines of, "What's the catch?" There's always a catch to something like this. Then he drops the bomb on me and tells me what I need to do. He tells me that   all   I need to do is surrender my life to him. Let him take control and just do what thinks is best. Now I'm starting to see just how crazy this fool is. He thinks I'm going to let him take control, then I'll be miserable forever. How could he possibly know what would be best for me...Like he CREATED me or something. So I told him to get out of my face and that he was full of it.  Well, needless to say, he kept on pursuing me. Its like he just wouldn't quit. The more he talked about all he could do the more I realized how miserable I was becoming. Every decision that I made just brought further frustration and more unsatisfaction, but he wouldn't quit on me and kept offering what he had to give. It slowly began making more sense and one night when we were in Memphis, at a conference together, I told him that I would do what he had been asking me to do. So that night I surrendered my heart and life to my friend Jesus Christ and he has fulfilled every promise that He made. I am satisfied, successful, joyful, at peace, and on my way to fulfilling the purpose that He created me to fulfill. It hasn't been an easy road, but just like He promised, He has yet to fail me.  Turns out He did create me and He does know what fulfills me. Matthew 6:33   "Seek first the Kingdom of God and His righteousness, and all these things will be added unto you."  
     
    
</post>


<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Here is a couple of thoughts that I wanted to see what you guys think. Bluntly I have been thinking, and getting annoyed with, multiple worship services. As of right now I am not sure if they have any good use.   Here are a couple reasons off the top of my head.  1. How many sermons do you actually learn from regularly. Me only maybe one at most. The majority of the rest of the verbage given on any given service is lost.  2. How does multiple services actually serve our cell groups and their leaders?        - Lets dig into that a little bit more. If our cell leaders are supposed to draw their group to authentic Biblical community, to worship, and to multiply, how then does stressing them to at least three events a week, two at least that have nothing to do with their cell groups, really support those goals. We have a regular business man working (at the very very minimum) 40 hours a week. We then add two services (wed. and Sun, and possibly even saturday) then throw in a ministry within the church they are asked to help with (this all besides the ministry time we want them to have with their cell at least once a month). I just think its insane.  3. Our church loves Ralph Neighbor, right? Well even he sayss that you can't have a two winged bird (in his book "Where Do We Go From Here?"). Neighbor says you can't have a church desiring to carry on a program based church (one that exists to support the services orientation of having a church building, programs, ministries, and multiple worship services), and one that is trying to spread the Gospel through its cell groups. I don't agree with everything Neighbour talks about, but on this point I think he is right on.  Not only does the "Two Winged Bird" mess with the cell leaders, I think it is also messes with leaders. If you have all your church leaders tied up in different worship services and investing so much of their time and talents in that, the leftovers are what get passed on to the cell leaders looking to them for investing.  So tell me if I'm wrong. 

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Rain and wetness gone-- Summer brings joy to faces Keeping people near 

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Are you a thermometer or a thermostat?   In other words... Do you reflect the environment around you or do you set the environment around you? 

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Anybody noticed yet that we live in the birthplace of jazz and there are virtually no churches that capitalize on this? Any ideas as to why?   urlLink .  

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ever since we first talked about having a group of guys talkin of good ideas and good stuff I have had a working title I refered to it as. It spawns out of our simple affection for the Chicken Box chain, and our brief conversation about how they started. Since that time I have always referred to hanging out with you guys to my wife as the "Thinkin Box" group. I thought it worked well. A Box could substitute as a tank I think. And if you slang "thinking" to "thinkin" you got a good replacement for chicken. I just it kinda rung true.  So I hereby submit this simple name for our "tank" of thinking. Tolkien and C.S. Lewis had their group, we have our Thinkin Box. 

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Is Jason a Reformed Calvinistic Predestinationalist? 

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Guys, I found the following information in the book The Search to Belong. Peep it out. The term "proxemics" was coined by a researcher E.T. Hall in 1963.  ------------------------- Public- Public belonging is experienced when we connect through outside influences.  Social- Social belonging is experienced when we connect by sharing a "snap-shot" or hint of what it would be like to share personal space/belonging.  Personal- Personal belonging is experienced when we share private (not naked) information, experiences, or feelings.  Intimate- Intimate belonging is experienced when we share naked information, experiences, or feelings and we do not feel ashamed. -------------------------------  Implications for Church Life  Public- Our worship gatherings are the public space for our community.  Social- Our church family fun activities provide our social space.  Personal- Our small groups are the venue for personal space.  Intimate- One-On-One mentoring is our intimate space.  ------------------------------  What do you guys think??  

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I can't believe that some people actually steal inside of a church. Have we lost our ever loving minds that we think that we can steal from God's house. Hello, does Ananias and Sapphira ring a bell to anyone? Have people lost the respect and fear of the Judgment hand of God? I think God needs to wipe out a small group of people, like Hollywood, with raining sulphur and Benzoate Acid just to remind America that he can take us out at anytime. This will remind people, that "HEY, YOU CAN'T STEAL FROM GOD, HE SEES YOU!"   I'm sorry, too much coffee this morning. 

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Jason, this is Randy.  I got your message and now I'm bloggin.  So far I think bloggin is pretty cool.  It is fun to blog. 

						
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The think tank group known as Manley, Randy, Mike and Jason now has an online presence. This is where we will publish some of our ideas for comments and critique.  Keep coming back for more updates. 

						
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Many people are fed up with the mega-church model.  The concensus is that the house church movement that is so effective in some other cultures will not be effective in America.  Cell churches are similar in structure, focusing on community rather than the individual.  Our culture is too individualistic for these models.  More people seem to think that a somewhat program based church with cell groups/small groups is the way to go, but that lends itself to the mega-church model that they were fed up with in the first place.  What should we do?  Should we combine some of these models to make a hybrid, or should we come up with something totally new, unique to our culture?  I know there is a good balance somewhere that will be effective, but to my knowledge no one has figured it out yet.  That's where you guys come in.  What do you guys think? 

						
</post>


</Blog>