<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    San Diego
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Las Vegas
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    California Science Center
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, Xuefeng and Heidy went to the airport with me actually. I asked them to correct my driving on the way to LAX. They said I drove pretty smoothly and they were amazed about our acoustics system. :) We had a traffice jam and see several minor accidents. It took us 50 minutes to drive there. I talked with the manager of united airline to let one of us into the terminal to help the old lady, smi' mon, for she does not know any English. I was chosen to be the person to get in, because Heidy and xuefeng did not take their photo ID. But the problem here is that I do not even know smi' s mother. After molesting a dozen of Asian mums in the terminal, I gave up. Because it is already 9:50 and the plane was supposed to arrive here at 9:30 (it was late, the origial arrival time should be 9:17). I gave up and exit to the baggage claiming area. Fortunatly, we found Smi' mum around 10:10 pm at the baggage claiming area. Then we knew that the plane was additionally late for thirty minutes. We standing at the baggage claiming area and talk. You know we saw whom? Davis, the Ex- governor of California, standing just 1.5 meter behind us and waiting for his luggage. We were so excited. hehe. Although I hate the hypocritical gesture of this governor, I can't help recognizing the difference between a Chinese government official and this one in front of me...It was very crowded around Davis. So I just took a hike else where and found a luggage cart....When we leave Smi's mum at the new portal, it was 11:50. We went to Heidy and Xuefeng's home to have some water melon... They told me they will go to SF today to see xuefeng's parents, who is visiting xuefeng's sister in SF.
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The other day, Hui came to the apartment. She said it was wonderful if she could have a place like this to live with Kecheng. Yes, it is roomy, confortable, and self-sufficient. I feel so at home when I came back this afternoon and take a shower. All the stress and unhappiness just disappeared without any trace. Hui described about the apartment to Zhou Ying when we eat "Zongzi" Dumplings yesterday for the "Duanwu" festival. She said it was a fabulous place. I can not imagine how "fabulous" it will be if I have sufficient money to buy some furnaturs for this place.   
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been always wanted to visit this great city, the capital of all capitals of human kind. All though it was not as diverse as Los Angeles in demographics, I suppose it is the most diverse city in economics, politics, and last but never the least, fine art. Just as some people said, it is just like a big apple pie. You can find whatever you want there. The skyline of New York City will be a permanent memory for its beholders, just like the statue of liberty can be the life time symbol of freedom for those immigrants on the Ellis island decades ago. I can not imagine how Louise Thomas sitting at his working desk in his office beside the East river pondering about life and society. But his view in the 70s can be one of the most refreshing and instructive for my life. I think it must be so exciting to be albe to see such a big city stretching out with concrete and steel, moaning, breathing, and egesting with the heart beat of this planet.It might be a skin cancer for earth, but I have to say it is the most amazing wonder mankind has ever acheived in history.   There should be numerous attractions in NYC. The place I wanted to go most is the Greenwich village. "The last leaf", a short novel by one of my favorite writer, O Henry, should have its setting at this place. All though with its world fame and commerciallization, I am not sure what kind of change has been made to this Mekka of all artists. Lots of O Henrie's novels have the setting of New York City. He wrote about wanderers, robbers, thieves, beggers, and non-entities just like me. "The gift of Magi" is one of them amongst my favourits. It was my bona-fide version of love for years, a true westernized version of "xiangru yi mo" .   So much about NYC.    Up north and up the river of time, is the age of Jack London. It was a time of interdepence of man, women, and dogs. It was a world of harsh weather, sleds, starving wolves, pine trees,freezing creeks, and remote towns. It's an impressionism master piece of how cruel nature could be and how passionate love could be. ... ....I read these novels again and again when I was young. I kind of assimilated by it and tried to live by these codes. The love sometime was not so refined, but you can feel its heat, truethfullness with your heart. . . . The man and women on the Yukong river.....   ..........   Down to the south, my first impression about the South part of United States is from the TV serial: "Nv Nu" and the  macaroni " Leon xiu". I touched the heart of Southerners from the ball parties of gone with the wind at the twelve oaks, the cabin of Uncle Sam, the hilarious stories of Tom Soya, and travellers on the southern rivers. Now, lots of black people have moved back to the southern part of united states for the same reason they left there more than 200 years ago. It seems histroy is repeating itself in a unperceptable, subtle way....     ..........   I made a wish tonight...                 ..................                        
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      06/18/04
    
</post>


</Blog>