<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Welcome to my first "MOVIE ina MINUTE" review! Since the summer movie season has begun, I am taking it upon myself to be your personal movie "critic" - not because I have ANY idea what that means, but because I LOVE flix and I see a lot of them...!   My first "MIM" is "Dodgeball", Ben Stiller's follow-up to his other hits like "Zoolander" and "There's Something About Mary". I saw it not once, but TWICE!  (Not because I WANTED to or it was THAT good, but the first time I went with my bro, then I had a date with a NEW guy - 'coz I just broke off a relationship with another guy - and HE hadn't seen it, and... wait, this could be a whole OTHER post!)   Anyway... The premise of the movie is that Stiller & Company,( a bunch of narcissistic athletes) must defeat a team of underdogs at a National Dodgeball Championship in order to win their gym.  There are a lot of different characters involved in this plot, but the main focus is on dodgeball itself.  Yeah, I know, we have ALL played this in phys-ed, but it is not REALLY considered a sport... (Do you know anyone with a Varsity D-ball letter???)   My parents said that it was the number one after-dinner neighborhood game when they were growing up (and a real chance to infict some serious damage on someone you didn't like...) I don't know - maybe it would be worth a shot at a beach party.  All in all, I would give the movie a "B-"; although I found myself laughing even when the jokes were pretty lame. My bro AND date laughed themselves silly - so I guess I would say this was more of a guy movie than a chikkflick...  But I get to pick the next one - let's SEE them laugh their way through "Arthur" - the remake of the Camelot tale!   That's "Movie ina Minute" for today!  (Drop me a line to tell me what YOUR fave Ben Stiller movie is!!!)   
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Not if my mom has anything to say about it - my driving, that is...     The end of an almost 16 year wait is coming; I start that supreme right-of-passage, "driver's ed", next month! FREEDOM! ROAD TRIPS! YES!     But wait - what are those OTHER words that keep coming to mind ?! GAS!INSURANCE! NO! It seems that the pure joy of getting my license and finally being mobile on my own is being tinged a little by the reality of the responsibility that comes with it.   Hey, my parents said that gas was 35 cents a gallon (!) back in the Ice Age when they got their licenses.  For two dollars, they could drive to Boston and back (well, maybe Old Orchard Beach), and still not empty the tank - what's up with the $2 plus today ??? I would have to babysit my cute (but bratty) younger sisters for almost 8 HOURS just to fill the tank...! And if history repeats itself in my household, as it usually does, I WILL be paying for my own insurance, like my older bro does. And since he has had a few, um, minor "infractions" since getting his license 5 years ago, I think he has to sell his blood to make the payments...   But that was him - I am going to be a MODEL driver: no speeding, no talking on the cell to my friends during rush hour traffic, no fixing my makeup in the rearview mirror,(Mom...),and no loud, distracting music... OK - I can dream, can't I ???   Seriously, though - I have waited FAR too long for this chance to blow it! I am gonna try my best to obey the "Road Rules", but just in case I am practicing  my most sincere line: " No, Officer, sir, I really, REALLY didn't know I was going a teensy bit over the speed limit..."
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     "Yeah, we're mean in green, too!"  "Yeah, we bad !" 
      
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          "No more tights and no more skirts, no more studyin' 'til it hurts -    Time to sun and cruise the Mall -summerz here,let's rock 'til fall!"       JUST finished up my last final Thursday, and turned in my final paper on Friday - I'M DONE! Freshman year is history - upperclass(woman) here I come!     How have almost 10 months (!) gone by since I started wearing the "bad in plaid" uniform of a McAuley High School student ?! OK, it wasn't love at first sight... (or even second or third) While my friends at other area high schools were busy raiding Filene's and Wet Seal for their "back-to-class" looks, I was figuring out where I could find enough gray tights to last me a year (tip: ALWAYS buy in bulk), and if the backs of my shoes were high enough so that my ankles wouldn't show... My contemporaries were wearing shirts that displayed a newly-pierced bellyring, and I was hiding  my  - ANKLES...    Not even my mom's promise of spending money saved on new "after-school" and "weekend" clothes made me feel a whole lot better, at least at first...    But then, little by little, something happened - I started to appreciate that extra hour or so of sleep I was enjoying by not having to get up and choose my outfit du jour (howz my French, Ms. Glennon?) No more washing, straightening, curling and spraying my hair into submission - totally "wash'n'wear".  Make-up?  WHY??? And for whom???    But it went beyond the convenience - the sight of all of us dressed alike became a sort of comfort; it was like the dresscode of a sorority, and they way we all recognized each other initially, before we even came to know each other's names.    Did I grow to love the uniform??   Duh! NO!! But - I learned to respect it as a symbol of our school, as much as the Lion or Gold Dome.    Besides, we have LOTS of "dress-down" days where we can wear (kind of) whatever we want, within reason.       Now, if I could just convince my mom to let me get that bellyring....           
      
</post>


</Blog>