<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I lost my head on that last post. At the end I was busting out in song. It's just so hard not to be Proud.
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The view from my front and back door is still completely vial. Neighbors have a special way of mucking up ones view and there is  really no legal way of getting rid of the problem. Can I get a "Amen Corner" on that one?   The United States Postal Service I couldn't be more PLEASED with the service. All you have to do to get a registered parcel off is make a reservation at least a year in advance  and then, you also have to PRAY that it gets to  its recipient in a timely fashion. OHHHHHHH , before you can get your parcel registered, you have to pay our USPS a good deal of money. This is what insures that your parcel will arrive, OR NOT!  To the owner of the parcels in which I speak, The above mentioned institution has misrouted your parcels for 14 days now. How does it go...I'm proud to be an American/Where AT LEAST I know I'm free...
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Australia celebrates the 20th Birthday of Amy Hollands on June 25th. I believe it is a National Holiday. All who knows of this famous beauty, SHOUT OUT Happy Birthday!  In other News, Aleph Null's Lead Guitarist hosted a private showing of there first video last night with close friends.  It was a complete success...to spite the fact that they didn't even use there own music.   Personal Note...still trying to figure that out.      HAPPY BIRTHDAY AMY!!!!!!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have to take a moment to mention Mr Luttrell and his passing. I never really knew him, but I knew his loneliness. He passed by my house so many times and I would watch him until he was out of sight to make sure he didn't trip or fall.  I was always worried. His gait was slow, his head always down.  Each time I saw him I wanted  very much to know what he was thinking, for he was always thinking. On a hot day I would offer him water and on to many days I would just let him go by. I still know Mr Luttrell's loneliness and am deeply saddened  by his passing. To his family I send my deepest regrets and offer my understanding of what you are going through. God Bless and God Speed Mr Luttrell.
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I would like to draw everyone's attention to "Princeton Beautification Program" Has anyone noticed that on the south side of the square, between some hair salon of sorts and I think a print shop, there is a picnic table and I believe 2 benches in direct sun all on top of huge rocks that do not appear to be user friendly.  If your looking for a Holiday type lunch without having to leave town, give it a try!  In a related story, a building collapsed on the north side of the square.  I can only speculate, but I think someone neglected that building.
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Welkommen!!
      
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HAPPY FATHERS DAY TO ALL OF YOU FATHERS OUT THERE!!!  "Sex in the City" has taken a regular time slot on TBS, sigh.  Bill Clinton is on tour with his new book "My Life" Yawn.  He is however very sorry for his naughty behavior. You know that a relief!  Australia is still 9000+ miles away.  I have 3 to many inches on my waist.   Viva Aleph Null!   
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My last post simply reflects my BAD ATTITUDE. So, I would like to invite on of my contributors to feel free to add something that is readable. 
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The search for Amy's parcels has NOT been called off...even though she has in fact recieved them!  The 4th of July is upon us and I think we are in the mood to liberate another little country that pisses us off or maybe has something we want.  It's rain,rain,rain at Cornerstone. Thats a shame! I guess Tabs and Ally will need to keep their shirts on. Can I get an"Amen corner" on that one!
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Mr Jordan Miller has studied for and has mastered ,The Tantric Practice. I have learned this on very good authority.  Question; Does Jordan Miller have Sex Appeal? Cast your vote in our comment section.  In a completely unrelated story, Steve Thomas was the lead actor in "Cabin Boy" not that other guy!  LOVE to Steve and Jordan!!!!!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      God Speed to all of you CS people.  Some of us have to stay Home this year to make a living.  I am Happy for those of you who need not work.  The option to work or not work must be a beautiful thing! Everyone who remains behind and in their jobs, there is a 4th of July Party at Josiah's. Party info and what you can bring is available at Anodyne.blogspot.com.   FYI When the post office looses your parcels, they give you forms called "The 542." The 1st instruction is, press hard to go through 5 copies. For some reason I found some humor in that. The 542 form is exactly like the form you fill out to ship the parcel in the first place,with one exception, the 542 asks you to describe the exterior of your parcel. On that, I was left to believe that we have a  possible situation here.  Naturaly I am thinking "They've lost our parcels", but how could this be!!!! We are dealing with a branch of our efficient local  government. Bitter? NOOOOOOOOO! I'm fine, REALLY!
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Blue Grass in the Desert, Happy 4th of July Ken! "All Night Long"  July 4th 1999, You could hardly walk, but you got up with Michael and went out to do your fire works. He was only 14 years old. You were such a grand Father and the biggest fan of fireworks. A few short days later(July 17) you went to sleep and the 4th no longer has the meaning that it did with you at home. You are still loved and deeply  missed. Five years on the 17th and its still  yesterday. I Love You!!!!!
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Sloppy Joes at the Brown house tonite.    Yard Sale canceled due to lack of rain.    Laundry is in its second day at my house.    Fun filled evening for Peg Prinner. She will be visiting   with the King of the Coin Op, Need I say more!    Michael Brown is a wise guy on most any given day,  while Jordan Miller lives vicariously through film.    Thats preeeeeeeeetty much it!       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Error 417: This blog is stagnant [ urlLink http://thedailydrab.blogspot.com ] Line 1
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Damn Insane is still President. Is To, cause he said!!!!!!  "The Terminal" is still NOT in Princeton's multi plex high def state of the art Theater  And the beat goes on.  Yoko Ono takes gay marrige fight to dance club.  She recently stared in a play "Every Man Has A Man Who Loves Him". HUMMMMMMMM.  Junior Clothing keeps getting SMALLER.  Jordan Miller is Cool! 
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Good news for everyone! Peg Prinner is giving advice. Just send your questions to timtam@insightbb.com and every now and then she will post her reply here. Of course everything will be anonymous. You can address your questions "Dear Peg."
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Lots of fun for Peg Prinner today....Dress shopping with Karina for her wedding Sept. 19th. Whats the deal with this run away marrige train?  I'm getting sick over here!   Just recently I decided I need to conduct an advice section, so if anyone has a question or problem I really believe That I am the "Go To Gal" Lets get started!!!!!  Kerry is leading in the popularity contest. Opps ,I mean The Presidental  Race.  And make no mistake, America will never have to come to this site and have to deal with proper grammer. We can do better than that!  I'm sure this has happened to alot of you out there and pretty dull, but I found it quit mind bending when a complete stranger came up to me, said I was beautiful, Kissed me and then disappeared.  BTW, he was  drop dead good looking! Like I said, I'm sure it happens to alot of you ,alot of the time.  Standing on personal belief, I had to refuse to run spell check on this Post. America can do better than that!  Most important for today and tomorrow,  Jordan is still really cool!   
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was too lazy and not enough of an idiot to send this out to everybody in my mailbox, so here you go. Do I still get my good luck?    4 you    I'll just take it as a hint if I don't get this back. How many people actually have 8 true friends? Hardly anyone I know! But some of us have all right friends and good friends!!! You have been tagged by the Friendship Angel Which means you are a great friend!! You will have good luck for Two Years if you send this to 8 people or more and if it is sent back to you then you know that you are a true friend.............  Of all the friends I've ever met, You're the one I won't forget. And if I die Before you do I'll go to heaven And wait for you I'll give the angels Back their wings And risk the loss Of everything Just to prove My friendship is true   You must send it in 5 minutes or your good luck will be broken!!!   
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      THIS JUST IN: NOBODY CARES ANYMORE. WHAT A SHOCK!  NOW BACK TO YOUR REGULARLY SCHEDULED PROGRAMMING.
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear Must Be Striking In Indiana, Sounds like a Good Time!  You must invest heavily in anti-aging products. Perhaps, just guessing here....but you may need to tone down your huge over inflated ,but i'm sure warrented,ego! Peg Prinner 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear Peg, I am a mother of 2 grown children and single.  The other day I am in ER with the youngest of the two and from ER we needed to go to his place of work to drop off some info  and release note from work. When my son returned back to work, a co-worker came up to him and asked"Hey man, who was that , that came in with you...was that your girl friend"?  What do you Do? Must be striking in Indiana 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hello everyone in drab land! For my debut post in pinktown, I decided to post a list. I haven't done one of these in a while so bear with me...    Top 5 things that caught me off guard this week     lemp&euml; ) 	The lady at the BMV threatened to suspend my already suspended drivers license.  canta )	The pricetag for anything and everything related to a wedding is... well... pricey.  neld&euml; )	"Fascination Street" by Stavesacre is actually "Fascination Street" by The Cure.  atta )	Tabby has officially started cleaning on a regular basis.  min&euml; )	Patty still thinks I'm cool.  Fight the Power. Stay Informed.
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I am here now.  You all may bow before my graceness!!  Please just throw roses! Wow what a great Site.  Love ya all!! Mwah Mwah     
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am writing on behalf of a friend that we will call,Peg Prinner. For the past few weeks Peg has been feeling like she's settleing for less when she dosen't seek all that much in the first place. All she wants is someone to be a friend, share her values, not completely unfortunate looking and possible relationship. Peg recently had a run in with a man at work and while they were talking he just TOOK IT OUT you know, IT! Now I'm asking, what do you do there? Another who doesen't mind being otherwise MARRIED, one who thinks that a Roll In The Hay is what defines a relationship. I could go on,but I'm about to hurl. What we need here is advice on wherther or not to ever leave the house again or WHAT? Where does a girl go to find a nice man that in NOT a FREAK? Settle is the wrong word to use here , because Peg is NOT choosing these types of encounters, they just seem to cross her path all the time. Another example of a FREAK; This guy is a real peach. He rides a Harley, governers lawn care at a golf course, pretends he's swinging a golf club while talking. I had to finialy say "Could ya just stop doing that" and he takes Valium with pot for the ultimate effect. Now this guy said I was beautiful and asked me out. My response was "AHHHHH Never" and to this he said I hurt him. Did I say he was a real Peach! HELP!!!!!!!!! Direct your advice to the comment section of this post. Sick on Seminary 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Right off the bat, this post isn’t really divine; and that contained aren’t exactly secrets. A trademark title was called for, that’s all. I thought it’s about time I should post, lest I’m served an eviction notice on my hallowed place at the table of contributors.   So you want some drab, huh? What could be more drab then the weather… I’ve even converted to F. Just for you my American friends.   As you may or may not realise, Australia is currently in winter. Winter and I have somewhat of an understanding. It can get as cold as it wants, as long as it’s not on a day I have to be up out of bed early. For the most part, winter sees to its part of the bargain. At least, the Aussie winter does.  American winter, I’m sure will mock my proposition. Michael and I discussed this a few weeks back and compared winters. I knew it was colder over there; I just didn’t realise it was  that  cold. As many know, I’m planning a trip over there in January. I shall be boarding a plane here in 95F plus temperatures and landing to cold like I have never known before. Never. Ever. Never. The coldest I’ve ever been in is about 28F and as I was 4 at the time, can’t really say I remember it. And I have never seen snow.   To further illustrate my point, one of our coldest days thus far this winter was about 40-54F. This is how I faced that day: Underwear Shirt Woollen turtleneck Scarf Jacket Leggings Jeans 2 pairs of socks Shoes  Conclusion: I’m going to freeze.   Forget about my accent. You’ll be able to tell me by my inability to walk due to 7 layers of clothing.   Just giving due warning… 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear Peg,  I have a problem: I have no problem. Keen to be an active participant in seeking your pearls of wisdom, I have been wracking my brain for the past week or so, trying to uncover a problem of which to submit. I have so far come up short. I'm unsure whether this is a reflection of a dull life or otherwise. Should I go about creating a touch of dramity within my life or those around me in order to have a problem to come to you with?    Unhappily Unburdened
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is the official announcement of the brand new Sparta Forum at:  urlLink http://varasa.homeunix.org:8088/~mjb/phpBB2/index.php   Feel free to register an account there. Although please note that the site is being hosted on my PC so please try not to generate too much traffic. :-) Many thanks, and I hope you enjoy the (steadily improving) site!
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear All Cleaned Out in Indiana, You have what could turn into real issues later on down the road.  Durning courtship its fun to do allitle more for that special person .  Relationships  that move toward marrige should have evolved into a more mature and mutual respect/ give and take partership.  "Compromise".  George may be under the delusion that its a womens job to clean up his mess and if he dose not leave that notion behind him, you will become soured in the relationship.  Remind George that he is not marrying his Mother ,but a life parterner.  I  think you and George need to have aPow Wow to find out what you need from each other and how you can add to each others life instead of wearing one another out.  There is love or you would not be getting married so, fire the house keeper and be the wife, lover, soulmate and friend and share rhe mundane chores as equals. Good Luck To You and George God Bless Peg 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear Peg,       I am getting married very soon and need some advice.  My fiancee, we'll call him George, is the messiest person ever.  George leaves his dirty socks and underwear all over the place, but expects me to clean it up for him.  I don't think he could hit the hamper if he tried.  George also leaves old newspapers and magazines in piles then gets mad when I accidently throw soemthing he wanted away! What should I do.  All Cleaned Out in Indiana
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Girl asks boy after dating for over a year"What is it that you want out of this relationship"? Boy responds "I want someone who will love me and share my life"  How would you change this response or does it need changing?  
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Your brown boots should look fine with Navy slacks, however I strongly recommend that you get a pair of black boots instead of blue. Forget the blue, just forget it. Your brown boots would be perfect for brown slacks, denim, kacki.  Good luck and God bless, Peg. 
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Dear Peg,     I am a bit of confusion and maybe you can help. Can I actually wear brown shoes with blue or should I wear blue shoes with blue?  Let me explain it a little better for you.  I have a friend lets just say who has a pair of Navy slacks.  With me so far? ok good moving on!  She has a pair of darker brown dress boots she wears with these slacks.  Now is it proper to wear those boots or should she be wearing Navy Shoes to go with?  Maybe your words of wisdom can help in this situation.          Thanks,     Fashion Confused in Indiana!   
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A women gets in her car every day at the same time . She starts the car, punches the gas on her gravel druveway,speeds down a 10 or so foot driveway, hits the street at an ungodly speed as if she is escaping her own death. What is going on there?  A  She dosen't know how to drive  B  She frightened by the very sound of her car starting  C  She has a death wish  D She is crazy  E  All or none of the above. You decide. 
      
</post>


</Blog>