<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is one for me and my friends.
    
</post>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      She exists at the centre of others' eyes and in the corners of a well-worn smile,  a marked territory of things all half-forgotten and places not quite so.  She is a small dark thing, always to the east and west, wrapped once in wood, once in brass, once in marble,  and again in a cloth of intellect and examination.  She is quicksilver and her forest path a cloudling, but she exists with the scent of hope at neck and navel,  with braided gold and tears around her wrist, with distance in defeat somewhere to the east or to the west.  She exists, for one dream ago she settled on a pillowcase and filled a sleeper's  eyes with wings. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Where the world ends there is a great dropoff into infinity, pleasant rainbows and light mist alluringly deceptive.  There are angels there, dark angels to deceive the innocent wayfarer; they call them mermaid, or demons of another world.  But it is a place where you can  drink undiluted sunshine from a small tin cup, and no longer notice how small the ship, or how creaking the deck, or how the kid won't be  quiet,  because in this place, at the very edge of the world, we are all silent, and all connected to eachother.  There, where the world drops off  into infinity, is where we are going, to gather in one foldful of lungrigging, spread wide our arms,  and see what is waiting on the other side.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am writing this poem as you requested - oh, not so much asked as silently demanded - but you well know one doesn't have to  ask, to ask.  I am writing this letter wrapped in simple prose and ineligant  language just like you wanted when your eyes folded shut.  I am writing this epistle in the hopes of enlightenment: we are back at the same old doubtful crossroads, and for that I am sorry.  I am writing this with my hands tied behind my back. You are not just anyone, love, and though it is frightening to hear it said,  I am tying this ship to a dock, to a future set in  stone; I am settling on a good chance. I am betting on a decent animal.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A knot formed where you spoke those words: they were whispered at chest level and exhaled,  and in that moments I became a curator - a scholar - examining the artifact from every angle.  I obsess over this small dark thing, this jade Rosetta, now, as if to plumb its  secrets would validate my struggle. But, as all museum keepers know, it is vanity.  Yet, this emerald-eyed demon has focused my ambitions and my orbit,  that you have not paid admission to see a worthless ancient object, but something living.  Thus, I have ironically buried that idol beneath spring's freshly minted grass and tamped the soil,  if only to say I have forgotten anything except the brightness of your eyes and smile.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       "The Morning of My Forgoten Loves"   This is the morning of my forgotten loves, blown like bright soap bubbles out, out and away to pop and dissipate.  They have left me like rain from a cloud, scattered in muddy puddles and runoff.  This is the morning of my old forgotten loves, none quite half-beautiful or fit to wear the throne, but all rainbow bubble, hot breath and dishsoap.  But you rest like a brick in my pocket, and I think, better a brick than a bubble.  You can't start building a house with soap suds.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Who can predict complexity? Some moments have no rhyme - no reason -  no symetry as a guidepost -  nothing to suggest that when the  filiments are gathered  a rope will emerge.  But the strongest threads form knots -  random seconds form tangled minutes -  hours, even, and there is no respite -  complexity breeds its own, and even an age-tried cable  is inscrutible.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When I stepped disastrously from a precipice (I named it The End of the World) gravity relinquished its downwardness -  but the physics of not knowing down from up  were beyond my grasp -  it was a heady  sinking or rising  I did not know which.  A sentence became my lifeline like a tenuous thread -  a small dark thread -  and you saved me.  Tonight, I'll leave off sleeping.  My heart has not yet regained the ground.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have forgotten how to light a match, how it was once to strike against a shoe and watch the ignition. A brave gust of flame and newborn smoke lifting hands high to an acidic tingle in the air. Oh love, I have forgotten how to strike a flint, until this morning, when I spoke to a dead sky of how night should be running along like a wicked child,  only to notice the dawn brimming with crimsons, pinks, with bluegreyorange - all colour.  Oh love, I have set the sky on fire, like a match, like a flint, like Forest Meets Cigarette, like a thousand litres of gasoline, and till you come like night, like a blessed child, I will burn with it and not be touched, like a dervish, like an angel, like a ghost -  Oh love, it merely morning and I burn. It is not past noon, and I expire. There are precious few hours in a day to waste with flesh aflame.  Oh love, I am coming down the eastline dome, to where you lie blankly, starlit, and when I do, let me forget how to make a fire, and fall into that marvelous black you.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Mankind has lost so many things in ruins and dunes shifting, under the sea, beneath lava, in war.  But there is a greater irony of the connected, the collective, that in our petulant childlike arrogance, we have forgotten the lessons history seeks to teach.  How it bitter to know, how sandboxes are the world's schoolmasters, and garden hose that inexorable movement, that inevitable decay.  We have forsaken this most of all: we've forgotten how to forget.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If memory flickers down, dullish, and dies; if all that's left is charcoal, dust, and ash except that last but brightly glowing coal, I'll place in on my tongue - savour the heat. It scalds to understand the pungent loss mixed in its grit with failure and decline. An Icaritic history defies my thought. Defies the knowledge of the crash, or how it came to pass; but he who stole the memory left a mantra to repeat: for when this fades, I'll pass in flame and dross, the pyre of a night when you were mine. A supernova. One final reply, to grass, to love, your kiss, your laquered sky.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      They found the mire to be most likeable, thank you. Nice place you've got here, next to the mud flats.  Does it get dusty in the summer?  The say even the burgers taste a bit of dirt,  but that's alright, knowing onion.  And no, it wasn't us that cut down the trees. They were gone before we got here, maybe even before  the war.  All's we remember  is what you can see until the sun set somewhere that way,  mud, mud, mud, mud, mud, mudmudmudmud and that dirty strained water Aunt Delores sometime boils for her tea.  Yeah, the mud flats run all the way over toward the sea. The it meets the beach and it stops, sometimes.  And we love it, here in California. Here in the greatest country  in the world.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tell me how love grows cold.  Is it an inherent numbness, an applied entropy?  Do the atrophitic limbs fail always by  the day?  There have never been answers for this question, just similies: love is like good music: one only know it when one sees it.  But deeper, love is a seed, and its own fruit, the irony being a labouriously exquisite beginning, a nuturing and teasing upward,  to find that love begets love begets love.  It is much like rainfall.  I will tell you how love grows cold: rote and ritual, forgotten moments and flippant meaning, a paycheque and a perfomance,  an apathetic evening, and eventual annonymity.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have captured this morning's sadness in a mason jar and set in on the windowsill.  It is a firefly, a wastrel, flashing on and off that something is wrong, is going wrong, has gone horribly wrong,  but I have never been a cryptographer.  It is a firefly, the sadness, it is a firefly trapped, and  whispering a secret that I must know! but can't quite wrap my arms around.  It is a firefly, and I am its prisoner.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I woke from a dream of finding to another day and its puppets and its strings,  eyes wide with the realization that  it is not the fading memory built of unconscious conquest,  but recussitating constantly and chafing at restraints  that makes this waking life a nightmare.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some days  cobwebs clutter my vision  like thread-spun strands of reasons and observance.  I told you  never to doubt, that there are always blue skies here.  But when that same sky boils grey, and the rainclouds fill your eyes, I find myself the  doubter.  What if you've changed your mind? Are the cobwebs are here to stay,  threaded around and over the dream? Hanging heavy with the  rain of yesterday?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A Certain Lack of Words      When I encapsulate you     in sentence     and with syntax,      the method fails,     each time I try.      There are no similes     that do you justice,      for you were made     a little higher than the angels,      and crowned     with glory, to reign     over this heart,      in ways that transcends     language and     expression.      When I ensconse you in     understanding,      I am always half-     short,      but I know this:     when God had finished shaping     you      he broke     the mold.  	 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There is always a subtext to our discourse, always some gravel in the shoe of the conversations,  and we understand subtly that this will always be so,  that jest is not so much jest as truth turned sideways and spun into orbit.  I read your subtitles as loudly as you show them, and wonder to myself  if you'll ever just tell me what you're thinking.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I catch you running and gather you in my arms to ask, "what's wrong, darling?"  But you never tell me.  You are a customer with coins suspiciously untarnished - I turn them over in my hand and I do not trust them -  but I give you all I have in hope you will one day run out of counterfeits and just  tell me the damn truth!  I am not so afraid of honesty that I would desert you,  but your varnished half-truths desert me every day.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When another permutation surfaces, I lose you as if in a sea of faces, only to with I could  create stasis  with outstretched arms and a prophet's mantle -  I wish everything were always and forever.  But I am no prophet, no son of a prophet: I am wrong. you exist in four dimensions, and that is that.  It is your magic and your curse,  that you bend backwards where I cannot look, to rend reality like tissue and tell me,   "I have dreams within dreams of a place without permutations" - and I see life folding in on itself, and that is that.  It is your magic and your curse,  my heartache and my joy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am alive for a few moments every day and I flip aside the veil to revel in a newfound somethingorother.  Try it - you never know what you never knew, what may be fluttering round n round the room -  perhaps, even, there is no room,  merely the  space of something unseen, the form and the substance,  and the wonder.
     

    
</post>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      You may find  urlLink this conversation  interesting. The difference, as far as I can see it, between rap and poetry.   MeHere:  Okay, then. Some rappers, I'd say a great many of them, are poets. I fail to see a difference between a rap and a poem other than the way it is presented. Now I've seen or heard bad raps but poems can be bad too. It's subjective, really. To one person, either work of art may be just scribble on a page. To another, that same scribble is felt and has flow and substance.   Steve:   She speaks the truth.   Skrappybiskit (me):  Actually, there are concrete things about a poem that makes it a *good* poem, at least as the poem relates to form. However, there's always that mysterious something that you can't put in a textbook that makes one poem better than another, or a slightly badly written poem seem better than a stiff well written one.  In that sense, there is and there isn't subjectivism in art. From a technical standpoint, some are good, some are bad. From a personal standpoint, some touch, some don't. The best art (and not a lot of modern art, imho) combines both of those things.  Which leads me to believe that most rap isn't art. It's skillful (sometimes) and relevant (at its best) and can be technically well-performed and well-written in relation to its genre but in the end falls short of true technical merit. Like much of pop culture.   Steve:   But I could rap the above poem to a good beat and then you have a good rap. Are you telling me that's not poetry?   Me:  Of course you could. But the presentation does change the art form, correct? If you film a painting, does that make the film art? Not necessarily. The poem, in its written form, is a poem. Spoken over a beat, it's rap. That changes it, at least in my view.  Besides, the question of whether or not someone *could* rap this poem is academic: almost no hip hop performers rap actual poetry. They perform a mutated type of poetry that is well-suited to being spoken over a beat, something normal poetry rarely is.  Again, I'm not saying that good rap is easy. I know it takes skill (I've written and performed a bit myself). But skill isn't the sole determiner of whether something is good or "high" art. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, since Sarah  urlLink addressed Dutchness , I'm going to have to as well. Too beautiful a peach to leave hanging.  I mean, our Dutchness (at least amongst the youth) has generally devolved to the point of it being butt of jokes more often than a source of pride. Though I do know a few guys who swear by their frilly lace curtains. But I don't know about them. Really.  But there's still these old hardcore people out there that just love the fact that they have this enormous heritage. Maybe they're compensating or something. But I always ask, what heritage? There's good things, sure. But there's a whole lot of bad in the mix. Certainly not something to be horribly proud of.  I mean check out this Calvin guy. The hero of every Dutch Reformer. For goodness sakes, people, the man was  French!  It seems in the five hundred proceeding years of history, the Dutch people co-opted this Frenchman and his theology and made him theirs.  So what else have the Dutch people done that they deserve our eternal and undying ethnic gratitude? Have they fought bravely in wars? Sure, but not many of them. Have they explored the world? Some of it. Have they produced musicians without number? No. They do, however, have two painters. Rembrandt and Van Gogh. Who apparently tore his own ear off.  I'd have to search the internet, but for Holland's comparitive contribution to the world, we're doing pretty badly here, aren't we? England's just a bit bigger, and they conquered most of the known world, from America to India and back again. They left their influence everywhere they went, and India still owes them a huge debt of gratitude for the advancements they provided to that once-backwards country.  Dutch East Indies? Is that the one? Ah. Nice empire. Feel free to flame me now, but at least the Germans can claim to be everlastingly evil. I come from a background of almost-runs. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Here are some witty samples of what I hear around work. And what I say.   Me:  I need to have more tolerance for idiots.  Stu:  On behalf of idiots, we thank you.   Lisa:  (while showing off an apendectomy scar) You should always try to find a girl with scars!  Me:  All my girlfriends have scars. From knowing me.   Me:  (tasting spaghetti from an anonymous co-worker) Hmmm. No onions.  Him:  You know my wife never cooks with onions.  Me:  You need to get her out of that "no onion" box.  Him:  Hey, yo, don't dis my ho!   Brian:  I see you're wearing your hat backwards! Steve's started a trend!  Me:  *edited for content*   Brian:  By any chance, have you seen the ladder?  Me:  It's in my back pocket.  Brian:  Really? *looks at my back pocket* (Okay I made that last bit up)   Me:  (holding two popsicle sticks) *glares at Stu*  Stu:  *burps loudly*  Me:  Aaahhh! My +2 popsicle sticks are nothing compared with your +5 burpaga! (Yes, that was for RPG fans...)   Stu:  *filing a block of metal by hand*  Me:  This is why we're worl-famous... quality workmanship.  Stu:  Yeah, me an my double-sided bastard. (The file was made by Bastard Tools)  Me:  I can photoshop an endmill in there, and we could put in on our website.  Stu:  Could you make me thin?  Me:  I'm not that good. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, so I got a new email account, and a Gmail account at that. I call it scatterfingers@gmail.com - and you can feel free to email me there if you wish for some reason that I don't understand.  But I thought it might be expeditious if I gave a small review of the service here.  First thing off, Gmail claims to be a different sort (pun!) of email service, and for once, the claim isn't just hype. What you'll see, instead of an inbox and folders, is an inbox, archives, and labels. No sorting into folders. Just a convenient search, and the ability to label things if you so wish.   You can mark messages with a star to denote that they are indeed special emails, and that label has its own pseudofolder. Otherwise, all your mail eventually gets archived in a catch-all psuedofolder, which you can search a la Google.com to find a particular past email.  The best feature that I can see is that fact that emails are sorted into conversations instead of each being delivered as a defacto email to your inbox. If you think that not having folders makes things a bit cluttered, this feature is one of the reasons that it's not. I have a conversation (which is formatted much like a chat session) reaching upwards of 10 emails.   Gmail is also very fast, except to load, which takes about as much time as a normal email service like Yahoo! or Hotmail (I spit upon thee, Hotmail!). But inside the account itself, nothing takes more than a split second to perform, from sending to archiving to expanding a conversation so you can see each message separately.  So, mostly positive, right? Well, not really. While the frontend is feature-rich and very user-friendly, it's going to take a while for people to get used to the Gmail system of starring and archiving in lue of folders and a proper inbox. Searching is a great feature, something other email providers need, and now. But the greatest drawback is in its Contacts features (or lack thereof). There's no nicknames or short names, and the information you can provide is limited at best. It also has no way to import or export addresses, which would be a great feature. Especially for those of us that are using Yahoo! mail right now; it would be a great thing if I could import a CSV file of exported Yahoo! addresses. And I have a large contact list. You could even set up something that would import a XML file such as a MSN Messenger contact list export.  Other than that, Gmail gets a 8 out of 10. It's clean, fast, and truly revolutionary. The ads are small and out of the way, something I can't say for Yahoo! or Hotmail. And though the 1gb of space you get is its most trumpeted feature, I'd say it's merely the icing on the cake. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, so we all hate parking the car. But now, you don't have to! With the help of a Linux box and a Volvo,  urlLink a bunch of Swedish students created a car that parks itself .  Also available,  urlLink this cool video , so you can see for yourself.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wow. From TRu-dAT music comes this shirt that expresses  urlLink most of what I think of TobyMac's music .   
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Once upon a time in a land not so far away, there lived a beautiful young lady who didn't know who she was. Although she knew her name quite well, as she had been called it all her life. She lived on the edge of a forest with her aunt, in a small wooden farmhouse, and though it sometimes seemed to her as though there should be more to her history, that was all she could remember. As far back in her past she could go, no other memory would appear, except for a constant thought in the back of her mind that somehow, sometime there was more to her world than just this little plot of land, the animals, and the deep enchanted forest.  Oh. I forgot to mention that the forest was indeed enchanted, like most forests are, didn't I? You see, deep in the centre (as the tales go) there lived a wiley old wizard who could actually talk to the trees. In fact, if one listened closely at times it would sound as if the trees were talking back in a language old and forgotten by men. Or it could have just been the wind in the branches, but who wants to believe that?   "Never go into the forest, Mackenzie!" her aunt had cautioned her on many occasions (for that was the young lady's name). "You know what happened to Hansel and Gretel!"  And yes, they had narrowly escaped death, the girl thought to herself, but that was because they were both quite clearly lacking any God-given common sense. Or sense of direction. "If I were in the forest," she declared later, "I'd use a knife to mark the trees and make a path to follow." She was an immensely sensible girl.    But this is all irrellevant, because she never did go into the forest because, as I've said, she was a sensible girl. Do sensible people enter enchanted forests? Not if they can help it! Enough cautionary tales have been told about enchanted forests to make certain that should a sensible person come across one, said person will pass by without even the slightest hint of curiosity. This is, co-incidentally, why there are so many more stupid people killed by sorcery that sensible people.   Now, she is not the only person that this tale involves. That would be boring. There is (as per tradition) a young prince. He too, was trapped in a place that he had always been, but he never had the thought that he was anything else but a prince. He hadn't the imagination, for though he was in no way sensible, he was so boring a person that he didn't need to be.  However, something happened to him one day that made him question everything that he had ever been taught, and all that he had ever learned. He read a book.    The castle he lived in – for a prince must have a castle – was a very large one, and had quite a few rooms that no one lived in anymore and were just ripe for a young man to explore. The only problem being the one young man that lived in the castle was too unimaginative to want to explore anything, and usually kept to himself in his room, watching the birds fly by. He never wondered how they flew. He knew they did, and that was enough for him.    However, one day quite against his will and also quite by accident, he was carrying some of his school books -- history books! what a bore! -- back to the old and hardly used library. His tutor (also a bore) had sent him there to get the next volume of the history of his country, which mostly involved faded pictures of old men with wierd hair using language no one could understand anymore, saying prodidgously important things about history-shaping matters, all of which was of the most pressing importance to his father who was also one of those old men with wierd hair who used the languages of antiquity. Strangely enough, the prince didn't understand what all the fuss was about, and why couldn't they have just had a nice civilized game of chess instead of all the bloody wars? (And if he had the slightest spark within him, he would have groaned at his own pun.)  These thoughts were running through his mind as he placed his book back on the shelf – stirring up a good hundred years of dust – and grabbed the next one. As he did, the prince noticed that behind the next volume in his history textbook there was a strange cubbyhole. Inside was nothing except a book, bound in leather, looking as if it had been stored there by another of those ancient men with strange hair. But this prince, lacking in imagination a he was, knew from all the fairy tales that his former nurse (who was fired for talking such nonsense) had told him, that something this old, hidden behind a bookshelf, bound in leather, written by ancient men with strange hair, must be hugely important and perhaps even interesting. So, with the expression of a man hoeing potatoes, he pulled the book out and gazed at the cover.  It said: "Imagination." Of course, you must understand that it's strange to hear a book speak, especially for someone who's always thought books were meant to be read, not listened to. As one my brothers might say, “Buy a Walkman, dude,” but that's neither here nor there. Regardless of what the prince thought the duty of a book should be, it still spoke to him, and he just about dropped it.  And then came the dilemma - forget about the book, put it back, pretend it never existed, and certainly couldn't pronounce words, or open the cover and find out what was inside?  Perhaps the book had already affected him, or perhaps he did indeed have a spark of curiosity inside of him that even fifteen years of training to be king hadn't snuffed, but he decided to open the cover.  There were no pages inside. It was a hollow shell of a book, with nothing but a quantity of grey powder inside. "Grey powder?" he thought to himself. "Grey powder?" Twice, because there was quite a bit of it.  Suddenly from the deepest part of his being came a sneeze, such as had never been sneezed in that library before that instant. The prince closed the book, climbed down the ladder he had used to reach the shelf his books were on, and looked around. Suddenly he was possessed of a mad desire to understand -- to know what things were, and how things worked, and why things existed -   Rushing out to the stables, he saddled his royal horse. Suddenly he looked up and noticed birds flitting along, singing songs, and he wondered, "How do birds fly?" And was startled by the thought that had never before entered his mind.   Now, just because he was suddenly afflicted with a great deal of curiosity did not mean he was suddenly particularly brilliant; if he had, the prince would have known that riding a horse is fit to teach one only of how much a bow it can put in the profile of ones legs. Knowledge, of course, would have been better found in the library.  However, it isn't quite that easy for a prince to go on a journey of the imagination into a world he has not yet tasted, especially if he has the stereotypically evil guardian looking over his shoulder. Imagine for a second sitting on a horse while your evil mother looks over your shoulder. She is very tall. Imagine also that she has evil powers that she can weild according to her evil will. She is very tall, and very powerful. You would get off the horse too.  "What are you doing!" she shouted at him (because evil people never speak softly unless threatening or offering poisoned apples, cf. Snow While). It wasn't a question. It was a statement, and it meant "Get back to your studies!" Because even though she didn't share her husband's passion for people of the past with strange haircuts, she realized there was no better way to keep the prince and his father busy, and also make work for tutor, which would in turn make her look beneficient, thereby raising public opinion of her Niceship, which in the end was a bang-up PR job. At least that's what her ad agency said.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The prince gulped, descended from his royal steed, and ran back to his room to cower under his bed. What he didn't realize in his terror was that he had dropped the book – which mysteriously remained sealed shut – directly in front of his evil mother.   Evil mothers are usually possessed of a keen sense of what most people (including myself) call curiosity, and this one (mostly because I didn't have the imagination or desire to create her otherwise) was no different. She picked up the book, read the cover, and tried to open it, but ornery as books are, it refused to budge. Someday you will have this too if you decide to read; there are some books you just can't get into.  Her evil brow furrowed into an evil scowl in a veritable earthquake of fury. "To the workshop!" she cried (again, loudly, because she was evil), as she ran from the stables to the secret set of musty steps that lead down to the bowels of her evil workshop. (Please note the word choice: “bowels” of her “workshop”. Not the “heart” of her “powder room”.)  She set the book down on a table next to a rather nasty-looking mixture of exotic ingredient boiling on a brass stand (even though there was no fire underneath, which is a sign to most people: "Do Not Drink!"), and went up to her crystal ball. It wasn't actually crystal, because the crystal model cost a little bit more than she could safely embezzle from the palace grocery fund, but made from a sort of obsidian-black substance. She whipped off the handkerchief covering in a dramatinc sort of gesture, and placed her hand over it. "Crystal ball!" she commanded, loudly. "Tell me how to open this book."  Nothing happened, because after all, she didn't have a crystal ball.  She frowned again. "Obsidian-black substance ball!" she shouted, loudly. "How do I open this book?"  The obsidian-black ball awoke and looked at her. It was sort of picture of a flaming blue eye, seeing in all directions. A deep voice came from it: "You have found the book of power," it entoned gravely. "With it you can conquer all of mankind."  "But how do I open it?" she asked.  "It must be opened by a prince of the line of Thebes!"   She raised an eyebrow in a particularly evilish sort of way. "My son?"  "Your son."  Smiling evilly, she ran up the steps to find him.  In the meanwhile, on the egde of the forest, the girl sat near the window of her little house, spinning cotton into thread, something that her aunt had asked her to do minutes before. She saw immense value in doing such household chores, because after all, she was a sensible girl.    Suddenly, she heard the sound of galloping hooves approaching, and looking out the window saw a little cloud of dust in the distance. She continued her spinning until she saw a young boy on a horse. Her aunt had taught her well in the art of entertainings strangers (which she almost never did, as the country was a quiet place with only the odd mistral coming through, and it was no use entertaining them, because they always insisted on entertaining you), so she – regretfully, because spinning cotton into thread is always a useful endeavor – stopped her spinning and went out to meet the young man.    "Hullo," she said, stepping up behind him as he descended his horse. "Oh!" he cried, suddenly falling to the ground and bruising a knee for his trouble. He looked up at her from his prostrate position. "Who are you?"  "That's a rude question," she told him, helping him up with one hand. "Hasn't your mother taught you anything about entertaining people?"  "I can play the lyre," he said dubiously, "and when I dance, people laugh, but I'm not very good at entertaining."  She giggled. "No you silly boy!" she said. "I mean entertaining, not entertaining!" Because after all, the difference was so abundantly clear.  "I'm not sure I've ever done it, then," he replied. "How does one entertain someone else, and by 'entertain' I mean 'entertain', not 'entertain'?" He was dusting himself off.  "Well," she said sensibly, "I must introduce myself to you."  "Introduce?"  "I am Mackenzie," she told him, offering her hand to him.  "Isn't that what I asked you before?" he said, shaking her hand. "Seems a rather roundabout way to do things."  "All polite things are roundabout," Mackenzie replied primly. "How else would one waste time otherwise?"  "So you're polite to waste time?"  "Quite so."  "So you discuss trivialities at length to avoid having to talk of anything meaningful?" he said incredulously.  She looked at him strangely. "There you go trying to be impolite again!" she said. "You should have told me your name."  He bowed. "I am prince Roderick the Seventy-Third of the line of Thebes, heir-apparent of all that you see, soon to be ruler of the world."  She nodded, slowly and politely. "How is the weather around your place this time of year?"  The prince frowned, greatly puzzled. "I tell you that I will soon rule the known world, and you want to discuss the weather?"  "Certainly," she said. "If it were otherwise, I would give the impression that I cared, which would be impolite.”  He shook his head in frustration. "I was like you, once," he said. "Then I opened a book –" suddenly he realized that he no longer had the book "Imagination" in his posession...  * * *
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      His wicked mother in the meantime was searching the castle high and low, and in a strangely convenient manner forgot to look in the stable until most of the palace had been turned upside down. When she did, it drawing on night time. She flung open the double doors of the stable with a particularly evil gesture, and stood there in the flaming light of the torches and screamed: "Where is the prince!"  Because of palace cutbacks, there was no longer at twenty-four hour stableboy, so all she heard was the echo of her voice and the nervous noises made by the only remaining horse. "Cutbacks," she muttered.   It was not long before she was riding into the evening toward the sunset, her obsidian-black ball tracing the route that the prince had taken.  * * *  "Are you sure we should be doing this?" asked Mackenzie nervously, glancing over her shoulder. "Won't your mother get angry?"  "Yes she will," the prince told her, "but I need that book!"  "What's so important about a book?" she said. "I always found books a waste of time. So unsensible."  "That's exactly what makes them so fun."  "What's 'fun'?"  "Don't ask any more questions," Roderick said. "All you need to know is that we are now descending into the bowels of the palace, and of my evil mother's evil workshop."  “Quite a sensible choice of words,” Mackenzie commented.  “Thank you,” replied the prince. “Now look around for a book that says 'Imagination'.”  They searched around for a while before the prince came across a bit of dust seemingly randomly scattered over the table. He recognized the dust, however, and looked closer. “Here!” he said, motioning to Mackenzie. “Look what I found!” She hurried over and squinted at the dust lying on the table.   “It's tiny little words,” she whispered. “What a silly thing to do?”  “Why are you whispering?” asked the prince. “And what does it say?”  “It says, 'Imagination wuz here,' and I'm whispering because it seemed like the right thing to do.”  The prince frowned. “That means she must have the book with her. We need to get it back!”  “Why?” asked Mackenzie, who seemed to be a never-ending fount of questions. “You've already got your imagination. What could you possibly do with the book?”  The prince frowned again. “I would spread it around the world,” he replied. He grinned. “Starting with you.”  * * *  The evil queen took the one-way path to Mackenzie's house, cursing the king the entire time for making one-way paths to distant villiages. What was the point? Did anyone like one-way streets? Were they in style back then or something? (In her further comments on the subject, I will replace any offensive words she may have used with the word “drat” or “dratted” or “dratting”.) And that dratted boy! Always meddling – well, not always, but once was quite enough – in places where he didn't belong! Just like his dratted father! Drat him! The man created one dratting way streets for crying out dratting loud! To quote Rex Harrison in My Fair Lady, “Drat, drat, drat, drat!”  She broke off her thought of the king and his errant son (and groaned at her own pun) to follow the lead of her obsidian-black substance ball. “Where has he gone, all-seeing eye?” she asked, loudly. Which disturbed the sleep (since it was now night) of Mackenzie's aunt, who hadn't yet realized that Mackenzie (a sensible girl who could be trusted on her own) hadn't tucked herself into bed. The aunt looked out the window, seeing what she thought was another loonie wandering around her front yard with an obsidian-black substance ball flaming blue fire, and went back to sleep.  It wasn't long before the prince's evil mother had traced all of his steps around the yard (using a method known in some countries as the “funky chicken”), and was galloping off down the one-way path back to her castle.  * * *  At the same time, the prince and Mackenzie had just left the palace, headed, for lack of a better idea, for Mackenzie's house on the border of the enchanted forest. As they galloped on the prince's royal steed, his mind flicked back to the race his royal steed had recently lost against his mother's royal steed. Which he suddenly saw coming toward him in a cloud of dust.  * * *  Her son! There he was, just ten feet away going in the opposite direction! And once again, the queen cursed the dratted one-way street as the prince sped into the distance. As soon as she got to the nearest McDonahue's rest station, she pulled a quick u-turn in the “emergency vehicles only” u-turn thingy, and began pounding down the path after him.  * * *  “She's coming up behind us!” shouted Mackenzie, who was terrified of this evil woman on that very fast horse. “She did an illegal u-turn in the 'emergency vehicles only' u-turn thingy! She's a monster!”  The prince nodded, urging his horse on just that little bit faster, the little bit that would be the difference between life and life as a toad.   Reaching the enchanted forest, they dismounted quickly and scurried into its depths. But not before Mackenzie cut a mark in the tree with her Swiss Chard Amy Knife.   “What are you doing?” the prince shouted. “We have to escape!”  “Not without leaving a trail,” said Mackenzie. “Haven't you ever heard of Hansel and Gretal?”  “No!” the prince, again, shouted. “C'mon, we don't have time to waste.”  They crashed through the forest, stopping ever so often to cut marks in trees, listening to the sounds of their impending doom coming closer and closer as they did.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The prince was practically begging. “This is a stupid idea,” he said. “Stupid. Who cares if we can find our way back if we've been turned into toads? We'll like it here! This will be home!” But she kept stopping to cut marks in trees. “You're hurting me,” he told her. “You're hurting the trees! Greenpeace would be horrified.”  “They're busy chaining themselves to the smithy,” she replied primly, even as the sound of breaking foliage and snapping sticks grew nearer.  They ran for a bit more, breaking into a clearing, where Mackenzie decided to make another mark in yet another tree.   “Don't put a mark in that tree,” came a voice from behind them. They whirled to see an aged man sitting in a rocking chair, rocking back and forth. “I'm a certified member of Greenpeace, and I'm afraid I can't allow you to do that.”  Mackenzie began, “Are you...”  “... the wizard that talks to trees?” the wizard who talks to trees finished. “Yeah, sorta. I mean, they do most of the talking, and I kinda just sit by and translate for the flowers and such.”  At that moment the prince's evil stepmother broke through into the clearing and waved her wand at them menacingly. It was a fresh wand, too, and a very nice model recently featured on the Shopping Channel.  Nothing happened. “Sorry,” the old man said, rocking in his chair. “Your magic won't work here.”  “Well, I can still kill him with my bare hands!” the queen shouted, scowling at her son. “Open this book for me, prince, or die knowing that you could have opened this book for me!” She realized as soon as she said it how stupid it sounded, but she scowled extra-convincingly to make up for it.  “Can't you help us?” cried the prince to the wizard who translated the words of trees. “She's going to kill me!”  “Nope,” the old man said, pulling a soother from his vest pocked. “I'm a pacifist.” He jammed it in his mouth, as if to make his point.  The queen's frown morphed into a picture-perfect evil smile. The grandmother of all evil smiles. She took the book from her evil napsack pushed it toward him, and said, “Open it, fool!”  Looking down at the cover, the prince was taken aback. Where it had once said “Imagination”, it now said “Sheep”.  “Why did that book just say sheep?” the queen asked, stepping back. But not fast enough: the prince opened the book in a lightning, or at very least a 1969 Ford Mustang, movement, tossing the dust contained inside over her.   There was a small flash, and in the middle of the clearing stood a sheep. A black sheep. “Did you do that?” asked the prince of the wizard who listened to the words of trees.  The little man in the chair shrugged. “I needed a sweater.”  * * *  Book of imagination in hand, the prince and Mackenzie followed the trail she had made back to her Aunt's house. They argued the entire way about whether or not his natural male sense of direction would have been enough had they had no markings. He almost instantly regretted sprinkling the imagination dust on her, as some of her comebacks were remarkably witty.  Eventually, they got married, so as to carry on the arguing more conveniently, but not before the prince had spread the dust of imagination throughout the land. Strangely, it never seemed to run out; no matter how much he gave out, there was always more to be had. Which, conveniently, is the moral of this story:  You can never get rid of dust.  Oh, and they all lived happily ever after. Until they died.  THE END.  PS: Okay, I lied. The moral of this story is that imagination isn't a static quantity that you can somehow exaust. There's always a bit more beyond the next bit of writers block. Or, for you people that enjoy carving, carving block. You may all groan at that pun. I should know this. I began this story, got half of it done in about an hour, and then finished the rest up six months later with fresh ideas, and much too much diet ginger ale.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I rode my bike to Subway for lunch today, only to find it took a great deal of time due to extreme headwinds. Which inspired me to write a poem comparing riding a bike and headwinds to life and how sometimes you get so busy that it seems like everything's taking forever. Ironically, I haven't written it yet due to the fact that I've been so busy.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well you can get it from  urlLink the CBC ,  urlLink Canoe.ca ,  urlLink the always-biased Globe and Mail .  Of course, there's not really much to be said. Martin wins a minority government, but barely. Even with the NDP, the Liberals don't have enough seats to actually rule properly, which means that we can expect another election on the inside of two years, if that. But the clincher of this whole story -- as always -- is that vote-rich Ontario blah blah blah is constantly re-electing the shitty Liberal government over and over again. Ontario is as redundant as that sentence was. What exactly do you need? Writing on the wall? God to step down and tell you how much that government sucks? Can you tell I'm a tad bit upset?  Goodness. Final tally (well, almost... some are being counted):  Liberals: 135 seats. Conservatives: 99 seats. The Bloc: 54 seats (who cares?). NDP: 19 seats (also, who cares?). Other: 1 seat.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Have you ever noticed how Hollywood trailers are often so faceless and generic? Especially for action flicks? Of course, so are the movies, so you kind of expect it, but c'mon people! You have a chance to be creative in restraints and you don't take it. Goodness.   So I've decided to write a "Make Your Own Homebrew Trailer". I'm not going to have any film for this, so you'll just have to use your imagination.  "Generic Trailer" (by Dax)  (A man who has smoked one million cigarettes begins speaking.)  In a (time / place / land / town) where (evil has triumphed / nobody breaks the rules / thus and such is forbidden) one (man / woman / group of adventurers) will (stand and fight / challenge the status quo / fight for his/her/their rights) and (change the world / alter history / begin a revolution).  (Jonny Q. Hollywood) and (Sally Q. Ho) star in a movie critics are calling (Action packed! / A thrillride! / High-octane!) and (The best action film since thus and such! / A triumph! / Heart-breaking!).  Don't miss this (summer / winter / fall / spring)'s  motion picture event, (dramatically name film), coming soon to a theatre near you!  ...  And this is supposed to make me want to watch the film. Pshaw.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      For some reason I got up really early this morning, like when my alarm clock first went off -- crazy crazy crazy crazy -- and I had a bit of time before I went to work. On an unrelated note, I'm very thirsty.   "The Morning of My Forgoten Loves"   This is the morning of my forgotten loves, blown like bright soap bubbles out, out and away to pop and dissipate.  They have left me like rain from a cloud, scattered in muddy puddles and runoff.  This is the morning of my old forgotten loves, none quite half-beautiful or fit to wear the throne, but all rainbow bubble, hot breath and dishsoap.  But you rest like a brick in my pocket, and I think, better a brick than a  bubble.  You can't start building a house with  soap suds.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      In  urlLink this article on pop culture , Douglas Wilson takes on the heathens and pagans, claiming pop culture as anti-culture. Disposable culture. You don't pass on your Frasier episodes to your children. Besides, they won't know what a DVD is.  But his logic is flawed, at least a bit. In the article, he claims (using his example) that purple hair  means  rebellion. Okay, I'll grant that, sort of. Purple hair means rebellion in a certain context: in the realm of people who don't wear purple hair. Which is society in general. Mostly. Of course, we can't lump society into one big blob and say "this is how it is," because it varies so much from place to place, especially in a multiculture like Canada. Or, as DW might argue, a no-culture like Canada. Makes it difficult.  Perhaps it would be best to judge these things from a standpoint of locality. Purple hair in a crowd of purple-haired people is not rebellion in the temporal sense. In that sense, even if they're all wearing it out of rebellion, you're conforming, not rebelling. In the final sense, of course, you're conforming to rebellion. But that hardly matters, especially when you have a whole bunch of people wearing purple hair so that the point of it all is being lost.   A potent example of this might be spikey hair. Once upon a time it was considered abnormal to do ones hair like that. It still might be, if you're a fifty-year-old man. Or an earing. It was once considered a sign of rebellion to wear an earing, if you were a man. Or, if you were a woman, to wear more than one. However, all the little rebels have now grown up to their rebellion becoming the status quo (no matter what you think of the history of it all), and no longer see that as abnormal. And because -- and again, Douglas Wilson and I will disagree on this -- there is nothing inherently wrong with piercing, at least in moderation, like most things, the infamous rebellion symbol carries no infamy or rebellion. At best, it's a nostalgic throwback to an era in which it was. Yearning for rebellion. Stupid, yes. But that's the way it is.  Of course, if we didn't have a culture of rebellion, these changes might take a number of decades and centuries happen, where in 20th century culture they only two decades, and no centuries. But that's a moot point that you can argue when Christians have once again taken over the world (come to our rescue, China!). We can't look at what something was thirty years ago, and judge from there. Especially, as DW will admit, in things that are only sinful based on meaning. Well, do they really mean that anymore? No, not really. You need to find a nice gangsta rap cd for that. And we won't talk about those little retards.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink The Haircut   urlLink Caffiene   urlLink Stunt Double.   urlLink Unused Emails   urlLink Sugarbob (especially good)   urlLink Theme Park   Okay, Kevin. Are you happy?
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, so if you want to have these entries emailed to you so you don't have to come here all the time (though of course, I know you want to), you can join at  urlLink Yahoo Groups .  That's all you need to know. Really.  /me
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       "Childhood"   All revisit the  sandboxes of their youth, be it in poptarts or handsurfing out car windows,  but there is still the problem of knowledge and how to forget what ripped childhood from our fingers.  The mind is a mysterious, acerbic place, and could we unremember, we might, to fly kites without the whisper of Franklin,  or build dams with dirty hands and no Pastuer preaching cleanliness,  or think that girls are icky and boys all muddy creatures, no hormones eroding those illusions like sandstone and breakers,  to view the world as a great mystery  without the textbook of  quantum mechanics to twist the conundrum in further knots (and a dead cat's a dead cat, stupid).  We all revisit the skinned knees of childhood with the placebos and bright bandages of an adult life,  where no balm comes for the wars of wisdom and experience, except to say the night was winking full of stars, where clouds now pass across the sky.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Be careful with dynamic memory.  Watch for stack overflows.  Always restrict access as much as possible.  Use the strongest encryption available depending on the sensitivity of your data.  Turn off all services that you don't use.  Don't set your root password to root.  Assume every user has bad motives.  Plan for the worst.  Also,  urlLink The Ten Commandments of Computer Ethics .  1. Thou shalt not use a computer to harm other people. 2. Thou shalt not interfere with other people's computer work. 3. Thou shalt not snoop around in other people's computer files. 4. Thou shalt not use a computer to steal. 5. Thou shalt not use a computer to bear false witness. 6. Thou shalt not copy or use proprietary software for which you have not paid. 7. Thou shalt not use other people's computer resources without authorization or proper compensation. 8. Thou shalt not appropriate other people's intellectual output. 9. Thou shalt think about the social consequences of the program you are writing or the system you are designing. 10. Thou shalt always use a computer in ways that ensure consideration and respect for your fellow humans.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I hate to be dogmatic about things, but the US court system is usually pretty dysfunctional, mostly I think, for lack of legislative oversight. And that would be the fault of legislators, whose job is to provide a balance of power by being able to revoke a court's decision in the legislature if they feel so called. Of course the status quo seems to be that the judicial activism is in, and legislative activism is out. The court system has been trampled over by liberal activists who do what like because they can, and the legislative assemblies have their hands in Big Business's pie, so they won't do anything even if they could.  That said, it seems even the US courts are a little nervous with the Patriot and Homeland Security Acts, and the way they chip at the foundations of US civil liberties little by little. In  urlLink a recent decision  they seem to be toeing the line of saying "we don't like this, Mr Bush. Not in a tree, not with a bee, not in a box, not with a fox."   In other news, if you want to read something about Quantum Mechanics, try  urlLink this site.  In the venerable tradition of science, it is quite ugly, but informative. Which is about as much as I can say about Eintein too, by the way. Ugly, and really bad hair, but informative as you'll get.  Want to know  urlLink the rules of soccer?  Well I did, and I found out how  urlLink complicated they really are.  The second link is for a PDF document put out by Fifa (the Federation International de Football Association). By the wayl, who made up that name? Is that like four different languages? I see French in there, and English, so what is this? Goodness, make up your minds people. You might as well have called it the Vereinigung Internazionale de Football Asociación.  Which for those of you who don't know, is German, Itallian, French, English, and Spanish.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Just to see if I can email in a blog entry. You know, sort of that  exciting feeling when technology is doing what you want it to. And  you don't have to pay for it. Nice.  
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I was asked today how many kids, grandkids, and great grandkids my grandmother has. And I had to do some figuring, but the end result goes something like this: 10 kids, 48 grandkids, 50ish great-grandkids. For crying out loud, that's over one hundred people! And that's not counting her brothers and sisters kids, who are my second cousins once removed.   So Steve was thinking that I should start up a site (like Steenhof.info) to keep all the relevant relative information on. And then we could gradually expand and it could become a veritable encyclopdia of the Steenhof family. Although Oma's pretty much comatose right now, so we won't exactly get to hear her little bit of the story.  Last night, coffeehouse was at the Zandstras. As in Pete and Laurie's. My drum was tuned up too high. Nick's sense of rhythm needs help. I taught them how to play the alt tune to "Take My Life and Let it Be", which is a cool song, except that Nick's guitar was tuned down two steps and it made it sound like we were a choir of bullfrogs. Pete Westerveld was there. So were all the younger YP children, who look like they're about five. But that's neither here nor there.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, so I don't love Microsoft. But there're some pretty interesting articles that come out of there every once in a while (not to mention leaked memos, even more interesting). Try  urlLink Twenty-One Rules Of Thumb  which attemts to describe how MS gets software to market on time. In the article it says "great" software, but I think we'll forgive them that bit of hyperbole, unless of course you're refering to MS-DOS, which really wasn't that bad.  I copped a few snippets from the article. These are somewhat classic, and use words that no one uses.    Pseudo-order is a maladapted defense against uncertainty.     A developer articulating the status of his/her component is an exercise that does produce information, but if it happens to communicate the component’s status, it is only coincidental. This is someone else’s job.     It is a simple enough matter to mentally run through the sides of the triangle, or force others to do so, when discussing any part of it.     This means that the granularity of development tasks must be such that deliverables are achieved at intervals sufficiently small that slips can be compensated for.     At a milestone, the team and its leadership also have the opportunity to perceive the whole project status simultaneously, to draw conclusions about erroneous practices, to remedy bad design decisions and to reorganize for peak performance.     There are many pathologies at play here as well as certain healthy patterns of creative behavior.     Often, when appropriate design value is awarded to timeliness, implementation time can be substantially compressed.   Yes. The man who wrote this is a very verbose person.
     

        
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Democracy really depends on the people of said democracy being informed and communally minded. At least as far as I can see. The sort individualism that North America espouses lends itself not so much to democracy as dictatorship, or perhaps a constitutional monarchy.  Think about it: our countries have no long-term goal and vision unless there is a truly exceptional leader. Our rulers live life in four-year terms. When the people become sheep blindly choosing whichever candidate promises the best candy, the system devolves in to a power-trap. You can't lose control, so you have to promise more, better, farther, bigger. And of course you do this with the people's money. Governments have a vested interest in gaining more control and more power -- and keeping it -- than letting civil liberties exist, because like a corporation, their main supply of income is made from the very people who seek those liberties. Loss of power entails loss of control, and loss of control entails in the end loss of that income. Generally.   On another note, it seems that TV producers are doing a good job right now with reality television, and by good job I mean that they make a crapload of money for a tiny little investment. Well, compared with a normal drama, that is.  Of course, they realize that they can't saturate the market with all these shows that are -- face it -- generally variations on the same theme without pissing off viewers. They realise that there's a need for normal drama, action, adventure, sci-fi. I personally find reality tv to prey on all the worst aspects of North American psuedo-culture: sex, power, sex, and more power. It's like they play only two cards. To me, these things are unwatchable. Survivor is stupid. It's base. It's bad entertainment on every level. Fear Factor is either unwatchably boring or indescribably disgusting. The Aprentice is like caging animals and watch them bite eachother. Donald Trump is the ringleader. The only thing I can think of worse than that is watching another episode of Big Brother. And I'm not even on the cutting edge, thank goodness. Queer Eye for the Straight Guy?   Yeah, here's last night's meal in a bowl, still warm from me throwing it up. And it's probably better for you than reality TV. I'm angry, alright?
     

        
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's interesting how we're taught from youth that romantic love is like Hiroshima, isn't it? Video, audio, hard copy; it all informs me that it's like a great tsunami (sorry about all the Japansese similes) that just  cannot  be stopped.  And life, of course, is different. I never cease to be amazed at the capacity of the human mind to believe what it wants in the face of what is obvious. Sometimes love creeps up on you like your own shadow, and you don't realise it until it's already underfoot. Sometimes love is both things, rainforest and desert.  It makes me wonder. What do you do when you walk out of a rainforest and a mood changes, and suddenly you're in the middle of desert? When the emotions of the thing seem different? The answer is ridiculously simple, I think, but utterly difficult to actually implement. The answer is trust, and committment. You trust that it won't be like that forever, trust in the love of the other person. You commit yourself to not abandoning things merely because they don't fit your expectations.  Of course these things have their limits, and they're by no means easy or even exclusive things.   Sometimes love is quite honestly seeking the best for another person. Sometimes love is denying yourself the safety of hideaways. Sometimes love is braving the long deserts, knowing that paradise is on the other side. And yes, sometimes love is like a tsunami, like an atomic bomb going off. I know. Right now I feel as if I'm on the borderland of a dry spell. Like I'm close to a place that will test these things in me. But not only in me. Maybe it's just an errant wind, or maybe trouble really is brewing.  Who knows. But I refuse to let something die so young, to kill it slowly with a thousand tiny divorces.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Software is a strange thing. It cost money to create, but almost nothing to reproduce. As in, a great deal of the cost of software is developmental; a very small fraction is in actual deployment. There're always advertising cost to consider, but let's factor those out. They're implicit in almost any venture nowadays, even the Novell/IBM/Redhat Linux ventures, based on Open Source though they be.  The wierd thing with this is that stealing software versus hardware become a convoluted issue. Think about it: you steal a CPU from Dell, for instance, and you've actually removed something from their factory that has physical value. You've decreased their actual profits by that one CPU. On the other hand, if you burn a copy of Windows and install it on your friend's computer, you've not actually stolen anything pysical. What's you've actually done is stolen "intellectual property" that has no existential real-space value. You've stolen  potential  profits from Microsoft.  But where stealing a computer from Dell doesn't exactly extend Dell's branding, where piracy of physical objects doesn't often help the object's maker prosper, Microsoft is in the unique position of actually benifiting from piracy, at least in developing countries.  You see, when someone installs a Windows system, even if it's free or pirated, they're joining an ecosystem of computing, or a culture, if you will. Microsoft's culture of computing. A culture they work very hard to sustain, though often through dubious means. And once you're part of that culture - legally or not - you have bought into an ecosystem that's hard to transition from, and intentionally so. In that sense, comparing Microsoft to a drug dealer isn't that far of a stretch. You give away your product for free (which, by the way, Microsoft pretty much does in developing countries), get the users hooked, and once they have your system, the next series of upgrades (with better piracy controls) assure you that the profits begin to roll in.  Which happens, partially. It's no mistake that Windows 98 was practically a pirate's dream operating system. It had no controls whatsoever, except for the usual "certificate of authenticity" number, which are so freely available on the internet, still, that it's not funny. But the inevitable point comes where you can either upgrade you system to another pirated one (a Windows that has implemented systems that are more difficult to circumvent), or pay retail and upgrade from there. Which is where Open Source comes in. You see, Linux is a great transition point when you decided you want something that you can for free, legally. Something that's stable, doesn't have more than two or three know viruses (despite widespread use in Apache servers, and desktop systems), and is fully supported by a wide base of knowledgable  users  who know more than "well, restart Windows, and see if it works."  Hooray for pirates!
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, when it comes to integrity and trust, the word "Microsoft" doesn't spring to many sane minds. And along comes a document detailing  urlLink how Microsoft funds anti-Open-source "thinktanks"  to rub it in a bit further. This on top of a suspected finger in the SCO pie, and a suspected finger in the Alexis de Toqueville Institute's blistering bit of FUD. And on top of  urlLink things like the Halloween documents . And taking out  urlLink every single conceivable patent they can  regardless of prior arts and the impact these patents will have on the IT community at large.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      One problem with the United States (among many, many problems) is that it's just so darn big. Japan, on the other hand, doesn't have that particular issue, although you practically have to be rich to breathe there. But imagine for a second actually stringing fibre optic cable all over the USA, versus all over Japan; it's no wonder they have broadband internet access nearly everywhere, and the US is nowhere close to that. Here in Canada (bigger than the US, with way less people! Yay!) it's limited to major urban centres: I have some friends who live just fifteen minutes out of a medium-sized city, and they're restricted to dialup because no one really cares about the five people living on their street. It sucks. Everywhere I go I have broadband. I can't wait for pages to load up on a 56k modem. That's like driving 40kph down a highway.   So yeah,  urlLink The Register  is reporting that  urlLink about a third of US adults a are currently rejecting the internet for one reason or another. Which is interesting, because who knew there were so many Amish to go around? Goodness. 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, so railguns (guns that use microwave, laser, and electromagnetic-kinetic energy to destroy or injure their targets) aren't exactly common. But you can  urlLink build your own with a few handy tips . So it's not the most user-friendly thing around (or, for that matter, hostile-friendly), and it requires a bit of technical knowlege, but I forsee a time when railguns of all sorts begin to proliferate the market. So when the neighbor's dog is barking in the middle of the night, you FR4G H1M with your R41L GUN. Take that, little dog. You've been 0wnz0red! 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I just dropped an entire board of tools (which were, thankfully, simple and undamaged for the most part), cutting my hand in the process. Yes, folks, this is what I get for working in a machine shop: long hours, hot days, immobility, and a  the death of a thousand cuts . Darnit. Oh, I also get payed more than most people.   In other news, Yahoo is reporting that SpaceShipOne's almost pristine sounding first flight and brief entry into space didn't  urlLink exactly go as well as you may have thought .   If you don't want to RTFA, here's a snippet: "Melvill said he leveled out the rocketship, but then experienced trim problems during his climb outside the Earth's atmosphere -- an issue that he dealt with as he made his way to a desert runway landing. During SpaceShipOne's climb, Melvill said he also heard a surprising bang, coming from the engine area where a fairing holding the craft's nozzle buckled."  Please be aware that fair use laws indicate that this quotation in entirely legal. *grin*
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I don't know why, but I'm sad today. Not for any particular reason that I can find, either. Maybe it's the weather. Maybe it's some nagging doubts I have. Maybe it's something that I haven't uncovered yet.   It's cool today, but I'm not. My feelings are as warm as ever, except they feel tangled and mixed. They feel slightly out of tune. Signals are getting crossed somewhere.   Firefly   I have captured this morning's sadness in a mason jar and set in on the windowsill.  It is a firefly, a wastrel, flashing on and off that something is wrong, is going wrong, has gone horribly wrong,  but I have never been a cryptographer.  It is a firefly, the sadness, it is a firefly trapped, and  whispering a secret that I must know! but can't quite wrap my arms around.  It is a firefly, and I am its prisoner. 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So my father and Kristin are going to China today, taking the like 1:00 flight or something -- the details are still unclear -- and they just left. My mom, who's driving them to the airport, is in a bit of a strange mood this morning: she decided to tell me that I have nice ears.   Thanks , Mom. I have approximately fifty visible bodily features, and what do I get a comment about? My ears. Wow, I have a bright future in male earing advertising, that's for sure.  So what happens when the US passes laws that are bad for the information economy? What happens when copyright laws are twisted into a measure used soley to protect the profits of copyright owners? Well, the Digital Millenium Copyright Act happens, that's what happens. Now,  urlLink someone wants to edit little bits of it , and I say good luck. Looks like the Personal Technology Freedom Coalition, the Electronic Frontiers Federation and the American Library Association are all behind it. You can probably expect the American Civil Liberties Union to be not far behind all of them, crackpots that they are.  You know, it's interesting to watch the US slowly begin rolling back personal freedoms in order to guaruntee "security", a guaruntee that's dubious at best. Especially now. What have the governments newfound powers done against terrorism? Nothing, at least not that we know of -- which is of course the kicked, because they could foil the greatest terrorist plot ever created, and you might not ever find out about it for "security reasons". This makes me thankful that I live in Canada. I think, for the first time ever, that we have more civil liberties here than anywhere else in North America.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This comes directly from  urlLink Wired.com , and considering what a wash of rubbish copyright law is right now, I'm going to reproduce it in full.   How to Disappear   Your inbox is awash in spam, your boss is chuckling over your credit report, and you've got a sneaking suspicion that Uncle Sam counts how many Löwenbräu you chug. Yes, your privacy's shot to hell, and you're tempted to shrug and settle for an open source life. But privacy isn't like virginity, forever lost after the first trespass. With some work, "reprivatization" is possible. Use this three-tiered guide to pick a level of solitude. But be warned: Going all the way off the grid is more Ted Kaczynski than Howard Hughes.   Going   Diss credit: Want to be hard to find? Start by dashing off stern opt-out letters to the big database companies and credit bureaus - Experian, Acxiom, Equifax. These folks may make a mint peddling personal info, but they can be cajoled into stopping. First, though, they'll make you jump through hoops - like filling out a 1040-sized form or idling in toll-free hell. Junkbusters (www.junkbusters.com) has a good list of opt-out addresses.  Anonymize: Ditch your ISP and sign up with a service that lets you surf by proxy, keeping your IP address concealed. Send email via an anonymous remailer like Mixmaster, a digital middleman that scrambles timestamps and message sizes. And if you're going to be advocating the violent overthrow of the government or bragging about your cool new bong, make sure your remailer routes messages through multiple machines.  Grok the fine print: Boring as it sounds, read the privacy statements that clutter your mailbox around tax time and sever ties with companies that admit, "Our privacy policy may change over time" - industry lingo for "We reserve the right to screw you."   Going Further   Ditch the digits: Want to drop out? Start by rustling up a new Social Security number.  The Social Security Administration doesn't accept paranoia as a criterion for granting a new card, but it recognizes cultural objections and religious pleas. One stratagem: Contend that your credit has been irrevocably damaged by a number-related snafu, or that you live in fear of a stalker who knows your digits. Once you switch your SSN, never use it. Instead, dole out 078-05-1120, an Eisenhower-era card that works 99 percent of the time.  Call cell-free: Use the humble pay phone. Mobile phones are being outfitted with global positioning satellite chips to comply with an FCC mandate. By 2006, all wireless networks must feature 911-friendly tracking technology. Marketers are cooking up ways to capitalize, like zapping burger coupons to your Nokia as you stroll by a fast-food joint.  Pay full price: You may relish saving 10 percent on Prell, but deep-six your buyers' club cards. Supermarkets and pharmacies haven't yet perfected the art of data mining, but it won't be long. "If you're having a child custody fight, they could subpoena your frequent-shopper cards and say, 'Look, he's buying too many potato chips, he's hurting the kids,'" says Robert Gellman, a Washington-based privacy consultant.   Gone   Move: Want to go completely off the grid? Start by moving - address changes bedevil databasers. But don't buy a home. All those loan apps will blow your cover. Residential hotels smell like cheap cigars and urine, but at least you can register under a pseudonym. Give a fake address: 3500 S. Wacker, Chicago, IL, 60616 - the front door for Comiskey Park.  Toss your cards:Pay cash for everything, and don't plan on a life of luxury. Any (legal) cash transaction more than $10,000 triggers government reporting regulations, which means you can forget about that Cadillac Escalade you've had your eye on. Settle for the subway or bus, using coins rather than prepaid fare cards, which keep a record of trips.  Go incognito: Facial-recognition gear will soon be ubiquitous in public spaces. To fool the systems, invest in a pair of bulky aviator sunglasses and a hat. If you fear being tailed, alter your gait every time you hit the street - a pigeon-toed shuffle one day, a bowlegged amble the next. There are also Central American plastic surgery mills, beloved of drug lords, that can alter the loops and whorls on your fingertips. It'll set you back 10 Gs, but then, Costa Rican doctors have been known to accept gold Rolexes in lieu of cash.   - Brendan I. Koerner    © Copyright © 1993-2004 The Condé Nast Publications Inc. All rights reserved. (Ahem)  ...and that's how you do it, folks. I mean, how hard can that be? Just dropping off the face of the earth. Almost makes me want to do it.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I don't watch TV because of the ads. I like Mississauga busses because they literally have no ads in them. Though they are sometimes covered in them. I use Mozilla Firefox to block popups. I use the Adblock plugin to wipe away and collapse ads and adframes. I buy what little TV I do watch on DVD. I buy shirts that are shirts, not billboards. This weekend I bought a blank ball cap, just to make a point. I hate driving in Toronto because of the billboards and flashing advertisements.  But every once in a while there's an ad campaign that I see (unavoidably, like before a movie) that strikes me in awe of how clever advertisers really are in appealing to base human emotions. Take the Civic Nation commercials for a great example. Catchy hiphop beat with some nice flow. Wide-angle, colour-treated shots. One car is driving. It's a normal Civic. Suddenly, other Civics are following. Then there's more, and fancier. Tricked out. Lowered. Modded. Crossing a bridge. Finally, they come together like fighter jets in formation, driving through the desert.  And what are they selling? Is it the quality of the car? Is it the solid reputation of the Civic name? Is it price? Service?  No. They're selling cool. Attitude. If you own a Civic, you're part of something. If you don't own a Civic, you don't know what's going on. You're not part of the club. Doesn't matter who you are, as long as you own a Civic. Then you have a point of contact. You're in the nation.  Does anyone else see the vaguely religious overtones of this? And does it scare you?
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      "Foxhole"  Lopez felt the sand chafing between his toes, and knew the last strap of leather had peeled loose -  least, that's what he told me.  I looked, and yep, there were holes in his socks.  He took his boots off when we were finall in our foxhole - it was too stale underground to pass out -  and tried to mend the thing with a bit of cloth.  I just cradled my gun, feeling the metal still radiating the hot afternoon sun.  It would cool down in a bit.  So I watched Lopez tie a knot in the fabric and sit back, probably thinking about his wife and kids back home.  I don't have a wife or kids.  Not even a dog, unlike all the other guys,  and unlike them, I don't really care if I die or not.  I don't ask for much.  My gun still works, and my boots lace up tight.  I can still shrug my shoulders.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This is merely a test.
     

        
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Last night I began a small book called "Empire" by Niall Furguson, all about the rise and fall of the British Empire, and whether or not it was (to use his lingo) a Good Thing or a Bad Thing. I haven't even gotten a quarter way through it yet, but there has been a good bit about what went wrong in America, and why Canada didn't follow the American lead. Not to mention the subjugation of India, the Christian religious invasion of Africa, the beginning and ending of slavery in the British Empire, and the beginnings of the reign of Queen Victoria (who, I might add, is a favorite of mine).  I had trouble concentrating, but it's a good read. Concise, alive, witty, and historically accurate.  I've always wondered. How can you be  sure  that the history books have it right? Maybe a whole lot of selective editing and memory "lapses" have ensured that we read a slightly -- or even very -- warped history of the world.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I have learned a new bit of female parlance: "It crossed my mind," which, when translated, means, "I've been seriously and extensively considering it."  Oh joy.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The acronym "NEW" stands for No Electronics Week. It stands for getting back to the things that really matter. To remembering where we came from and to find out where we're going without the haze of LCDs and CPUs in the way. It's about becoming old to find the NEW.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This morning I broke out in hives. I drove to work caressing the sterio. Hugged the computer as soon as I got in to work.  Okay, I'm lying. It's actually been quite nice so far. Some incense, some 1998 Burton Chiraz, and I bought the first three Harry Potter novels just so I can see what all the fuss is about. And if, in grand Douglas Wilson style, there  is  nothing wrong with them, I will personally hunt down the people making Christians look like fools and whip them with a wet noodle.   Nothing else new. Got into a discussion about biblical inspiration and how to prove it without resorting to circular reasoning. Got into a discussion (again) with the ignorami that insist on labeling music "entertainment only" and going from there. And no wonder we have generation of kids that like Kid Rock. They just don't know any better.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Friday night I had vowed to clean up my house, and despite the fact that Mary, Gus, and Nick went out and did something that may or may not have been fun, I stayed home and bloody well cleaned the house. Exciting. And, believe it or not, it's clean. Needs a bit more work, but we're almost there. I even filed all my paid bills and receipts and stuff that I'll need down the road for some reason. Makes me wish there was an alternative to filing that involved a scanner and a computer, but right now that's not an option.  Saturday I got up late and did a load of wash. Then off to Burlington to go bike riding with Nick. We went all the way down to Lakeshore and watched a bit of jazz. I have become convinced that I need a mountain bike as well as a road bike. And some maintainance stuff for both of them. Watched the Bourne Supremacy. Pretty good movie. Better than most of the crap out there right now. Had a payphone conversation with a certain female. Went home. Finished reading a bit of "Mere Christianity". Also working my way through "The Flying Inn" by G.K. Chesterton. Interesting, if confusing. Had a bottle of Sleeman Honey Brown. Distictive, but perhaps a bit too smooth. A bit weak perhaps? Better than generic domestic -- so's drinking toiletwater -- but not by a whole lot.   Sunday I got up late again: the beauty of having church at 2:30. I haven't been to the Presbyterian church in a long time. We out biking in the Mississauga Greenbelt, only to find that it ends at the 403. But you can bike the whole way down the thing. Lots more cement that you'd like to see, so there's probably a lot of lime leakage and stuff like that. Still, it's a greenbelt, and that's better than nothing. I think. Went to bed later than I should have.  Also! This week is non-electronics week! Of course, here at work, I have to use them. But at home, with the notable exception of my alarm clock, car, and phone, there will be no electronics in use whatsoever. This includes all three computers, the PS2, the television, the Palm Pilot, and the Remote Missile Launching Station. Oh, right, the last one was fictional. This will be a very hard week. I will also only be available from 7 - 6 every day via email.   I'm already starting to sweat and shake.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      In Mississauga, there's this gas station on the corner of Derry and Kennedy. They know me well. I stop in there and pick up a coffee every morning (and, by the way, next week I step down to large coffees in the morning), and every once in a while pop in for a cold drink of some sort. Speedpass helps.  Anyways, pretty much every Thursday this place decides to drop its gas prices to somewhere around the 68 cent mark, causing major lot congestion. It's become the local watering hole. Or in a Pumba-esque sort of way, the local gassing hole. I topped up my tank for the mere price of $20.   I also figure that by forgoing the morning coffee, I can save myself close to $400.00 a year.   And I can even remember when gas was 50 cents per litre or less. Of course, back then you could buy a burger for a dollar, but I digress.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      In the comment field of my last post on marriage, this was added:   hey it's me again. your second post on this subject was an improvement. you obliterated the first 1/2 of my reply. but the following has yet to be responded to:  (1)"first of all, you wouldn't want your kids walking innocently in the park and seeing something immoral taking place (i.e., drugging, drug-dealing, boozing, violence, bestiality, vandalism, foul language, etc.). obviously we can't shelter them, but we work to keep our societies free of such actions taking place without consequences. your child suffers much less harm from witnessing any of the above if a cop screams into the scene and shows discipline, than if they are done and not challenged, if they are considered normal. if we allow homosexuality to be okay, same-sex couples cuddling and kissing on a park bench will not be challenged authoritatively. it will be seen as normal. THAT is harmful to your child.  (2)"secondly, don't forget the children these same-sex couples will be adopting. how will they grow up?  (3)"we need to keep in mind the practical outcomes of such allowances."   In answer to point (1), yes. You're right. Children must be guarded, from your perspective. My whole point is that you have no right, in an a-moral, religiously free country, to impose your own system of morality on others, whether they be gay or straight. You can only impose on them what laws the country has, and only then by force of those entrusted to guard and make sure others are upholding those laws. If you're telling me that an amoral state is  wrong , then so be it. There are great evils in both secular and religious authority. If you're saying a (supposedly) amoral state should be making moral judgements about behavior in its constituents bedrooms, than no. That's just wrong. The government should only be able to make rules that it can enforce, and rules that can quantifiable be deemed societally helpful.  Now, you mention the park. This is government property, and it has the right to make up whatever restrictions it wants on that land. It can ban kissing, handholding, and baking of cakes if it really wants to. It can put blindfolds on small children who walk through. That's the government's business. However, their business is not to punish the behaviors of men and woman in their own houses, except in extreme cases, aberant and unnatural as those behaviors may be. Let me ask you a question: in the state's eyes, what is worse, spaking or homosexuality? Two homosexuals perhaps love eachother and are expressing their love. On the other hand, the father is beating his child! Of course this is only a surface evaluation -- you and I both know that spanking is beneficial, because history bears that out, and that homosexuality is a punishment on a country, because scripture says that. But the state has neither the means nor the option to make a judgement scrictly along scripural lines, unless it is a scripturally-based state, which lead to it's own set of thumbs and strawberry tarts.  (2) is answered in the logic of (1). Obviously I can't prevent a gay couple from "having" kids. Obviously a secular state, hamstrung as it is, cannot as well.  The whole point is that governments do not make and enforce moral reality. We all know this. The government could throw all gays in jail and electroshock them until they renounced their lifestyle, sure, but that would be stepping outside its purvue. Remember, the US and Canada are nations under God -- but from what the framers of the Constitution and our national anthem said about it, they really meant nations under god, small "g". That's the sort of all-inclusive everyone's-god's-a-God bullshit (to quote Luther) that the Enlightenment *cough,cough* brought us. And they've taken it and ran with it. And in that setting, in the setting we're in, the public morality determines the government's morality, not the other way around.  So, who's fault does that make it, the moral cesspool our culture is playing around in? Well it can't be Johnny Government's, because he's just the mast of the ship if you know what I mean. He's the compass that points toward the closest magnet. It's not Bill Populace, he doesn't know any better. He's a Bhuddist and a Mormon and a Muslim and does transcendental meditation in the park when his toaster stops working. The fault is ours. Yours and mind. The world needs a moral revolution in the form of revival -- again, not in the form of legislation -- a sweeping world-changing sort of thing. Christianity is the  only  solution to present-day moral chaos, not Christians insinuating their moral code on the unwilling who happen to live in the same country. That creates resentment, and worse, opression.  (3) The practical implications are much more immense that I even thought at the beginning. Literally thousands of laws would need to be re-written, and concepts of spousal benefits rethought. Of course, as it is, marriage is a tax disaster. That's one problem this idea would solve.  Thoughts?
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, who knows what it could look like, eh? But quoting from  urlLink this article about the past , here's maybe an idea:   Predicting the future is a risky business.  Even visionaries turn conservative when facing that challenge. But the four winners of this year’s Draper Prize from the US National Academy of Engineering are as qualified for the task as anyone. Bob Taylor, Alan Kay, Charles “Chuck” Thacker and Butler Lampson were recently honoured for their groundbreaking research at Xerox Palo Alto Research Centre in California 30 years ago. Among their accomplishments: accurately envisioning the office of the future that most of us now use daily. The four winners shared with PC World their views on the future of computing.   Only the beginning  “The computer revolution has only just begun,” Lampson says. The four expect that several hot areas of research and innovation will become even more important when combined: wireless technologies, ever-higher-speed communications, speech recognition, improved search engines, and management of huge volumes of related information. These segments’ total impact could be much larger than the sum of their parts. “I think wireless will make a fundamental difference in the way people use computers ... this will cause a wide variety of new devices to appear,” says Thacker, who worked with Lampson on Microsoft’s Tablet PC designs. Tired of your PC’s messy, pesky cables? The solution may be wireless. “I think that short-range wireless will take over for nearly all connections between computers and peripherals, because it’s much more convenient,” Lampson says.   Next step: PCs fall apart  Look for the traditional PC – keyboard, screen, hard disk, network adapter — to become “disaggregated”. The pioneers expect that the components will become separated but will continue to work together. Many computer research groups at universities, and at private and corporate labs, are working on this assumption. As wireless access becomes common and cheap, as chips and communications get faster, and as prices continue to drop, there is less reason to tie a disk to a keyboard and screen. The network will be everywhere, both wired and wireless. A PC’s screen could also become whichever display device is closest. Current research includes such examples as flashing advertising panels in the supermarket checkout line. Or you may pause to check data on an office hallway’s video wall that displays a computer’s output using special electronic paints already in development. Another future display in the works is a laser-powered holographic system that shows text and video in the air using tiny programmable actuator chips called MEMS (micro electromechanical systems, already used in many commercial products). Or the display you use might be a piece of electronic paper that you crumple when you’re through. Input and control could be via a wireless keyboard, a handwriting-recognition device, or an array of microphones embedded in the surface of your desk or your car’s dashboard. With voice recognition technology, such input devices are always listening for you to “wake up” the computer.   Embed and spread  Fundamentally, most computers may simply vanish from view, either through disaggregation or by becoming embedded into walls, appliances and even your clothes – or a combination. “Although putting computers into things like toasters and refrigerators seems a little silly today, it is becoming increasingly less silly,” says Thacker. Indeed, some consumer electronics stores already sell early versions of computerised appliances. Cars already have dozens or hundreds of computers built into them to control everything from the steering wheel’s angle to the DVD player, as well as to monitor petrol consumption or to power the wheels, brakes and suspension. Lampson wants to see that go a giant step further. He envisions cars that drive themselves, primarily for safety reasons. Meanwhile, expect the way you get your telephone service to change, especially with the advent of voice over internet protocol (VoIP). The hold-up is the so-called last-mile problem: the expense of rewiring that last few hundred metres from the network in the street up to your door.   Qwerty talk  Also still early is speech-recognition technology. A number of products are out, but the technology is less effective when tasks are complex, such as correctly recognising and responding to voice commands. Even relatively simple speech dictation usually requires positioning a microphone near the mouth to cancel extraneous noise. “The larger problem of speech [is that it] requires human-style commonsense reasoning to be pretty well done by machine,” Kay says. “I can’t think of any good reason why this won’t happen. It’s just a difficult problem to [deal with] outside of restricted contexts.” Lampson concurs: “Getting the computer to understand what you say to it and behave intelligently is an entirely different matter” from speech recognition.   Self-aware computers  Even after 60 years of development, computers are still basically machines that can only crunch an endless stream of ones and zeros. Although several research projects are focusing on imbuing computers with reasoning and decision-making cognition – one has been under way for 20 years – that remains a holy grail for computer science.   I believe the children are the future  “I don’t think anything really important has happened yet,” Kay says. He predicts that changes will come as computing “co-evolves with the users, especially children, until a new kind of fluency will be able to happen. And then, those after us will see some big changes.”  
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, one of the cases I've been following lately has finally been dismissed. SCO (Caldera)'s case against DaimlerChrysler,  urlLink as reported here [Groklaw.net] , was thrown out today by a female judge/olympic speed champion. Which is, of course, good news for those of who use and/or care about the Linux kernel.   Also please note that the Groklaw observers are rabidly partial and pick sides with apparent alacrity, so everything they say is biased towards Linux and away from SCO. But then, at least they're honest about it, in a sort of Slashdot way.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It was an interesting night last night. I met up with a suburned Nick and we hung out and talked and drank Jones Soda. And watched  I, Robot  which, to my suprise, was a very good movie. Better than Spiderman 1, also a great movie. I need to watch Spiderman 2, just to see if it's as good/bad as I've heard. As in my friends say it's horrid, but all the critics like it. So who's right?
     

        
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Since the sermon on Sunday was quite vocal about how important it is for parents to know what their children are listening to, Mom, this is what I'm listening to.   Radiohead ,  Kid A, Amnesiac,  and  Hail to the Thief   Explosions in the Sky ,  The Earth is Not a Cold Dead Place , and  Those Who Tell The Truth Shall Die, Those Who Tell the Truth Shall Live Forever   Xiu Xiu ,  These Fabulous Muscles   The Listener ,  Whispermoon   Sev Static ,  Speak Life   Coldplay ,  Parachutes   Andrea Bocelli ,  Verdi   Dawn Upshaw ,  Sings Pucelli and Bach   Espers ,  Espers   Derek Webb ,  She Must and Shall Go Free   Godspeed You! Black Emperor ,  Yanqui U.X.O ,  Lift Yr. Skinny Fists Like Antennas to Heaven   Thee Silver Mt. Zion ,  This is Our Punk Rock   ... and the list continues. Now, Mom, you can make sense of some of these incomprensible titles. I mean, I can't.
     

        
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      One of my friends over at the Cmcentral message boards, known as BennieM, had this to say about the foundation of government (evolving from a discussion on whether or not one should support laws that legislate ultimate morality, which evolved from a discussion about the Religious Right):    ...But I'm going to ask you to think harder than normal. I think most of you ultimately have self-contradictory beliefs in government.    The answer to your question is very simple: Because a law is not supposed to "promote what is good and right". The purpose of the government is not to make people better people. If you firmly believed that the purpose of government was to make people better people, then the logical conclusion would be to support an absolute monarchy with as extensive a feudal system as possible and strict rules for The Powers That Be. In Christian ethics, humility is, of course, one of the greatest virtues. To promote it is to promote what is good and right.    There is no system of government that better promotes humility than one in which the most people are subjected to rule which they cannot overturn and which they must either serve humbly or hate spitefully; this would, of course, provide the ultimate promotion of comportment that is good and just. By this system, you would find more and more people turning to the Father of Lights to light them afire with love and strength to do their duties, because there is no other relief; this happened in the Middle Ages and beyond. The select few who were in charge would, of course, be subject to many strong temptations, but by enforcing strong legislation this could make them better people also; the absolute monarch himself might have to suffer by notbeing made more moral himself, but this is, of course, a small price to pay if our goal is indeed promoting as much "good and right" as possible.    But I doubt you support fiefdoms, absolute monarchy, or slavery. Therefore you do not really think the purpose of government to "promote what is good and right" and establish "moral laws", if that means laws that will make people good people.    I believe, and suspect most of you believe, that the purpose of a government is to promote or allow good moments: a couple on a date at a restaurant, a kid on rollerblades in the park, two friends out fishing on the river, a bookworm curled up by the winter fire. All our wars, all our taxes, all our elections are in vain if they’re not aiming at this. This is why we ban murder and allow people to lie. This is why we make theft illegal and civilly turn a blind eye to unforgiveness. This is the real deal: something good and thick to aim at promoting.    You have asked, Why we do not support what is right when we have an opportunity to do so. The answer is, We ought to; but with what means we do it is the question. You do not, I imagine, think we ought to create a secret police to force everyone to be moral at gunpoint; that is a misuse of power. Is it proper to support what is right with a government also?    No, it isn't, because the reason behind having a government is damage control and protecting moments where good things can happen; it is not assuring piety itself. We do not actually believe that is why governments exist. If they exist to promote equitable distribution of power, as in Reinhold Niebuhr, that is not because equitable distribution of power is itself the Good. It is not; the universe is set up like a complicated and divine monarchy, not a democracy. Equitable distribution of power is a means to getting Johnny to grow up to love watching a sunset, reading Chaucer, playing football, or eating a fudge sundae. It is, in effect, to let him be fully human, not to make him a good human. It is to prevent what Coleridge records,     O grief— but farewell, Love! I will go play me With thoughts that please me less and less betray me.     Theft, murder, and the like are the prime enemies of this; that is why we think they ought to be removed, not because we think them wrong. Our moral judgments have nothing to do with why we support legislation, except by what is, in logic, an "accident".    This is why I believe in democracy, even though I observe that monarchy itself is a very good thing; monarchy is the foundation of the universe. I do not believe in democratic action because I think everybody good enough to have a say. I believe in it because I don't think anybody good enough to have unrestrained power. I believe in it because it is damage control and will hinder those moments that destroy Johnny's love of nature, poetry, food, games, music, and all the other good things of this world—this  were-eald , this Man's Age.    This is why I support legislation on slander and copyright but draw the line at lying and fornication. A secret police itself may act immorally, but the legislation that creates one is not immoral because secret police are bad; it is immoral because it is a lie against what we believe a government exists for. To live in fear of losing your store will not help your leisure time to become holier. To worry that you might be shot dead tomorrow cannot help you love your wife better.    You are not asking the right questions. You're blowing on the fire before you try to light it; and that's just getting us all dusty. The issue isn't whether this is a "moral law", if that means one that promotes what is good and right. It's whether this is a "moral law" in the sense that it agrees with why we legislate in the first place; that is, if the law itself is moral and not an hypocrisy. 
     

        
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      While giving my kitchen a somewhat cursory going-over, I have coined a new cleaning maxim: "When in Doubt, Use Alcohol." No, this does not mean that before cleaning one should have a beer. Don't drink and clean. You could end up plugging a toaster into the sink.     Oh, what am I saying. If it helps you before you begin cleaning, have a glass of Burton Cabernet Sauvignon (1998 Reserve) before you begin. The subtle flavour of peach wood, and a good nutty taste with a good hint of leather. Really. I know what I'm talking about.    But I figure, what does the modern kitchen cleaner have on rubbing alcohol? There's nothing that stuff can't do, including but not limited to dancing a jig on your counter. Or maybe that was me. I forget. When I passed out, I think I was doing the stove, cause I woke up sweating.     That was a joke, for the humour-challenged. I didn't pass out. Some fruitflies did. Nothing like chasing down fruitflies with alcohol whilst screaming, "Die, kraut mothers!" or something dramatic.    Now Playing: Listener, "Whispermoon", Track 4.  
     

        
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, so my idea of letting religions marry people to eachother as they see fit isn't going over too well with anyone that I raise it with. Most of the time the objection is "well then they'll be able to do whatever they want!" but some of the time the objection is the wide-ranging legal implications that are present, not to mention the fact that even this idea still needs safeguards.    Of course, that sort of brings us back to the question, What Is Government For? which stems the debate in the first place. In my view, the primary purpose of government is to create order and protect its citizens. How far it can go in creating and maintaining that order is another question in itself.    So, let's say that children need to be protected. Obvious, because they don't have the mental or physical capacity to be in a marriage relationship. Animals also would need protection, unfortunately. Let the only restriction be that marriage must involve consenting human adults. Then let religious authorities do their thing, whatever that thing may be. Frankly, it's not the job of the government to enforce a certain type of morality on a group of dissenting people: that's how democracies work. You don't change people from the government down, but people change the government from the grassroots up.     So let the government wash their hands of it, get out of the marriage business, let the debate die down, and let the Christians get about their bloody business of evangelizing the world, instead of bothering with every bill C-250 that comes along, or with the latest petition that everyone is circulating.   
     

        
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Women can be a lot like those little tomatoes you get in your salad. If you're brusque with them (imagine spearing that tomato with a fork), they're dismissive (and the tomato rolls away), even when you're right. But if you give it a little patience (a bit of gentle pressure and  then  spear the darn thing), most times it goes over fine (and you get to eat a tomato, unless that's not your picnic, in case you suck and should be reading another blog), even when you're wrong. Wierd.  
     

        
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So last night I'm driving home from Ancaster, exiting the QEW/403 combo to the Ford Drive/403 offramp, when I see a Ford Focus ZX3 execute a bizzare (but not unheard-of) cross-highway lane-change to get onto the same exit. Now, seeing that we're not the most common cars on the highway -- whole lot more sedans than hatches, you understand -- we feel a certain gas-pedal-pressing kinship. And so we do this racing thing down the highway for a while, until my conscience got the better of me, and I pulled onto the Hwy 10 offramp. Those things got the better of me.    But the thing that got me, on that highway, is that at night, all the slow driver don't drive in the  right  lane like they do during the day, but right in the freaking middle of the highway. So that the cars going faster than they are (such as everyone else) have to either pass on the left and congest the entire highway while doing, or pass on both the left and the right, one of which is illegal. Point #2: if you are a defensive driver, remember that defensive driving does not mean timid driving. Timid driver make other people have accidents, because their actions are almost impossible to predict. If you don't know what to do in a dangerous situation, you  are  the dangerous situation. You're just waiting to happen. Point #3: immigrants should not be allowed to drive unless they know how, regardless of whether their buddy works at the licencing office or not. I mean, I have no problems with immigrants. They can come if the government wants to let them. But for goodness sake, there are  so many of them  in Mississauga that can't drive worth six beans and a hoola hoop that it's getting out of hand. When you see three cars across three lanes driven at -60 kph by three men wearing three garish turbans, it's time to tell them that they're not in India any more, and it's most likely that they won't hit a cow if they go too fast. Sorry about the blatant racial steriotyping there... Point #4: If you are a woman, get off the road.    Okay, that last one was a joke. I know quite a few excellent female drivers. And yes, I'm talking to you, hot stuff. ;)  
     

        
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, this is my thing here. Every time the government ratifies a civil union (the only recognized marriages), they're making what is basically a moral judgement, because the only civil unions that the state will currently ratify are unions between one man and one woman. Now, obviously the government has no philosophical basis for this particular value judgement, considering that they claim to be an amoral state. So what will eventually end up happening -- as it is -- is that various groups with "alternative" lifestyles will be haranguing the state for legal status as perfectly sanctioned civil unions.    I propose to circumvent this problem, along with several others. Take control of marriage out of the hands of the government. With the way common-law marriages are happening nowadays, what's the different? We certainly can't  force  everyone to accept a Judeo-Christian mindset. So we have to either convert the entire culture, or work with what we've got.     So let the various religions marry people the way they want. Within limits of course. You shouldn't be able to marry a child, because the state still has a legitimate interest in protecting children against predators. But that would solve the problem of a supposedly amoral state making value judgements about something they really can't control. And it would also remove even more of the hands of the government from meddling in church business. Marriage is still a religious affair. The state has co-opted the process. And it needs to go back where it came from.  
     

        
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've turned down a certain road at least seven times in the last two weeks to see cops pulling into the same street. You might say that this is a lot of cops, and I'll tell you that I work right next to a police station. So there's cruisers everywhere, all the time. The thing is, these cruisers never use their signal lights, or as some people like to say, their blinkers. It annoys me. They just scurry around at the speed of light on little industrial streets and ignore all the traffic laws that they feel like, and it makes me mad. I could get a freaking ticket if I did that sort of thing. Which I don't.   But the police force, just like every other authoritative body, needs to lead by example  first , and then force of law or force of authority  second . This becomes more important the closer and more personal the authority structure becomes. I'm not saying this is right, but this is the way it is. Deal with it. The government, well, it doesn't really matter a whole lot whether or not you respect it, because you have to pay your taxes or they'll boot you to prison. However, people like fathers (with teenagers), elders, and bosses don't have this option. It matters very much whether or not people respect you -- not because the people so much know how to do this, but that you are  respectable . If you are respectable, then no one has any excuse. Not even the tiny bit of understanding that can be given to kid who doesn't respect his father when the old man's a jerk.  Christian culture is really the only kind of culture worth having. The only one that really has the "elevation" of humanity in mind. No other culture that has developed has done that. And modern agnostic "culture" is laughable at best. I mean, come on. Agnostic culture? Riiiight.
     

        
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Laura and an amazing handsome (but not too tall) guy exited the most rocking concert of their lifetime by the side door. Everyone else was filtering out of the building into a slow drizzle. Laura looked at him; probably the cutest guy she had ever seen. Not too tall, but craigy. She didn't know his name, but now, in the moment, that didn't seem to matter. Somehow she had ended up holding his hand as he puller her from the building, adrenaline still coursing through both bloodstreams.  Oh, it had been a concert. Right. Not a concert. The concert. The concert to end all concerts.   They collapsed at the side of the building, both laughing. It had been a rush getting to the exit -- quite literally a rush. Under, over, around people.  He pointed. "That's my car." Laura looked, and there it was. An old brown minivan of the Aerostar variety. Here, it was a rarity.   "You call that a car?" she asked, laughing again.  He grinned like a kid. "Oh yeah, quite."  Then he pulled her again, over to the van. Suddenly, a beeping. Cellphone. Pulling it out of his pocket, the guy flipped it open. His eyes filled with concern. He said something soft, something almost frantic, and flipped it closed again.  "My mum," he said, getting into the driver's seat. "She's had a stroke."  Oh, thought Laura. A stroke.   He turned the key. Engine started. Into gear. He didn't let the clutch out. Instead, he handed her the phone. "Take this," he said. "Call me."  She watched him go. Watched him circle the parking lot. Felt drops on her shoulders. When the van came back, she wondered if he wanted the phone back. But no. He leaned out the window. Asked her what her name was.  "Laura," she told him. "I'm Laura."  He nodded. "Take this, too." He leaned out the van window and kissed her on the lips. Then waved. Drove off.  She put a hand to her lips. Strange.   Flipped the phone open. Caught a glimpse of a few numbers. Watched the battery die.  Smiled.  Cried.
     

        
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Life moves in rhythms and cycles, and it seem sometimes like the crest of a wave, sometimes the trough. Often like this is the  same  crest and trough as before. Like circles.  But then, circles bring their own perspective. Earth revolves around the sun, but the sun is constantly in a state of flux. A moon circles the earth, and though it follows the same circuit, the vista always changes. Circles bring perspective. They allow reflection, the sort that forward movement does not always allow. Every time around brings new thought, a different angle on a problem, sheds another colour of light.  Circles are not always the evil they seem, says I. I have been running circles around myself since the day I was born.
     

        
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      There is nothing worse than a lippy kid. You know, one of those who thinks they can say anything to anyone in any way or at any time that they please. Just won't shut up. It's become epidemic, but you're not allowed to just take them and give them the good tanning they obviously need. Really, they need some respect spanked into them good and proper.  But this brings me to that other thing. You know, how nobody has discipline these day. Like, for goodness sakes people, the truth is self-evident! You say that spanking ingrains violent tendencies in small children, but the evidence of a largly non-spanked society gone violently haywire asserts something else indeed. It boggles the mind that humans insist on believe whatever the ahem they want in face of incontrovertable facts. Is this not insanity? In fact, I think that spanking does good for a child along those lines but in the  opposite  way. It is a humane, guided use of violence -- well, not even violence, really. Just force. It gives them a taste of what violence is like and at the same time teaches a lesson in restraint and necessity.   And in a somewhat bizarre footnote, I have to say that having a large family is an adventure in discipline. Thus, I shall never have one. There. I said it.
     

        
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      That's right. You heard it first here. A geekblog in progress has been discovered at  urlLink http://unshortness.blogspot.com , and there is geekiness aplenty, enough to keep even a slashdotgeek happy for like ten seconds.  Also, in other news, I got my new insurance in today, and behold! it was cheaper than it was before. And I had a 1998 Sunfire GT. I tell ya, add two doors to your car, and you're a family man.  Now in place: a one coffee per diem cap. So that means one xl 2c in the morning and no more. Then I'll wean myself to large. Then to medium. Then skip small and go off altogether! Darn, I'm good.   That last bit was sarcasm.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well, here's a link for you:  urlLink Wikipedia.com, a free online encyclopedia  with over 300,000 articles. All user-contributed. Pretty sweet place!  If you ever want to post mindlessly about music, you might try  urlLink the CMCentral forums . Frankly, the rest of the site isn't worth much, except to read rather inanely positive reviews, but there are some intelligent people that inhabit the forums, such as Murlough23 and bloop, and of course me. You may all laugh now. And some guy named Steve.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So on Saturday I got my new Ford Focus from the dealership, and it's a sweet little ride. ZX5, black, all the bells and whistles (except leather and the Audiophile system). Power windows, locks, mirrors; heated seats and mirrors; traction control; A/C; and of course a tonne of bootspace (by which I of course mean trunkspace).  Set me back a fair bit of change, but because Ford Credit gave me a 0% interest loan, it's basically like forced saving, without having to pay interest like all the other "forced savings" I do.  It's nice though. If you finance a car on a 48 month term as opposed to a 60 month (goodness, that's a very long time) term, they give you $1500 cash back. Of course, Mr Hamstra says that goes to show how much money they actually make on each car. I think it's probably something to do with the fact that one extra year at 0% interest costs Ford Credit somewhere near $1G. And the fact that they're trying to make up in volume of vehicles sold what they lost in margin on the final cost.  And so, ladies and gentlemen, automobiles have become commodity items. Ta-da!
     

        
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Every once in a while I get an email from someone asking why I don't ever post about subject x on this blog. Well people, I'm a human being. Not to sound snotty or anything to those people who post every six hours, but I have a life. A good one. I don't have time to be the Encyclopaedia Brittanica, you know?   But the main reason is that there's a whole lot of things I don't care about. Like buying furniture, or the latest in car. Or baby clothing. Or why and why not someone should read Cosmo Girl. Although I start to care about it more when I see the crap that people read. No offence, Cosmo Girl. Oh wait, I also don't care about offending Cosmo Girl. They stink. They prey on the insecurities of pre-teens. They should be hung, prominently, in the middle of my local Gap store. In effigy, of course. And then burned. With torches and pitchforks.  Of course, sometimes I start to care about things, like I just did, up there. I can't help it. It happens.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      See, I don't like the band Kutless. They are to me everything that the Christian music scene should not be: derivitive, bland, and shallow. Obviously a product of their influences, they never actually rise above or even approach those influences. And that's not exactly cool points for a band that lists Linkin Park as a influence, albeit a small one.   It's time Christians stopped imitating the world. I mean, sure, take their forms. Take rock, take pop (but only a tiny little bit of it), take classical, take whatever, and make it  better , not just a mediocre or even good knockoff of something someone else has already made. Why recycle crap when you can make good music? It would be one thing if Kutless was imitating the innovations of bands like Talk Talk or Godspeed You! Black Emperor. But they're not. They're amalgamating bands that don't themselves make good music. Creed. Linkin Park. Those sorts of things. Add a splash of generic Christian AC (they have to have  some  radio play, you know), and there you have it.  Or, in my case, there I don't have it.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, it's a big topic. And I'm not going to address it all here. Not all at once. And I'm not going to write a book on it, here or elsewhere, considering that most of my friends have been made over the last few years.   With that little bit of a disclaimer, let me begin.  Friendship requires flexibility. That's it. No more words. Just those. The topic's not very broad. You can learn these few words in a matter of seconds, process them, and throw them away. But don't do that. I know it's easy to say "be flexible" in a sort of academic, arm-chair-critic way, aknowledging the facts and then floating them on down the stream, but think about what that might mean. You need to be flexible.  This gets at the goal of all friendships. In all relationships. (And, if you can, divorce the words love and relationship from any romantic context for the time being.) I need to explain where I'm coming from first, so you can see where I'm going. What is the end result of all friendships? Is it to give? Yes, partly. Is it to get? Yes, partly. Is it to grow? Yes, again, partly. But at the end of all the being there for people, and loving, and bearing eachother up, what's the purpose? I think it's simple. You are friends to do nothing more than enjoy eachother.  Think about it. What's our highest goal in life? To glorify God. That's it. But how do you do it? By  enjoying  him. By finding joy in his company, in his doings, in the echoes of him you see in this world. And friendship in that context -- a Christian context -- is one of those God-echoes. We're made in his image. We enjoy friends.  But there's always going to be tension in this imperfect world. Always a bit of annoyance, maybe a friend who sometimes gets under your skin. This is where flexibility comes in. Relationships don't belong to anyone. They're sort of a joint chequings account, where you both have to sign on the dotted line. That means that your preferences aren't important, or at least as important as the friendship. Within reasonable bounds, or course.   That means that sometimes you're going to have to bend one way and not do or be something. Sometimes that means you're going to have to say something to a friend. If you're terribly uncomfortable in a relationship because of something that's going on, your friendship suffers. With major issues, you can't just set that discomfort aside. You have to deal with it. This is where the other side comes in. Because that friend needs to value the relationship just the same as you do. When you raise an issue, that friend needs to be able to process that without getting insulted or offended, and you the same.  What's a big issue, you ask? What's something that you should raise, what's something that you should aside? Well, you'll have to decide that for yourself. There's no fast and hard rule of thumb. But here's a little hint. If it involves a petty thing like hairstyle or the way the flip-flops drag along the ground, ignore it. Let it go. If it's something big, like suppose you hate swearing, and your friend is swearing, raise it. And don't be suprised if both of you have to move, not just one. Be tolerant of slip-ups, as long as they don't cause you harm. But above all, be sure that it's worth the trouble.  And that's about all I have to say.
     

        
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I received this insightful comment about my recent almost-rant about pride in heritages.   I guess if fighting wars and exploring worlds is what makes a heritage worthy of pride... then you have it right. Frankly I think you miss the point. There doesn't have to be greatness and fame for someone to be proud of their heritage.   First, this person (examining note: probably adult, at least some formal education) may indeed be right. Maybe there's something I'm missing. But if pride in heritage isn't based in what that heritage is made of, then what is it based on? Just be proud, because?   Second, I'd like to separate Reformed from Dutch. Those words shouldn't be used together. Dutchness is not an attribute to Ontario's Reformed churches. It's a detriment that needs to be excised ASAP. While I'm sort of meh about my supposed former Dutchness, I'm extremely proud of my heritage as a Reformed Christian. Not to the point of being arrogant and looking down on those wierd little Reformed Baptists and such, but it is after all the clearest view of scripture in existance.  So Mr/Mrs Annonymous, I ask that you explain your point further. If heritage isn't based on what impact the culture or country has made in history, then what is it based on?
     

        
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Just in case you don't have enough tension in your life, welcome to the internet, where frustration is to be had... for free! (Unlike, of course, people who buy Mercedes-Benz. They actually pay for it.)  Try, for starters  urlLink Frustration: The Trivia Game  which promises to be the most up-to-date trivia game ever. Thank goodness for  urlLink our old friends at Google  who make searching for those answers either very quick, or even more frustrating.   Or, if you don't want complex, try good old  urlLink Twenty Questions versus the computer . If you can win this one, congratulations. You know some obscure stuff.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, so we know the Japanese get all the cool electronics. But the Brits, man. England is so full of cool stuff. Examples: the London Tower, the now-dead Queen Mum, and about sixty thousand public houses.  Also now,  urlLink The Register reports on the Big Brother Awards , a sort of Oscars for the worst of the worst privacy invaders. Included are companies, civil servants, your favorite branch of the government, and the neighbor's dog. Okay, maybe not the dog. Read this and weep.  They should do this in the US, too. Like, there's so much material. Really.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink And today, from the CMCentral Forums:    (Wildcatblue7 @ Jul 4 2004, 05:23 PM) I freakin' hate these sorts of threads because all I see is attacks from both sides of the argument--those who emotionally connect and those who must critically examine everything. It's a two way street.   I disagree. That's like saying a woman can't be smart and sexy. And that threads about women must invariably be arguments between those who appreciate smartness, and those who appreciate sexiness.  But I see where both sides are coming from. For instance, I have no pretensions that Lifehouse is actually good music. It's not. It's pretty generic stuff, but I still like Stanley Climbfall, and I listen to it on occasion. On the far opposite is a band like Xiu Xiu that takes actual work to listen to.  However, there are bands -- and I think a band like Radiohead qualifies -- that have made music that connects with both types of people. Music that is deeply emotive, and deeply intellectual both in structure and in composition.  And I will be honest with you: I'm pretty sure you have something missing if you never emotionally connect with a song. And you also have something missing if *must* emotionally connect with everything you listen to.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The United States is a wierd place. Either you have a president that encroaches on civil rights, or you have a pretentious left-wing nutcase. Like, I'm mostly conservative myself, but when the US presidents claim to be conservative but at the same time spend money they don't have and such, I have to question whether or not they actually are what they say.  Maturity is a wierd thing, and a concept that not many people understand properly. And the way this culture ties maturity as a necessary product of age drives me crazy. Not every person who is of advanced age exhibits traits of maturity, an idea proved to me twice this weekend. By the same man. People have to get used to the idea that a 22-year-old and 40-year-old are  equals  unless one of them has proven himself to be more than that. Unless one of them is in a position of authority. But if you want respect because of your age, let your actions display that your age has taught you something about life. Otherwise, I have no time for the jabber.  Look outside your window. Are there grey clouds rolling over rooftops? Does the day look cool? There are these days in every soul. They roll over you, and then they are done.  For those of you about to go back to school again, be of good cheer. Things will be better this week.  I haven't had any caffiene today. That on top of not getting enough sleep to function properly. That on top of a few details. It's not the best day of my entire life, except for the fact that there is pizza on the horizon. Pizza! PIZZA!
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I love reasons to be optimistic in love. For that, my thanks. And my affection.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      When it comes to love I am continually an optimist.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I hate the Christian ghetto. But it's a nice place. There's people hawking Christian fridge magnets and Christian computer games on the side of the road. And it's clean, you know? If you swear, you get thrown in the slammer. But it's a nice slammer. You can walk down the street here and buy a Latte Christo or chow down on a MannaMuffin.  The only problem is it looks exactly like the Secular ghetto, just with a fresh coat of paint and brighter colours. And our fridge magnets are so much more encouraging.   You know what I mean? We're like the Jews. We've got scripture verses tied in little scrolls around our necks, and written all over our doorposts, but we've forgotten what it  means , dammit!   Can you think of any better way to trivialize Jesus than by drawing him as a cartoon figure on a freaking magnet that you stick on your fridge? Can you? I can't!  This was actually brought on by me going to Nick's workplace where he's a shipping person, and seeing the rows upon rows of "Christian" merchandise that was contained in that warehouse. And so much of it was just useless junk! Who needs a pad of paper that has a scripture verse on it? Why not just plain paper, or fancy paper without the Christian brandedness? Do people fancy themselves more spiritual because they have more junk? The Wall Street Journal, I believe, ran an article the other year about this. Incisively, they said that there was a whole lot more Christian merchandise being sold than ever before  but we're not getting any more spiritual!   Anyone else find that? We have the trappings of the religion, but there's not much to it other than those trappings. It's a house made of curtains. 
     

        
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The mind is a strange place. Thoughts are hard to control. And I'm not talking about your typical guy crime-of-the-mind stuff. I'm talking about having disciplined thoughts, not being petty, and being able to push out of your head thoughts that don't belong there. Like jealousy, annoyance, or uncalled-for anger. These are all forms of pettiness that I try to avoid. Unsucessfully, sometimes, but I try nonetheless.   I find the best thing to do (and this one works especially well for jealousy and unhealthy worrying) is focus on concretes. And by concretes I mean things that you're sure of. Things that you know. Like, if I'm worrying like a silly git that my wife (hypothetically) doesn't love me anymore, the concrete I can focus on is the fact that she's told me (hypothetically) that she does. Or if I'm jealous of another man's car or house or something, the concrete is the fact that in the end none of these things really matter. People aren't friends with me because of what I have, but because of what I am. The kinds of people that are friends because of stuff are predatory, leaches. They suck the blood out of you and leave when they're full.   For annoyance, there's not really much I can do. Some people are, frankly, annoying by virtue of the fact that they were born. Annoying to everyone. But there's also people that are annoying only occasionally, and annoying only when they do certain things. And there's people that clash with other people just because their personalities are so different or so very much the same. Ever notice that you tend to get annoyed with people when they have the same faults as you? I've noticed that, and it drives me crazy at myself.  Petty anger is another good one. Personally, I don't typically display my anger with fits of rage, yelling, that sort of thing. I sort of do a slow burn and then gradually fizzle out. But both blowing up and letting the acid drip go on inside are not good options. Now if anyone has tips on controlling anger, I want them. Because frankly there are one or two people in my life that know exactly how to drive me absolutely nuts, and they take pride in doing it.  I supposed sometimes it helps to focus instead of on the person and their absolute angrifyingness on the fact that they are human, and I'm human, and there's no point in one imperfect being getting mad at another imperfect being, but there you have it.   How do you control anger when someone is getting under your skin on purpose? Because, honestly, the anger doesn't spring so much from what the person is doing or not doing, but the fact that they're  trying  at it, with an intent to make me angry. Like teasing when I was a child. It didn't bother me so much what they said as that they were trying to tease me! I get tense just thinking about it.
     

        
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I wonder if people ever think about how uncharitable we are in our speech. Not so much to people's faces, no, we have a knack for being gracious there, but in private, in the little corner of your room where you talk to your friends. There.   Example. I'm growing sideburns. Nothing major, just some burns. Alright, to be accurate, they're huge. Think Elvis. Think Starsky and Hutch in disguise. And naturally, someone's going to make a comment. And it's one thing when someone says to my face, 'Wow, you look like a big shaggy dog!' Because, you know, I'm pretty much made of metal. Doesn't phase me. But when someone says behind my back, 'Look at those things. What's he trying to do, get attention? What a freak,' now, that's a bit more harsh. It's an attack on the basic level.   This is what I'm telling you, people. I'm telling me too, because God knows I'm not anywhere close to perfect on this one, but here's the deal -- nothing's safe. If people don't find out about it now, they'll find out about when God takes into account every idle word. Darn it, every idle email, phone call, slip of paper. Even every serious email where you're making a valid point and throw in an aside. These things cut. They wound. They kill, even. They're like cat litter on the rug. Nobody likes the stuff.  *pauses for breath*  Now, onto other things. Happier things. Ever notice how different friends bring out different things in you? It's just the way people are, but you're not the same person everywhere. Not even in public and private. You maybe be friends with Xander and Abbie, but maybe Xander brings out in you a sense of adventure, and Abbie calls forth  a compassionate side.   I've noticed this. Just a personal observation. Also, you become more and more like the ones you're around the most. You have that sense of adventure drawn out long enough, and it becomes integral. Maybe you become compassionate. Maybe you lose your lustre. Maybe you gossip.  Have you wondered, though, what if? What if a friend is drawing out in you the negatives? Maybe a lack of caution. Maybe a certain way of speaking. Maybe even a way of looking at people. How long do you go on? How can you stop that?  It makes me wonder if you can ever really change the combinations. 
     

        
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, so you know female cosmetic magazines? Have you ever read one, or even skimmed the product reccomendation pages? For crying out loud, girls, how long do you spend every day just trying to look perfect?  I mean, there's nothing wrong with the occasional facial masque, or a nice relaxing foot soak, or rubbing some ointment into your skin, but all these things I don't understand -- what do you do with them? How does one know which layer goes on first? How can that possibly be good for your face?  Personally, I don't even like makeup. I mean, some girls need it. They have skin that cries out for whatever that stuff is that you make skin look better with. But some -- nay, most -- girls are just fine without it. Maybe a little bit of mascara (okay, lots of it), but if you're going to put it on with a trowel, at least go all ironically goth so that you're a walking parody of the Jezebels of Hollywood or something.  Jezebel of Hollywood. Hmm. That sounds like a good makeup company name.
     

        
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I find myself thinking of Christian liberty too often in terms of abstracts. It comes, I know, from growing up in an individualised quasi-American anticulture, from regarding liberty as a concept to be merely a list of things that yes, I can do -- but of course, that approach is deeply flawed. And thus our current concept of what "freedom" is comes to be overbalanced on the  freedom  and very light on the  responsiblity . Sort of a culture of licking all the icing off the cake. When you're done, all you have is a sick stomach and a cake that would appeal mainly to barbarians.  Christian liberty is the same way as secular liberty, and the modern evangelical looks much like the the modern citizen who enjoys his vacation in Florida but doesn't like to vote. It's as if Christian liberty were a gold rush, and millions of people are flooding into a metaphorical California in search of a few nuggets of the yellow stuff, forgetting that they're all the while trampling down another man's vineyards.  I'll take an example. We all know, for instance, that there's nothing morally distinguishing about one's middle finger. It's just a finger. On the other hand -- so to speak -- the cultural component of raising one's middle finger to the sky doesn't involve so much telling your pagan fellow drivers to look up as it communicates a certain vulgar dislike. So one might say that there's nothing wrong with sticking up one's middle finger, but then again, there's something quite wrong with sticking up one's middle finger. And of course, the human mind is legalistic, so we like to pick at nits and split hairs about things like this, and I'm sure someone's going to read this and go,  well what about if I accidentally wipe my eye with my middle finger? Have I sinned?  And I will, of course, tell that special someone to go soak his head.  All this to say that we just need to know what things  mean . What does the middle finger mean? Well, that's obvious. And if it's not obvious, I'd suggest taking it up with your village's elders. What does spikey hair mean? That's suddenly not so obvious. There are those who will suggest that it implies rebellion. And -- in my own view -- it did, at least fifty years ago. But we no longer live in an age where one can count on one's castle to stand for three hundred years; cultural mores change quickly, and they didn't have so much gel in the 18th century.   This means more than anything that the debate has shifted. It's shifted from  what do the scriptures say?  (which is, admit it, pretty darn clear) to  how do I apply this culturally? . And this tends to be a more difficult task. I, for one, am not trained to think in the context of now. I live and act in the context of now, but hardly think that way. Which is interesting, because it seems that we argue in a perfect world and fail at living out that perfect world in an imperfect reality; we're all like closet communists, refusing to take notes on human nature, preferring to discuss how Marx would function in Utopia.
     

        
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I always wonder what people stare at others for. It's this steady gaze, it's sort of unnerving, and it's a source of endless mystery to me. Are they staring in dislike? Are they hoping to see a head explode? Are they merely trying to gauge reaction or read expression? I never know, and try not to do it.  Now this is a question for the masses: have yall ever noticed how easy it is to be a pompous windbag? Maybe not as in some British fellow constantly looking down his nose and speaking loudly at people, but just being full of oneself. Full of ones own opinions and viewpoints and advice, full to the point where people can no longer stand to tell anything or listen to you? Yeah, it's hard not to do. 
     

        
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's wierd what you find out, and the way you find it out, you know?   In other news, the week has begun and everything is fine and dandy. I ran out of room on my C drive earlier this morning (or / if you prefer), so I got to work late, having to fix that up. One thing that annoys me about windows is how it won't tell you what drive your programs are installed on when you're trying to remove them. Grrrr.  But, in the words of Relient K:   Marilyn Manson, he's not cool. Marilyn Manson went to Matt Hoopes' school. Marilyn Manson, he's not nice. Marilyn Manson shows are overpriced.   And that's all for now.
     

        
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      If you're a journalist in Afghanistan and you get your hands on two computers that belonged to Al Qaeda, what do you do? Well, turn them over to the CIA, of course. But first,  urlLink you copy the files for yourself . Then you write about it.  1. Get computers from Al Qaeda. 2. ??? 3. Profit!
     

        
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      What is love? Is love a choice? Is it an action? Is it something expressed in emotion? Is it perhaps a combination of both? When is the right time to start trying? When is the correct moment to end? How hard is too hard? How rough it too rough? How much is one person worth? How much is an idea worth working towards?
     

        
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Becka : "I've got a headache in my eye!"   Anonymous : "Relationships are great, but sometimes they suck. Like right now, it sucks. I mean, it's amazing, but it sucks, you know?"   Stu  (with little yellow forklift): "This is a fifteen hundred pound machine."  Me : "Don't drop it."   Me : "No, really Steve, that $88 goes towards us flushing the toilet every day. It's called 'overhead' ironically enough."
     

        
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's been a bit of wierd week. You know how you have days when everythings kind of meh? Yeah, having a few of those. I dunno. How do you explain to someone why you're feeling blah when there's no good reason? I'm in perfectly good health, God is alive, I have a job, I have good friends who love me, I have a functioning car that isn't going to break down any time soon, etc, etc. So why am I not bursting with joy?   Who knows. Maybe it's something. Maybe it's nothing. Maybe it's just life moving (to quote Jack Allen) "in rhythms and cycles." Next week will be better I think. Oh well, at least I don't pin my hopes on an expectation of always being happy. Which would be also knows as being discontent half the time.   And this is where my Jungian self-analysis ends. Finito!
     

        
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today I was mindlessly tumbling some thoughts in my head, and suddenly something struck me (much like when I was thinking about Kate back in the day and realised that she would hit lows every time she saw what's-his-face), something so obvious, something so brick-trucklike that I wonder how I didn't see it before. I'm not CIA analyst, alright? But there you have it.  So I investigated, and it's true. It was so absolutely true. No doubts. And I laughed gleefully, because I put two and three together and came up five. Finally!
     

        
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Recently Sufjan Stevens (of "Seven Swans" and "Michigan" fame) granted two interviews, one to the New York Metro, and one to Pitchforkmedia.com of all people. You may recall him as a multi-intrumentalist in the New York area, a prolific songwriter -- having vowed to do an album for each of the 50 American States -- a Christian, and a sort-of member of the Danielson Famile. Check out some of his music; it's really quite good.  First off,  urlLink Sufjan talks to the Metro about Top 40 pop  (and please forgive the fact that he liked Peaches), but he  urlLink chats with Pitchfork  about the state of modern music, what the Danielson Famile is like, and strangely, why rock music has such an aversion to overtly didactic themes. Enjoy.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I got my hands on a CD called "Under My Skin" by Avril Lavigne this weekend. The problem is, I was expecting to hate it, from what I've heard (the first single about not sleeping with a guy, which was like, good concept, bad execution), but it's actually catchy. It has no redeeming quality except that: it's catchy. So goodbye Miss Lavigne (the name always reminds me of Leslie Anne Lavigne, of Decemberists fame) and hello something better.  You know, I had this same thing with Linkin Park's debut album, "Hybrid Theory". Nothing to it but angry little man/boys screaming about their horrid love lives, but it was really catchy. "Meteora" didn't have even that grace.  And I don't want to go all no-good-canst-come-of-Nazareth on secular pop music, but will they every produce something that will appeal to me on more than the "catchy" level? For crying out loud, people, The Shins were able to make good deep songs with Beatle-esque arrangements, why can't you do the same with pop music? I mena, the last CD I can remember even slightly respecting was "Life for Rent" by Dido, and that's not saying much.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Have you ever wondered what the difference is between conscience and preference? It's kind of a fuzzy little old line, what with people feeling quite strongly about their preferences. Me, for example, I prefer playing volleyball to baseball for some very good reasons -- but that doesn't mean that I feel so strongly about not playing baseball that I never want to and try to stop people around me, you know?  People get like this with cars a lot, for some reason that I can't figure out. They prefer Chevies, or Mazdas, or just imports, or just European imports and then go out and act like anyone who buys anything else is insane. I've gotten a lot of that owning a Ford Focus. People are like, "You bought a Ford? Here, check out this cute acronym you've already heard 751 times!" Not that they know anything about the Focus, not really, but the preference and bias are still there.  Okay, so that's a bit more like fanaticism than preference-cum-conscience, but there's other places that this shows up, too. And none so sharply as in the church. Now obviously there're extenuating circumstances: this is, after all, religion, something that touches the innermost core of a person's being. But on the other hand, stripped down to its essentials, Christianity is really not so complex as we make it out to be. And a lot of what goes on around the essentials is tradition and preference. Not that there's anything wrong with that -- tradition has been formed over a long while, and while the tradition is useful, helpful, scriptural, and understood, there's no reason not to keep it in place. On the other hand, some preference and tradition is no longer any of those things.   Take as an example some Reformed (and sorry if it seems that I'm ragging on the good old Dutch Reformed, but to be fair, I've spent most of my adult life amongst them) churches and the emphasis they place on organs and hymnals. As if these things somehow sanctify worship, give it some sort of holiness that isn't present in the praise teams down the street, endow it with a gravitas the culture has forgotten.  The ironic this is that it  does do that . At least, it appears to. Hymns are wonderful gifts from God, no questions asked. Organs have an inherent magesty. But then, our worship of God isn't just about gravitas, magesty, sanctity, and deep theological treatises put to music; worship is also about the sheer joy and energy of exaultation, something that the hymns we sing -- face it -- aren't all that good at.   But in the face of everyone  knowing  this, or at least a lot of people admitting it, nobody actually wants to change. At least not now. And why? Because people would object, because some people wouldn't like it, and because (and this one always gets me) some consciences would be offended. And let's be honest, most of the people who fit this category are a) extreme Regulativists and b) old people. In the case of "a", I don't know how to deal with that. Regulativism  is  conscience-binding, for sure, but it's straight-up legalism. Inventing law from hints and echoes yanked out of context out of the scriptures.   But with "b", you have to wonder how someone can be walking with Christ for fifty, sixty, seventy years and still have a weak conscience? You'd figure that they might have begun to understand a few things in the meantime, and I mean no disrespect to the aged. Dr James McDonald even goes so far as to say that if you  understand the concept  of conscience, you are not a weaker brother. But I'm willing to bet that we're mostly mislabling this phenomenon, that these men and women have perfectly functioning relationships with Christ, not to mention intact and fleshed-out consciences. Maybe what we're dealing with is not conscience, but inflexible personal preference.  Not that somehow, because it's preference, you can just steamroll over them. They must be considered, just like everyone else. The thing is, they have to realize that preference is never a good reason to join or leave a church. Doctrine is a great reason to join or leave a church, whether or not the church is expressing the marks of a true church is a great reason, whether or not the church is an example of Christ's joy and love is a great reason, whether or not the church is alive or dead is a a good reason, even friendships can weight the balances between two churches. But personal preference in worship styles, clothing styles, building styles, or lifestyles is not. I'll go so far as to say almost never.   I would richly love to be part of a church that had a more contemporary worship style. But I can't find a good one that does, at least a good Reformed one that does. It would be wonderful to go to a church that doesn't make a big deal about whether or not a guy has an earing or not. But then, that's not important, is it? So I'll set aside that particular preference of mine. Restrict my freedom.   But it's not just about restricting freedom, you see. That's not what conscience is: when Paul talks about having one that's weak, the obvious implication is that it must somehow become strong. Weakness is not used as a metaphor because the Greek language was too limited in expressions. It was used because weak is bad, and strong is good. You might say that some people have to restrict their freedom out of love, but others (the ones with weak consciences) need to expand their boundaries out of the same love. The scriptures say do no injure, but they also say do not judge.   And by that I mean you may love the Chevy of worship, but remember the Ford. It's not so bad as you all think...
     

        
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Goodness, what a kitzchy movie. Cliched. Not to mention retarded. And hits a little too close to home. 
     

        
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I should call this blog The Weekend Report and Assorted Nonsense, because that's what it's becoming. Ah, devolution. But I have an excuse this week, much like last week, that only three of the days did I actually have internet connectivity.   Thursday I left to go camping. Of course, this isn't the sort of camping that involves hiking and lighting bark with flint and cooking eggs on flat stones; it was sort of camping the way the English "roughed it" at the base of Mt Everest. So yeah, I'm on my way to Port Burwell, and I remember as I'm driving that my Aunt Mary's place is just nearby, so I stop in for a quick chat and some nonexistant coffee. It was nice, and the countryside smelled that of that wonderful catch-all perfume: pig manure. Ah, memories, memories.  Got to PB and walked into the campsight to find Eric and Wassink lazing around, obviously waiting for the party to arrive (and looking up brightly as I did). So I hit the book (Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix) as they did whatever. Later, it was a gigantic Milles Bourne tourney which I ended neck-and-neck with the big W. Johan came later that night. And we did the normal guy things around the campfire: told uplifting jokes, drank ice-cold pop, and made smores. Wow, I just told lies. We didn't make smores, because someone forgot to bring graham wafers. *cough*eric*cough*  Friday was uneventful. Gus came. So not entirely uneventful.  Saturday, the girls came up (finally!). Let me tell you, bachelorhood is a great thing, no questions asked, but two days without even seeing a familiar girl? Oh, that's not good. Nooooooo, not at all.  Sunday we went to Church in the park, which was suprisingly not horrible. A Baptist guy preached and we sang some praise songs. Not the most focused sermon ever, but who am I to rate sermons? I don't even write them. And we can all remember what Voltaire said about critics, who then proceeded to give the back of his neck a friendly introduction to Mr Guilloutine.  Now here I am, back to normal, working late because I need the money, sporting legs that resemble a lobster's legs, and a hairdo that is 47% sand. Not to mention the fact that my beautiful car is covered in dust. Oh, so sad, Horatio.
     

        
</post>


</Blog>