<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The flood of investment into the Downtown Los Angeles market is slowly producing a world class, 24 hour city. Already a sports and cultural powerhouse with the Staples Center and Walt Disney Concert Hall, the influx of new loft dwellers is finally drawing essentials like a  urlLink Ralphs supermarket  slated to open later this year.   The Walsh Team is at the forefront of the area's explosive growth with two new downtown listings: 1)  Artist's Lofts  at 900 E 1st St, an industrial adaptive reuse with wood floors, exposed brick, and killer views of the downtown skyline (currently under contract); and 2)  urlLink  The Oviatt SRO Apartments   at 1315 S Flower in the heart of the exciting developments in downtown's  urlLink South Park  district. It's flanked by the Convention Center and a Blue Line Metro stop and contiguous with Legacy Partners beautiful new 100-unit luxury building  urlLink City Lights on Fig . You'll see from the photographs that the owners have adopted a similar paint job to blend their 1911 brick building in with the 2003 wood frame and stucco. The Oviatt has been dramatically renovated with a new lobby and leasing office, fresh carpet, mailboxes, and new windows on the sides facing Pico and Flower, but still has lots upside with more improvements. There's also vacant retail spaces on the bottom floor, valuable assets for a retail-lean market that's adding so many new households.   Five years ago, it would have been unthinkable to renovate these older single room occupancy hotels with shared baths and tiny rooms, but the market forces are unstoppable. That doesn't mean everyone's happy about the trend. SRO buildings in other parts of downtown like Skid Row have always been the housing choice of last resort for the  urlLink poor and homeless . According to a recent  urlLink Los Angeles Business journal article , homeless advocates aren't too happy to see developments like this:   For decades, the Cecil, at 640 S. Main St., was among dozens of run-down single room occupancy hotels on Skid Row that rented rooms without kitchens or private bathrooms for between $150 and $200 per week.   But Street Wise Investments LLC, owner of the 634-room Cecil, has made nearly $4 million in improvements since it bought the hotel in 1999....Gone are the advertisements for $150 weekly room rates. In their place are efforts to lure budget domestic travelers and European and Asian backpackers.   Many of the SRO hotels are owned by non-profit groups like Skid Row Housing Trust, which buys small hotels to preserve as affordable housing, but that leaves 4,000 privately owned units near Skid Row, which worries the Trust's executive director Jim Bonar:   With limited affordable housing in the city, gentrification is threatening one of the few options [left for low-income tenants]. "I'm afraid the handwriting is on the wall," he said. "At this point it's only a matter of time."  Looks like he's right:   Gilmore &amp; Associates LLC, a pioneer in downtown loft conversions, has purchased a condemned SRO called the El Dorado at 416 S. Spring St., where it plans another market-rate condo project.   Limiting development problem either, since the major cause of homelessness is the growing gap between wages and housing costs. And the major cause of skyrocketing housing prices (besides ultra-low interest rates from Greenspan) is lack of supply due to backward land use regulations and NIMBYism.  A  urlLink Heartland Institute Study  found the implicit zoning tax on a buildable quarter acre plot of land is $303,178.  No wonder it's so expensive to live in LA!   Downtown Los Angeles is one of the last available areas where significant new housing resources can be built. Along with efforts to provide education and health care to those on the margins of society, we need to let the market develop enough new housing that everyone can afford a place to live.    For more about the exciting story of downtown see the  urlLink LA Downtown News , an excellent resource about  urlLink downtown development  and the  urlLink Central City Association . For more about homelessness in LA, check out  urlLink Beyond Shelter  and the  urlLink Los Angeles Homeless Services Authority .  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome to The Walsh Team Blog, a place for us to provide you timely content about how trends in the global real estate market and new  technologies are remaking our businesses and creating endless opportunities. We've always strived to provide our clients excellent advisory, marketing and transaction services. With this blog we hope to provide knowledge that will always keep you ahead of the curve by identifying value before your competitors. Feel free to add your expert voices to the mix in the comments sections -- we appreciate productive conversations and closer relationships those bring. Enjoy!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The barrage of corporate scandals over the last several years has sapped confidence in our proud securities markets. Driven to inflate results (and executives' fat stock option packages) large firms like Enron and WorldCom used dubious accounting methods, questionable  urlLink foreign tax havens , and  urlLink bogus underwriting  from Wall Street's largest investment banks to bilk thousands of naive investors. But according to a new article from  urlLink Knowledge @ Wharton , Real Estate Investment Trusts have been model corporate citizens:   Unlike the boom of the 1980s, whose aftermath revealed a host of shady deals between real estate developers and unscrupulous S&L executives, publicly traded REITs have largely been untouched by the most recent scandals.  So how did they do it? The article gives three reasons:    One  is the necessity to create cleaner companies after the 1989-92 recession that played havoc with the real estate industry. "There is no question that real estate had a horrendous reputation in the public markets," [Sam Zell, Equity Group Investments of Chicago] said of the pre-1990s era. "But come 1992, the shoe was on the other foot. We were desperate. We had to raise money or our industry was gone."  Zell noted the  second  reason is that "the nature of our business doesn't lend itself to quite the same amount of Mickey Mouse" as in many other companies. It is hard for REITs to cook their books when they pay out 90% or more of their cash flow as dividends. (REITs are exempt from federal tax so long as they distribute at least 90% of taxable income to investors each year.) The  third  reason is the level of ownership by management. "No segment of the S&P 500 has a higher concentration of ownership by management than the REITs do," said Zell.  Looks like the rest of Corporate America could learn something from the big REITs. Though not practical for all firms higher dividend payouts keep companies honest by discouraging them from using the tax line as a profit center. Guess Bush and friends knew what they were doing with the dividend tax cuts -- better to have the owners watching the money than the managers.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The reality&nbsp;sets in across&nbsp;urban Southern California:&nbsp; urlLink 6 million  people by 2030. Where will they go?&nbsp;   Developers in Orange County&nbsp;want to solve the problem with&nbsp;vertical mixed-use developments that place apartments and condos over retail or workspaces. Large central county cities like Anaheim, Santa Ana, and Irvine all have projects in the works because planning departments are finally  urlLink adding some flexibility  to their books:   In the Platinum Triangle, an area of predominantly industrial buildings near Anaheim Stadium and the Arrowhead Pond, the city has loosened the zoning with the goal of encouraging private companies to bring their own proposals to the city. Instead of micromanaging what's going there, the city is throwing open the doors, believing that the market will turn this area into a vibrant downtown for the county. The city expects high-rise offices, new commercial centers, new housing and the emergence of a mixed-use neighborhood where underutilized buildings now stand.   Already developers have  urlLink plans in the works :   CREA/Nexus Anaheim Corners LLC, an affiliate of the residential division of Nexus Properties Inc. of San Diego, plans a 390-unit apartment complex and 11,000 sf ground-floor retail space.   There's another innovative project in the pipeline for  urlLink Santa Ana :   Urban+West+Strategies and the Lennar South Coast Division plan 108 units of for-sale, live-work lofts at the companies’ new Santiago Street Lofts, which the developers describe as a transit-oriented development across from the Santa Ana Train Depot...The 108 units will be three stories each and will range from about 1,540 sf to 2,300 sf, with the ground floors of the lofts designed especially to accommodate the work portion of the live-work spaces. “A key to the project is that the work spaces will be completely separate from the living spaces,” DiRienzo emphasizes.   Live-work strategies like these will become increasingly prevalent in future years. America's workers are trading in stodgy corporate jobs to&nbsp;become  urlLink free agent &nbsp;marketing consultants and&nbsp;indie publishers. Trends like outsourcing and improved  urlLink collaboration and conferencing technology  will allow more people to telecommute and stay mobile. Office condos,&nbsp; urlLink wireless networking  enabled Starbucks, &nbsp;and live-work spaces&nbsp;meld perfectly&nbsp;with these 21st Century workers.   Sure, single family tract homes will continue gobbling up the deserts of the&nbsp;Inland Empire but for those who prefer to live in vibrant urban environments these new projects are exciting developments.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What if building your own custom home was as simple as pressing "Print" on your computer? Science fiction fantasy? Not if  urlLink Dr. Behrokh Khoshnevis &nbsp;from my alma mater, USC ( urlLink #1 in the AP preseason&nbsp;poll  -- Fight on!), has anything to say about it. He's pioneering a new construction method called  urlLink Contour Crafting . Here's how the  urlLink New Scientist article  describes it:    It takes instructions directly from an architect's computerised drawings and then squirts successive layers of concrete on top of one other to build up vertical walls and domed roofs. The precision automaton...can work round the clock, in darkness and without tea breaks. It needs only power and a constant feed of semi-liquid construction material. The key to the technology is a computer-guided nozzle that deposits a line of wet concrete, like toothpaste being squeezed onto a table. Two trowels attached to the nozzle then move to shape the deposit. The robot repeats its journey many times to raise the height and builds hollow walls before returning to fill them. "The goal is to be able to completely construct a one-story, 2000-square foot home on site, in one day and without using human hands," says Khoshnevis. The robot can install plumbing and wiring as it goes, but can't do windows -- yet.  Khoshnevis's prototype robot hangs from a movable overhead gantry, like the cranes at ship container depots. Khoshnevis speculates that they could also be ground-based, running along rails and able to build several houses at one time.   Not only will the homes go up faster, but more beautifully as well. According to Venice architect, Greg Lynn, ""I'm convinced this will allow you to make beautiful, innovative and as yet unimagined kinds of houses." Unconstrained by 2x4's, the technique will allow for complex curving walls and dramatic domed ceilings. I'm thinking about a funky mix of Taj Mahal, Walt Disney Concert Hall, and old school Mongolian yurt for my dream house.  &nbsp;  The technology's speed and cost also makes it perfect for emergency housing in cases of earthquakes or war, low income housing, and even space colonies. Imagine future space colonists reading the directions: "Mix one part moon dust with one part water and stir..."  &nbsp;  The construction industry has been a laggard in the productivity miracles that have already remade agriculture, manufacturing, and services. Looks like that won't last long.       
     

    
</post>


<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Figured it would be a wise decision to start off with some fiction, but true to the intention of having this reading group be challenged, I chose Pendulum.   Eco's a challenging author, to say the least, but he's not so busy being clever that he forgets to be really interesting as well.   So, off we go.   I think 3 weeks was discussed as the reading time for books... so lets try and have this one done in 3 weeks.   I'm going to go ahead and post 1 entry for each 50 pages of the book, starting with the first 200 pages, so that people can post observations, questions, points of interest, related links, comments, or whatever, as they relate to each 50 page packet.   As a request, to make this interesting, try and jot down interesting thoughts or questions you have as you read, or if you're feeling ambitious, make a list of things you don't understand/have never heard of as you read, then post it... we can all tackle the task of figuring out what those items on the list are, and probably all wind up enriched.   Guess thats it for now. I can't wait to get started on this puppy.   -Me
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Looking forward to the first meal.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the official first post.   We'll read something soon.   Then probably write some.   -Me
    
</post>


<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There's a heart warming  urlLink story in IEEE Spectrum  about the power of teachers and collaboration by Vernor Vinge, the guy who coined  urlLink The Singularity . Some clips:     YEARS AGO, GAMES AND MOVIES were for indoors, for couch potatoes and kids with overtrained trigger fingers. Now they were on the outside. They were the world.     ...    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The modern economy scares the hell out of a large portion of the population. The less educated feel doomed to lifelong Wal-Mart serfdom and the elite have nightmares about training their Indian replacements. (Some choose to  urlLink outsource themselves .) Others can't even hit the lowest rungs on the economic ladder after a rough life on the street, broken families, and failing public schools drain their self-esteem. To help build the personal business networks that can drive a career forward, a San Francisco non-profit called  urlLink Street Tech  is experimenting with social networking software  urlLink LinkedIn  (others maybe more familiar with its cousin  urlLink Friendster ) for graduates of their low-cost computer training programs:    [The hope is] to allow marginalized and disadvantaged folks to build a personal network that allows them to leap over the old boys/girls networks that have traditionally shut them out...that social networking can be used as an effective tool for social justice. ( urlLink link )   Strong social networks are one of the primary driving factors towards a successful career. Anyone can learn the skills of computers or finance or real estate but knowing the right people -- building trusted connections for leads and referrals -- is essential to accessing the best jobs, most of which never hit the jobs websites.   So after getting their Microsoft Certified Professional designation, Street Tech graduates can safely and efficiently test the jobs waters online:    One of the real advantages I see to a tool like LinkedIn is that it allows the hiring manager to feel more comfortable about a referral because, in theory, the referral is coming from a trusted source -- thus making their chances for success much higher than if that same hiring manager just received a stranger's résumé on his or her desk. Second, our students can use the tool to search out numerous employers at one time and don't have to go to numerous job boards or make cold calls without first having an inside connection. Finally, the Internet is a much safer place for our folks to start out. Here they are anonymous and will not be judged by their physical experience or lack of mainstream professional graces. Even those on the margins of society can build tribes for support.&nbsp;The mighty&nbsp; urlLink Aztecs  were once a weak nomadic tribe that got bullied all over central Mexico till they found their own swamp, er, island to build&nbsp;their famous capital&nbsp; urlLink Tenochtitlan . After serving as mercenaries (entry level jobs) for the Tepanecs of Azcapotzalco, the Aztecs became the most powerful empire in Mexico. Likewise the Street Tech grads can build alliances with some key contacts online and eventually build careers that rival those who came up through more conventional channels.   Bootstrapping&nbsp;the ever faster, better, and cheaper&nbsp;tech tools&nbsp;allows the&nbsp;disadvantaged to close the digital divide. The common fear that a global technocratic elite will consistently outpace the poor and eventually evolve into&nbsp;a separate species does not fit the facts:&nbsp;the cost of technology per unit of performance -- especially the bio-info-cognotech&nbsp;products whose value lies in their knowledge, not&nbsp;material&nbsp;content --&nbsp; urlLink inevitably drops to zero .   The explosion of mobile phone&nbsp;use in the developing world is a perfect example of this trend. More people access the internet through their phones than conventional PCs. Huge political rallies in young democracies like the Philippines are  urlLink coordinated by SMS&nbsp;text messaging .  urlLink Farmers in India  can check daily&nbsp;market prices&nbsp;for their crops to avoid getting screwed by the local government commodity buyer.   The first generation of online social networking tools are still cumbersome, but they will improve. The disadvantaged will have&nbsp;to play catch up&nbsp;against those born into better circumstances, but they'll have better tools to do it with. Our greatest challenge comes back to equipping learners with the meta-skills like critical thinking and communication they need to quickly and creatively adopt the best new tools, a good subject for another post.   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bashing the worldwide expansion of American fast food brands is a favorite sport amongst  urlLink anti-globalization activists , but it looks like Americans aren't the only ones with their eyes  urlLink on global franchising supremacy . Indian entrepreneur Dheeraj Gupta has launched his own concept to bring cheap and tasty food to the masses. His product is a traditional favorite called vada pav, a batter-fried mashed potato with bread and chutney. His brand, Jumbo King. The company's competitive edge?  urlLink Hygiene and automation :    Easily the most hygienic vada pav seller in the city. The wares are untouched by human hands before you reach hungrily for one. Stainless steel machines are used to cook, mash and peel potatoes. While the bread is caramelised, the vegetable oil is changed every few hours and filtered water is used. The vada pav comes wrapped in paper, with a little onion on the side.  Gupta already has three outlets located near busy train stations -- another trick he learned from Ray Croc who always said McDonalds was in the business of real estate first and food second -- and has plans for many more.   Another example of locally-grown brands poised to give the Americans a run for their money is Halal Fried Chicken in Paris, France. Halal Chicken offers the city's many Muslim immigrants extra crispy meals they can trust. Halal, like Judaism's kosher rules, specifies rules for the care, feeding, and slaughter of animals for human consumption. The  urlLink Marketplace report  on this new phenomenon mentions that KFC has been halal for over three years but doesn't publicize the fact. Do they want to avoid tainting their brand as something "those people" eat? Seems like a bizarre marketing choice, but I've heard racism can be as strong in France as here in the States.   These aren't the only bright shining knights battling the forces of free market colonialism and the global consumer monoculture. Another French Muslim company called  urlLink Mecca Cola  looks to cash in on anti-American sentiment around the world. The company's founder, Tawfik Mathlouthi, puts it  urlLink this way :   It is all about combating "America's imperialism and Zionism by providing a substitute for American goods and increasing the blockade of countries boycotting American goods."  Agree or not with Mr. Mathlouthi's assessment, boycotting American products is a more productive method of dissent than blowing up buses on the streets of Jerusalem. The cola, which comes emblazoned with the slogan "No more drinking stupid, drink with commitment," has enjoyed brisk sales and might have led to the 40% decline in Coca-Cola sales to Saudi Arabia in the first quarter of 2002. And taking a cue from generous American social entrepreneurs like  urlLink Ben & Jerry's , the company donates 10% of profits to charities operating in Palestinian territories and 10% to European NGOs.&nbsp;   These developments&nbsp;demonstrate that globalization is more an&nbsp;additive than destructive&nbsp;force. The consumer gets Coke, Pepsi,  and  Mecca Cola.&nbsp;If she doesn't like the taste or values of a brand there's always alternatives.&nbsp;Foreign brands&nbsp;that fail to modify their products&nbsp;for local cultural conditions will lose market share to nimble, home-grown brands that understand what makes the country's consumers tick. In the end, everyone gets cheaper, better tasting, and more culturally sensitive products.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In this space called Eckotek, I push back against the information onslaught by spinning my own mix of global culture, presenting my own takes on the toughest problems of the day, and spreading my vision of a world animated by artists, entrepreneurs, and learners.     The project is borne of my refusal to be a passive receptacle for of other people’s stories, some hungry eye balls to be tickled by cathode ray tubes. My voice will not be drowned out by the dopamine-draining   buzzzzz   of the mediasphere and its cable news fearmongers and reality television hallucinations. The fear and ignorance that mutilates innocent children and beheads infidels will not sway my hope in humanity’s limitless capacity to invent cooperative/competitive solutions.       Many blogs choose to specialize on a specific knowledge domain but I have  waaaay  too many interests for that. Instead I'll be a crack you trip on heading elsewhere in a Google search, a flash in your peripheral vision, a whisper that infiltrates your own thoughts and interests, a wormhole to transport you from one knowledge universe to another.    As in the fleshworld, I'll wear many hats here -- Capitalist Shark sniffing out the Next Deal; Party Ethnographer exploring the mysterious confluence of music, place, and chemical; SciTech Junkie on the lookout for the coolest new breakthroughs; and Policy Wonk proposing solutions for our world's many woes. I welcome your comments and suggestions here at the site, but rampant comment spam might disable that in the future. Even better, start your own indie publishing empire at  urlLink Blogger  to engage in the blogospheric dialogue. Make your mark in the electronic sand and then encourage someone else to.   Enough introductions, let's go play.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Say it with me now, soft and slow in your most sultry bedroom voice: "Ben...Ben...Ben." Getting a little weak in the knees? Need a cold shower and not sure why? Turns out my name has that  urlLink effect  on people:  So what are the ingredients of a sexy name? For boys, a good name will contain vowel sounds made at the front of the mouth, such as 'e' or 'i' sounds; names with fuller, rounder vowel sounds such as 'u' tend to score lower. So pat yourself on the back if you're called Ben... but if your name is Paul you might have to work harder to snare a date. They discovered this advantageous phenomenon by posting 24 pictures on  urlLink hotornot.com , an online meat market where users can rate people's attractiveness on a scale from 1 to 10. When the photos were accompanied with names like Ben or Mike they scored higher than with names like Paul or Ralph. The conclusions of this breakthrough scientific work sound good to me. It's the researcher's explanation that makes me a bit uneasy:  The finding that men with 'small-sounding' names are attractive might seem counterintuitive, Perfors admits. "Front-mouth vowels imply smallness," she says. "But when girls are looking for mates, they don't necessarily want a super testosterone-charged guy. They want someone who will hang around and be a provider." Small-sounding?! Provider? What happened to my raw sex appeal? I want women to jump into bed when I growl my singular syllable of sexiness, not size me up for future child rearing! I was thinking more along the lines of "Who's your daddy?" than Daddy Dearest. Guess you can't have it all. At least I'm not a Paul.  ------- For more cool science, don't miss the  urlLink Annals of Improbable Research's Ig Nobel Awards . One of last year's ground breaking winners was "An Analysis of the Forces Required to Drag Sheep over Various Surfaces." As my friend Brad says:  Science!  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Chicago, one of the country's most beautiful cities, just got  urlLink $475 million  of new jewelry, including a gigantic chrome coffee bean and multi-story video screen fountains for kids to splash in. Don't miss this amazing  urlLink photo essay  on a daring new public space. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Blogging is anything but a one-way medium. It's a multi-way, raucous network of conversations. Some will just lurk, read, and absorb but others will be moved to write a response in your comments or on their own blog. The sphere of chatter allows one person's thoughts to feed into all the others. We're all watching each other. We're all performing for each other. My friend Lalarene's question  urlLink "Is blogging a world of voyeurism or exhibitionism?"  sets up a false dichotomy. The answer when it comes to most new technologies is yes and yes, an additive world of multiplicity and choice. Look out onto the millions of connected individuals, each only a random google away from peering through the window you've opened to your brain. Welcome to the global stage where you're both actor and audience.  The public conversation allows everyday people to produce and share their own digital culture, tinkering with ideas like with a car, adding a little horsepower to a puttering argument, painting flames on an underappreciated classic. All those parts we leave lying around in our heads, a stunning insight after that third cup of coffee, a rant festering under intimidation and rules, can  urlLink come out :  Blogging...blurs the distinction between the private and the public....by doing both private and public communication simultaneously, you can save both time and effort, and that might make it economical to engage in forms of communication with oneself and with others that would previously not have been possible.  Our narcissism fools us into putting those nascent, half-formed conversations out into the world: "Hell somebody'll get a kick out of this, even if it's just my mom." Knowing how much we like watching others, we get off on the hope others might watch us. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>