<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heyhey! Today was amazing. obviously. had a grand old time. life is perfect, im on top of the friggin world! wootwootwoot! lol yea sorry about that, but hmmm i dont kno, life just seems so amazing and carefree at this moment in time. WOOO. lol tomorrow is CANADA DAY. rock on! wahey canadians rock:) having people over to swim first off (heather bekah and alexa) and then we are headed to zee fireworks. July 1st,.... that means still over 2 months of SUMMER. omg i love it. i love summer so much! YESSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS! As you can tell, I'm living it up in my psycho little world. Its finally hot out, and i have ... er... summmer fever? is there such a thing? i dont know and whats more, i dont care:) yay for that. yay for everything. (and no, im not doing as raver carebear does, im just happy.) (dont ask me why...) anywho, its dinner time. i suppose i will probably be blogging later if i have anything even remotely interesting to say. which i WILL cuz im HAPPY. lol rock on my sweetlings!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Raver Bear    urlLink   Which Dysfunctional Care Bear Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bonjour! hmmm what did i do today? oh yea, i cleaned my room!!! it is some crazy pristine shiat now! yesss score and a half. presently i'm talking to heather about micheal whosisname (jackson) and other pedafiles. she is a pedafile magnet... i mean, look @ her profile... Lol :P I went out for coffee also, with my parents hahaha. on the plus side, i didnt have to pay for the amazing frozen hot chocolate i LOVE so much. from second cup. it is liquid heaven i swear!  hah im watching "outback jack" which is helarious, its like the simple life times ten. right now they are catching fish! sadnosity indeed. well im excruciatingly boring today, so i will be off for now, until i find something fun and exciting to contemplate and put into your little minds. lol :) au revoir mes petits!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heylobonjour i'm at Rebekah's house, hangin out yall... lol Heather might come over but shes a bit hopped up on perkaset so we never ever kno what could happen. :) wahey good times good times.  why is everyone in France right now and I am in Guelph?! somehow that doesn't seem fair at all. AT ALL damnit... ok calm calm...  ...Let your waves crash down on me and take me away.... lol ocean avenue. rock on rock on!  hmmm i should get going. will blog more later! slong schlong... ahahahahahaha whoa like the same word! woootwooooot!!! bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heylo all! yessssssss my plan worked! First i went to the beat goes on and sold 3 cds. i got 10 bucks for them! woot! then, we went to pick up jill and popped into macondo books. I then sold a ton of books and got 13.50$ ! effin eh! so after that, we cavorted back to my house, stopped in for a snack, and went to Zellers to pick up applications. they are helarious. theres this questionnaire about words to describe you, and there are 80 words and you have to put beside each one a number 1, 2 , 3 , 4 or 5, describing how much it applied to you. 1 is does not apply, 2 is hardly applies, 3 is somewhat applies, 4 is often applies and 5 is exactly applies. the words are so weird, and basically mean the same things. here are some: energetic, enthousiastic, enlightened, placid, vigourous, meticulous, witty, amusing, resistant to direction, wants more, etc etc etc so anyway we did that. then she left, and here i am. lol how exciting am i? not overly... im eating cantaloupe yum. mmmmm melon. i remember one time heather and i seduced melon. and popsicles... and then there was that one time... well, what HAVENT we seduced? I will leave you with that question in your little minds. tah!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bonjourno today i am being very productive! Its only 11 30 and I have already gone out for an excellent breakfast with family. had a very large amount of fruit, a bowl of cottage cheese (it comes with the fruit) and 5 home fries. very stuffed. i am going to sell cds, books and clothes to various shops today.  sounds like an EXCELLENT way to get some money, am i right? Good frickin lord that stupid Hilary Duff song is on AGAIN. why must they torture us with her horrible voice on a daily basis?! WHY!? lol I went for a run last night in my fabu new running shoes and my knees didnt hurt! YESSS score!!! now i can get fit without injuring myself! :) c'est excellent. anywho, i should go grab some lunch even though i just ate brekkie. yea, im hungry again... *sigh* the hunger just never ends.  30 days until camp starts! heather if you read this make your wisdom teeth stop hurting. SOON. NOW, in fact! DOooo it! lol i miss you all...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alas, el boring day #1 of the summer. sadly enough, its only what, the 5th day of hols? lol babysitting, i have found, is absolutley useless. only got 14 dollars. then gave my mother 4 dollars becuz i owed her it... generously she gave me back 2$ of it. Why is money always here and then gone? I used to be very good at saving. now i cant even find enough money for a new shirt let alone a bag from bag it that i want very badly. come to think of it i need mascara and concealor. also, jeans, cds... ipod, digi camera, trip to greece in grade 11. *sighh* why couldnt i have been born rich?! Rightnow i have.... HOLY i have 24 $!!!!!!!!! thats the most in a while. except im going to Toronto on friday, so that wont last long. I think I am a shopaholic. considering the fact that i long for going shopping and i wish and think about clothes etc. constantly, i think i may be. uh oh, that can't be good. Tomorrow I am going downtown with jill r. to sell some various stuff such as books and clothes that i dont like/want anymore. yay what fun. then we are going job hunting. wooo money here i come! Anyways, since nothing is happening and its pissing me off, i think i will do some yoga and situps to balance my chi (and in the process tone my stomach) have fun doing what people do. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heylo/bonjour/aloha whats new folks? I went to see man on fire last night (with andrew), it was a Really Good movie:) yay. a bit gruesome tho,.... i mean, like, ppls fingers get chopped off/people kiled/shooting and wutnot. yea. but really well done! Today i am sitting, freezing, waiting to babysit. thankfully for me i have bugged Alexa into going to the park with me and the bratty child. wahey, this cloud has a silver lining. edible silver infact! mmmm i ate pavlova after lunch. that is some GOOD STUFF. hehehe what does one do on a lazy saturday? i need something to do tonight. if your reading this and u have any ideas, call me or email or comment. yupeyupers. Anywho, best be off (wearing my new running shoes no less) to walk off that pavlova and hang around with Alexa and the kid. tahtah for now! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting here in my beautiful new Brooks running shoes from "The Running Works" !!! Rock on, I was especially fitted and everything, because my physiotherapist told me if I dont run in proper shoes my knees will probably always feel as nastily as they did today when i run. Today I went for a short run and it felt quite like someone was crushing my knees in a vice grip. Horrific and almost made me cry! Today I went for a run, went to physio, drove to waterloo with my mom to return my rental flute, checked out singing reperatoire, drove back and went to the running works. j'adore these shoes! Its friday night and here i am, sitting around like a loner. where is everyone and why arent i with them? need a party desperately. else i'll be forced to like, clean my room or something exceedingly sadistic like that. good god, is this what summer is like? on the plus side, i feel like a tennis player or something in my running shoes because im wearing a short white skirt. Maybe i'm the next Anna Kournikova. Only Canadian, and less fit. Tennis players are hot. I want Andy (e)Roddick (lol heather alexa and i call him Andy Erotic) becuz he is so damn fine! sexy sexy. now i really need a party... lol. please people... call me!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy crrrap my head ached this afternoon. like the devil, i swear. It might have been a migrane, only it wasnt. nearly tho. I had to lie down. It was sort of like the time i had to get my dad to pick me up @ 12 at night from jill's cuz i felt sick, only less on the "oh my god im gonna puke this instant preferably all over the car on the way home , that or jills basement's carpet" front and more on the "holy shit my head hurts excuse me while i pass out from my debilitating headache that feels like a brain tumor" side. Only its not a brain tumour. (is that how you spell tumour?) (oh welll) This afternoon i basically sat around and read. ate strawberries, and everything else in the house. at this point in time i am contemplating going for a run tomorrow. i think i will... it wont be THAT bad, and i love the way it makes me feel afterwords:) a run it is. (even though it will kill my knees and then i will complain... more.) speaking of running (im talking about it with jill right now) go to her site (yes i know that has nothing to do with running. deal with it.) www.poodle.squarespace.com Have you ever wondered why i always use these fricking dotdotdots? the answer is simple my dear disciples... (there i go again) its either a)my "austin powers" pauses (example: heather licks...her... balls?) b)regular pause for effect c)where normal people with computers that work use hyphens. unfortunately for me (and you) my computer is an ancient (4 yr old) turquoise ibook, and i also spilled chocolate milk on it, greatly damaging the keyboard and obliterating, in a sense, the hyphen/underscore. its a bitch, but thats life. lol what a long entry! yay i am SO good... lol not that anyone COMMENTs.... *hinthint* yea i would try to subliminally message you or whatever, but i cant be bothered. carry on mr.bodock (looong story short, i read a book called something like that in grade 6.) (quite amusing. ) (too bad it wasnt bodick....) run. run fast. run very fast. run so fast you are a blur. why arent you running?! lol
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woot woot. went strawberry picking with Jill Ross this morning:) i picked 4 L of strawberries... holy shitload of fruit! lol That was at 8 30... yes, i was up at 7 30 on a holiday day... the 2nd day of summer hols no less. yes, maybe i am a bit insane.  Ew you know those strawberries that are so mouldy and gross and mushy? Yea, i have issues with those, especially when i dont pay attention and then i accidentaly shove my finger into it... ick ick ick ! hmmm what am i up to today? I think i will go downtown and work at my moms store, becuz i have nothing better to do. also then i will have money. I wish there was a party or something happening tonight.. come on! well, carpe diem, seize the day or whatever... maybe i will go do some yogaor try to get into shape (run or etc... lol)  party on garth (waynes world rocks my sox!) COMMENT, PEOPLE!                                                         
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      " Your soul is WILLFUL. You are determined and a little reckless, and you do whatever you want to do. You have strong opinions and are not easily swayed, and your headstrong resolve is not easily countered. You have few regrets. People find your refusal to go down without a fight formidable, and they respect you for it. You are a proud and content soul."    urlLink   What Is Your Soul's Trait?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   Its creepy how true these are. creepy i say. (there was a piccyture, but i deleted it cuz i think it was messing up the works.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nobjour (thats bonjour, only nobby... ok not really nobby, but nob is bon backwards. you know what i mean, dont act like you dont. ) lol i'm just chilling in the shizouse... with my homies... ok on my own.. hah. watching the simple life 2. oh yes, so this is what my life has come to... watching rich girls cavort around mooching off of people's services... sweet deal.  Im on msn again. talking to Heather, Andrew and Anne Marie. seperatly. you kno, like not in the same convo... yep thats the one.  god i am boring tonight. i really need someone to hold me right now, to wrap their arms around me. I dont kno why, I just need to be loved.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was uber fun! Good times... except after was... um interesting lol. well, I went to Bekah's house, and Kristin and Heather went too. We hung around, watched several moooovies, (a lot of movies.) sat on the porch, and eric and luc and dylan came over to her house. then we all went to the park, and came back to the house. it was fun, except i was being a bit negative, and very apologetic for some reason. but its all good, we had fun and partied it up. getting to bed was a bit of a toughie. lol... Today Jill, Lauren, Liz, Heather and Lisa came over to swim. i think i got a bit of a sunburn. what is up with me never tanning but just burning? grrr... it forces me to use nastily fake tanner occasionally. guck. Ooooo i love summer. the only thing bad about this summer is possibly the deal with andrew, becuz i want him back NOW not later lol... hard it will be!!! I got a really nice taste of what summer is gonna be like today, and i adore it. i still sort of still feel like im in school, however... but i can't wait to enjoy an amazing summer! Rock on... party hard, play it safe y'all! lol (jk ... dont play it safe... have the best frickin summer of your lives!)
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heylo all! FINALLY, exams are over. thankfully... i wasnt so sure i was going to get through that last one. geography is a brute on a bike. lol roight... now all there is to do is PARTY UP. lol i cant even wait , the entire summer is gonna be awesome. i am sooo excited for a stress free life that is the summer with nothing happening (until camp in august, which is so fun it doesnt count as something i have to do..) Tonight i'm sleeping over @ Rebekah's tonight. should be fun (yay) it always is... i love you all!!! i swear, i am like highly elated today! walking home i tried to say something and it came out as gibberish... thats what i have come to.. lol well, id best be off, for now! MUAH 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You're Element is Fire. You have a strong, independant, fiery personality and you obviously don't ley other's puch you around. You like being in charge and don't care what other people think. In fact, you like to stand out and be yourself. You're probably shy when people first meet you but your a ball of energy that could explode at any given moment. You like to laugh and whether you admit it or not, you like to fight. You're peronality that is wild and untamable. You're beauty is physically fit and a little sexy and you have a very pretty face.     urlLink   What's Your Element(girls)? (PICTURES)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        you are the cute but psycho happy bunny. You adorable, but a little out there. It's alright, you might not have it all, but there are worse    urlLink   which happy bunny are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    *Yay I got the cute but psycho one. sweet frickin deal* 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey hey hey! My god i am tired. I'm just on msn (as per usual) after having dinner (spaghettit, ceaser salad, bread) and talking to rachelle. one crazy kid. here, i will put some of our conversation: Rachelle: I keep telling you to take your medicine! Me: I know, but its hard. its just so nasty, it tastes like yeast! Rachelle: Well no wonder, thats what it is. its yeast infection medicine Me: Well i dont have a yeast infection, so lay off the vagasil!  Rachelle: lol Me: Your not just a gyno, your a gynosaur. Rachelle: your so sweet Me: I try. Rachelle: DUMPED! lol  Me; oué... je suis coolé Rachelle: way with crayons Me: crayons? Rachelle: some crazy thing i ingenionized  Lol , yes... interesting... thought it was enjoyable (sorry for outing your secret gyno job, rachelle...) Anywho, now to go... away laughing on a fast camel! *muah*
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Argh, what zee hell. I can't study for geography. Ive come to the radical realisation (realization?) that no body cares about géo. it can, quite litterally go to hell. then again, how does a subject go to hell? i really dont know. Ryan wont put me in his blog *evil eye* am i not sexy enough?! *sigh* fine... lol tah for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh , my god. This morning i found the beginning of a stretch mark. ON MY THIGH. What the frick. *scared* that wasnt there before!!! lol enough of that. actually there is a good reason for it.. my knees are taped into place at physio, and donc the skin up my thigh stretches... righto *sighs of relief* So, today there was a perfectly pointless english exam. really really crap, but i did well i think (hope). Unfortunatley there is a géographie examen tomorrow. im prepared to fail... lol.. ok maybe not fail but do BAD, mostly cause i cant make myself study. wonder why... ok, probably because its geography is why. Heather and Sharon came over this afternoon. we "studied" well not really at all. Says Heather : "my brazilian waxer has gone farther with me than anyone!" great... except she has never had a brazilian. YET. lol this summer is the summer for ... fun?!  yea, thats the one... righto. lol sharon waxed one part of her leg. she then screamed in pain... we wont mention that i waxed my upper thigh... PAIN is the word im looking for.  All i have to say is, the other party im NOT invited to had better not be the party of choice tomorrow night. if it is i may cry. :( whatever. bye!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bonjour bonjour wow, i just went to the saddoest "party" ever... lol. I sang at it, which went quite well (ok really well, no screw ups!!! lol which is definetly saying something for me...) yea, there were like litterally 6 people there. good effing god. :S omg only two exams left. I can't wait until school is over. once its over, no more fricking things to worry about like tests and projects and... yes. all of that shiat. Party up (wootwootenschtein... yea weird i kno.) so excited!!! (Heather the cottage thingd better work oot...) by..e..i...
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heylo heylo! I comment so much on Bekah's blog I thought I would try to make one of my own. hoepfully I will actually post on it instead of ignoring it like i always manage to do with other stuff. Righto, so i would introduce myself but i figure if your reading this you already kno who i am... or you SHOULD. My life isnt that interesting. thats why i was a clever bunny rabbit and put interesting in QUOTES. rock on!!! so what did i do today...? oh yes, i woke up, ate pancakes for "fathers day" (a hallmark excuse for a holiday) (i swear, the world is going to the dictators and hallmark card writers...) and then waited around for years until jill came over. read "the onion". (helarious) according to my horoscope in there i will find my husband sleeping with my best friend who has been dead for a year. lol... yea its FUNNY, ok? yes, that is right. funny. then jill came over and we "studied" for geography. god i hate geography.  probably because the teacher is a fat belgian porcine dictator... yes....i wont get into that... we were sitting by my pool and we used fake tanner to attempt a tan, and now the smell of burnt plastic/half baked ass is following my like rubbin cox's lost pussy, sylvie. lol... despite my efforts to smell less like fake.tan.ass, my legs still lean slightly on the horrific smell side. so i dont suggest anyone goes around smelling my legs for a while... lol :D heh. i have to sing at some concerty thing tonight... wish me luck! and i'm off...
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       reer.... im here, at meg's house..... yes, my mother bought the store from her mother. that is right! anyways, yes. im sitting here on the computer (obviously) talking to andrew (yawn) who looks like a mofo in the picture with braids. (idiot)(mofo)(reer)(wigger)(thats right) (bryan if your reading this dont comment that i am being a bitch... because you can just live with it.)   errrgh i worked today. i hate it... icky. oh well, it was payday last thursday yay so now i have money.. i could be saving to go to Amsterdam with heather. i wish i was but my parents wont let me. also id never be able to get enough money:( its sad, because it would be kickassed. but im going to cuba and camp again next year. and tehres a dance exam... 6 dances is gonna be expensive. rrrrrrrrrrraaaaaaaaahhhhhhhh. yes, anyways, ill write more later... maybe.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bonjour bonjour my day was pretty good, a fun camp day. except we sang "MacMillan Toys" which is kind of creepy. it sounds like death and reminds hilary of the old creepy men that sit outside the grocery store in mountforest. thats right, a song can do that. but honestly... its very scary.  im watching "much in the stars" and thinking about horoscopes and star signs and stuff. im gonna see if theres a pattern in people i hang out with, ex boyfriends, who i dont get along with, etc. right here on this very page! Friends signs: gemini(heather) cancer(alexa) virgo(rebekah) scorpio(jilly, lana, brit) sagitarrius(jill) aries(meg) hmmm who else? there are more but those are the ones who i know their signs lol. ex boyfriends signs: aquarius and pisces people i dont get along with: um yea i cant think of what their signs would be. i guess thats not really something you ask people you hate. meh. for curiosity's sake, im a taurus. i actually havent met a taurus i didnt like. yay. except im not very taurus like at all. according to my astro profile... well i guess parts of me are really taurus like, for example... extreme determination and strength of will and i can have "brooding resentment" and enjoy "humour and outbursts of fun". and so on and so forth. also, it says that the colour of choice for taureans is pink, my fave. colour. maybe there is something to the whole astrology thing,.... maybe. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello everyone oh my god im tired.... i had the busiest most tiring day ever.. k maybe not ever, but you know, close. ok this is what i did. i got up at 7:20, got a ride to the river run, rehersed and was choreographed in one number for the entire day good lord it is a long song.. not even a good song really hah... yes. so i was at camp till 2:30. then i walked home, got home just before 3. then i relaxed (computer time) till 3:25. then i walked to physiotherapy , was done physio around 4:10. THEN i went to tim hortons and got a blt sandwich and blueberry muffin for dinner. then dashed off to work for my 5 oclock shift. was there till 9:20. i am so freakin tired. anyway, camp is going awesome. im having fun, today was a bit tedious though, with the one song over and over... meh, it happens. anyway, i should be off...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! yay, SMTS started today (thank god... i was dying from waiting) and i got a part... some secretary named Miss Watson... not that bad, i have a weird little solo in there. :):s im having a lazy evening, which i guess is kind of good. because im tired and headachey from singing. but sort of in a good way. good because its from somethin i love but bad because its a tinnish sort of headache. sort of nasaly almost. its weird feeling. gross. lol ew i have to work tomorrow. thats ok tho, i get my paycheck on thursday! which seems to me like the only fricken perk to having a job, let alone being a stock bitch at zellers. lol heres a sort of cast list for BIG: Name of person/         Name of character Britanie/               Susan Lawrence Mitch M./               Josh Baskin Me!/                    Miss Watson Hilary/                 Mrs Kopecki Crystal/                Mrs Baskin Mitch W./               MacMillan Sacha/                  Young Josh Some dude i dont kno/   Billy other dude idk/         Zoltar/Paul Megan/                  Cynthia Benson  and thats about all i know. because i am not very observant, it seems... lol anywho. talk to y'all later!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey one day left until camp. eeeeeee i am tres excité, im honestly doubting how i will pass the whole day tomorrow. i am so impatient about things , everything in fact. lalala... *calm calm* maybe i will do excercise ish things all day, then i will be able to sleep... im watching grease presently. i love this movie, somehow it never gets old. which is funny cuz it actually is very old... speaking of old, my stepgrandma found some dresses that were my actual grandmas (my dads mom... she died in like, 1974) from the 50s they are so amazing yay, i will even wear them , because they kick complete ass. thats right.  im thinking about ways in which i could be healthier. basically im bored out of my mind. "party" on 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! yay i got a BEAUTIFUL pink blazer today. it is the most fanfuckingtastic peice of clothing ever. i am wearing it now. yes i do know its hot out. i dont even care, its that amazing. however, what istn amazing is that rebekah is also leaving me. so here are my countdowns.  >>2 days till rehersals/camp (BIG) start >>7 days till heather comes home >>17 days till rebekah comes home >>27 days until the performace of BIG. you are all coming:) lol >>0 days till lauren comes back, cuz i think she is back. lol >>46 days till school (ahhhh) >>152 days until christmas (what?i think ahead) >>153 days till we go to cuba (hopefully) >>289 days, 3 hours and 15 minutes until i am 16 (thats not THAT long...)  >>332 days till school is out next year (haha)  wasnt that fun. i thought so:) hehehehehehe. yes... calming down.  worked today. thats. about. it. muah
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello! knees are painful again. hopefully not for long... went to physio, she taped my knees below the kneecap, on the tendon. in case you care, the tape this time pinches the tendon and spread the surface area so that when the knee is in motion the stress and pull isnt directly up and down of the small tendon, but instead its a wider area for the muscles and joints to pull on, thus decreasing my pain. i dont know, all i know is in learning a hell of a lot about knees... lol which isnt necessarily a good thing. knowing too much creeps me out, cuz then i know all the bad things that can happen to your knees. ewwy. talked to heather on msn (shes in france) this morning. but then she sorta just left, but it says shes still on, according to my msn. very weird. she's staying with dutch people in a villa in avignon. we might (hopefully) go to HOLLAND sometime together. that would be so very cool... dutch people are veerd like goldmember. yay. what shall i do today to pass the time? i need to buy alexa a birthday prezzie. then again, i could buy it at zellers after work tomorrow, seeing as thats most likely where i'd get it in any case. hey, i get a 10% discount... :) lol 4 and a half days till rehersals for big start! how the hell am i going to last?! i have no idea... god i cant wait. !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! anyway, i am VERY boring. i will try to find something to do now (unlikely..) 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bonjour mes amis. aujourdhui was very busy! i got up early (7 55) so that i could have a shower before the people came to rip up our bathroom floor and start to tile it. its supposed to take 3 whole days... 3 whole days of having to use the nastily downstairs bathroom (its not THAT bad, but its very inconveiniant..) and yes, it was far too early to be up in the summer. but it was ok because i went to work @ 10, and worked for 4 hours. then, i came home, ate lunch, and went for a run with alexa. it was a good run, ive never run with other people before, but i like it. its more amusing, and makes the run seem shorter. i like it a lot yay, so alexa and i are going to go once a week now. which is good because then i only have to run alone twice a week. wahoo. then hopefully ill get back into tennis with rebekah. life is going to be pretty busy for me in august, because i have camp every week day (not saturday and sunday), lots of hours at work, and running and tennis. not as bad as septemeber/october/november though, when i'll have school, homework, work, dance, ultimate and hopefully feild hockey. god, dont want to think about That. right now im just hanging around, and i had some ice cream, and im evidently on the computer. damn it my brother just came in the room... i bet he wants the computer, which bites. maybe i wont give it to him...oh, perfect, he left. lol in any case, i probably should go... comment , people, if you are reading this! au reavoir!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! i made lots of money last night for babysitting... absolutely pro. i babysat 2 girls in waterloo for steve (music director from smts:)) and they are very cute, which is good. then i spent about 2 hours explaining to bryan and andrew why i had to dump andrew. i would explain here only im tired of it. tired of explaining myself, tired of people not really listening to me. but everything is ok now... finally. my list of songs i have downloaded recently is:  Ocean Avenue (yellowcard) Heaven ("los lonely boys") Everybody's Fool (evanescence) Come as you are (nirvana) This Love (maroon 5) Magic Carpet Ride (steppenwolf) Flashdance "Shes a Maniac"  Heaven is a place on earth (belinda carlisle) The Reflex (duran duran) Wonderwall (Oasis) Leave (Get Out) (jojo) I need a hero (bonnie tyler) River Below (billy talent) You Can't hurry love (diana ross and the supremes) Where are we running (lenny kravitz)  Lol yea... interesting... i thought so... my downloading music is a huge novelty , because i only recently figured out how to actually use this. my brother taught me, actually. i might even download "Cant Touch this", MC Hammer style! Naanananana na na na na Cant touch this.... Stop... Hammertime!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello! i had a realisation (realization?) today. I realised that people often think i hate them, when i really don't. at all. maybe its that i joke around too much, sometimes i dont realise that i might be, you know, hurting someone, while they put on a facade of laughing at what i have to say. so maybe i should try to stop joking about potentially hurtful things. would that help? mostly if i say something thats taken as mean though, im actually jealous of the people. i think that people believe i'm a bitch, and think they know how i am before they really get to know me. but then, i guess thats something we all do, we all do it and too often at that. personally i think i'll try giving people a real chance before judging them as whatever. and i hope others will do the same for me. because really, we all want the same thing: acceptance. is that too much to ask these days? no matter what we do or say though, someone, somewhere will end up hurt. thats just the way it works. we've all been there: so just give me (or whoever) a chance, because once you get past all the superficiality in life, i hope to find that people are really not all that bad. thanks...  thank everyone who has helped in everything i do thank you... whoever you are... for reading this thanks... for being there thanks... for telling me when something's up thanks... for giving me a fair chance, a fair shot thanks... for not judging and most of all, thanks just for being you.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [[10 Favorite Bands]]... some of them arent "bands" persay 10 Duran Duran 9 Maroon 5 8 Steppenwolf 7 Yellowcard 6 Oasis 5 Bob Marley 4 Evanescence 3 No Doubt (the old stuff) 2 John Mayer 1 Robbie Williams  [[09 Things You're Looking Forward To]] 9 Musical (BIG) 8 already lookin forwards to turning 16 (next may!!!! lol) 7 heather coming back! 6 tennis? 5 August parties (bekah's, heather's , mine.) 4 being in grade 10... better than gr.9 3 being free 2 ...knowing what my work hours are? 1 Performance @ dance next year  [[08 Things You Wear Daily]] 8 "panties"/ "knickers" 7 bra! (thank god..) 6 watch 5 pants/skirt/sometimes shorts 4 shirt 3 silver bracelets(3 of them) 2 hair elastic 1 toothbrush bracelet  [[07 Things That Annoy You]]... ie things i can't tolerate 7 Hypocrisy 6 Ignorance 5 Pain 4 George W. Bush 3 Cheaters (i mean like the cheating on their girlfriends kind) 2 dead things 1 PIGEONS.  [[06 Things You Touch Every Day]] 6 clothes 5 toothbrush 4 computer 3 food/drink 2 shower (nozzle..) 1 myself. lol j/k (or am i...)  [[05 Things You Do Every Day]] 5 Listen to music 4 shower 3 make/eat food 2 talk 1 usually computer...  [[04 People You'd Want to Spend More Time With]] 4 Bekah 3 Kristin 2 Ryan (he put me on his... finally my name was mentioned!!!!!! lol) 1 Britanie and Hilary!  [[03 All Time Favorite Bands]]... wasnt this here already? 3 Duran Duran 2 John Mayer (i know, not a band.) 1 Bob Marley  [[02 Movies You Could Watch Over and Over]] 2 AUSTIN POWERS. 1 American Wedding  [[01 Person You Could Spend the Rest of Your Life With]] 1. i don't know, how is one to choose... what about my imaginary friend? :P  Yes, this was on so many people's blogs i felt inclined to do it myself. isnt that jsut peachy? i thought so.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heyhey! didnt write yesterday... was too "busy" lol actualy i just didnt feel like it... no one is ever on msn because they are all away. *sigh* so i sit and read a lot, since no one is here. fortunately i start work today, so i guess thats something to do. however sucky that is. yesterday i went to Alexa's, and we went to the mall. lol her cousin is going to mexico on a mission trip for his church so her mom gave us money to go to the dollar store and pick out little things for underprivelidged mexican children. yes. here is a conversation we had in the dollar store: Alexa: So should we get them some little hair things? Me: Do they have hair? Alexa: Of course they have hair Me: How do you know? Alexa: *rolls eyes* because poverty doesn't take away your hair. Me: *skeptical* well maybe some of them don't have any. think of how they would feel. Alexa: Ok then, lets get some hair things for the ones with hair. Yes i am pro, i convinced her that mexican children are bald. wow, i really am bored. right now i'm listening to music. Oasis "Wonderwall" is on. this song is very mellow. i once had a rabbit named mellow....we don't ask, but all i will say is that its parents were my rabbits, who were, according to my dad the vet, supposed to be both girls. and worse yet, they're brother and sister. don't think about it, it wil only disgust and revolt you. let me tell you though, there is truth to the saying "going at it like rabbits" on that note, i think i will go make some lunch. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heylo heylo! today i got my first job! at zellers! yes! thats right, i have a job at zellers eramosa road, store 100. wahoo. i think i do stuff related to incoming/outgoing merchandise etcetc. stock shelves, too. wow, très chic. not. but i get better than minimum wage, which is protastic ineed! lol so yea, maybe im a bit excited... bekah: its ok if you cant play tennis today, cuz i cant either accounting to the fact that i can hardly walk my knees hurt so much. also i got home just before 1 from my 3 interviews (at zellers), so i wouldnt have been able to. so its cool.  *shes a maaaaniac, maaaaaaaaaaaaaniac oh no oh... and shes dancin like she's dancin like she's never danced beforrreeeee* lol sorry, just listening to that. you kno what i'm obsessed with right now? Duran duran! i dont know why. prolly cuz i love "the reflex" it kicks major ass. dont ask me.... lol rock on y'all
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! Oh dear lord, i have a job interview tomorrow... at zellers...at 11. that's gonna be weird...i've never ever gone to a job interview before.. i really hope i get it though, because i need money right now, and i dunno, working somewhere would be good i guess. even though it freaks me out a bit. *sigh* zellers indeed. :P i'd better not muck it up. because , well, that would suck. why cant i be like my brother..everyone likes HIM.  today i went to play tennis with Bekah and Heather and Kristin. it was fun but i sorta blew up at rebekah (ok sorta is very much an understatement... i totally cussed her out... *blush*) but i'm sorry... i was in rather a bad mood today i guess.  what else did i do? um i guess i ate and watched tv. wow, productive. tomorrow is interview (11) tennis (1) and bikkini wax (4 15) ! wow!!! much better, i wont sit around all day. not that i really did today, cuz of tennis and swimming. meh, shit happens. anyways, i should go help my mom make dinner. don't know what we're having, but even so. teehee. will write more later!
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ommmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm lol. i am feeling pretty good, probably because i went for a 20 minute run this evening. it was tiring and hot, but afterwords i always feel good, and thats when i understand why I actually bother running at all. after being active all of these days, today i wasn't and i was so bored i had to run. and I guess running isn't all that bad, i mean, it puts me in this healthy, active, happy, calm and all that after, and so i feel excellent. it seems that the pros of running (health, state of mind, use of pent up energy) outweigh the cons (not being good at running, exhausting). so i guess thats why i do it. the only other things i did today were drop off my resumé at Zellers (yes, thats right, Zellers... do you have a problem with that? lol) and entertain company (grandparents, aunt and uncle). I could have swum (swam?) but i really didnt feel like ruining my hair lol. as it turns out, i pretty much ruined my hair running, but hey, it happens... ;) so basically i had a relaxing day. exceptional, because i was Very tired today. i should get agoing, because i have things to do, people to see (not really, i'm just out of intriguing and pensive ideas to share...) i might write later...  y'all come back now! (lol)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! I once wrote a list of all the things in this world that in my materialistic (sort of) state of mind, would be awesome to have! here are some:  15 things that i want:  15. Andy Roddick (yea so we can dream, correct?) 14. Guess wallet (pink and tan... makes me drool everytime i see it) 13. miniature thighs (again, we can all dream) 12. a proper computer (i hate macs i hate macs i hate macs. yes, i have a mac.) 11. several more pairs of pants (jeans, because i wear jeans.) 10. silver cuff bracelet. maybe the kind that supports cancer/or aids research 9. dirty dancing havana nights (on dvd) 8. stylist (how cool would that be? you'd never wear black with brown again. ever.) 7. a non cheaterous boyfriend. yes, thats right. 6. new mascara (mines old and quite possibly germy) 5. trips to cuba, greece, florida, japan (those are the places i want to go but havent been to. yet.) 4. my own tv back. some japanese dude my dad has as a grad student is "renting it" (ie my dad gave me 10 bucks to lend it to the guy for 6 months to shut me up. if i'd said no he would have taken it anyway, but this way i got 10 bucks... which is long gone) 3. more memory on my computer so i can run "Poisoned" properly. 2. a million dollars. 1. to believe in love  *Muah* so long for now, its confrontation night number 1 of the summer! (number 2 to come july 17th...)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what ever happened to those carefree days in elementary school where all the girls, of all shapes and sizes would sit underneath the shady trees and eat chocolate, chips and whatever came our way, without thinking twice about the way it would affect our figures? when we could excercise by having fun, not planning out our every move to banish thigh fat and stomach bulge? we HAD those things, but nobody cared. we could live our lives happy and healthy, carefree, without worrying about whether all of our friends were excercising too much and/or hurting their bodies, through eating disorders and everything? Why can't life be a holiday back to our childhood? why then, did some people end up stick thin anorexics, or stick thin but healthy kids, average people with eating disorders...seemingly happy kids who stop their smiling facade, their disguise, to go home, rip off their cheery masks and break down in tears, leaning over the toilet, waiting for their "fat" to melt away. WHY is the world so unfair?! if i were all knowing, i would help you all. in fact, i would even help me. because even the most healthy among us manage to get sucked up in this vacuum of spiralling hell on earth, the betrayal that is the standard of "healthy" that, in essence, is the lyposuctioned dream girls of the media. if you care about yourself, just listen to me. i've been to the world of the excercise obsessed, the scewed self image. just take a look, an honest look into the mirror. i promise you are beautiful, exactly the way you are.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this world it seems has lots of things wrong with it... 10.my hands smell like metal. 9. there is no underscore on my computer 8. i feel really really betrayed right now, and if you dont know why you dont deserve to know why. 7. ashton kutcher is going out with demi moore. indeed what the f*ck.. 6. my brother has a drum set. 5. its cold out. its july. 4. still betrayed, stupid, cold 3. i can't make everyone happy 2. people hate me with no reason 1. BETRAYED.   that being said, i do have some thoughts... good things that are happening in my life: 10. tennis today 9. killer highlights 8. summer 7. my friends are supportive in the face of betrayal. 6. im almost free.. 5. my shirt is pink 4. sean william scott is hot (no shit) 3. camp soon... then i will be able to forget all the lies and have fun doing what i do! 2. my hair no longer smells like hair dye ass. 1. REVENGE will be mine (well actually probably not...)  so, my dears, enjoy the lack of sunshine and try not to be too depressed when you learn that people that mean a lot to you are really being traitorous assholes behind your backs. oh boy, have a fricken good day.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heyloheylo je suis chez heather. she is in the shower (oooer) and i am downstairs, on the computer, talking to rebekah. she'd better come! i miss her already! Today i got my hair cut and coloured. i think it looks pretty good. at first i really noticed the new highlights cuz they're a bit redder than last time, but now i think it looks exactly the same as it did before. which it probably does. but meh, it happens. the hairdresser also straightened the front bits with a ceramic flat iron, so its not all nasty and curly like it sometimes gets when she does it. yay and a half. tonight we are watching "the butterfly effect" and "not another teen movie", which should be fun. hopefully i can get my daddy to bring me my stuff... :) anyways, should be off. goodbye my minions
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heyheyhey! yay i had a good day! sweet, because... a) my physiotherapist told me that I don't need as much physio anymore because my knees are on the road to recovery! (yesss) b) i went to play tennis with rebekah, which was fun and healthy... i feel quite fit as a result. c) i feel happy in general, like my lifestyle is healthy and so glad its summer.  but i guess it was a bit bittersweet because: 1) andrew is leaving tomorrow and i'm gonna miss him a lot 2) i get this pain in the left side of my ribs that makes me a bit scared to breathe because it might happen again.. lol 3) i drank a lot of water, so i am a racehorse.  right now i'm watching "Newlyweds" and i just watched "the Simple Life"... Nicole Ritchie is my hero she is so funny... although snobby and rich and a biotch... lol naw not really. but i thought it was funny when she said "lets get slutty" i dunno, had to be there. then again, who knows whats funny in my mind? example, no one understood when i said "this is what sex is like" you know, i knew what i meant.... *goes into a corner and cries*. Tomorrow I have a hair appointment! woot. hair cut and highlights... the reddish brown kind i always get. theyre nice. takes forever, tho. i might get my ends razored this time, so that my hair will be all cool and flippy. or just leave it stick straight. whatever. im not gett much off, just a trim. because i actually really like long hair... feels so much sexier... lol on me i mean. no i really don't even know what I mean... lol anywho, i should go, because i am boring right now. nothing of note left to say. and im spent.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mmmmmmmbonjour! just got back from seeing "Stepford Wives" with Andrew. movie was not too bad, if a little short. an hour and a half, ish. wish it werent so short, because its the last time in TWO FREAKING WEEKS that I will get to see Andrew. Why do his parents have to effing make him go freaking camping?! and then he's going to camp. then to cottage. grrrr im going to miss him!!! Anyway, what else did i do today? I PLAYED TENNIS. VERY fun (with knobs, in fact) and more. we had le good time (Rebekah, Heather, Lesley and I) and had an amazing work out. I hurt. lol all over. and we came back and went swimming after, which evidently felt amazing on our hot sweaty selves! I had to try two times to get down and back my pool without breathing... sad, i know. but meh. the others were good at it.... sigh.  I just had some ice cream (hence the subject line)... sooo good. with blueberries. yum and a half! ooo i love ice cream. tres summery! indeedydoodly. now i'm eating babycookies. why am i always hungry? meh, it doesnt matter. we tennised for freakin ever today! lol yay. how healthy am i? anyway it doesnt matter, becuz apparently eating small meals (which i did) makes your metabolism faster. and mines pretty fast anyway. woot. so basically what im trying to say is.... TENNIS ROCKS. you betcha. lol i know, i make absolutley no sense whatsoever. whatevs.   i think i will become a nutritionist because i keep lecturing heather and my mother about how to eat properly. it just gets on my nerves when people are either careless or unsafe or anything about what they put into their bodies. i mean, your body is your temple. you live in it 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. if you don't treat it properly, who will? no one. thats right. not eating properly causes such bad things to happen! i mean, if you can control things like immunity, health, and general well being with merely takign care of your body and eating right, why not do it?! its so simple, i don't understand why people don't do it. I eat well, why do you think the last time i was sick was 4 years ago? i guess my message to you is.... TAKE CARE OF YOUR SELVES.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Et bonjour mes petits amis! I just got back from a runnnnnnn yay, now i feel good. much better now, because now i've done something productive with my day. also i was feeling creative after dinner, so I started a really funky collage about basically how i'm feeling right now, and basically representative of a lot of stuff that happened through the entire year.  its so weird how this year, so many things have changed. I'm still pretty focused on school and do the whole "work ethic" thing, but I am doing less "square" things than last year, hanging out more, enjoying life and caring less about school. its sort of weird... i dont know anyone else that has the same "priorities" and stuff as me and gets 90s. i sometimes wonder how much longer i can keep up both sides of life you know? because i dunno, i dont really have anyone to... look up to I guess. it just feels weird. maybe i will just have to keep "my summer life" so to speak apart from my school life. i honestly don't even know. life is weird. it happens. i'll think on it... but i won't change.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all just got back from getting my report card... the school was all weird and empty. it was bizarre. did really well in all my classes, pulled my average up from 88 to 90! yesss sweet indeed. 87 in geo, 91 in english, 90 in math, 91 in gym. so itsallgood.  its funny tho, becuz i did better than ever this year even tho i kinda stopped caring at the end. which, i guess , must have been beneficial. i still think mr. dumas should go eat a cow... oh wait, he is one. lol then hopefully he'd get mad cow... lol god. im glad that class is over with. i dunno, report cards have such a sense of finality. like, only now do i totally feel like school is over. which is EXCELLENT, let me tell you. heather and rebekah should be coming over soon, after they pick up their report cards. i dont kno what we'll do, since its cold and yet humid outside, so really not ideal swimming conditions. i went for a run this morning, but i had to stop after 5 minutes because i could not breathe. excellent. i felt like ass until i had a shower. but before my shower i talked on the phone for an hour to andrew, then a bit to heather and then alexa, then my mom. i've been on the phone for far too much time today.  im wearing my kickassed new green tube top ish thing. its nice. je l'aime.  WHY DOESNT ANYONE COMMENT? i realize its hard to click on a button, click on "post anonymously" and then put in a few words...  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        BUTTERCUP! You rock! You're funny, tough, and a bit stubborn. You like people for who they are, (most the time) and that's why they like you! *sarcastic tone* Now were are a big happy family, yay. BYE!! ~rox~    urlLink   What powerpuff girl are you? w/pics *tee hee*     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bonjour mes petits clones a gogo (s) I am sitting in the fricken blazing fricken fires of fricken hell in my tv/computer room.  this is the extent of what i have done tonight:  6:45. Ate dinner: homemade hamburger and carrots. seperatley, of course. 7:15. Read (4th princess diaries) 7:30. Rebekah came over to borrow some booooks 7:45. Bebekak's mom shows up prematurely to pick her up 8:00. Read some more, contemplate starting to stop eating junkfood 8:30. Eat ice cream with chocolate sauce (screw low fat.. actually its Chapman's Light Ice Cream... vanilla bean yum) 8:50. Decide reading is not what i feel like doing at this moment in time, go on computer  Now its 9:10 and i'm watching the tour de france (tour de lance, really... they dote on that man... and by "that man" i mean Lance Armstrong.) and i am a bit beyond tired, boredish and hot. and i dont mean hot in the sexy sense.  So, i will leave my ramblings at that. baby byebyebye! (woot)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! today i played tennis in the rain, with heather! fun. but my hair got soaked *sigh*, which is the price one has to pay. actually there wasnt much tennis playing, more running around to get to heather's dad's house ie out of the rain, after having played tennis for about 10 minutes. rock on. then when we were dry we came back here to my house, but on the way it started pouring (again) and i had to blow dry my hair (again) when we got out of the rain (again.).  add that to the fact that i actually cant play tennis well at all, and you have yourself a weird day, but amusing nevertheless. we then watched moonstruck for 5 minutes, goldmemeber (which we also watched yesterday) for about 15 minutes, and the entire thing of American Wedding (for the billionth time... like austin powers it never gets old. as long as you fast forward thru the bachelor party scene...)  wow i didnt blog yesterday! thats prolly cuz i was upset, because both Andrew and Heather are going away!!!!!!!!! at the SAME TIME. in fact so is jill. combine their names and Handill is MIA for like, EVER. thank god Rebekah and Alexa are still around, other wise i would die of loneliness. everyone else is away too. *sigh* On the bright side, i got my photos back from Canada day, etc. very good pictures! yay. they're très cuté. if you want some of them talk to me on msn and i'll send them to you. :) ah BON. anyways, i need to go eat some dinner, and Bekah is coming over around 7.30 to pick up some books. yessir! keep on rockin in the free world.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! Oh my god, i went a whole day and a half without going on the computer! thats (almost) a record, which is really really sad... meh it happens. Yesterday was really fun! Heather Rebekah and Alexa came over to swim, and we sunbathed and stuff, danced, partéd ate pizza. Bekah is right,... there WERE lots of boobs involved ... heh heh heh...  then at like 7 we went to riverside park and watched the fireworks. We were very decked out in our Canadian...ness... i even had a canadian flag in my hair... and on my tats... lol and my back. rock on! Andrew and Cory came and watched the fireworks with us and we saw tons of other people we know, like Anne Marie and Jerica! oh, and Ben P., with his new hair colour. very nice, though a bit on the poserish side. lol nah not really poserish. it was THE BEST Canada day everrrr! indeedly. Today I went to Toronto. We walked around, down Queen street to all the fabby stores. there were sooo many nice clothes, but they were super expensive. there was this AMAZING "Guess" wallet that i wanted in the worst way, it was pink and tan and absolutely fabu. good god it was perfect. except it was 40$, which is all the money i have. there were Juicy Couture socks, 555 Soul shorts, Louis Vuitton bags, French Connection shirts and tons of other things i wanted. oh dear lord, i really wish i was rich. I mean, I'm perfectly happy with the stuff i have, and like, lucky to have what i do, but GOD i want that stuff. I mean, i'm a happy kid, so why not have millions of clothes and bags and shoes and cds and dvds and such too? lol i wish. the thing is, its a dream to me. right now, with the money I earn myself i'll stick with my Bongo jeans, Baby G watch and the kickassed bracelet i bought at a little street vendor today. bright neon pink... its awesome.  oooer we went to the Rivoli for lunch and had a yummy scrumboes meal. delish. and then we went out for coffee (twice actually) at Balzaks (had a diet coke) and then at Starbucks (had a light mocha frappucino) yummy ! i think i'm addicted to frozen hot chocolate and also to mocha frappucinos.... SO GOOD. yay for caffeine, i will be up late tonight i suppose! unfortunatley not doing anything fun tho, just sitting around, probably reading. I read so much more in the summer. not that i dont read a lot in the year too, i just have more time now.  maybe i should go running. I dont really WANT to, but i probably will. because i sort of feel like a fat cow at the moment. probably just the coffee... it does that... does it? Is it possible to have like 10 songs stuck in your head at once? Because I think I do. If you're reading this Bekah, you left your cd at my house. Thats where all the songs got stuck in my head from. lol anywho, i should go do SOMETHING. keep on rockin' in the free world! (lol)
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ive decided ive been all too damn serious lately so i decide to attempt to make a list of funny quotes/things that have happened to me and pals. mostly heather. oh well. here goes  Me: I have plumsauce in my hair H: So do I , only i think its discharge and not actual plumsauce Me: but seriously,  this  plumsauce is nasty  "Sheep arent the smartest people in the world" ...me...  Dude who is friends with bobby who smashed into a tree: OH NO! Alexa: Ohhhh yes.  H: you burn lots of sex. CALORIES! i mean calories!  "PHWOAR" (anyone with half a brain)  "He's a woman" (heather...)  Its come to my attention that anyone whos anyone works at zellers. im talking thepard man (of the lisp inspired running down the street screaming "its a thepard!!!" at some poor innocent guy walking a sheltie)  Chicken orgasms. ive said enough.  "you guys... i lost my pussy last night" ...Robyn. aka. Rubbin Cox. Cox is totally actually her last name.  "*SAAASAAAAAA!!!!!!*" (this is what i do when im happy. or pleasured. JK about pleasured.)  Anyways thats all i can think of as i type but yes... that made me rather happy. i love the love (btw hilary said that. she's "wildy sexual"... also her thing/ row....row... rrrreee!) tahtah!!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its seems like only yesterday i sat at my table...  smiling because life was so simple the smell of sweet summer breezed through the open screen windows tickling my nose like a feather when the weather turned cold  the harsh winds and blankets of snow were penetrated by the joys and happiness of a cold christmas day now that cold is locked inside rushing through my veins and filling my body the innoncence of that summer day fleeing the scene like an a scared child that scared child is still deep inside chilled and massacred by the words that cut like a knife threats of what could happen  those words sting but the outside seems calm masquerading as someone more heartless  bitch... slut... do you know how it hurts? its times like these that leave summer days of the past... a simple memory in a heart that is left to learn how to love life again only when that child is picked up again loved again no longer alone... do you know you make my life alive? thank you..
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am bored and i like this it was on rebekah's awesome blog... i hope u dont mind if i use it bekah! thnx... enjoy  1. Whats your idea of perfect happiness?being healthy and hanging around enjoying myself with friends knowing that in the morning my life will still be the way i left it. and when im with friends having fun in the summer i dont worry. just enjoying life to its fullest.   2. Whats your greatest fear? sickness, death, being wrong, being alone in the dark. 3. What trait do you most deplore in yourself? bitchyness. and sometimes stubbornness and impatience 4. What trait do you most deplore in others? secretivity. and acting like things are ok when theyre not, and over explaining/analyzing things. 5. Which living person do you most admire? my dad i think... he did exactly what he wanted with his life. i also admire anyone who is commited to something and driven in what they do. those are the types of people i want to be. 6. Whats your greatest extravagance? material possesions (ie clothes, cds, books) i guess... maybe food... or...is laughing an extravagance? 7. Favourite journey? living in france (it has a lot to do with who i am now, i think.) 8. Whats the most over-rated thing?  explaning feelings. lol maybe beauty. everyone tries to be beautiful when it Shouldnt matter. but i guess it does 9. On what occasion do you lie?  to avoid making matters worse, occasionaly to get out of things (ie work) and if im doing something i dont want my parents to know about. 10. Greatest regret? being a horrible kid to my parents when i was younger i guess. or letting myself become a total hypochondriac. 11. Who or what is the greatest love of your life? laughing and being with friends.  12. Where and when were you the happiest?when im at rehersal, or laughing with friends, or doing modern. when im with people i love. 13. Which talent would you most like to have? the ability to totally not care what people think about me. talent to excell in everything. 14. What do you consider to be your greatest achievement? overcoming shyness 15. What would you like to be reincarnated as?umm i dont like the idea of reincarnation but i think id like to be... ok heather says id like to be a vag. riiight. NO.  um.... someone famous and happy.  16. Most treasured possesion? all my pictures 17. Where would you ideally like to live?  Montreal or Toronto 18. What's your most marked characteristic? i asked heather and she said Boobs. but then sense of humour if you know me.  19. What do you most value in your friends? making me laugh and making me happy. not being able to stand being without them for any period of time. being able to be completly who i am around them 20. Who's your favourite writer? Sophie Kinsella... or Louise Rennison!!!! 21. What can't you wait to see? me standing to lose (lol) i cant wait to see how everyone around me grows up i guess. 22. How do you relax?  talking. music too. and getting massages from my boyfriend eric.  23. What keeps you awake at night? worrying about various things. anything from that damn itch in my vag to the meaning of life. 24. How would you like to be remembered? someone who was always themself. confident . funny. and of course, a freakin sexy beast. 25. How would you like to die? getting it on. no. in my sleep, old, healthy, happy, fullfilled and not alone. 26. Anything you'd like to add? oh my god i actually did that seriously! lol... awesome!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey all! whats up. my life is pretty boring right now im thinking about the same "thing" ive been thinking about allllll weekend. ok, all week too. its amazing... just ama fricking zing. rebekah got back! happiness! i missed her when she was gonnnnne.  im watching the simple life... a rerun. but i love it so oh well. this one's pretty damn great;) haha. they are going frogging on the show. very snazzy. now I want to go frogging. only i dont because frogs are slimy and they scare me. thats right.... damn come on msn (you know who you are!) tomorrow is camp again (awesome) and then work (shitty). i dont know why i hate work so much... ok i do know why, its horrifically boring. and quiet. i can hear the fan and thats about it. i dont get why they dont pipe the cheesy shopping music into the back. i wish i wasnt a stock bitch... oh well payday is thursday!!! yay my favorite day of the week. beyond a doubt. im singing "i turn to you" for river run idol at camp on tuesday i think! what fun, wish me luck. oh, and come to my show... August 19th 20th and 21st at the river run. go to the box office, pick up your eyego tickets!!!!!!! only 5 bucks with your student card! 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im sitting here waiting for a certain someone to come on msn. i really want them to come on because i am lonely!!!! oh nevermind, there they are:)
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the world of the confused and i definetly live in it. why does it seem like some days things are great and then all at once you break down in tears? and the more people are nice to you, the more you feel sad but at the same time loved and sometimes decieved because everyones nice to a crying person? i have no idea... no idea at all. all seriousness and tears aside, im having a really good time at camp again this year. its kind of a different experience this year. i know more people, and i have a different sort of part. its change. i guess change is good,  it keeps you guessing.  such a short blog... im too nervous and excited to write anymore. muah
     

    
</post>


</Blog>