<Blog>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's time to discuss something architectural.  Due to the recent boom and an explosion in the demand for housing, developers are building homes at a staggering rate, comparable only to the years right after WWII where displaced soldiers need immediate housing accommodation.  With the way houses are built and designed, the very core of regional architecture is being obliterated by cookie-cutter style track housing.  You can find the same type of housing in Southern California as you can find in Connecticut. Think about this, what if the architecture in Rome looks the same as in France, or in Japan and Thailand? The very essence that separates us apart from the animals, "individuality" and "creativity" are destroyed at the expense of quick return on your dollar.  We, as home buyers, perpetuate the thinkings of the big developers that "if you build them, they will come," mentality.  Good for business, not good for our culture.    
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. Chicks that stuff their faces with everything they can find during pregnency, and complains that its' "soooo hard to lose my baby weight!". 2. People that point to their wrist and ask "what tims is it?"  Are you wearing a fucking invisible watch that I can't see?? 3. People that say "You don't happen to have/know/want to....." If you don't think I have/know/want to do whatever you are about to ask me, why the fuck did you ask in the first place???!?  4. People that ask what the room temperature is.  IT"S ALWAYS ROOM TEMPERATURE YOU DUMB NUT!! 5. Straight guys that think every homo wants to sleep with them. Dude, look in the mirror, even gay guys have standards. 6. Fat chicks at the gym who has been on a treadmill for 20 minutes doing a 2.0.. brisk walking!  7. women i work with that feel like they have to be a bitch and half to show the men that they are equal. Just chill out and show up to work when you are supposed to, instead of taking smoke breaks, coffee breaks, tempon inserting breaks..bla bla bla. IDIOTS!!! 8. People that post quesitons without wanting an answer. Well, shit..if I knew it were a rhetorical question, I wouldn't have wasted my fucking time trying to help your ass out. 9. Women that think men have that...ESP thing. I CAN"T READ YOUR MIND!!! even AFTER you told me what you are thinking, I still might not get it. 10. people that blog.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      alright people. This BLOG is officially under major transformation.  As you can see the format has changed, and we are moving towards a different direction.  We will be funnier, nastier, and not to mention sexier.   We will be providing brand new content, no more mindless blabing about things people don't care about. We will also be having architectural news update, weird news update, social commentary, funny pictures, bla bla bla.   So please be patient while we are under construction. Check back soon, and have a great 4th of july weekend. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. Turtle neck tank tops. This is usually worn by women. Looks kinad like a turtle neck sweater that has the sleeves chopped off. My question is, so are you hot or are you cold? make up your damn mind!!!  2. Nextel Walkie-Talkie phones. So you mean now I have to hear the phone ring AND your whole god damn conversation??  3. Cell phone ear pieces.  Okay dude, this is ONLY supposed to be worn when you are either driving or on the phone. You ain't got to be wearing it when you are just shopping at Best Buy. Do you think it gives you super powers or something?? or that chicks are just going to fall on their knees in front of you because you got a cool ear piece? It looks fucking retarded!!!!  4. Supersize at McDoanld's for kids. Do YOU...i MEAN....where should I even start?? Do our kids really need a supersize meal?? how about a supersize kick to the parents in the groin for stuffing their kids' faces with grease and lard??    
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It appears that some of you need some edumacation on these terms, so here we go.  Contextualism and Regionalism basically mean the something, but contextualism is a more micro interpretation than regionalism. The easiest way to explain the concept is this; when you go to Italy, you expect to see a certain kind of scenery, when you go to China you expect to see a different kind of scenery than Italy.  That's the essence of regionalism. Every region is supposed to have its own unique interpretation of architecture that derives from either climate, culture, social or other characteristics that is uniquely identifiable to its people. Architecture then takes cues from its "context" and respond either as an antithesis, or with what is accepted as the norm.    One of the most famous architects to practice regionalism is Frank Lloyd Wright, the grand daddy of American architecture.  His buildings uniquely respond to its immediate context, and at times the region at large. Such as his falling water house that sits directly above a waterfall, it responded directly to its context by brining the water fall into the house, making it part of the scenery.  When he built out in California, he responded by taking cues from the old Mexican temples, because he felt that Mexican architecture IS the essence of southern California. He built with concrete blocks that is reminiscent of Mexican temples and the organization sometimes also follows the general plans of the temples.   So, you can see as an architect how PISSED off one becomes when the entire united states is becoming homogeneous because of the track housing, can't you??
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    YOU'VE GOT TO BE FREAKING KIDDING ME??? WHERE ARE YOUR BALLS??? Oh wait, your wife has them.. you are an embarassment to man everywhere. go shoot yourself and stop wasting air.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://starandal.com  What kind egotistical self-indulgent prick of a couple would put together a website to annouce you are getting married??? As if the rest of the world would give a flying fuck on how you two met and how you fell in love.. who gives a shit if you met in a buffet line somewhere in vegas?? Nobody gives a shit about Star Jones and Al Scales Reynolds..Star Jones is a C-list celebrity at best, and the other guy's just a nobody. We all know Star Jones wants the whole world to know that even though she's fat, some guy really wants her, not her money (wink wink).. check out this website if you can take it. I couldn't. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    old town San Diego
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my hot wife!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    bedroom in waley house, just the same way it was back in the days
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Original furnace in Waley House.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Old town San Diego
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Waley House in Old town San Diego. This is an original marriage license from 1810's.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    one of the oldest graves in california. dates back to 1810's. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      COLUMBUS, Ohio -- A man accused of grabbing a 9-year-old boy, carrying him behind a Kroger store and stealing his socks has been arrested on kidnapping and robbery charges.    Maurice C. Teague told officers he has more than 500 pairs of children's socks.   Investigating officers said they couldn't confirm the number but said they found "a lot" of socks at Teague's home, police spokeswoman Sherry Mercurio said on Tuesday.   Police said Teague, 28, accosted the boy last Friday evening and dropped a piece of identification as he fled. They arrested him at his home on Sunday, Mercurio said. He's jailed on $75,000 bond.   "It's odd, obviously -- someone going after little boys' socks," Detective Guy Patete said.   Police said the child was on his way home from the grocery around 6:30 p.m. when Teague asked to buy his socks for $5. The boy refused again when Teague offered him $10, and Teague picked him up, ran behind the store and pulled the boy's shoes and socks off his feet.   Police said the boy picked up Teague's identification and his mother called police. Teague, who has no criminal record, at first denied the account but then admitted grabbing the boy, police said.    
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    my new IPAQ H1945  Here are just some random notes I have taken on my ipaq   July 08, 2004  10:05am take a piss and scratch nut sack  10:46am take old cups to the trash and get a new cup, fill up with coffee  11:25am take a piss and scratch nut sack  11:45am go eat lunc 5:50 pick up dog shit
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    That's actually a ping pong ball.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    we saw oprah!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Trip to the zoo!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, well.. It turned out to be a great mini-vacation!! We did a lot of stuff that we just haven't done or didn't have the time to do, and it was overall a very relaxing weekend.  Friday Dinner at my parents' house to semi-celebrate my brother James' 27th birthday. We had sushi, some chinese meatballs, fried rice..tight!!! Afterwards we went to bowling, and I somehow managed to get a 56. FIFTY FREAKING SIX, man..depressing to say the least. That's probably the absolute WORST score I've ever gotten.  Saturday Headed down to La Jolla for a mini 3 day vacation. Of course I managed to fall asleep AGAIN while I was driving. Anyways..hotel's very nice, we were up on the 9th floor with a full view of La Jolla and San Diego's skyline. We visited old-town San Diego and the world famous gas-lamp District at night.  Old Town San Diego was great. I love the feeling of being completely overwhelmed in the history of the land and just to imagine what the frontieers lives were like.  Gas Lamp District is not as exciting as it was made out to be.. seems like a lot of trendy clothing store and restaurants, nothing really worth a while to actually stay and look at.  Sunday SD Zoo!!! I almost forgot how much fun zoo is. We even saw a PANDA!!! Polar bears, a big ass hippo (about the size of Andy's ass) and a lot of other exotic cool animals. After the zoo we went to Balboa park for some cultural experience. We visited natural history museum and just walked around.. great place!! Sunday night we went to Old Town San Diego again for some nice Mexican dinner at this place called Coyote Diner... our waiter looked like the bastard child from Bruce Willis and Christian Slater. hahha.   Monday nice drive home..it only tooks me about an hour and 15 minutes to come back to Rancho from San Diego so I stayed awake the whole time. Went over to our neighbor's house for a little BBQ and hot spa action, tight!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DURHAM, N.C. -- Mike Krzyzewski is staying at Duke, ending talks with the Los Angeles Lakers about becoming their coach.   "Your heart has to be in whatever you lead," Krzyzewski said Monday. "It became apparent that this decision was somewhat easier to make because you have to follow your heart and lead with it and Duke has always taken up my whole heart."   Krzyzewski, who has won three national titles at Duke, said the timing of the Lakers' offer, reported by ESPN's Stephen A. Smith as a five-year, $40 million deal, and their prominence as one of professional sports' most famous franchises made the chance to coach them tempting. But he never got to the point of being ready to leave.   "The decision has always been to stay at Duke. It would have to be something changing [that]," he said at a news conference on campus.   Even Lakers star Kobe Bryant was reportedly trying to persuade Coach K to take the job.   The Los Angeles Times reported that Bryant told Krzyzewski that he wanted the Duke coach to head to L.A. Some Duke basketball people were in a campus gym when Krzyzewski came in and told the group, "You'll never guess who called. Kobe Bryant. He wants me to come coach him."   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    guess what I found in my dog house. Just a little background story, we believe our dog ate half the body and left the head in her house for dinner.. SICK!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This guy must be a billionaire
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink ESPN.com - NBA - Kobe stays put, picks Lakers over Clippers   FUCKING KOBE'S STILL A LAKER, DDAMN IT. HE CAN'T WIN WITHOUT SHAQ, AND NOT WITH BRIAN GRANT AND LAMAR ODOM... WE ARE SCREEEEWWWED!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, happy freaking 26. Now I am officially going down hill and hitting my late 20's. My wife took me out to a Japanese restaurant last night and we had great food!! She also bought me sun flowers (my favorite)..too bad I was about an hour late getting home 'cuz I had to work, then I ended up working at home from 9 to about 2 in the morning. Dragged my ass out of bed at 7:30 and now I am at work. Sorry babe!!!  We will probably go catch a movie tonight after I get back from my meeting in Riverside..hopefully the traffic won't be too bad.  thanks sweetie for making my birthday special even though  had to work!! love you!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is the American soldier accused of abusing prisoners in Iraq. Lynddie England. Also check out her fan website  http://fourstrings.fanspace.com/photo2.html
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    our picture from my brother's graduation from Wake Forest Medican school
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    whatever she's playing, i am in!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MUSKEGON HEIGHTS, Mich. — A suspected shoplifter was found when, after dropping her purse at the scene of a crime, she called police to claim her bag. The woman allegedly set off an anti-theft alarm as she fled a Family Dollar store. She dropped her purse in an parking lot while being chased. When she went to the police station to retrieve her lost purse, she was promptly arrested  KIEV, Ukraine — A Ukrainian candy company has begun marketing what may be the stickiest, richest and most fattening treat on the market: pure pork fat covered in chocolate. Cracking open a finger-sized stick of ''Fat in Chocolate'' reveals exactly that: a vein of white fat. The dark chocolate product pokes fun at the traditional Ukrainian snack of salo, or salted pork fat, usually consumed with vodka and pickles.   MOUNT LEBANON, Pa. — Paul Wellener's family found the perfect marker for his grave: two blue plastic seats from the Three Rivers Stadium auction. Wellener, a lifelong football fan and a Pittsburgh Steelers season ticket holder for 42 years, died unexpectedly on March 16. Wellener's son, Paul, and widow, Mary Ann, bought three pairs of stadium seats for $2,100 at an auction — and knew they had found the perfect gravestone. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so last night around 11:00...after a long ass day consisted of running errands, IKEA, chasing our dog around the house, we saw ANTS!!!!!!! Ants were all over our pantry and we couldn't figure out where it was coming from or going to. So, after we took out EVERYTHING from the pantry, we noticed that the ants were all heading into the cereal box that was left open. There must had been hundreds of ants crawling all inside the cereal box, and you know stupid ants travel in a straight line, so I followed the line all the way back to the outside wall. I then sprayed my trusty ant spray and killed every single one of those little bastards. I hate freaking ants!!!!!  So there goes another hour of time that I could have been relaxing with my wife, wink wink, damn the ants!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Sports Network - National Basketball Association 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I guess to the governator everybody's a girlie man compare to him    Some California legislators are angry with Governor Arnold Schwarzenegger after he referred to them as "girlie-men" during a speech on Saturday.  The movie star-turned-politican used the term to describe opposition Democrats he said who are too weak to stand up to unions and trial lawyers demanding changes in the governor's state budget proposal.  The phrase comes from an old television comedy routine where two Schwarzengger-like bodybuilders use it to mock those who lack their bulging muscles.  Several Democratic lawmakers say the remark was insulting to women and homosexuals. State Assembly Speaker Fabian Nunez said the comment was "beneath the governor."  But a Schwarzenegger spokesman says the comment was the governor's way of saying that legislators are "wimps" (weaklings) by giving into special interest groups.    
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       EAUMONT, Tex., July 14 - It is merely a four-mile stretch of asphalt on this East Texas city's outskirts, dotted with some ranch-style houses, a few decaying trailer homes and a shuttered gun shop, in the distance the rice fields that brought a small group of Japanese settlers here a century ago.  But the name of the country lane, Jap Road, has long angered many Japanese-Americans. Equally outraged are numerous people who live on Jap Road, which has 100 or so residences; they view criticism of their address as meddling in their affairs.  "I hear 'Jap' cars and 'Jap' bikes all the time," Buddy Derouen, 69, a retired petrochemical worker who lives on the road, in the community of Fannett, said in a recent letter published in The Beaumont Enterprise. "Why not Jap Road?"  The competing positions are set to clash in a meeting on Monday at the Jefferson County Courthouse. Leading the county commissioners' agenda is a discussion of whether they should change the name.  Advancing the issue this far has been a victory of sorts for Sandra Nakata Tanamachi, whose family settled in Beaumont after immigrating from Japan in the early 1900's. Before moving away to Lake Jackson, south of Houston, Ms. Tanamachi, an elementary-school teacher, lobbied more than a decade ago to have the road's name changed. She was unsuccessful.  Last December, however, she allied herself with Thomas Kuwahara, a helicopter pilot from Lafayette, La., who was stunned to come across the road a few years ago while driving to San Antonio to visit a relative. They filed a complaint with two federal agencies - the Department of Transportation and the Department of Housing and Urban Development - trying to keep Jefferson County from getting federal money unless the road's name was changed.  "We Japanese are often ignored, but we're still individuals with feelings," Ms. Tanamachi said in an interview, speaking with a thick Texas twang. "I felt I could not stand in front of my students and talk about values like dignity and respect and not fight this thing."  Scott Newar, the lawyer representing Ms. Tanamachi and Mr. Kuwahara, said HUD had told them that it did not directly finance any housing programs in the county, a circumstance effectively limiting its actions. The Department of Transportation has asked Texas state authorities to examine the complaint, Mr. Newar said.  Civil rights organizations, meanwhile, including the Japanese American Citizens League, the League of United Latin American Citizens and the Anti-Defamation League, have voiced support for changing the name.  Considerable outside involvement has come in recent weeks from the Japanese American Veterans Association. Drawing attention to the sacrifices its members made in World War II, the group will be using the meeting in Beaumont to discuss the role of the 442nd Regimental Combat Team, a segregated Japanese-American unit whose exploits included rescuing soldiers of the Texas 36th Division, national guardsmen who were trapped by German forces in the mountains of eastern France in 1944.  "Jap Road should not be a part of the United States landscape,'' said Kelly Kuwayama, 86, a member of the 442nd who said he planned to travel from Washington to Beaumont to speak at the meeting. "And Texas is certainly part of the United States, or at least it was the last time I checked."  The thought of outsiders' descending on Beaumont makes many here bristle. More than 100 residents of Jap Road and supporters of their effort to maintain its name gathered at an open-air bar on Wednesday evening to drink beer, eat barbecue and ponder how to thwart their opponents.  "We're not here to bash the Japanese," Wayne Wright, a retired petrochemical worker who is spearheading a movement to preserve the name, said in an interview before the meeting. "How can I be considered a bigot and a racist when I got a Puerto Rican son-in-law?"  Mr. Wright's wife, Polly, said she believed the name was originally intended to honor the memory of Yasuo Mayumi, a Japanese farmer who, according to local lore, settled in the area in 1905 before returning to Japan in the 1920's.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay, so if you have been wondering where I have gone, this is a recap of what my life has been like the last month. I've been working about 15 hour days for a whole month and half (with no end in sight).. I am currently working on the design of a new elementary school, a 500 sq.ft. add on in Rancho Cucamonga, another 500 sq. ft. add on in Ontario, and a patio/deck cover addition in Upland. Oh yes...the pain of trying to start your own business while you are still working full time. I hope all this is worth it in the long run, that I can have my own successful architectural practice doing residential and commericial work.. which eventually will need to designing of mixed-use development projects. I am also in the process of registering my own company to make it a legitimiate business with tax benfits and all that. So ladies and gentlemen, it's time to jump on the Jeremy Train. Hop on board to a prosperous future!!!!! okay, maybe not dramtic. But I want to clear enough money so my wife and I can start having little Jeremy's... Do you know how much it costs to have kids?!??! god damn!!! Anyways...as soon as next year starts, I'll start working on my own addition to our house, and hopefully I can get our add on published in Dwell!! oh yeah..aiming low for now. Give me another 10 years my ass will be in architectural record biatches!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It looks like two guys in their mid-2o's developed advanced tongue cancer, and the only reason they can link it to is the teeth whitening system they are using.. read it for yourself. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      read the whole story at ESPN.com, but here's my commentary   DENVER -- The woman accusing  urlLink Kobe Bryant  of rape filed a civil lawsuit against the NBA star in federal court Tuesday, a move legal experts said could cripple the criminal case less than three weeks before the trial begins. Attorneys for the 20-year-old woman asked for a jury trial and compensatory damages of at least $75,000, with punitive damages to be determined later.   what a biatch. All she's asking for is $75,000?? All this trouble for $75,000? you freaking kidding me? on top of being a slut you are a moron, too??? it really doesn't matter what the amount is, she's showing that her real motive is that she's after Bryant for money. Just when their case seems to crumble in the criminal court, because she evidently bragged about sleeping about being "raped" by Bryant.   Attorneys John Clune and Lin Wood said their client was owed money for pain, "public scorn, hatred and ridicule" she has suffered as a result of the alleged attack last summer. They also accused Bryant of similar misconduct involving women, but provided no details   public scorn, hatred and ridicule?? you freaking kidding me?? you brought it onto yourself when you decide to make up the damn story. I say you deserve what you get, biatch. Go read the stroy yourself, un-freaking-believable.        
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      NO KIDDING!!!!!! This guy weighs more than 1072 pounds and he's trying to get down to a respectable 200lbs.  Go to the website and look at this guy's picture. holy crap that doesn't even look real. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woo woo, I remember something exciting that happened over the weekend. We were driving to Old town pasadena on the 210 friday night, we were riding smooth in the car pool lane. All of a sudden these two white cars came out of no where, and passed me like I was dong 35 (i was doing almost 80). My wife and I made a comment "those two are gonna crash!!" They were racing each other down the freeway, cutting in and out of traffic like nobody else's around. Finally, fate caught up to them. One car (CAR 1) tried to over take the other car by squeezing in between a big tow truck and the other car (car 2). He didn't quite make i. Car 1 sideswiped car 2. It caused car 2 to steer to the left and hit another innocent passing car, the passing car flipped ovr on to its top and slided down the freeway for a good 30~40 feet before it came to a stop. After hitting car number 2, car number 1 bounced off the center concrete divider, flew threw all lanes of traffic and landed on the right hand shoulder.   I ran over to the driver, fearing the worst... He was convulsing and foaming from the mouth, a nurse on scene said he might have brain damage. The other four passengers in the car were all shaken up, one girl in the back got a big cut on her head because of the windsheild shattered, and the other front passenger had to be taken to a hospital along with the driver.   Moral of the story?  If you are gonna race, drive a Hummer. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i guess my life is just not as exciting as I thought it was. I just realized that even after 10 days of not updating my blog, I GOT NOTHING NEW TO TALK ABOUT!!!!! I get up at about 6:00am everyday, goes to work about 6:45... leave the office about 5:30, comes home, eat dinner.and start working again about 7 pm.. Then I go work out at 9:30, comes home about 10:30..work on my projects some more than head off to bed around 12.  And that's EVERY SINGLE FREAKING DAY!!!!  Not that much excitement going on at the chou hall.  anyways.. I might as well talk about my marriage. Marriage is going grrrrrrrreeeeaaat!!   Things could not be better right now between my wife and I. We are communicating very well and she is starting to understand why I need to work so god damn much. I just feel bad that I don't spend as much time with her as I would like. BUT, if I want to acheive what I have set out to acheive before I turn 30, I gotta do what I gotta do.  Anyways, nothing new happened last weekend. It was my wife's little brother's 21st birthday, so we took him to lunch along with her dad and his wife. Had a great lunch, it was nice to catch up with the in laws. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>