<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, this certainly is not going too well.  It would appear I have nothing to say, but actually that is the farthest from the truth.  Currently, I am concentrating on my immersion French class.  When that ends in one month, perhaps I will feel more motivated.  Perhaps not.  At least not so guilty for doing something non-French.   I do manage to amuse all  - okay,  most  - my friends with my wit and humour, but this isn't a friend, is it?  Is it my diary?  The only time I have kept a journal was when I was wallowing in the darkness of depression.  And then, when I came around and was my old self, I was shocked at what I had written.  I ripped out all the pages and tore them into tiny pieces (no, I haven't gotten around to a shredder yet) and was oh-so-grateful when no one appeared at my door with an  Order for Commitment  and a white jacket with extremely long arms.  Phew!  But I digress.  As usual.  This actually happens rather often when talking with my friends.  I have to stop and think where I was going with a certain point and where that point came from.  I get lost all the time.  And I am not even menopausal!  Yikes!!! I can only imagine what  that  will be like.  Luckily my best friend is older than me.  Ha!  And I am rather fortunate to have a very understanding, P-A-T-I-E-N-T man in my life.  Both these people are gifts.  I do tell Him, but I need to tell her.  Ta for now!             

						
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Okay.  I will do better.  Promise.  But just not too sure what exactly to write in this blog.  Don't want to be too personal.  (Or do I?)  Some topics will not be discussed, at least that is the plan at the moment.  I mean, do I use my real friend's names?  Make up alias' for everyone?  How do I keep them straight?  Do I discuss intimate details?  I can see this blog will give one more thing to obsess about.  Just what I need.  Thank you, J.   

						
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   .....however, not quite sure if I will have done it correctly. I do seem to have quite an ambivalent relationship with technology.  

						
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    ..........and at least there is no French to study. It was difficult, at times, maddening, but I will definitely miss the class. But a few of my classmates do have plans to make themselves at home in my flat for some French movie nights. That should be fun. And I won't even have to rent movies for the first few times. Thanks, John.    Over one week on my "new" meds and I think I have adjusted. But it gets increased this week, along with adding a new med, so not sure how I will be feeling then. The first few days, I was extremely tired, and suffered from migraine-like headaches for a few days.  Migraine-like  due to the fact that they were gone each morning, only to begin again in the afternoon. Also very teary-eyed, but that seems to be the norm lately, starting way before the medication.  I just HATE taking medication, and not sure these will actually work.  And how will we know if they are working?      (And yes, aware reader, I edited this post.  Some things are private and should be hand-written in a journal and never broadcast to complete strangers via the internet.)                            

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Hi again.  I know it's been awhile and apologies are in order, but that French immersion class got the better of me.  This Wednesday is the last class, and then I plan to pleasure read non-stop.  There will be more French but perhaps not until the winter term as my wonderful professor is retiring and not sure what I want to do.  I can't study French with just  anyone .       I am quite pleased with myself for sticking with this.  (The French, not this blog.)  I   have not been feeling myself as of late.  Well, truth be told, I have been feeling perfectly like Trish, but not the good Trish.  I was afraid I was going into another depression even while I was vacationing in France last October.  But, I blamed it on my age.  (Note:  I am not old!)  I blamed it a health challenge that I have since resolved, at least as of this posting.    I blamed it on my job, which IS a problem, but that's an entirely different blog, which will not be written, at least at this time.    I blamed it on various friends, and how they had let me down.        I was trying to blame my unhappiness on everyone, trying to find the person or thing that was responsible for my unhappiness.  And then, last weekend, it finally hit me, as I was sitting an   old breakwater between Fullerton and North Avenue Beaches.  When I thought it would be lovely to jump in and just keep going down, allow myself to be pulled under, and smashed against the cement.  But instead, I broke into tears, thinking of my cats.  My cats!  Mollie and Madeleine stopped me from doing anything stupid.  Now, maybe if I had jumped in, I just would have gotten wet, but where there is a will, there is a way.  And just the the fact that I was thinking all this should tell one how utterly hopeless I felt.         Now, after seeing my doctor, and starting on medication once more, I have made the resolution to do better on getting better.  I hate that I need meds.  And I've only started.  In 1-1/2 weeks, she will increase the Lamictal to 50mg, and add an antidepressant, I forget which one.  Then, every two weeks, the mood stabiliser will be increased, until............   not sure what she will be looking for.  Until I am totally flat?  Until I don't cry anymore?  Or laugh hysterically at my own jokes?  Or say inappropriate things?  At least this drug does not metabolise through the liver so I will not need to have monthly blood levels done.  And it will not make my hair fall out.  But the antidepressants, of the SSRI (selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors, if you're interested) family, will effect my libido.  Lovely.  I think it very odd, not to mention sad, that these wonder drugs also manage to take away something that can bring so much joy.         Oh well, the important thing is, I will be alive.  Flat, but alive.  This is exactly why bi-polar (manic-depressive) people always stop taking their medication.  They want to f-e-e-l everything life gives them.  Own every emotion.  Even if it tears them apart, they need to feel everything.  I need to feel everything.  Own each emotion, thought.  Embrace them.  This is who I am.  I really don't want to lose this.  But I don't want to die just yet either.    'Tis a puzzlement.                 

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    ..............that kept me from writing. Ha! But, I've never been that great with written diaries. I think it has to do with feeling like I  have  to write everyday. And I tend to have problems with  have  to's. I think it's related to the authority figure thing. Whatever.      Did not go for my usual walk on the beach this morning. Just didn't feel too energetic. I guess this will be the norm until I am stabilised on the meds. But, I am keeping busy, and not just sitting here moping, crying, obsessing. And I had a lovely "drop-in" visit which is always most beneficial.       Now, to my bills that didn't get paid last week and trying to get through  A Brief History of the Smile . (Where is the "underline" icon?) It is interesting, but you can tell that it was written by a academic/curator. They always assume everyone has a degree in whatever their discipline is, in this case, Art History. So, at times, I just skim through the wordy spots until I get to the parts that are understandable to the common reader. Note: This is not a criticism, J., just what I've found in the past. And it never stops me from reading them, although not as quickly.    

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Why, oh why, do people always end up in front of me in the line at Starbucks whom have obviously never stepped foot inside a Starbucks - or any other coffee shop, for that matter? Every Starbucks is the same, they all have the same exact thing, and staring at the menu board, reading each line, will not help you decide. It only pisses off everyone behind you. This is ESPECIALLY true at 6:30 a.m. on a weekday, when those of us that are regulars just want to get our coffee and go. Where do you all come from? You are obviously not from the neighborhood.   And some of you are very,  very  high maintenance. Please people, go to your local Starbucks, or, #1 wait until rush hours are over, or #2, know what you want BEFORE getting into line. And do not pull out your credit card for a drip coffee and a bagel.  You really do   not realise how dangerous your actions might conceivably be. They could get you hurt. Rather badly. Jeez!      

						
</post>


</Blog>