<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i wonder why every time i open this site up, and get to the posting page, i can think of almost nothing to write. why do my thoughts flee? is it due to the possible fact that maybe they do not wish to be recorded, to be remembered? such thoughts only wish to vanish, never to be, or   possibly   never to be thought of again. enough metaphors, at least i think they ark metaphors. why do ppl argue? to prove a point i suppose, but why does everything have to be right or wrong? black or white? i wish that there was a different kind of God and set of rules that the ones i believe in. like there would be a God, and he would create a set of rules for people to live by peacefully. and there wouldn't be a SET form of religion, and you didn't HAVE to believe, actually maybe believe in him, but his rules wouldn't be too strict. and despite whether or not you were christian, muslin, jewish, buddhist, hindu...etc, you could always get into heaven, just as long as you were genuinely good. cuz the way christianity was taught to me, you have to be almost, or exactly perfect, and even though God doesn't expect you to be, it's just weird. i mean for you to make a set of rules that you know that no one could perfectly adhere to, seems kind of weird. i just don't get it. g2g 2 bed night.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      what's the driving force behind people? i mean, what MAKES you get up in the mornings to face another day? i don't even know what causes me to get up. what am i here for? am i here to make a difference these days? if all those wishes were granted, wouldn't all those things, all those differences, not make THAT much of a difference? then what would be the point? so that means someone's difference would be denied, right? i don't like how this started, but that doesn't matter because i can't really change what i think. sometimes i would like to change what i think, but i can't- it's already been thought. and if i could change the past i would, but then i might now. cuz bad things can lead to good things. ya know? it's weird. time machines are weird. like how when you travel to the past, your past then becomes a part of your future because your present is experiencing things, or something to that effect. i dunno. actually, i do know. it's just im too lazy to think it over and type it all out. but i hate it when people do that. so i guess im kinda being hypocritical. and that sux. ::shrug:: in my head , there are sooo man thoughts and ideas going through it, that i can't get them all down, and i lose some of them, which isn't nice. i can seriously be soo forgetful, and that NOT kewl. i remember when i WAS, hopefully WAS, really violent, and i worked on it, and now i don't think i am anymore. at least i hope so, and i need to also work on my verbal abuse. it's not kewl that sum1 can just say one little thing and i can make an insult out of it almost immediately. "the tongue is the only instrument that grows sharper with use." o well. i gotta work on that. ugh. tired, but there's soo much that i wanna write on this thing. everything is rushed these days. lol. "these days", as if i've known any other. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i was listening to this Christian station today, which is a rarity on it's own, unless of course my father happens to be the one driving, in which case- he was, and something the pastor/preacher, said was that one of the benefits of being a Christian is that you're prepared to die, that's why you have the courage to live. and i was just thinking about it, and i think it's true. Christians, who truly believe that they are going to heaven, are ready to die. that's why you see them so calm. because their religion has eased the thought of what comes after death, instead of this uncertainty that most, in my opinion, people have that causes such severe amounts of stress. i think that that's probably one of the reasons that religions were created, to make the idea of dying, a lot easier to cope with. i mean where would we be and what kind of society would we live in w/ out religions to control mass amounts of people. don't get my wrong, im not saying that religions are fake little leashes that keep people under control. but that's just one of the things i wonder about. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Song of the Day: "Disappear"  There's a pain that sleeps inside It sleeps with just one eye And awakens the moment that you leave Though I try to look away The pain it still remains Only leaving when you're next to me  Do you know, that everytime you're near Everybody else seems far away So can you come and make them disappear Make them disappear and we can stay  So I stand and look around Distracted by the sounds Of everyone and everything I see And I search through every face Without a single trace, of the person The person that I need  Do you know, that everytime you're near Everybody else seems far away So can you come and make them disappear Make them disappear and we can stay  Can you make them disappear? Make them disappear  There's a pain that sleeps inside Sleeps with just one eye And awakens, the moment that you leave And I search through every face Without a single trace, of the person The person that I need  Do you know, that everytime you're near Everybody else seems far away So can you come and make them disappear Make them disappear and we can stay 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i've made a blog. interesting. though i know NOTHING about what's going on in this thing. ill just take the time to sort it out. maybe i should have just kept my xanga but there's no turning baq now. even though my cluelessness may be the only thing displayed on this page, i just wanted somewhere semi-private. because in a xanga they show EVERYTHING, and that's just not a journal anymore, it's a chat room made by me for posting messages of parties and other such trivial things. but i think ill like this, and maybe when i become bored enough, ill just work on this journal bit by bit, to make it look more like the kind of person i am. i dunno. i think i might have to ask 4 help. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so many things going through my head. that's why people always ask me what's wrong, cuz i sit still and try to sort things out, but im usually hyped and happy. so this doesn't follow suite along w/ the rest of the world's interpretation of my daily behavior. sometimes i just sit and try to think, but then i end up thinking about nothing really, and i don't get anything solved, but somehow i feel just a tad better, so maybe within the depths of my mind i have come to reconcile the diffrences of me and an issue. i wonder why im trying to sound smart, i have only a modicum of the connotation and denotation of thw words that im typing here. im trying to sound "cryptic" ha. riight. anyways, back to the analyzation of tiwa. why is it that when people are deep in thought, they look sad? maybe because everyone is naturally sad on the inside, and they make this phasad of who they want to be. i dunno.  i dont' feel very happy right now. iono. just my parents, and sum friends. too many issues that i don't feel like thinking about. i just wanna go away to a place where i can just think and rest. im being pulled every which way. i just wanna think with clarity. i mean im being burdened by all these THOUGHTS. and some of them are so COMPLETELY random. even I don't know where they cam from, so how can i expect otehrs to? higher level thinking can be such an annoyance.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i wish i could lose weight i mean, it doesn't REALLY show, but i dunno. i guess i have fallen victim to the peer pressure of my fellow youth to look like a twig. but since my un-twiggy figure isn't linked to a very determined mind, i suppose it will just have to be content with lookin like a log. i wish that ms.jenkins would let us perform Bang Bang You're Dead. which is an awesome play, but unfortunately i was warned, by others who had delt w/ the likes of her, to give up. o well. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>