<Blog>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      At a local deli, I'm a stock boy. I'm not positive on the pay...but I'll probably make like 6 bucks an hour. Which is pretty darn good for me.  All I have to do is put some peanuts in a bag...more peanuts in a bag, then put some fruit in a bag...some more fruit in another bag. Then put some cardboard in a box. Shouldn't be too hard......right?
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, since it was a nice summer evening, not too hot not too cold. Just perfect, the air even smelled nice! So, I decided to take a bike right around my usual path (which is a jogger's track outside of a local school). I'm riding along and think to myself..."Hey, I'm on a jogger's path, why not jog?"   So I do. I hide my bike underneath some bushes that are close by (you never can be too careful ya know) then notice an arrow next to me. Apparently someone was shooting arrows. I pick it up to see if its sharp or dull, it was dull. I played Zorro for a few seconds, then toss it. I blast my mp3 player and job for a few minutes. I notice it starting to get dark, so I head back to get my bike and go home.  This is when the bad part happens. I can't find my bike. I'm looking in all the bushes I can find, not there! After about 5 minutes of looking at the same bushes I start to go further back, I then noticed an arrow! I looked around and there it was! If it wasn't for that arrow I might have had to walk home.  So, if you're out there, thank you mysterious archer!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Took this neat little test, here are my results:              INFP  - "Questor". High capacity for caring. Emotional face to the world. High sense of honor derived from internal values. 4.4% of total population.  
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Ok, when I first saw William Hung on American Idol, it was good for a laugh..but you felt o.k about it because he decided to publicly humiliate himself on t.v, even with his good-heartedness. Now...well, now he just pisses me off.  With that being said, I'll go through what I call the "Stages of Hung".  1- Ridicule.: You see this Chinese immigrant singing his heart out with bad accent, and an even worse singing voice. It was pretty funny because he REALLY tried and REALLY thought he can sing.  2- Applaud.: I heard he was getting a record deal, and despite his horrible voice, I thought, "Good for him. Its nice to see the good guy get what he deserves." Because, he is a nice, modest guy. Heck, he showed up to one of his shows in the back of his parents' Honda!  3- Feeling Sorry (this stage is optional).: Maybe I'm the only one that felt this, but this kid thinks he can truely sing good, yet people are laughing at him when he sings. And I don't think he knows it. I felt kind of bad for him for a little bit.  4- Annoyance.: This is the stage where you start to get annoyed (duh!), this guy sucks at singing yet he releases an album, performs numerous shows, he even performs at a canadian sports game(can't think of which one it was). He's probably making alot of money off of this, all because he sucks!  5- Enough.: This is the last and final stage, this stage is when you want to rip out his vocal cords and attach them to a nuclear bomb which hits his house. After hearing him ruin "Rocket Man" and "We are the Champions" that set me off. Why won't this fad die out?!  Welp, that is what I call the "Five Stages of Hung".
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, heres something that made me mad.  I went to my local CVS store to get some photos developed from my trip, and I decided to pay some extra money for the one hour photo..which is a few bucks extra. Anyways, I come back an hour later and guess what? They said come back later on this afternoon. What?!   So, I go out to Marshall's to do some shopping, go back to CVS, and I'm told to come back a half hour later. I come back a half hour later and FINALLY the pictures are done...after about 5-6 hours.  Why say 1 hour photo and charge extra money when it'll be done in the same time it usually does?!  Argh.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My first blog ever.  Got back from my trip to Busch Gardens / Water Country U.S.A the other day. It was like every other trip, the rides and all were fun. The hotel seemed a little sub-par after staying at Disney's Animal Kingdom hotel. That place was amazing.     Anyway, at Busch Gardens I was one spot in line from being stuck on Escape from Pompeii, which would have really sucked since it was so freaking hot outside.  We stopped at Paramount's King's Dominion, which was suprisingly better then both the parks we planned on going to. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>