<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Friday night, Alexis and I took Amber out to dinner at Bucca de Beppo. We shared the baked ravioli & the bruscetta. It was yummy! I guess they don't sing Happy Birthday with all the waitstaff like they used to, because someone actually wrote a letter complaining about how it ruined their romantic evening once. =P So our waitress brought out the candles and did a solo for Amber, but Alexis and I joined in, too, so it was fun anyway. LOL  On Saturday, Jason & I took the kids to the mall to find a Dodger t-shirt for Matt. We found one at Sears for $5! Jason, Matt, Dave & Russ were all going to the game against the Angels on Sunday. Everyone had a t-shirt but Matt, so we had to get him one, especially since it was his first baseball game!  So on Sunday, I packed some food for Matt to take to the game. They left around 11am, because the game started at 1:00. Joey & Emily stayed home w/ me, and I cleaned up around here and cooked a lasagna for our pot-luck youth leaders meeting we were having at 5pm. With Matt at the game, and Joey sleeping for 3 1/2 hours during his nap, it almost felt like I had another day off! LOL I watched the game on TV just in case they showed Matt & Jason, but they never did. I guess it was Kid's Day at Dodger Stadium, so they were showing a lot of dads & sons together. It was really cute, but they never showed MY son. Oh well! Jason said that Matt had a really good time, and was really well behaved. He had cotton candy, and a chocolate malt ice cream, plus a Sprite and all the food I packed for him. No wonder he sat still the whole time--he was busy eating! LOL I guess he also drew some pictures, and asked a lot of questions about the stadium and the game. Jason was excited because the Dodgers actually won 10-5! It's the first game he's been to where they didn't lose. LOL  They got home just in time for our youth leaders meeting/pot-luck. Our youth pastors brought their kids, so Matt got to work off some of that sugar playing with them, and Joey was cured of his loneliness. LOL But there was one time I had to intervene in their "game"... I walked by their room and saw Matt sitting on an upside down rectangular laundry basket & Joey was sitting on the floor nearby. I heard Matt saying, "You have 5 more minutes!" and I asked them, "Where is Josiah?" (our youth pastor's 2 year old son)...yeah...he was under the laundry basket!! Matt was sitting on it so he wouldn't get out! LOL I guess they were pretending he was their prisoner or something, but Josiah didn't seem to mind. He was just laying their quietly and wasn't even crying or anything. LOL I felt so bad, but at the same time I couldn't help laughing! I did apologize to his parents, though. LOL Thankfully they still want to be our friends. ;)  And, as if this wasn't a great enough weekend...our friends Cherish & Dave had their baby! It's their first baby, a boy, and he was born exactly one month after Emily, on June 26th. Congratulations guys!!!
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      =) Hope it's a good one!
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Matthew visiting us at the hospital. 5/27/04&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Joey is helping Emily learn how to use her binky at the hospital. 5/27/04&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yay! Lindsey (my MIL) was nice enough to take the boys for the day today. She and Grandma came by to pick them up around 10:30 this morning, and we don't have to pick them up until after Jason gets home from work and we get some dinner. That means Emily & I have a date! LOL And she's even going to give them a bath and have them in their p.j.'s for us. What a saint!   Last night I took the baby to church. It was only our second time--we went on Sunday for Father's Day. Jason had to be there early for worship practice, and so he took Matt with him. That made it easier for me to get out of the house with Emily & Joey when we went later.   Since it was my first time taking the kids out by myself, it was definately an adventure. I had to feed her before we left, so that took some time. Then she spit up as soon as I put her in the carseat...so I took her out and changed her clothes. Well we haven't done laundry in awhile, so it took me some time to find something that was clean  and  fit her. Then, I put her back into her carseat. She spit up again. =P This time I just wiped her down really good with a burp rag because we were running late! I made sure she didn't smell...LOL So we were finally out the door!  Well, I left early so that I could go by Taco Bell (thanks to Pam for the gift certificate) and get some dinner for me and Jason. Well, the boys don't eat from there, so I also had to go get them some french fries from somewhere. We finally get to the church at 6:30 and we eat our dinner in the Cafe. Then at 7:00, it was time to put the boys in their class, and Jason went to the youth room to do worship, and I went into the sanctuary (it's quieter for the baby). Of course, since she is still eating every 2 hours, by the time I got seated it was time to eat again.   Alexis sent me a link to this comic strip that really explains it all.  urlLink Check it out.  LOL  Thankfully, next week is VBS at church so I won't have to do that again for awhile...
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, so Joey has been curious about this whole breastfeeding thing lately. Yesterday he put his hand on my shirt and asked if milk came out "there". I said yes, and then he said, "Can I squish it?" ROFL  Today I was switching over to nurse on the second side and he said, "She drinks on one side and then the other?!" I said, "Yes!" And he then said, "Oh...one is regular milk, and that one is  chocolate !" I could have died laughing!
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Our newest addition, born 5/26/04&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, so after much thought, I realized I'll never keep my Geocities website up-to-date as much as it needs. So to satisfy far-away family members, and because I thought it might be fun to jump on this blog bandwagon, I set this thing up today.   And just to get it out there in the open right off the bat--I can be a bad speller, so don't make fun of me too much. ;o) Oh hey--I just noticed this thing has spellchecker! LOL Nevermind...
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      *Note to Grandma: Thanks for the advice on my sunburn! I'm feeling much better now. My nose is peeling a bit, and my arms & legs are itchy, so I'm assuming they are soon to follow... I hope you made it to the basement. That made me chuckle because I knew exactly what you were talking about. "The Basement" will always be your nemesis! (BIG HUGS)*&nbsp; &nbsp;  So my new big news is that Emily rolled over today! She was on her tummy and rolled to her back for the first time. She is 2 months old as of yesterday...I can't believe how it is just flying by! I have new pictures of her, and when I get them scanned in I will post some here. Keep checking for updates! =)  &nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday Emily had her 8 week check-up. She is huge! Average weight gain (according to her pediatrician) is 2lbs a month. In 6 weeks, she has gained 4lbs 10oz... she is now 13lbs 4oz ! Everything is fine, though...she is just a good eater, and&nbsp;a good baby. =) I'm so proud of my lil' chunker. LOL  She did get her first set of vaccines, though. She had to get 4 shots--2 in each leg. Poor girl slept all day yesterday and today. =( And they used an evil Bioinjector instead of needles...It's an air gun that forces the vaccine into the skin. I hate it. If I can't get them to use needles from now on, I'm going to seriously consider finding a different pediatrician. It was pretty traumatic for her, and now she has 4 little round bruises on her thighs.   We went to the beach after her appointment. It was our first real trip of the summer. LOL I'm such a land-lover... Lindsey, Patti, and all 5 of us went to the local beach and hung out for about 2 hours. Jason and I were the only ones who got in the water, except Lindsey got in up to her knees. She was having fun playing w/ the kids on the sand. However, Jason and I got really burned...Jason's head and neck are red, but my whole body got it. My arms, face, neck, and tops of my thighs are all red, but the left side of my body got more sun and so it hurts more. My left arm aches...and I look rediculous on top of it all. LOL And knowing how I am, it will all go away soon and I'll be white again. I don't tan. *sigh*  Last night was the last night of our church women's revival. Patti is done with all her speaking engagements out here and went to Knott's Berry Farms with some church ladies today. She leaves tomorrow. It's been a very nice visit, but she'll be missed. There has already been talk of her coming out again next year to speak at the prison again, and maybe at a different church. I really hope Chrystal can come out then! We'll be praying that it happens.  For now, I'm just trying not to cry every time one of the kids climbs on me...you'd think they would run away since I smell like vinegar...LOL (which, by the way, is no magical cure, like people say it is...*whine*) 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      No sooner did I pick up Emily to feed her, and I smelled *that* smell...Sure enough, Joey pooped in his pants again. So Emily had to fuss a little longer so I could clean him up. I made him sit on the potty (no arguments this time--whew!), and he ended up pooping more! He was really proud of himself, so maybe this is the beginning of the end? Oh, and then, while I was feeding Emily, she spit up all over me and herself, and then proceeded to poop out of her diaper, all over my shorts. So now I have to go do a load of laundry, and I swear I'll scream if I anyone else deficates on me. I'm protesting bodily fluids right now... 
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Joey has been in underwear for a week now! He has even slept in them a couple of times and has stayed dry. We're making good progress...however, going poop is another story. He still goes in his pants, but we're trying to get him over his fear of sitting on the toilet. I still have hope, but maybe it's just sleep deprivation making me delirious...LOL &nbsp; Patti is in town this week doing a conference at our church.&nbsp; It's so great to have her here, but I really miss Chrystal and wish she could have come out this time, too.  *Note to Chrystal: your mom has lost her "Em-Cam"! But hopefully we'll find it soon...we're looking everywhere!*&nbsp; Last night was awesome though. I can't wait for tonight's service!  &nbsp; Emily finally caught the cold that was going around our house this last week. But we're all finally feeling better now. Emily was such a trooper during her first cold. Not fussy one bit--even when I suctioned her nose. She would just smile at me, as if to say, "Thanks Mom, that feels better!" LOL &nbsp; Tomorrow is Emily's 8 week check-up. I'm excited because I'll get to find out what she weighs. Her last check-up was at 1 week, and she was 8lbs, 8oz. My guess is she's at least 11lbs--she is a chunky monkey! I'm not excited, however, because she'll also get her first set of shots.&nbsp;Hopefully it will go well, but our pediatrician uses an evil air gun thingie to give the shots, instead of a simple needle. The boys hate it, and I don't believe the doctors when they say it's supposedly less painful than a needle... &nbsp; Anyway, I wish I could post more, but Emily is crying to be fed! 
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So we're trying Joey in underwear now. He's been wearing pull-ups for quite sometime now, and he goes pee in the potty more often than not, but hasn't mastered #2 yet. But I figured he could wear underwear during waking hours, and we'll see how it goes. Poor guy has a terrible diaper rash, so I figured in this heat, the breathablity of cotton would feel better to him. He cried at first--he had the same reaction as Matt did. He finally settled down and played as usual, but when I was nursing Emily, he had a pee-pee accident. =( So I cleaned him up, made him finish his "job" in the toilet and put fresh underwear on him. He was happy to put on the second pair, so maybe this won't be so hard after all! At this rate, he'll be potty trained earlier than Matt was.   We'll be sure to keep you updated on this exciting event...LOL
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday was my youngest sister's  16th  birthday. I couldn't post this yesterday since I was barely home, but I wanted to least get it up today. Hope it was a great one, Jess! XOXO
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sorry I haven't updated all week! I'll just give you a quick rundown of stuff that's been going on...   Sunday, July 4th  We skipped church because Matt had a runny nose, and so he wouldn't be allowed in his class anyway. We just bummed around most of the morning. In the afternoon, we went to Dave & Lindsey's for a BBQ. We had a ton of yummy food, and a good time with them and their friends, Keith & Camille. We were supposed to meet up with the Anderson's at the park for a fireworks show at 6pm, but we were still eating at 5:30. I called to let Alexis to let her know we would be late, but I couldn't get ahold of her.   Around 6:30 we left for the park. Lindsey said Matt could stay the night with them, but Joey wanted to see the show, so he came with us. We got to the park around 7, but had to park our car about 1/4 mile away, and walk the rest of the way. We still weren't able to get ahold of Alexis, and so I was just hoping they weren't too mad at us for being an hour and a half late! We looked for them in our usual spot (this was our 3rd year going w/ them), but didn't see them. So we decided to just peruse the food court area and then find a spot of our own. Well, no sooner did we turn down the first aisle did I see Alexis! LOL It turned out that they were late, too, and had just gotten there about 10 minutes before us. Steven and the kids camped out at a spot while she went to look for us. We all thought it was pretty funny.  The show started at 9pm. Emily slept thru the whole thing, so the noise didn't even bother her even though it was pretty loud. But Joey was afraid of the fireworks, so he just quietly hid under his blankie and layed down next to Jason on the sleeping bag. When it was over and the park lights came back on, we thought he was asleep, but he had his eyes open. He was so glad when it was over. But then, we had to walk back to our car...he was exhausted. The poor little guy had a busy day with no nap! We all slept in until around 9am the next morning.   Monday, July 5  Jason had the day off of work, so we lazed around the house all morning. He went to pick up Matt at Lindsey's and then we were all going to go out to lunch at the Olive Garden. But as soon as he got back and we were about out the door, one of the hospitals called him in to work. =P Yay about the extra $$, but Boo that we had to change our plans. By the time we finally made it to the restaurant, it was 4pm. So we just decided to have an early dinner instead. So much for cheap soup, salad & breadsticks--I was starving by that time! Then we went to Toys R Us to buy a kite--Jason swears it's for the boys, but I think it's more for him. LOL While they were in there, I went into Mervyn's because they were having a sale. I didn't buy anything because we really didn't have a lot of money, and I wanted to save it for Spiderman 2. But I did find out that I fit in a size 12 now (up from an 8 pre-pregnancy). It's not so depressing...I'm sure I'll be back in an 8 in a few months. At least I hope...LOL My body has changed after every baby, so who knows this time?  We finally got home around 5:30, and Jason wanted to take the boys to the park to fly their new 3D pirate ship kite. Well, I really wanted to go see Spiderman 2 with Alexis, so I called her up. There was a 6:10 show, but I had to feed the baby, so that wasn't going to work. So we decide to go to the 7:00 show. We leave for the theater, just us "girls", but Alexis had to make a deposit at her bank. By the time we were done there, it was 6:56...so we weren't going to make that show either! LOL Well, there was still hope because there was an 8:00 show. We drove across the street to get Alexis some dinner from Subway (I was still full from earlier), and then we went to Trader Joe's & Rite Aid for movie snacks. For $3.50 (about the cost of one candy bar at the theater), I got a bottle of water, a king size Payday, a king size Almond Joy and a large pack of gum! Theaters are such a rip-off. And everything fit neatly into my diaper bag. LOL  We finally get to the theater, and guess what? The 8:00 show is sold out, and there is a line forming for seats to the 9:15 show. Well, we HAVE to see the movie now...we've been trying all evening! So Alexis bought the tickets while I waited at the curb, and then we went across the street to Mimi's Cafe. We were not going to stand in the line at the theater for the next hour with the baby, so we decided instead to have tea and a plate of fruit while we waited. Yum. We finally get to the theater a little before 9:00, expecting to still have to wait in the line. We put Emily in the stroller so we wouldn't have to hold her the whole time. But when we got up to the front of the theater, we found out they had already let everyone in. So Alexis took the baby, with the intent to find us seats, and I went back to the minivan to return the carseat and stroller.   When I got back to our theater, Alexis was standing just outside, by the guy who takes your ticket. I was a bit confused...I asked her if she found seats and she said that not only were there no seats together, but she fell! As she was climbing up and down the stairs looking for 2 seats together, holding the baby, in the dark, she tripped coming down and fell down hard. Thankfully, Emily was fine--she didn't get dropped, or hit her head or anything. She was safe against Alexis' chest. However, Alexis was not so fine. She skinned her left knee and twisted her right ankle! We debated about whether or not to wait for the 10:00 show because we wanted to sit together, and decided to go to customer service to exchange our tickets for that showing. When they found out she fell, they didn't make us stand in the longggggggggggggggg line that was formed outside. So we found a bench and Alexis propped up her foot. I got her some ice from the concession stand. We probably could have gotten our money back, too, but we didn't push the issue. We just wanted to see the darned movie!   Finally, we got up to go into the theater, but Alexis' ankle had started to swell and she couldn't put any weight on it. We hobbled over to the doors, and I asked her if she would rather just go home since this was looking like a serious injury. She said No Way! After all that we have invested in this night, now we HAD to see the movie. LOL We found a good seat up near a railing where she could elevate her foot, and we watched the movie like that. And it was a good thing that the movie didn't suck, because I would have been so mad! I'm actually looking forward to seeing it again when Jason wants to go see it. Hopefully, the next time will be less eventful. LOL   Wednesday, July 6  Today, Alexis and I both had doctors appointments. Her for her ankle, and me for my 6 week post-partum check-up. Since Alexis has been crippled for the last couple of days, I drove her to her appointment. All her doctor said was that it was a classic sprained ankle, and to ice it and keep it up. I had to leave Alexis there to go to my appointment, and then I picked her up afterwards. At my appointment, Emily was cranky and cried during my whole exam. Finally, when the doctor was finished, she picked up Emily and took her out front so I could get dressed. Emily was happy as a clam in the doctor's arms, but as soon as I took her back to put her in her carseat, she started to cry again. LOL Figures.  When I got home from all that, Jason was getting home with the boys after an afternoon of kite flying at the park. We had to be at church by 5, for a youth event. We had a pizza party in the gym, and then at 6, we left to go to Cabrillo Beach. I took the kids, including the baby. But we only stayed for about an hour and then I took them home. It was cold, and the kids were tired & dirty. We didn't swim, but there was a bonfire and marshmallow roasting. Jason had to stay with the youth, because aside from the youth pastor, it was just him and one other adult to watch an entire bus-load of teenagers. So when I got home, I did a marathon kid-bathing session and had all 3 bathed, in their p.j.s and the boys in bed in just 45 minutes. I sat down to nurse Emily at 9, and just about fell asleep because I was so tired.  So that's been my week. Oh yeah, and I forgot that now we're all sick. Except for Emily, lucky girl. The boys and I all have runny noses, coughing and congestion, and Jason has a scratchy throat and sneezes a lot. I swear summer colds are the worst because all you want to do is go hang out with people somewhere like the park or the beach, and no one wants to be around you because you're contagious. So, we're stuck at home for awhile--quarantined. Except for tonight--Jason got paid, so we're going out for some fine Mexican food. ...Fajitas...YUM! 
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am already gearing up for the holidays...well, at least planning & budgeting anyway. But we were at Big Lots the other day and we found Matt's birthday present! A big kid's bike w/ training wheels for only $25! We couldn't pass it up, so even though it's 6 months early, we bought it. It's hiding at Dave & Lindsey's for now.  Thursday night Jason & I dropped the boys off at Dave & Lindsey's, and we went to Shakespeare by the Sea. We saw the first half of Two Gentlemen of Verona. It was really cold & windy after it got dark, so at intermission, we left. We went to Starbucks & then picked up the kids by 10pm. It was fun, but it was the first time in 4 or 5 years that we havent' seen the whole play! We usually go every year to see the comedies (they do one comedy and one tragedy every summer).  Everyone has something to do tonight except me. Boo hoo! Jason is at another baseball game w/ his parents--this time it's the Angels v. Dodgers at Angels' stadium. Alexis is out on a date w/ her husband. Kelly & Casey even found something to do! LOL Oh well, at least there are a couple of good movies on tv tonight.  I hope everyone has a great 4th of July weekend! 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's been almost 24 hours since he threw up, and he's fine. He's been able to keep down crackers, pretzels & 7-up, so when he wakes up from his nap I'll give him a bath and he can have real food. Well, as real as he likes...peanut butter sandwiches anyone? LOL  Tonight we're going out to eat with Jason's family, but we're leaving the boys home with a babysitter. Woo Hoo...grown-up time! Except we're bringing Emily, of course.  Alexis and I have been making a lot of jewelry lately. I think we've made about 14 pairs of earrings, just as many bracelets, and about 3 or 4 necklaces. Our problem? We don't know where to sell them! I think she is going to ask her mom if we can sell them in her shop (she owns her own hair salon in the rich part of town). But other than that, I don't know. We've considered Ebay, but to be honest, I'm not sure if they'd sell very well on there. But I'm open to try! If you have any suggestions, leave a comment, or email me. For now, I'm excited to just make stuff. It's fun. In fact, when I'm done here, I'm going to go make another bracelet to wear to dinner tonight. =) 
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's Matt's turn to be sick. We went to the mall today with Jason's aunt, cousin, grandma & my MIL. Matt complained that his tummy hurt a little, but he was acting fine the whole time we were there, until we were in one store...he said he was tired, but I figured since we had been there for 2 1/2 hours and he missed his nap that maybe he just needed to sit down. When we walked out of the store, he turned around and projectile vomited all over the floor. And it just kept coming...It was a little embarrassing, but I felt bad for him more than anything. He looked very pale after that. We rushed him home, and he is doing so-far-so-good. It's been about 2 hours since it happened, so I'm hoping that it was just a one-time thing. Stay tuned...  As for the rest of our visit with the family, it's going well! They flew in late Friday night, so we hooked up with them on Saturday. We all went to the beach, and that was fun. This time I remembered to wear sunscreen! But all the sunscreen the world wouldn't have helped Jason when he was swimming along, and got stung by a jellyfish! I guess he just brushed his hand across it by accident and before he realized what had happened his whole hand was red and was swelling up. The sting traveled all down his arm, about halfway to his elbow. We had a lifeguard look at it, and he sprayed it with vinegar &amp; water--after which we all reminisced about that  Friends  episode...you know the one...LOL! We ended up leaving the beach a little early so we had time to bathe the kids and take naps before dinner. We went out for some yummy Mexican food, and then Jason & I went home to put the kids to bed and watched Johnny English. It was pretty funny.  Yesterday, Jason &amp; the boys went to church while I stayed home to clean the house. I got all my weekly chores done in the morning so that I would have time to play this week. I'm really glad it's done now that Matt is sick, although that just means I'll have to scrub the bathroom again. Oh well! The family all went out to Santa Monica to do some shopping, but we stayed home and then met them for dinner at the Macaroni Grill. That was fun, but the service was really slow and they screwed up our checks. When we got home, we tried to watch Minority Report, but Jason fell asleep. He had already seen it when it was in the theaters, though, so I stayed up to watch it while he went to bed. I really enjoyed it, but I had to turn away at one point...ew. It was pretty mild, I'm sure, but I'm particularly grossed out by things having to do with those body parts. Why do sci-fi's have to be gross? LOL  P.S. John Hefron won Last Comic Standing! Yay! 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday we got paid for the damages done to the minivan. Jason had to drive out to meet the lady (her son was the one who hit us), and she just gave him a cashier's check. Yay! Now we can get it fixed. I'm so glad the whole process went smoothly, and we didn't have to fight with anyone. I guess the teen is a fairly new driver, because it was the first time he took his dad's car out--and his parents were out of town, and his girlfriend was leaving the next day to go to school, I guess. It was just a bad night for him! I feel bad for the guy, but it explains why the parents didn't want it on their insurance.  I also got my wedding ring resized, so I picked it up yesterday. It's the first time I've been able to wear it for about 2 years. It's like wearing a new ring! I was a size 3 when I first got it, and now I'm a whopping 4 1/2...LOL It just wouldn't fit over my knuckle, so I knew it wasn't just a matter of gaining weight (I've had 3 babies since I first got it, afterall...). My wedding band & engagement ring were soddered together, so they had to take them apart, resize both of them, and then put them back together. In all, it only cost $58, which is reasonable. But it's so shiny now...it was so dirty before...I guess I didn't realize how much I missed wearing it.  Jason's family from Pennsylvania are coming out to visit. They fly in tomorrow night and will stay a week. I'm not sure what they have planned while they are out here, but if we end up hanging out with them a lot, it might be awhile before I get to update again. 
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      He is 100% better today! Just thought I'd update you. What a weird 24hr bug! 
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Poor Joey is sick today. He woke up complaining of a tummy ache and then threw up all morning. He doesn't have a fever or anything, just lethargic. He seems to feel a little bit better now...at least he can keep down food and liquids.  Matt spent the day at his Granna's house, so that Joey could rest and Matt would be able to play outside and stuff. Jason just left to go pick him up--he has been over there since about 10:30am and it's almost 7:30pm now. I bet he will fall asleep as soon as he gets in the car. LOL  *Thanks Lindsey!*   I spent the day caring for Joey (& Emily, too, but she slept most of the day LOL), and making jewelry. So far we've watched Ice Age twice, Oliver &amp; Company, The Prince of Egypt, Dora the Explorer on DVD, and a video called "Little People" (claymation about the toys). I'm so glad Last Comic Standing is on tonight because I could really use some grown-up tv right about now! =)  *Vote for John Hefron!*  
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I forgot to add that Emily is sleeping through the night now (although my milk machines don't seem to know that yet...). LOL She is sleeping from around 7-8pm to 5-5:30am, eats, and then sleeps until around 7:30-8am. I'm so happy! =) And today when I was playing with her, she was really giggling...not just the grunt that sometimes accompanies her smiles. That is what I've been waiting for! I have always wondered what her laughter would sound like, so I'm excited that it's finally happening. *cheesy, I know* 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jason was able to get free tickets to the Dodger v. Pirates game yesterday. We had awesome seats! We were on the field level, under the overhang (translation: shade the whole game), and right in front of the consessions & bathrooms. We took all 3 kids, and so Joey got a chance to go to the baseball game this time. The boys had so much fun! We were in the last row, so they were able to stand on their seats without interfering w/ anyone else's view of the game. We bought them foam fingers, and they would stand up and shout "Dod-gers! Dod-gers! Dod-gers!" LOL It was so cute. We also took Emily, but I borrowed a Baby Bijorn carrier from a friend so we didn't have to worry about where to put a stroller or infant carrier (we only had 4 seats for all 5 of us). She did so well during the game, and I'm so glad we were in the shade the whole time. And even though it was fun just to be at the game, it was a bonus when the Dodgers won 8-3! They hit like 4 or 5 homeruns, and it seemed that every time they did, Jason was up getting food for the boys. LOL Oh, and Sylvester Stallone was there. They showed him up on the big screen, but I could see where he was sitting (behind homeplate, of course), and tried to take a picture. It was a lot of fun.  After the game, we went to Jason's work to get his paycheck and then went to Downtown Disneyland to take the kids to eat at the Rainforest Cafe. After dinner, we walked around in the stores a bit, and then went home. We got home in time to put the kids to bed and watch Last Comic Standing  (vote for John Hefron!).     Kelly, I read on your site about your car window...that stinks, but I can relate. We were out to eat on Tuesday night and while we were sitting in the restaurant waiting for our food, a waitress came up and asked if the minivan belonged to us. When we said yes, she gave us a "look" and said that someone had hit it and wanted to talk to us...turns out some guy was backing out of the space next to us and turned a little too soon. He scraped our bumper and shattered our brakelight on the drivers side. =( We got an estimate from our insurance company, and it is going to cost about $494 to fix! Well the driver's dad is going to pay for it, but we're not sure if we'll just accept cash or let the insurance company handle it. Either way, our minivan looks ghetto now!  I posted some pictures from my recent developments. I know some of them are washed out, but I have a cheap scanner, so there's nothing I can do about it. I just dropped off the film I used at the baseball game, so I should have them back by next week. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Jason & Joey at the fireworks show on July 4th. Joey posed for this shot...during the show he hid under his blankie. LOL&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Emily at about a month old&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Matt at his first LA Dodgers game &nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Emily trying to see her world without getting run over by her brothers&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>


</Blog>