<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      alright so im writing in this again cuz my last entry deleted god damn fucking stupid blog. so today i babysat sam, alexa and deanna...sam learned how to ride a bike. she and alexa fought a lot...blah, and deanna has hand, foot and mouth disease. great. i still havent talked to william cuz hes a butt but i guess i can forgive him since i lurrrve him so much. anna is supposed to come over today, i hope she does. i also have to babysit tomorrow at 12:30, but i get to see baby max for the first time!! haha which reminds me i guess i havent told you, kara had her baby! w00tw00t! except now im going to have to babysit max and sean. im sure i'll love max, but i think sean is the most annoying five year old on the face of the planet. fucker. my kitty's kinda sick but not too bad, shes not peeing all over so its probably just a cold. ick. also im gonna go ride rebel today. oOH!  i got to ride my friends mare yesterday!! she was SO freaking fun!!!!!! rahh i guess i should take a nap or go get high. this is my life.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so i spent the night at shane's last night...twas fun...i got really depressed though. we also watched a lot of family guy. i havent talked to william for like 4 days. this sucks my butthole a huge amount. i spent the weekend with my cousin, and she has always struck me as a really kind of...goodie two shoes kind of girl. i dont mean that mean, she just never really did anything bad. but we actually drank together. i was really surprised...mm, vodka...we were going to break open the captain morgan but i think mother would notice. i havent done anythign with sarah lately, i think we're going to hang out tonight and have a scatergories party because we're losers and have no life. oh wait thats just me haha..sooooooo this summer is pretty uneventful, on wednesday i get to go see my aunt-in-law's baby!! he looks so cute, i've seen some pictures. then friday i have summer band which is fucking retarded, i hate summer band. and we're going to have a test after 4 weeks what the hell is that shit??? ugh. oh well. i guess i should get going because i have horseback in a little bit...it got moved up from six to five, and i have to leave at like 4:15. and im still in my clothes so i need to get in my breeches. i bet ya'll care a heap. haha. there was this button i saw and i really want it, its got this cow on it and then it says "DONT TIP ME OVER YOU FREAKING HILLBILLY!!" i was laughing so hard i was crying...im gonna buy it somtime, you mark my words. even if i have to buy it off of ebay which is lame but hey it works. you know everyone loves ebay a bunch and i think its just stupid. they dont even have that great of stuff, get over it people!! and its all for "such a great price" WELL MAYBE BECAUSE ITS USED AND PROBABLY SUCKS MY BUTT just like you. hmph.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      im really sick of boys *sigh* i talked to william yesteday...er...sort of...well he left a bunch of messages on my away message...god i miss him...i dont know why he didnt tell me he was leaving though. i guess he doesnt care about me as much as i thought. heh. oh well im sort of used to that when it comes to guys. so i saw dodgeball yesterday and it was really really funny! ack hehe apparantly im a cum guzzling slut. ohh baby ohh baby. blah. my schedule for next year sucks some ass. glynis if you're reading this i hope you have eagle band first hour cuz then we're together!! woo! or if you signed up for enriched english, 4th hour with froehle...im not looking forward to that though cuz froehle is a fucking slut bitch. ugh. oh well. or maybe world studies 7th hour with a teacher that is unknown! woo!! or individual sports 5th hour second semester...thats all i remember off the top of my head. yes. well anyways...im in a pretty crappy mood today but i guess thats fine because i get to go ride rebel! woo! the people are here working on the projector...apparantly it was put up too close to the screen and stuff but oh well. haha... .... ..... ohhh!!! and this weekend jenna and i get the house to ourselves!! woo! its gonna be a BLAST!!!!!!! alright im going to stop boring everyone.....!!!!~~~~~~~~~~
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woo sarah is at my house right now and we are going to go to dodgeball because it looks like a silly little movie. if you want to see somthing funny go to http://world.std.com/~mmcirvin/rar.jpg because its funny. glynis is my buddy also, and she dumped michelle because michelle is crazy. yay for glynis!! and ross still hates me but thats okay because hes ugly. and im still upset at william because he didnt tell me he was leaving. bastard fuck. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ughh i have such a hangover
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeaa well some rich lady in a mansion wants me to babysit for her and im assuming shes gonna pay well and the little kid is cute so im excited haha...yay...im not mad at michelle anymore, and i met someone whos name is star!! it was krazy weird!! she was nice but if i were her i'd change my name because its pretty retarded haha...annnnd then my mom decided to make me her slave and i had to cook a bunch of shit for her...thats right folks,,,well okay they were special k bars and cookies and stuff for this picnic thing...i guess...i dont know why im writing in this i have nothing to say!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              urlLink   Your Years at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry         Name         Age         House     Gryffindor  Hufflepuff  Ravenclaw  Slytherin       Family Line     Muggleborn  Half-Blood  Pure-Blood        Dated      Dean Thomas        You are well known for      The best witch/wizard Hogwarts has ever seen!Wo0t!       Percentage of student body you shagged -  97%                                                                             How do the staff and students feel about you      Can i have you autograph?              This   Quiz   by  urlLink  lady_ameily   - Taken 146665 Times.          New! Get Free  urlLink Daily Horoscopes  from Kwiz.Biz 
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      blaaaaaaaaah i love williammmmmmmmmmmmmmm and im pissed at kyleeeeeeee and im supposed to do somthing with johnnnnnnnnnn and rossssssssssss isnt mad at meeeeeeee and blaaaaaaaaaaah
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry i havent written in this in a long time...so michelle has royally pissed me off. i dont want to talk about that, i dont care about *that* anymore. and kyle has pissed me off too, and i do want to talk about that, because i do care about that a lot. so he took some vicodin, and i know im sounding hypocritical but hes going to get addicted and im really pissed. he totally is better than that and the FUCKER GOES AND TAKES IT god im so mad. i cant even ...ugh...im so pissed right now i cant even ...i dont know nevermind. FUCK. im at a loss for words and that really takes a lot.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yep so last night i went to accoustic cafe with john and then back to his house until midnight...twas a fun time...haha we were on the computer and found some pretty funny things...like that "hey ya charlie brown" and this one airline commercial for blacks...i'll find it somtime soon and put it on here so ya'll can visit it, yo. hehe...i talked to william yesterday, and we had a fight the day before but it was mostly just me being a bitch...gosh golly gee i lurve that boy so much...spidey time!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today i had summer band *fuck* and anna came over..and now im going to accoustic cafe with john so im going to stop this post and write later. haha
     

    
</post>


</Blog>