<Blog>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tomarrow im going to the mall but i can't decide which one to go to.there's the shops at willow bend,which is where all the rich,stuck up people go.there are better stores there.and they also have a toni&guy.i need a haircut bad.my friend works there,so i can get it cut for like,$15. or i could go to stonebriar centre. its ok,but nothing special.then i'll probaly go to thriftworld and buy some stuff there with my leftover money.or i could use my leftover money on pot.i like the 2nd one better.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      6/22/04-im feeling better than i did yesterday.i just finshed helping ny neighbor move.my back hurts so bad right now.i woke up at 9:45,took a shower,got dressed,ate breakfast,did some stuff,came home,and then went to help my neighbor move.im pretty sure you don't care about what i did today,but i told you anyway. i wanna go to warped tour,but i don't have any tickets.and i also don't wanna stand around all day in the heat.i try to make my blogs entertaining,but this one's boring as crap.oh well.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      6/21/04-um...hi i guess,this is my first blog ever,so i'll try to keep it exciting.MABEY IT'LL BE MORE EXCITING IF I TYPE IN ALL CAPS,MAKE IT SEEM LIKE IT'S PACKED FULL OF ACTION.but i won't because it pisses alot of people off.       i think emo's cool.the thick framed glasses,the black hair,the kick-ass music,well it's not really kick-ass,but you know what i mean.and if you don't,then just guess what you think i mean.sigh,it's 11:35pm right now.today's been a  very long day.i feel extreamly hung over,because i am.i went to a party last night,there where so many people there.most where already smashed by the time i got there.the party was b.y.o.b.,but i couldn't get any to bring,so i just took a half emepty bottle from someone passed out on the couch.then later that night,i come home totally wasted,and i have to get past my parents,without them realizing that im drunk.don't worry i didn't drive drunk,im not old enough to.and somehow i get past my parents,and into bed without falling over.tonight me and my friends accidently started a fire at my church.but we didn't get caught though.and nobody got hurt.the building didn't catch on fire,only a bush.i don't like the way this turned out.this is really crappy materal,but im going to post it anyway.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>