<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I pray you'll be our eyes And watch us where we go And help us to be wise In times when we don't know  Let this be our prayer As we go our way Lead us to a place Guide us with your Grace To a place where we'll be safe  La luce che to dai I pray we'll find your light Nel cuore restero And hold it in our hearts A ricordarchi che When stars go out each night L'eterna stella sei Nella mia preghiera Let this be our prayer Quanta fede c'e When shadows fill our day Lead us to a place Guide us with your grace  Give us faith so we'll be safe.   Sognamo un mondo senza piu violenza  Un mondo di giustizia e di speranza Ognuno dia la mano al suo vicino Simbolo di pace e di fraternita  La forza che ci dai We ask that life be kind E'il desiderio che And watch us from above Ognuno trovi amore We hope each soul will find Intorno e dentro a se Another soul to love  Let this be our prayer Let this be our prayer Just like every child Just like every child  Needs to find a place, Guide us with your grace Give us faith so we'll be safe E la fede che Hai acceso in noi Sento che ci salvera    i Fell in luv with this song, since the first time i heard it... 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you ever wondered if you touched my soul, yes you do. Since I met you I'm not the same. You bring life to everything I do. Just the way you say hello. With one touch I can't let go. Never thought I'd fall in love with you.  Because of you. My life has changed. Thank you for the love and the joy you bring. Because of you I feel no shame. I'll tell the world it's because of you.  Sometimes I feel lonely and all I gotta do is think of you. You captured something inside of me. You make all of my dreams come true. It's not enough that you love me for me. You reached inside and touched me internally. I love you best explains how I feel for you.  The magic in your eyes, true love I can't deny. When you hold me I just loose control. I want you to know that I'm never letting go. You mean so much to me, I want the world to see it's because of you     This song dedicated 4 my beloved one.. ARISTON HERWINDO     
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seneng banget semalem.. banyak ngobrol n curhat ama yayangku :) sekarang yg ada jadi berbunga2 deh rasanya.. pengen bareng terus sama dia.. i hope u're the last in my life..   Love u so much cintah :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not a perfect person As many things I wish I didn't do But I continue learning I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you  I'm sorry that I hurt you It's something I must live with everyday And all the pain I put you through I wish that I could take it all away And be the one who catches all your tears Thats why i need you to hear  I've found a resaon for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is You [x4]  I'm not a perfect person I never meant to do those things to you And so I have to say before I go That I just want you to know  I've found a reason for me To change who I used to be A reason to start over new and the reason is you  I've found a reason to show A side of me you didn't know A reason for all that I do And the reason is you     Gak tau kenapa, tiba2 lagi suka ajah ama lagu ini.. mungkin karena liriknya simple :)    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hhmmm.. ceritanya seh pengen mulai bikin blog.. :)
     

    
</post>


</Blog>