<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As the sun begins to rise, an alarm goes off in the Bruschwit home. Felix arises next to his wife Caroline and he passionately kisses her good morning. As he goes into the bathroom, Caroline goes to the kitchen to make coffee. The telephone rings. It appears another mysterious disappearence has occurred, one of their family members was abducted. Felix is furious and demands to speak with “Lolini”.  Meanwhile, Ioli is sitting in front of her computer researching something suspicious. Richard then storms him demanding food from Ioli. Ioli explains she is busy on cracking down on the Giddeon family for destroying her by spilling the details of her past. Richard then says he knows a perfect way to do so, and half of it has already been done. Ioli stares in suspense, asking Richard, “What exactly have you done?”  In the Giddeon home, there is a knock at Jacquelines door. As she throws a towel on she goes to answer it. To her surprise it’s Ernesto at the door. She asks, what the hell he wants, and he says he isn’t leaving without Daniel, her son. She protests that she is going to call the police and charge him for trespassing and harassment. Ernesto then slaps Jacqueline and tells her never to speak to him that way again. He threatens to tell the town of Helena what a slut she was in the past, and that her and him had an affair. She then dwells on Ernesto’s plan and thinks how bad she would be looked at by the town, she would have no choice but to leave. After discussing some business with Ernesto she decides to pack her things and get herself and Daniel out of Helena for good.   Back at the Lolini residence, Richard explains how Tasha had been taken hostage by Griswell, and that Griswell isn’t letting her go until they get the ranson from Felix and Caroline. Ioli asks how this will help her get back at Jacqueline, and Richard assures her that with the ransom money that Griswell will get from Felix, can, and will be used against Jacqueline, and she will have no choice but to flee Helena, leaving Daniel behind with Ernesto to raise. Ioli’s face lights up with delight; and she now realizes that the demon child perhaps can do the entire family good.   Caroline makes a call to the Fitzpatrick residence, but there is no answer. She then recalls how they had gone on a vacation to Europe, and how they won’t be back for another week. Felix assures her it’s alright and that he will make sure their daughter is found. He tells Caroline to call Samuel, and that he would deal with Taylor to see if he may have any answers.  Griswell is driving his car and there are screams coming from the back seat. Tasha is in the backseat attempting to scream but she has her mouth taped shut, and she is blindfolded. Griswell assures her he will not kill her, yet anyway. He tells her how he needs this money and that if he doesn’t get it that the demon child will overtake Helena, and that what he is doing is best. Tasha manages to untangle her tied up hands and reaches for her cell phone to call 911. Griswell then slams on his breaks and asks her “What the hell do you think you’re doing?”  Next Episode Spoilers:  Tasha manages to dial 911.  Felix walks in on Taylor as high as can be, and lashes out at his son and nearly hits him. Taylor admits he may know where Tasha is….  We see the demon child, and find out Jacqueline has no clue…  As Jacqueline prepares to pack… Ernesto is secretly watching her every move through a hidden camera he had implanted on her shirt…
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So here it is. I was bored one night and I decided to begin to write a never ending story with a tint of a soap opera storyline to it. I then decided I could create another blog (aside from my  urlLink ACTUAL blog ) So I made one and decided to share my story with the world. I guess I will update it when I feel the need too.  In the mean time.. meet the families of Helena, Oregon, USA. (Fictional town I suppose)   Fitzpatrick's:    Andrew Fitzpatrick 37 Year Old Male Automotive Technician  Gloria Fitzpatrick 35 Year Old Female Radiation Therapist   Neopolano's:   David Neopolano 42 Year Old Male Police Officer  Jennifer Neopolano 39 Year Old Female Head Doctor; Helena Hospital  Hailey Neopolano 19 Year Old Female Underground Drug Dealer   Giddeon's:   Jacqueline Giddeon 29 Year Old Female Single Mother  Daniel Giddeon 11 Year Old Male Possessed Child   Bruschwit's:   Felix Bruschwit 41 Year Old Male GP (MD), Bruschwit Clinic  Caroline Bruschwit 40 Year Old Female Receptionist, Bruschwit Clinic  Taylor Bruschwit 21 Year Old Male Student; Drug Abuser  Tasha Bruschwit 17 Year Old Female Student; Liar/Manipulator  Samuel Bruschwit 24 Year Old Male Medical Student; Vulnerable, Weak.   Davis':   Sara Davis 26 Year Old Female Stripper; Manipulator/Kniving “Bitch”  Gina Davis 33 Year Old Female Waitress, Single Mom, Romantic/Warm Hearted  Evan Davis 29 Year Old Male Gang Member, Violent/Drinker  Graham Davis 25 Year Old Male Student; Drug Abuser   Lolini's: “Villain Family”   Ernesto Lolini 56 Year Old Male Head Of “Helena Devils”  Richard Lolini 24 Year Old Male Gang Member, Liar/Cheater  Griswell Lolini 30 Year Old Male The “Good” One, Bad Past  Ioli Lolini 52 Year Old Female Secret Underground Gang Member, Liar/Cheater/Manipulator.
     
    
</post>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everyone, few words before work...   I had to mow the lawn today, and I am so relieved because my yard is pretty big and cutting it is a hassle at times. It was so hot out too, I was sweating like mad. That's okay though, when I finished I had a nice cool shower. It felt good.  Tomorrow is Canada Day and this town goes smoke-free as well. Now we have "designated" smoking areas and we can't smoke anywhere near/in a place of business. It's a joke in my opinion, but whatever. Laws are laws, and I guess the majority voted this one in.   Work should be okay tonight I guess, we weren't too busy last night. I am hoping it drops a bit more today. Too many people calling, they have no life. Haha.  It seems like another storm is coming in, the TV is cutting out and I can hear thunder in the distance. Shit, I have to catch the bus to work today too. I better not get rained on!   I am in the whole natural mood of things right now, so here's another poem I wrote:   As dusk is descending, the stars entrail in the night, The sky is pleasant pink, meaning sailors delight, The breeze is so passive, and gracious in it's advance, The trees seem to whisper, and move slowly at glance, The lucidity of the ending light, is mindful at heart, Today is now ending, and a new day will soon start, As the sun sets in the west, the moon is now distinct, The night and day for just a moment, are conspicuously linked, I look into the night, and observe the dark sky, Which persuades me to say, "To this day, good bye"  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  Words of inspiration: Accept life for what it is. I will post later.   .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Bye everyone.
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Miss me?   It just started to pour outside, and it got really dark. It then started to thunder, and lightning lit up the sky. Welcome to the late evening in my world.  Hello everybody. As you can tell from my "ever so suspenseful" introduction to today's post, its storming like mad out there. I am kind of excited too. I love storms. I am the kind of person that will stand outside in the pouring rain until the lightning is very close, then I run inside like a baby because I would prefer to live. I am in the mood to ramble so heres another poetic word from myself:    A passionate kiss, and a gleeful smile, The relationship is there, but in turn is so vile, Acceptance is virtue, but rather profound, The existence is there, so clear and so loud, To ponder the meaning, and distinguish its truth, Can complicate matters, and become quite uncouth, The constriction of thoughts, and feelings both alike, Bring chaos and tribulation, to that of the psyche, With emotions and concepts, coming from the heart of a child, I looked into your eyes; and in turn,  you smiled.    © 2004 Tyler Kuhk   I am beginning to love my interest in poetry. I am noticing more and more how I can type from the heart and at the same time explain my thoughts in some sort of a "fictional" way. I can honestly say though, I have been inspired by so many people in that of what I do. Michelle Nicol (who's like my big sister) is my judge when it comes to a new piece I write, I always have to check with her before posting it :) I love you for your inspiration Michelle.  The posts I noticed are getting more less about my days, and more about my contemplations. This could probably be a good thing because there's actually something decent (I think anyway) to read rather than to read about my daily adventures in Thunder Bay (Ya, right).  Anywho, I am out for the night. I downloaded some more movies to watch (:O Illegality :P) so I suppose I should go and watch them. Leave me some comments to let me know you were here :)  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Bye for now everyone. See you all later.
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       And once again, I speak...   I recently downloaded "The Passion Of The Christ" and I just finished watching it with my cousin. All I can is "Wow". That movie was phenomenal. I was totally into the entire thing. The way it was portrayed was absolutely amazing. I think it showed a more realistic approach to what Jesus really did go through. Even so, I don't understand the whole controversial point to it. It didn't seem to show any indication that Jews were responsible for his death. It simply showed the facts. I was extremely impressed with the camera angles and filming as well. It all looked so real. To summarize, it was  very well done.   This is the twentieth post I have published in less than a week. I have hit over 5 500 words too, I guess it shows, eh? I love it though. I have gotten so many things off of my chest and it feels good. It also feels good to know that people read it and leave me comments. It's also inspired me to write from my head, and not to worry about any ridicule. I can say anything I want, and it can only indirectly effect anyone. In other words, this is a way to get a point across without offending anything or anyone.  I have been in and out of reflective moods recently. I go from thinking about one thing, to completely forgetting about it and doing something else. I don't know whether or not it's on my part, in being that I am suffering from lack of concentration, or if I am just trying to shut thoughts out of my mind. Either way, I will never be able to shut anything out of my mind. I think so much sometimes, I keep myself up at night.    Seemingly complex, yet exceedingly intriguing thoughts unfold, but I find myself yielding, whether or not to make sense of the situation,  perhaps it's a figment of my vivid imagination  One thing is for certain, I can feel it is true, it's like my sanctuary at heart, with exceptions make do, a deep piece of intellect, waiving my faith, it's like the sun and the moon, so slow and so paced,  With windows and doors, and long hallways and lights, I feel as if I am dreaming, and perhaps I am right To be known, to be seen, is something so true, but at times the perception, is difficult to undo  A fight and a battle, makes nothing but war, only I am able to understand, my concepts galore, To see and to fathom, are two different things, but one thing's for sure, my mind will always keep, wandering.  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  And yet another poetic ramble of my own. Must indicate I am in a reflective state. Poetry is so complex, I can state whatever I want, and it just comes out fluently. That's what I love about it. Anyways, hope you guys enjoyed today's post.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Talk to you all later. Leave me a comment so I know you were here :) 
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       A word from an insomniac...   Wow, whoever hasn't seen Chronicles Of Riddick yet, get your ass to the theatre and see it. The entire two hours of the movie rocked my world. And no, not in a sexual way. A couple of the women in the movie we very good looking though, but that's mandatory I guess, "sex" sells.  So as I sit here, listening to Crystal Method, I realize the bordum that is present in my state of mind. Nothing to think, nothing to do, and I am not even hungry so food will not cure this dormant state of mind.   That's okay though, I guess it can't be that dormant if I am sitting here typing. The mind; the most complex, part of the body. It amazes me.  And hence the boredness, here's another piece of work I just rambled off:   I feel a meaningless sense, tapping on my shoulder, A breath of success, filling my lungs, A thought of immorality, bringing sickness to my stomach, A face of happiness, as my eyes meet yours.  An impact of glorification, held high in my thoughts, The sublimity of the light, that meets between us, I feel like I love you, but my feelings are distorted,  A blurred vision leaps into action, and encompasses my true sight, Could this feeling be nothing but a mere fabrication? All I can ask is for you to hold me tight, and never let me go, For if you do, the correlation between us, can become nothing, but a mere mockery of imagination.   © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  Basically the whole sex talk going on with friends lately has lead up to this. Don't jump start anything, because it could end up biting you in the ass later. I've seen it happen.  Well, I guess I have said my piece for the day. Even though it's now Monday. I don't want to work today, it's so nice being off :).  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Bye everyone.
      
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hello again...   I guess this is the first time I am posting my first post in the evening! I'm usually right into the game when I wake up, I guess that wasn't the case today. I was so tired, I slept till about 1:30 PM. I was up until 5 AM talking to  urlLink "Paco"  on MSN. I realized how much I want to visit New Zealand, seems like such a deadly place to visit. Taeghan, your a cool guy. :)  Tonight, the plans are to go see Chronicles Of Riddick at around 11. It should be good, I've heard its a good movie and Vin Diesel is a good actor, so I should enjoy it.   Last night we all went for coffee, and met some of Andrea's friends there. Andrea was saying the dumbest things, so all we could do was laugh at her and make fun of her blondness. Haha, but we all love Andrea. We got back to my place around 1:30 AM and watched 50 First Dates. The movie was awesome, Adam Sandler played his funny, yet serious role very well. I was impressed. And as for Drew Barrymore, she rocks in every movie she makes. She's one of my favourite actresses. And she's so beautiful.  Today is my day off, it was really nice not having to be at work today. I have some day shifts this week to work so it will be nice to rake in some cash.   Only 3 days until Canada Day! And I work, but only until 8! So I still have time to go all out, find a party, and get drunk. I am so pumped. I'm going to be wearing all Canada stuff. It's going to be great.  I will be updating the site shortly, I have some stuff to put up and change. So check it out in the next few days. I think I am going to get off of here and continue getting ready now.   .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Take it easy guys. I will post later.
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       And The Canadian Is Back In Business...   Hey everyone. I worked all day today, so nothing too interesting happened. Work was slow, so on my lunch break I went over to the mini mall and bought  Bad Company - Jack Higgins , it's all about Hitler and the war. I read about 60 pages of it at work today so I am right into it. I love historical, war-like books. However, when it comes to reading, nothing beats Stephen King, he is my ultimate favourite writer.  Only four days until Canada Day! I'm so pumped, I love being Canadian and I am so proud to live in a country as good as Canada. I hope to go all out this year too. Canadian shirt, canadian boxers, canadian socks, canadian shorts. Trust me, I'll do it. Even if it requires a bit of shopping :)  I laughed today, I got home and checked my messages on IRC. I guess some guy had accessed my site or journal, and he leaves me a message saying  "Do you consider yourself creative and imaginative?"  Like, what the fuck is that? I suppose my thoughts don't render into his mind to well, typical "simple" minded person. It's sad when you see simple minded people trying to compensate. They try so hard to seem intelligent and witted, that it's even more of a joke to begin with. I guess it's somewhat hypocritical of me to be bashing others; but face it; they chose to have a close minded approach to everything and everyone in their lives. If they like that attitude, then so be it. Don't bring it around me.  If people could only understand half of what reality is. It's indeed frustrating having to listen and see all the bullshit that happens. But what can I do? Run a course called  "Mind Training For The Simple Minded" ? Give me a break. I guess it just comes naturally.  I wonder what  honestly  possesses a person to get a rise out of putting other people down. It doesn't make sense to me. For one day I would seriously like to be able to think like some of the idiots in this world, perhaps it could explain their foolishness, llogicality, arrogance and instability.   People that have to impress others are nothing but unstable, mindless individuals.  Anyways, I didn't intend for this whole spiel to be typed all out, but I guess it's too late to go and think of something else to type out.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Leave a comment if you wish. And no idiots please. Constructive criticism; not impracticality. If its idiotic, I'll delete the damn thing anyhow. :) 
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everyone...   I got back from Berries at about 1 AM. We had a blast there tonight, so many stupid jokes and what not to laugh at. I had a chicken quesadilla, and I split it with Alley (It was so damn good) I met Alley's sister today, and her 6 week year old baby. Shit, it was the most adorable thing I have ever seen in my life. So beautiful, and innocent. Just think, at one time in our lives we were like that, then we grew up.   It was amazing holding her as well. To possess such innocence and in turn to be holding that piece of innocence is the most amazing feeling in the world. I suppose that's why its so moving when you hold your very own child. I wouldn't know but I have heard.  I work tomorrow from 12 - 6, which isn't all that bad I guess. I really need to drink though. I want some beer in this dealcoholized gut of mine. It's summer time, I gotta get out and have a damn good time! And I need to endure it for 2 months; PARTY TIME!  Work was alright I guess tonight. They had me strictly on the supervisor line so again it was a bit slower. But I had some nasty ass people to deal with. One guy called me a  "worthless piece of shit that should drop dead"  I really enjoy being verbally abused by customers over the phone. (That was sarastic by the way) I guess it's better over the phone though, if it weren't I'd come home with bruises everyday, or even worse, never come home.  Ah well, people are dickheads. I am getting tired so I will head to bed.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   I've written so much stuff on here, it's crazy. Goodnight all. 
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well, I am more awake now...   I am heading to catch the bus to work in about half an hour, I am working 4 - 8 PM tonight, as usual. So you guys can give me a holler on my cell and I will call you back. Anyone wishing to goto Berries tonight, call me :)  Right now I am listening to  My Beat - Blaze  it's an awesome song. Last night I got bored so I went thru all my old CD's and stuff. Brings back memories of way back in the day.    *Sigh*  so innocent those days. Whatever caused human innocence to dissipate? And don't give me the Adam & Eve story. We were all innocent as babies, then we grew up. I think humankind knows too much for their own good. And we all use it to our advantage. So much selfishness, greed, and hatred. It's sickening. I dread reading the news everyday; it's pretty bad our world is in the state it's in. There is no such thing as respect anymore. The world is so corrupt I don't even think respect has its own definition anymore. People are miseralble, depressed, and selfish. The world relies mostly on "looking out for number one". That's not the way it should be.  Society, in my perspective, is nothing but a mere experiment. And I think we've disproved it's hypothesis.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   I should get going to work. Bye all.
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Welcome to Friday...   So yeah, I predicted myself I would get up  after  noon, and I did. Crawled out at exactly 12:38 PM. Pretty refreshing sleep if you ask me. I am still half dead, but its all good. Helps me not to care about anything that much :).  I wonder if I will ever have the chance to go somewhere, where I won't have to worry about  ANYTHING.  It would be cool to have a feeling like that. Because everywhere I am theres something to worry about, or to dread. For example, I have to work today (LOL).  Tonight is a hopefully a coffee night. But I wouldn't be surprised if it got moved until tomorrow or something. I'll find a back up plan if that doesn't work. It's summer, plenty of time for coffee, friends, beer :) Mmmm. Beer.  This morning is kind of weird. Err, afternoon. I have nothing much to write about. Weird because I always got shit to vent about. But it's probably the fact that I am half asleep still. I am surprised I'm not typing jibberish.   I should go catch Days though, it's on at 1 PM, and it's now already 12:54 PM.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Later, I will post something worth it later :)  
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I swear I suffer from insomnia...   HONESTLY! I can't ever sleep anymore. I guess it's because it's summer holidays now, thank fucking God. I get two whole months off. I fucking deserve it too. I worked my ass off this year. One more year to go, *sigh*  I just finished what I hope to be my last cigarette before I goto sleep. They usually relax me and allow me to close my eyes in peace :)  My fucking website is down right now. Stupid server shit. I can hardly wait until I move so I can set my server up on my other computer I don't use. Then we won't have to worry about these "minor setbacks" will we?  I promised Dicaz I'd mention her in one of my posts. So I am. We need to get drunk man. I could go for some nice cold beer this weekend. I need to get smashed; it's been awhile. More or less since Liisa's going away party. We got smashed and sang karaoke. It was massive fun.  It's pouring rain and I can hear the taps of the water on the basement windows. It's so relaxing. I just hope it doesn't rain all day because I have to take the city bus to work today. :( Dirty ass bus.  By the end of the summer I'll have my car :) Until then it's bus for me.   Well thought I'd make a quick post before I head to sleep for the rest of the morning. Maybe I'll be up before noon again tomorrow, eh? I doubt that :P  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Good night, morning, afternoon or whatever to you all :)
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I just rambled this out of boredness...    Misery is the world, and the world is misery,  Sin is human, and human is sin,  Perfect is a dream, and a dream is perfect  Contradictions exist within reality, and reality exists within contradictions,  Seeing is believing, and believing is seeing.  Knowledge is power, but  without power it's dormant.  Life lessons are from experience, but life is its own.  Learning from life,  bestows us with knowledge  Using knowledge proves your beliefs, and your beliefs are then seen.  To see is to observe, and observation causes discrepancy  Consistency excludes uniqueness and, in turn eliminates life.  Life is sin.  Sin is misery.  Sinful Misery.  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  I guess I brought my own meaning to my nickname. That was a moving experience. Wow.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Later.
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       And it's me once again...   So we ended up not going for coffee tonight, too hectic as my friend is moving out so she went to clean some shit out of the room she's moving into. I guess it's all good, I don't really want to go anywhere tonight anyway. I am in one of those,  keep to myself  moods. I never get much of those because I am so outgoing, but it's nice to have a break from all the wildness.  My day went good today. The hospital visit went awesome, it was good to see everyone I worked with this past semester. I am currently working on a schedule to volunteer there with some kids. I loved the placement so it'll be no sweat getting my community hours in order to graduate :)  Work also went well today, was fairly busy until around 6:30, when the call volume dropped considerably. So I sat around talking to some buddies at work, all "computer" talk. I swear, this guy I work with is so smart with computers, he makes me seem like an idiot. He's so talented at his web design and what not. He also designs computer games so I agreed to be a beta tester for one of his games. I am looking forward to doing that :)  I am still pondering whether or not I still like my ex-girlfriend. It seems like the connection is still there between us, but I am not sure, and I am not jumping to any conclusions because I don't want any hurt done. I would prefer to get to know her better once again. I don't know whether or not I will be able to commit to it though. I love the whole relationship thing, but I want to figure out if I want  this  relationship or if I want to seek out someone else.  Life can be so confusing at times. I try to be optimistic about it, however. I guess it's like a test though, and a challenging one I might add. I am just thankful that my life has turned out as good as it has. (As I see it) I feel for so many people in this world, and it's sad. I feel almost selfish at times because I have it so good, living in Canada and what not. There are people out there without a roof, without rights, and it's not right at all. I then shift to my perspective  "Everything happens for a reason"  and the whole  fate  ordeal. All of the shit that goes on this world must happen for a reason, life is a test. A test of how well you cope with certain things, and how you act in certain situations.  Fuck, I vent a lot, eh? I swear this journal is an asset to me. Even if I had nobody read it, I would still feel better deep down because I got my thoughts out. I am so intellectual now, unlike my previous self. I am done with the normal teenage attitude on things. I can't help it anyway; if I feel more mature than I used to,  then all the power to me.   I love the outlook I have anyway. I just wish others could see life from my perspective. I suppose it's neither positive, nor negative. It's just a perspective. Neutral. Mediocre. The way it should be.  Well that's my piece for now.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Talk to you all later.
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everybody!   Got to bed last night about 4, couldn't fall asleep any fucking earlier. I guess it was alright though, I watched two episodes of Elimidate, that show is awesome. Brings out the worst in some of those girls I suppose though. I feel for some of those guys on there, all they do is fight with each other trying to prove how  "good"  they are. Give me a break. Relationships are more than that. But whatever, it's entertainment right?  I actually woke up before noon today. I am surprised at that, but I knew I had too. I am heading to the hospital for around 1:30, then I will stay there until around 3:00, then head to work for the evening.   Tonight's a coffee night, as well as tomorrow I think (I'm a coffee whore, LOL). So I will be at Berries tonight. I am enjoying the last little bit of time where we are able to smoke within a business. July 1st is when that stupid no smoking by-law goes into effect. It's fucking stupid, you can't even smoke on the property of your workplace, or better yet ANY place of business you goto. It's bullshit in my opinion, us smokers have no fucking rights! We all know it's bad but let it be our choice, and whoever runs a business (Like a bar, or restaurant) shouldn't have to run it smoke-free if they don't want too. I just find it so ironic and hypocritical to encourage drinking in a bar, which could cause so much trouble - Like getting in a car drunk and killing someone, or drinking too much and getting alcohol poisoning - but we'll make you stand OUTSIDE for one measly cigarette.  Ah well, it's bullshit but theres nothing anyone can do. Besides this stupid by-law we have that federal election coming up soon (I'm too young to vote yet though) which is a huge joke. This country is going to go for a shit and I can see it clearly.  Stupid Politics.   .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Later guys, I'll post sometime tonight.
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Good evening, or morning, or whatever...   Wow, just as we were going to watch Mystic River my buddy Steve got called home to babysit his little cousins last minute. He just had to take the movie with him too. I'm making a big deal out of this, but  seriously , I want to see that damn movie! Everytime I seem to have a chance to watch it, fate stands in my way. (Bit of exaggeration, LOL)  We compromised anyway. Andy, Robyn & I watched Mrs. Doubtfire and ordered pizza. The only drawback was that it was Pizza Hut, which isn't  ALL  that bad, I suppose, but they were the only ones in town with the portable debit machine. I am the kind of person who never has cash on them, and if I do, it's maybe a twenty dollar bill.  Funniest thing, I ordered a 2 litre of Pepsi as well, and when the pizza guy handed it to me, it was all wet and it flew out of my hands, fell down my front stairs, rolled down the sidewalk, and barely reached the road. I felt like a complete idiot. But fuck, dry the damn bottles (Haha!)  I have a fairly long day ahead of me, I am actually going to goto bed at a decent hour tonight. I am going to pop into the hospital tomorrow and visit with some people and do a bit of volunteering, as it was my co-op placement during second semester. I loved working with the children, gave me a lot of insight on being a paediatrician.  This stupid insurance telemarketing scam keeps calling my cell phone (how they got my number I have no idea). I have been dealing with it for nearly 6 months now and everytime they call I tell them to put me on their "Do Not Call" list, but that never works. Anyways I was out for a smoke with some friends at work and my phone started to ring and it was a BC number (604-550-7000). I answer and it turns out to be some British guy. He was really rude too, kept trying to probe my name and what not. He kept mis-pronouncing it as well. I got really snarky back to him and told him to quit fucking calling my cell phone as his company wastes my daytime minutes. After flipping on him for a bit he asks me if I am on any sort of medications (because of my attitude towards him). I then replied  "Yeah buddy, I'm fucking stoned on drugs"  and he says  "Yeah I figured so".  Fucking moron, nice interpersonal skills there. No wonder you waste your time calling me everyday. Everyone got a laugh out of that one including myself.  I think I need a cigarette... *lights one up . I should really stop. It's so hypocritical of me to even consider a career in medicine if I smoke. I do plan to quit before I graduate next year. My dad went on Zyban and was successful, I plan to try that.  Well it's late I should get going.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site    *Sigh* Life is so philosophical. 
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Bahh, posting it up again   Steve showed up with Mystic River tonight! He's making up for ditching me for his woman, LOL. So we're waiting for a few others to show up so we can watch it. I am pumped to see this movie :)  Work was deadly tonight, they put me strictly on the supervisor line so I got next to no calls. It rocked. About time I get a break from 50 people waiting to get thru over the phones. I got a bunch of good calls tonight though, some extremely irate consumers that were sick of speaking with the normal representatives. Such adament bastards. I swear some people are so selfish and don't have the morality to give anybody a break.  Anywho, I will post later. Movie, and food time.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Keep it real guys! Make sure to  urlLink visit my site! 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Change of plans tonight...   If any of my buddies happen to be reading this, Sodzy is bringing Mystic River over tonight. If you wanna come chill then give me a holler on my cell. I am working 4 PM - 8 PM, but I will return the call (Caller ID :P)  Anyways I am off to work.   .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Talk to you all later!
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       *Yawn*, Hey All   I am a lazy shit, 12:17 PM and I crawl out of the sack. I love not having to dedicate myself to anything right now. Except for that fact that I work at 4 PM Monday to Friday. But I am not that lazy. I am still half dead, sitting here smoking a cigarette. I should probably go grab a coffee.  Mmmm, caffeine!   Work has been so damn busy these last few days. For those who know nothing of my part-time job, I am a customer service rep (supervisor) in a call centre. I am one of those "supervisors" that people talk to on those 1-800 numbers. I work for the T-Mobile Rebate Centre. The job is fairly good, pays good, but fuck, the customers I have to deal with over the phone are horrid at times. Customer service is an extremely stressful field of work. It's fun at times though.  I am probably going to go for coffee tonight with some people from work if everything works out as planned.   Tomorrow I am heading to the hospital where I did my co-op placement for last semester. Even though school is done I still want to pop in and volunteer every once in awhile. It's in the paediatric ward in our new hospital. It was an awesome co-op, I had a lot of fun, and gained a lot of insight in a career of medicine. Co-op is an awesome class to take.  I should probably go get some decent clothes on. I am suppose to head to my new house to help out, but I work at 4 so it may not be so feasible.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   I'll write later. Bye guys!
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       2:00 AM, Still Up & Running   My cousin is staying overnight so we're still up and chatting. I was bored and decaffeinated so we took a stroll down the block to Robin's Donuts so I could grab a coffee. I was generous enough to by my cousin some juice and a muffin. There's my good deed for the day. Even though it was like $2.50, it  is  the thought that counts!  Sodzy never showed tonight. I suppose his woman is more important then me. Which is fine. No Mystic River to watch tonight. I guess I will have to rent the DVD sometime this week since I have been wanting to see it for some time.  Well, just a quick late night update on my life. Feel free to leave comments regarding the posts; I'd love to hear your thoughts or feedback.   .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   I wanted you all to see this messed up picture. Makes me wonder what the hell people are on. The picture is too big for the page so  urlLink click here  to see it. I am assuming someone was on an acid trip?  Night. 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Phew is all I can say...   It took me like an hour to get rid of this god damn trojan I had in this computer! I tried all these programs to get rid of it and none of them worked. I ended up finding a forum post about it that helped. I had to close the damn thing down because it was running in my processes menu, so with that done I used my AVG and it deleted the damn thing. Now I can finally get back onto DALnet on IRC!  I decided not to go out and do anything interesting tonight. I just have people over so, the "chill session" can get underway I suppose. Sodzy is suppose to bring Mystic River, but whenever he decides to get his ass back to Westfort from Current River, we are watching nothing but television. (I have no movies I want to watch)  Mmm, the sweet sound of Crystal Method. I have had their music on for about 2 hours now. Such awesome tunes, electronica music truly rocks. Whenever I have extreme techno stuff like that on it stimulates my thinking mode. I feel so eccentric and curious right now. I never understood why the hell it makes me feel so  "thoughtful" , but it does.  I realized today how much I have changed over the past few years. I used to think so cynically, when I honestly never really had a reason too. Besides my parents divorcing back in 1999, I had everything a normal pre-teen would have. Maybe it was the whole  hormonal  thing that was going on. Chemical inbalances and what not. I used to feel so bitter inside, and I didn't necessarily show it on the outside. It came out in huge rage modes though, and I remember those so clearly.  Essentially, however, I have opened my eyes and realized a lot of things about life. I know I am 17, but my perspective differs from so many my age. In a way it's kind of good, I feel a uniqueness to myself - but in a way it's frustrating. I am unable to express a lot of my thoughts & feelings to others, simply because:                     a)  They don't understand                    b)  They don't  WANT TO  understand  That I guess I can,  or better yet , have to deal with. I guess I can handle that though, because sooner or later they'll grow up too, hopefully. I wonder about a lot of people I know, even some good friends of mine. I guess it depends on what they want to learn from life, and I do believe at some point in everyone's lives, we  DO  want to get  something  from life.  Life is such a beautiful thing, if it is looked at in perspective. So many wonderful things happen, and will happen in life. Most people think so negatively about life. But, life is much more than bad things, people tend to dwell on them however, which you can't blame anyone for; it's human nature. It is however, possible, to break that habit and focus on positive things in life. In order to do that however you must want to be more optimistic. :)  Is it worth the stress and pain to worry about something bad?  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Later guys.
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Ha, I am back, miss me?   I just want to express how much I  enjoy  that new Janet Jackson video I saw on MuchMoreMusic last night, All Night (Don't Stop). Wow, what a video. She's got a damn nice body :)  I've been in the retro music mood recently, as I am typing I am listening to  Come Back To Me - Janet Jackson  from the early 90's. But that is nothing, I have been downloading all the old Michael Jackson stuff from the 80's and even some Pink Floyd. Music like that makes me realize how shitty the new generation of music is. In a recent FHM magazine I purchased, one of the writers asked Slipknot  "What's wrong with rock?"  Slipknot came back good with the fact that  "Hilary Duff sells 7 million albums - which must be the first clue that aliens are on their way to earth to blow us up."  Amen to that. Even though I don't listen to Slipknot, that's a damn good point. What the hell is with the horrid music that's coming out nowadays.  *Sigh* Whatever.   It's not just the music in this world that is bad. The whole place is corrupt. People are so messed up nowadays, nobody has any respect for anything. What really bothers me is the lack of  SELF  respect there is. That shows how bad this world is getting. I don't have any faith it will get any better. Who's to say though?  I just caught Days, it was semi-good, I suppose. I think Jenn is being extremely mindless in that getting on a plane to see Jack. Even though he isn't "dead". I have so many theories on this so called "twist" they are pulling, but I am honestly baffled at them all. I can just hardly wait until the entire thing is played out. I am getting sick of waiting.   This post was somewhat long, eh? I wanted to quickly type a few things but as you can see I got all into it and babbled about a lot. That's okay though, that's the point of having this thing. My place to vent.   My mom just walked in with groceries  *Drool*, food!  I am going to get going. I am bored today so understand my typing needs :) Bye all!  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well, good morning / afternoon   It's good to know I did get to sleep after my night of insomnia. Haha. It was a good, comfortable 6 hour sleep as well. I could go for another :P.   I changed the layout of the journal, as I personally thought the other one was a little too dark, this one is easier to read and a bit more "user" friendly.   I dreamt last night about that movie, A Day After Tomorrow. But that it actually happened in the world. It was a crazy dream, Thunder Bay had these fierce thunder storms and tornadoes during the WINTER. So it was cold, windy and really stormy. Fucked eh?  I work tonight at 4:00 PM, until 8:00 PM, like usual. I hope it's not busy tonight, thats all it has been recently. Calls after calls and the majority of them are about the same damn thing. You might as well ALL call at the same time and I'll fix everything for you. Ah, the customer service field - always fucking surprises me.  Well, thought I'd post some shit before I go and get ready and what not for the rest of the day. I will talk to you all later.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site    Our greatest battles are that with our own minds. - Jameson Frank 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everyone!   I have decided to discontinue the whole journal thing hosted directly from my site. It is rather complex and boring to have to type all that stuff out on it's own page everyday. This way all I need to do is log in and type up today's summary. Ah, life can be so simple at times. It's almost 5:00 AM, and I am so awake it's sick. I broke my damn chair in my room so I had to drag it out in two pieces, which was wonderful. I had a hell of a time getting the leather recliner in here to replace it; but it was worth it. It is ever so comfy sitting in here now!  So if you are just "surfing" into the journal, you should check out my actual website which can give you more insight as to who I am and what not.  urlLink Check It Out!   Well, a quarter of this new day has past. I need to get to sleep. But I can't at the moment, so I'll just rant for a bit. Sound good?   I just finished a cigarette, perhaps that will calm my nerves down and help me to sleep, in a bit that is.   Work was busy as hell tonight, we had so many people waiting to get thru the lines, and all it was were people bitching all damn night. I wanted to kill half of them. But whatever, I am paid to listen to it, so I suppose it's "all good".  I am looking forward to my holidays that start July 14th. I get a whole 2 weeks off while we move houses. It will be a nice break, except for the packing part. I suck at packing, I mean, I can't even pack for a trip. It's horrible I know.   Ah well, life isn't always fair, is it?  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site    I am going to head to bed now though, I will try to sleep my awakeness off. Bye guys! 
      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Once again, hello all...   I guess I should make this post short as I have to get up early, I work a 10.5 hour shift tomorrow and I need to be energized. 10.5 hours, it's fucking long, but good money. So I think I will try to be positive. Even though my day goes to waste, but ah well :)  The smoking thing is going alright, I cut down more today. Today's cigarettes go as follows:    1) 10:25 AM    Morning Smoke    Routine  2) 10:58 AM    After Eating Smoke    Routine  3) 11:17 AM    Smoke Before Work - Filling A Craving / Lasting Until Break  4) 2:03 PM    Break Smoke    Routine  5) 4:24 PM    Break Smoke    Routine  6) 6:04 PM    Break Smoke    Routine  7) 8:08 PM    After Work Smoke / Filling The Craving  8) 8:57 PM    At Computer / Bored / Craving  9) 10:29 PM    Craving / At Computer    A tenth cigarette will probably be added to that list before I fall asleep. It all depends though, maybe I will try to cope without it :)  Ah well, besides all of that I am fairly tired and I don't have too many ideas of what to type tonight. I think I am going to call it a night. Expect some more interesting words soon to come :)  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Night All!
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey Everyone...   Today I began my journey to quit smoking :) I call it a journey because I have to journal my smoking for a week, and study the patterns of my smoking to attempt ways to cut down in certain situations. I have been prescribed Zyban, but I am not going to start it for another week or two. I want to take it nice and easy to make quitting as smooth as possible. I have come to the conclusion that I want to want to quit, and I believe that my mentality and state of mind will grant me willpower to do so. I just think positive; as in one day it'll pay off. I won't have to worry about the effects if I stop now, and I can have a more healthy and well-worth life. Smoking sucks, it kills, and it needs to stop for me.   today's journal goes as follows:   1) 10:13 AM    First Cigarette Of The Day    Routine  2) 10:54 AM    Bored - Waiting For My Ride To Work  3) 11:14 AM    Before Work Cigarette    Smoking Before I start Work Helps Me To Last Until Break  4) 1:35 PM    Break Cigarette    "Stress" Relief From Work    Routine  5) 4:01 PM    Break Cigarette    "Stress" Relief - Filling The Need To A Craving    Routine  6) 4:22 PM    After Eating Cigarette    After Eating, Food Gives Me A Craving For A Cigarette.    Helps "Wash" Down The Meal.     Routine      7) 6:03 PM    Break Cigarette    Filling The Need For A Craving  8) 8:06 PM    After Work Smoke    After A Long Day At Work, Relax, A Nice Cigarette To Calm Me    Routine  9) 8:26 PM    After Eating Smoke    Routine  10) 8:57 PM     At The Computer Cigarette     Bored, Had A Craving.  11) 11:33 PM     Sitting At Computer     Had A Craving     Did Some Work From 9-10:30   So I am down to just under half a pack. Not too bad. I really tried to limit myself today, and work aided me in that, which is rather good.   I plan to cut down a bit more each few days... I want to work myself down to about 8-10 a day, then I plan to start taking the pill which will help me decrease my cigarettes per day even more. I have it all planned out and I hope for the best :)  Other than that I went back to work today, my holidays are now over, so they have booked me right steady from now on. I will be raking in 80 hour checks though so I will be getting in the 700s every two weeks. Life is sweet :)  I hope to have some money saved for a car since I get my G2 October 25th. I have two more driving lessons then I go for my road test. I am pretty excited about that!  Moving is going smoothly, we are pretty much there. All of my stuff is mostly unpacked and what not now so I don't have too much else to do. I did have a lot accomplished these last two weeks so I feel really good I was able to do a lot and not feel so rushed.   I have to admit, I feel much more stable in my mind than I have been recently, and I am sure that the next few weeks will only get better. Positive outlooks and attitude begin to set in. I suppose I won't be writing such morbid and bashful poetry, it would be nice for a change :)  Speaking of poetry, my poem  urlLink "Assurance"  was selected for publication by Voicenets. I had entered it in at the beginning of July and heard back from them the other day. I have yet to send them my permission slip to publish it. I also ordered to book as I would like to own what my poem is being published in :) That inspired me a lot to keep writing as I have seen many poems of people I know rejected by them. I guess they enjoyed that one :)  I suppose I should get going, this post is fairly long but I need to compensate for the past few days I have slacked off in blogging :) Talk to you all later.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Good night. 
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hello everybody...   Well, it's a fact - the move is now over and everything is pretty much finished. I am now sleeping in a house with internet, cable, and all the other necessities of life.  I still have some stuff to bring over from the old house, minor things like my sister's desk, some beds, and some of my things. I need to get some of my clothing and shower accessories as well. It will be kind of hard to shower with no shampoo :P  Anyway besides all that, the past few days were alright. The funeral service on Saturday was very well done. I was impressed with the entire thing. His navy mates from the second world war were there and did a whole respect/honouring type ceremony. It was very nice.  Afterwards I was out at camp (as you can tell from my "interesting" audio post..) And that went fine, however, it did feel good to come back into town and clean myself with actual clean water. I can only camp for so many days...  Other than that, I really don't have too much to say, at this point anyway. I have been rather busy lately and times of thinking and poetry have somewhat faded. But now that everything is settling back to normal I will be back in the game :)  For now, I am going to go though, still got stuff to do.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Talk to everybody later... :)
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everybody..   It's been a few days now, I have been extremely busy with moving and everything. Everything is now painted, and 90% of our furniture has been moved, so I am stuck sleeping on the floor here because we have no cable / internet at the new house until Tuesday. I am going to sleep there tonight though, I have a bunch of movies and DVD's to watch, and that way I'll somewhat have the TV, and I will have a really good sleep too. I need it.   Yesterday I woke up at 11ish, and I went back to bed around 2pm, and slept around 7pm. I am still kind of wiped out from cutting the grass and everything. Has been a big job with painting and moving furniture and what not. Once the entire move is over though, we're all going to be so much more relieved.   So nothing too much else is going on, I have a funeral to goto on Saturday morning for Robbie's dad. His sister got in town last night so we went to visit them. It's really sad, and I feel so weird because I don't know what to say to them, other than sorry for your loss. I know that may mean a lot to them personally, but I feel there's more I could do, it's just that I don't know what. Anyways, funeral will be sad, I really don't like going to them, they are so depressing and morbid. I hope this is the only funeral I have to goto for awhile.   Until Then  The final stage, As the last bit of strength is revoked.  The final moment, As the last seconds are no more.  The final breath, As the last of the air inside you escapes.  The point of no suffering, As you slip away from the physical life.  The point of true return, As you enter a spiritual world.  A place in which suffering is non-existent,  A place in which happiness flourishes,  A place in which one day, we will all be united.  An endurance we must all face, An endurance that we may fear,  Death, by peace. Peace, by death.  We will all rest. Sooner or later.  Until then, rest, in true peace.  © Tyler Kuhk 2004  I wrote that the other night, as all I could think about was death and how we, and people close to us, are not going to be here forever, and that death is something we must endure both directly, and indirectly. And, I will admit, I am terrified of death. It's something I wish never has to happen to me, unless I know for SURE what is going to lie afterwards...  I suppose that's where faith comes in. I do believe in an afterlife, but it's the whole unknown thing that frightens me. I'm not too sure what to expect, and in life, there is so much to expect and think of, but when dying comes into thought, my mind completely goes blank and I can't think or expect anything. That's what scares me. Something I am unable to comprehend.  I guess I will have to find out one day, but for now I want to discontinue this post because death is not something I like to talk about....  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   I will post within the next few days, hopefully with something a little more happy...
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So yeah, the best word that can describe today..."fucked"   The day was going alright, Robyn and I painted the entire basement apartment which took quite a long time, since it's pretty big in there.  Anyways, it went alright, but the bad news is that my mom's boyfriends father passed away today. He was 91, and he wasn't doing too well, he's been in and out of the hospital even before I did my co-op placement.   Although we know he's in a better place now, it's going to toughen a lot of things up. The process of moving is going to be backed up I think due to funeral arrangements and what not. It happened to much at the wrong time as well, we have all been stressed and my mom and her boyfriend have been stressed and pouring money into that new house, and now this. It's like at times life really bites you in the ass. Even though I wasn't very close with his father, I have talked to him numerous times, and visited him in the hospital before I started work there during school. He was a very religious and kind man, and it's going to be hard for his family and friends to let him go, he was a very well known individual.  So the day has just turned, thinking mode sets in and I sit and feel guilty that someone just died, but yet I am walking around fully healthy doing whatever I please. I just can't believe death when it happens, I dislike it so much, and it makes me feel weird and unstable.  I don't have much else to say, I feel to weird, and wiped out to type more. I did, however, write two poems last night. Here's the one I liked the most...   Transition  Emotional distress, as it possesses my only known truth. Hurting and bleeding, in the depths of my one true self. I am not depressed, nor am I cheerful. My soul hurts, my heart burns, struggling with comprehension.  Attempting to figure out if this transition is a burden, Or if the transition is positive at this time and point. To be unable to relate with most people I know, To be ridiculed for my morals, ethics and thoughts.  I am not ashamed, nor am I completely content, My mind is in it's own state of contradiction, Confused, yet amazed that I have grown this way. Distinguishing meanings, pondering thoughts.  The fact that it must be done alone, Has to be yet a burden in itself. Relations are untrue, could this be wrong? Emotions grow sore, and trying is not worth it.  Acceptance has overcome my new self, Relating to the others is the problem. I stand for what I stand for. And its final, that's good enough for me.  © Tyler Kuhk 2004   .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   I hate these stupid mood modes. Later everyone...  
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So I return...   I really need to write something. I can't sleep and I am so frustrated and disturbed by life right now. I don't know why life had to pick today, but it did. I am emotionally instable, and I can feel it deep down.  I hate when I get like this, and it's always by something stupid and small as well. Something in particular was comments made about sex and virginity tonight. I'll admit it, with no shame, that I am a virgin. And it's not like I haven't had chances, or desire. More or less that was before, I still have desire, but I choose not to act on impulse. I have learnt too much from that previously in life. I guess I could consider myself somewhat grown up in that sense, but honestly, there is so much more to life than sex. Sex is an overrated act of pleasure that is portrayed way too much in the wrong ways. I can say that with pride as well, I don't want the hassle of a child at this age, I don't want the hassle of the risk, and I would like to share it with someone that actually means something to me. I know most guys will do whatever it takes to lose it, but I want to force myself not too, I don't want to be like everyone else. I want to stand for what I believe in, and if anybody disputes that, then, (I apologize for this mood I am in..) they can seriously go fuck themselves. I'm so irritable at this moment.   I tend to try and understand the mentalities of so many, and it never works. It's like a burden in disguise, I am done with pretending who I am, I am what I am. It's not like its a bad thing. I am really beginning to notice differences in myself, that I thought would never happen to me, even 6 months ago.  All I can ask is WHY? Why do I have to endure this? Why did I wake up one morning with a more respectful look on everything. And, is it a burden or not at my age? I am 17 years old, and I feel like I think like a wise adult at times, the ones I am supposed to "know more than" at my age. The ones I am supposed to talk shit about behind their backs, and protest to everyone my dislike and hate for them because they "grounded" me.   I don't know whether or not to accept it fully, or let some of it linger and play it all by ear.   Anyways, I am frustrated, confused, and I feel so desolate amongst everyone. I fucking hate when I have to feel like this.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   I really need to fall asleep though, maybe headphones with do... Night... 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Evening everybody...   It's about 11 here, and we just got in the door awhile ago. I painted the entire ceiling in my apartment today. My bedroom is all done and painted now, and tomorrow we are going to do the walls in the main part of it. It's starting to look really good.  That's basically all I have done today, I went to bed really late, or early I should say. Alley & Ty came over around 3am, so we hung out here then went to Robins for coffee, I didn't get home until about 5:30am. And then to top it off I didn't fall asleep until around 7am. So I slept until about 2pm, showered, then went off to the new place to paint.  That would be about my day in short. Nothing interesting, nothing fancy. I didn't have any time to write tonight either, so no poems today as well.  I realized something I wanted to post the other day but it slipped my mind. I was listening to Janet Jackson's old Rhythm Nation CD from '89, and I was really impressed with the lyrics to some of her songs and interludes about the world. The one in particular I thought was so well thought of goes as follows:   In complete darkness we are all the same, it is only our knowledge and wisdom that separates us, don't let your eyes deceive you. - Janet Jackson   I really like the use of equality in that quote. And if you ever had a chance or get a chance to listen to songs from Rhythm Nation, such as  "State Of The World"  or  "The Knowledge" , take some time to listen and appreciate her lyrics. She is truly one of a kind, and her mind is where it should be. Even though some of her new stuff is more sexually oriented, she's my number 1 favourite artist, and she knows how to make kick ass songs. So, let this be my shoutout to Janet, YOU ROCK :)  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Anyway, more painting follows tomorrow. Talk to you guys soon.
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I completely packed my room today. I lugged my bed upstairs, some dressers, my nighttable and I packed a bunch of books, CD's, and other odds and ends. Talk about work. The picture below shows where my bed, and one of my dressers were. Now all the exists is an empty space, with my stereo sitting on the ground. It's kind of depressing since this room hasn't been empty for nearly 14 years...     Unfortunately, my webcam can only take such amateur pictures, that's only one little corner of my room, but, it is the most empty :)     This on the other hand, is my more full part of my room. It's going to be extremely tough to move that large dresser of mine out, but, we can all be mighty strong that day :)  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Anyways, just a quick update of my busy day! I am going to start painting my apartment tonight, and steak awaits me for dinner *drool* I will post later. Bye.
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had to post this one up quick, I love it. Try it out for yourself :P        How to make a Sinful_Misery        Ingredients:  3 parts pride 1 part self-sufficiency 3 parts leadership        Method:  Add to a cocktail shaker and mix vigorously. Add a little cocktail umbrella and a dash of wisdom        Username:       urlLink Personality cocktail  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com    I suppose that could be a good description of me, good picks :)   .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   urlLink My Poetry Portfolio    Later guys. 
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everybody...   I am using that BlogThis! link I found on the Blogger website, it is so much more convenient than having to manually log into the site. I just simply surf, and when I feel like posting, I click the BlogThis! button on my links bar, type away and click publish when I am done. Blogger, you truly make life simpler... :P  So today went very well. I went to the mall with Andrea. I got some CD's today, and it's probably been the first CD's I have purchased in about 3 years. I have over 150 mixed CD's and all of them are burnt. But today I wanted a change. I bought Janet Jackson's new album Damita Jo, and her older album Rhythm Nation since the one I got along time ago got all scratched up and ended up in the garbage. I also bought a Euro Trance pack that came with 4 CD's. The music is awesome too, was a good buy I'd say. After I hit up HMV, I went to American Eagle, and spent 70 bucks on a shirt and shorts. Just a bit expensive, but I don't care as I have a nice cheque coming in on Friday, might as well enjoy my last 300 dollars or so. And I mean the clothes I bought were good looking, so I figured, why the hell not, eh? :)  Afterwards I helped out at the new house today, we brought a bunch of boxes and stuff from my house, and unloaded them at the new house. We also hauled a bed up in Current River from my moms boyfriends house, and unloaded that to my apartment. Was a big job considering box springs don't like to bend down narrow stairways :P  I wanted to post a poem I wrote last night since it's been a few days since I have done so, I wrote it last night while I was talking to Allison about some personal stuff. Enjoy   Love Succesion  Whispers of success Succession of the heart Together we can be Never again to be apart Loving for the moment Caring for the time Sensual experiences You are truly mine Heaven's door is open I am grateful for the day When I feel I love you I know you're here to stay Friction of achievement Failing to be the best Will it work or not? Put me to the test.  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk   And there you have it, my day in it's own post. Interesting, yet weird at the same time. I used to think journals and diarys were pointless, but I have completely changed my perspective on that. It's such a good thing to have.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site    urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Anyway, I am gone, talk to you all later :)
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hello, everybody...   So the new layout has completely been kicked into gear. It took me a few hours in total to get everything perfect. But I didn't do it all in one gulp. Did some in the morning, some after work, and some late last night. I love it too, doesn't look so plain anymore.  I got my hair cut today. Short and streaked blonde. My head is now able to breath. But I miss all the hair I had. :P  Other than all of that intriguing information, I do have some bad news that is disappointing to me. My trip to Winnipeg is now off. My friend doesn't have the money to cover it as her check was smaller than she expected, so she had to cancel to hotel reservations and what not. It was kind of a kick in the ass because I really wanted to go, but shit happens to I guess I will have to deal with it.   I packed some of my room last night, half of it is in several boxes, laying all over the place. Moving isn't pretty, especially when you discover things from about 5 years ago all around your room, that you forgot about. I am not one to adapt to change very easily, so moving is going to be hard. I love the current house I am living in, and I like the one we are moving into, but, even though this one is smaller and what not, I am so used to it and I am not used to the other one. I know that within a month I will get over my old house and settle in, but the transition period inbetween is something I hate enduring. Even though I know it will come out positive, it's that little period that bothers me.  Tonight a few of us from work are going to see Lisa and her baby. She brought it into work yesterday; it was adorable. Afterwards Nadine & I, and I don't know who else, are going to Berries for "smoke-free" coffee. Should be a good first day of work holidays.  It's so hot out today, I walked to Terra Nova (Hairstylist place) and back and I worked up a massive sweat. I love it though, because at least it feels like summer now. It's current 27 C, with a humidex of 32 C. Good temperature, for up here anyway :P  Well, Nae & I are heading to McDonalds soon, I will post later  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Take it easy all.
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       A new discovery...  So I stumbled upon this Audio Blogging thing that was on the Blogger homepage. This recording is pretty pointless, but more or less was for an experiment. :) Enjoy    urlLink   
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Morning everyone...   I have about 20 minutes before I start my long working day. I was up at 6:30am, which is very rare for me since I haven't gotten up that early since I had to leave for the airport when I was in Seattle, back in March. That is pretty scary, I need to be able to get up that early on school days but it doesn't seem to work that well.  Anyways, Geri and I had a game of rings outside at the back before work because we wanted something interesting to do. She's not in until 11:30am so now I am just sitting in the lounge typing this interesting entry.   My coffee is now cold, so I think I will stop drinking it. Cold coffee tastes disgusting.   Well this I am going to make short and sweet, and I am going to go have another cigarette before I sign my life away for the next 8 hours.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Talk to you all later.  
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Once again, hello   My damn cell phone is being stubborn and won't charge, it keeps saying "Unable To Charge", well the thing is stupid. The battery has less than one block left, and it won't charge the damn thing. It makes me mad.  So I made some slight changes to the layout of the blog, the other one was so boring and plain. This one is a little more intriguing. I still have some things I have to do on it though, some colour changes, backgrounds changes etc. I will fiddle with my web design power.  I have a massive headache at the moment, and it doesn't want to go away. After I finish this post I am going to take some more pills and I am heading to sleep. (I just had Deja Vu of typing that.... weird..)  So my holidays are set back one more day because I decided to cover a shift for an agent at work. So I have to work at 8:30am tomorrow. Only until 5pm though, so it isn't too bad. This way my cheque will be a little nicer than it would have been originally. Plus my vacation pay is going to be exhausted and I believe it's almost at $200. Couldn't have picked a better time for this whole paid vacation type deal to come about.  Well I suppose I am going to cut this one short, I am tired, headachy and feeling annoyed. I guess it was a little less than 2 hours for tonight's downtime. If it were any longer than I wouldn't have posted this.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Two more days of having my hair, then 75% is going to be swept into the garbage. *Sigh* my head is going to feel so naked..
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       How's everyone tonight...   Coming from a fellow Canadian here, I feel rather pissed off after reading something. I was looking through blogs out of boredness, and came across a post that honestly, even though I shouldn't care, insulted me greatly. Entitled "Fuck You Canada", it posessed a meaningless point in my eyes, and it was very rude and arrogant. And to that I seriously take offense.  urlLink Read It  Anyways, it's not something completely major, but it seriously shows the mentality and common sense of the world. Based on a complete stipulation / statistic this individual runs his opinion about how "Canadians Hate Americans" and how it's made to seem that "America is the most generous country". I wasn't aware I hated Americans, and that half of Canada did. The last time I checked I am pretty sure I had family in the USA, and plenty of people I know do as well. It just honestly makes me upset at the fact that an insulting phrase like "Fuck You Canada" can be based on such vile information.   The other thing that gets me is that, out of all countries, why Canada? Canada should be the least of the USA's worries. Specially when it comes to hating one another. I do believe a lot of Canadians have opinions about not supporting this whole war situation in Iraq, but how can we possibly hate the citizen's of America? I am sure there are plenty of Americans already who don't support this war that has no point to it, why should that be a bad thing? We live in a fucking democracy, we can think what we want, which is fine (I am not trying to be hypocritical) But before thinking, think long and hard that what your actually thinking has some sense and meaning to it.  And believe it or not, not all Americans get along either, as well as Canadians. Everyone has a different opinion so before one is meaninglessly overrated, think twice and find out information for yourself. I could make a poll right now saying that "statisically speaking" Americans hate Canadians, post it on the internet, get a lot of traffic to wherever I am hosting these "statistics" and in turn, people would believe it! It's a joke. Does anybody ever read "The Enquirer"? The magazine is full of shit, and yet people still pay the money to read the worthless piece of crap. Why not support something valuable in life rather than some rich idiots making shit up to ruin other's lives?   But back to the point, MY point is that I don't hate ANYTHING personally. There are things I dislike, but hatred is too strong a word/feeling. To make a generalization about a country our size, and the size of America is never going to get anybody anywhere. There are people in Canada that I know that I dislike, and I am sure that an American citizen has someone that they dislike in America as well. But as soon as someone hears "Hey, That Canadian Hates You I Read It In A Magazine" (Figuratively speaking) then shit hits the fan. Take it easy, learn to cope, and understand that wherever you go not everyone will support/like you, but there will always be people who will support/like you. Take it into consideration.  Anyways, that is my 2 cents for todays post. No offense given, and none taken. I have no problem with Americans, there, I said it.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   I pray for this world to mend itself, but that will never happen... *sigh* Goodnight all.
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Evening everyone...   It felt so good be off of work today. I did, however, have to cut the grass today, and it was so damn hot out. It was awesome though, I improved my "sexy" tan.   I am so refreshed as well, I slept until 2:30 today, a sleep I really needed. To catch up over the past few days of my insomniac ways.  I have to be up for 7 AM tomorrow, as I have to work at 8 AM. That's an extremely early morning for me, I am going to be pretty burnt out at the end of the day. But oh well, the more money for my trip, the better my trip!  I start my holidays on Wednesday, so I will have a nice break from work, and the best part is, my trip is in 12 days! Winnipeg is going to be awesome, I get to see some people I haven't seen for awhile and have a good time with nobody around but a few friends. No family, no drama, no work, no home, no nothing. Except relaxing and fun :) Everybody needs one of those, you know what I mean. :)  Anyways, I am going to go now. Short post, but I thought I should write something!  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Later all. 
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hi everyone....!   I am pretty tired today / tonight so I decided I didn't feel like going out and doing anything interesting. With work, and early mornings I feel I need a break. Welcome to "Real Life" though I suppose. I guess that's why a lot of adults don't go out as much as teenagers - they like their days to relax.   Relaxing is a good thing though, and it's healthy. If I didn't choose to rejuvenate myself / stabilize my state of mind, it would all lash out and unleash in a way I wouldn't want it too. Stability is the key for me. I like to be on top of things, and feeling normal and refreshed.   Tomorrow I am finally off for a day. I have to mow the lawn though. Which won't be that bad, all I will do is throw my headphones on and cut away. Music is relaxing and soothing.   I honestly listen to music WHENEVER I have the chance. I find myself even putting televison on closed captioning to listen to a song. It makes me feel so good and relaxed. Music is truly, pleasurable to the mind and soul.  Work was pretty busy today, for a Saturday anyway. We went in and out of queue for the day, so it was busy for awhile, then dead for awhile, then busy etc. It was like a pattern of calls. Now that I can handle, because it wasn't bombarded with people waiting on hold, I think the highest we had today was 9. That is nothing compared to the time we had 77 people waiting on hold to get through to us. And because we were understaffed that day it kept building, it seemed like for every 1 call we took, 3 more called in. We couldn't win that night.   Anyways, that's the updates as of today. I start my holidays on Wednesday, so I will be having more interesting experiences to type on here..:)   A Sad State  Saddened by the heart, Careless to the touch, Succession is the key, Knowing, is too much.  A gateway to the concept, The key unlocks the stipulation, Life to one, and it's own, To me is a mere revelation.  Irony and bliss are present, Duties and respect are gone, Followers withhold pretense, Nobody exists but pawns  Dystopian realms of what? Full of judgementals and fakes, To change the worlds ridiculing ways, I would do whatever the hell it takes.   Saddened and mortified by this place, Grief exists, and contentness is overrated, We all live in the dark, and we Know nothing; we are shaded.  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio    Talk to you all later.
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everybody..   I had a really long day. Feels good to be able to relax and unwind. I just posted some more poems, so my portfolio now has 14 poems I think.   I worked all day, and it was horrid. I had so many angry customers and irate people being transferred to me for 8 hours straight. It was evil I swear. It's really annoying when you try to explain and do your best for the customer, but yet they are still not satisfied. I told one consumer, that I didn't appreciate being sworn at and that I was trying to explain what happened, and what I can do to fix it for her. She got really snotty with me, but eventually listened and when I did everything I could that still wasn't enough for her because she had to wait a few weeks to get her money.   If only people could learn to relax, and be patient. I guess the world revolves around number one, so it seems anyway. Pisses me off, it's not just the people I deal with on a daily basis, but everyone in general. They will do anything to save their asses, to increase their well-being etc. No respect at all. It's sad, and pathetic.   Anyways, I took another shift tomorrow, so I am working another 11:30 AM - 8:00 PM shift. Then I work 12:00 PM - 6:00 PM on Saturday, off Sunday, then 8:00 AM - 4:30 PM on Monday. I am so excited though because I start my holidays on Wednesday, and I head to Winnipeg in two weeks! Summer rocks :)  I had written this poem last night, it's about open mindedness.. enjoy!   Open  Generic ridicule, Cheap stimulation; Are that of a simple mind  Thoughtful opinions, Modish revival; Are that of an open mind  Amateur thought, Not caring why; Is that of an unpretentious mind  Deep contemplation, Wondering why; Is that of a transcendent mind  Simple versus open, Unpretentious versus transcedent,  Can be compared too,  Seeing what you want, versus seeing everything Caring about what you want, versus caring about all; Unimaginable benefits, compared to thinking in tact.  Minds are elaborate Humans are as well.  To choose your elaborated style To truly peer into yourself  Will only produce an outcome, If you open yourself, open your mind.  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  And so it's been done. Another day gone by. Another moment lived. I will post later.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio    Take care everyone.
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       And once again I am here...   It's getting pretty late for me tonight, as I have to get up early and goto work. Sounds fun, doesn't it? Not.  I went out for coffee tonight and had some really good laughs. It felt good to get away from all of the ponderings and thinking I have been possessed by. I guess when I got home it was once again waiting for me. I wrote 3 poems tonight. But, I don't want to overflow this post so I am going to post the one I can relate to mostly in this mood I am in.   What  Immoral acts of shame; Shameful acts of morality; What is truly ethical?  Foreshadowing the distress Commemorating the beauty Brings us to what?  Anticipation to advance, Hesistant to relapse, What lies ahead?  Shuddering to the thought, Intriguing to the mind, What are we up against?  People in agony, Existing within disease What are we here for?  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk   The poem obviously speaks for itself, I can define it as unanswered questions of life, that perhaps aren't worth pondering; but I can't help to ponder it. Anything unknown intrigues me, which I suppose at times can be a bad thing.  Anyways, life is feeling pretty good at the time, just confusing, love-ridden, and contemplative.  All of my poetry is located in my portfolio (link is at the bottom of the post)  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio    I am going to rest up for my long day tomorrow. Good night all.
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hello, once again...   I am heading to work in about a half an hour so I decided, since I have nothing better to do at the present time, why not leave a quick post? Hence why I am here typing this out now.  I haven't written anything new yet, I plan to do so later on tonight. I have to get to bed early though because I work 11:30 - 8:00 tomorrow. Which sucks because it is going to be busy and retarded. That's alright though, well, actually it's not.   Anyway I had a deep conversation with Nikki last night about a lot of shit. It was really cool considering I don't know her that well. But, in the same, I feel like I have known her my entire life. The conversation was pretty open minded and cool though :) I got a lot off of my chest.  As if I don't get enough off of my chest on here as well though :P It's a bit different when your talking to someone directly though, but this blog does me just as enough good.  I have ranged from, positive outlooks on life, to love and relationships, to society and its flaws. I have logged them all, will be cool to see how my viewpoints change in 20 years or so. Also my poetry has gotten me into all of this blogging shit. It's awesome to include a piece of my work on here for the whole world to read :)  Once again; for those who take the time to read, understand and think about anything I have said or put on here, I really do appreciate it. It's good to know people do that :)  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   I am gone for now, I will post later on, hopefully with some new poems. Talk to you all later :)
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hello, once again..   I am enjoying all of the feedback I am getting on my poetry. It's good to know that people can relate to my feelings and emotions expressed through it. For the people who take the time to read and understand, I appreciate it :)  Anyways I wrote another one last night, I feel as if I am a machine. My cousin and her boyfriends relationship inspired me to write it. They care very deeply of each other, but the age difference bothers the family, and my cousin is struggling with the family finding out. Even through all of it, it works out for the best. Here it is, enjoy.   Love Survival   Frightening amusement; Cherishing the time. Living for the moment; And making you truly mine  Societal perspectives; Differ from my heart An everlasting commitment; Is letting itself start  Feeling your touch; Fills me with intensity I know that I love you; A sensual sensitivity  Frightened to move on; Too late to turn back Loving each other forever; We can do it, it's a fact  Until acceptance is granted; We stand here hand in hand Be by my side forever; And never let me strand  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk   And there you have it :). I should continue getting ready for work. I plan to go for coffee tonight, smoke-free too. Never done that before. We will see how it goes I suppose, eh? Take it easy everyone!  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio  
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey all...   The title says it all. It's back to work for me tonight. Bleh. I hope it isn't busy. I would like to sit, and relax for once while I am there. Haha.   So my trip plans are confirmed now. Andrea and I reserved the hotel last night through Expedia and we are hitting up Winnipeg on July 23rd. We are going to stay there the weekend and come back Monday the 26th. I am pretty pumped, I am going to do some shopping and roaming around. I also get to see some people I haven't seen for awhile as well. It will be nice to relax and get away! I plan to be on the road at about 5am, road trips are so fun.   I downloaded a bunch of new Janet Jackson songs off of her new album Damita Jo. The songs are awesome. I am going to buy the CD soon.   I wrote another poem today, entitled "Assurance". It has to do with instability of the mind being able to be controlled. Enjoy.   Assurance   Productive outcomes, Sinful thought, Inspirational genious, Yet had to be taught  Firm grasp on reality, Shunning from the past, Helping the matter, Can resolve this at last  Lost and alone, Yet surrounded by everyone, Feelings of dismay, Weigh upon my back a tonne  A hierarchy of madness, Harmonious acts of discretion Setting the bar where its needed Organizing each thought in its section  Intricate formulas, Alluding the rest Attempting to give, Showing your best  Freedom to roam, Pressure of my life Swaying back and forth Cutting, like the blade of a knife  Regretting what is past, Concentrating on the future Throw away the pessimistic views, Then truly, can yourself assure.  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  And so you have it. Another day gone, a new day to start. Seems to me that life goes by so fast. Time rushes like it is out of style. *Sigh*  I have posted my poems in an online portfolio, if you want to check them all out visit  urlLink this page    .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Until later, take it easy.
      
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everybody...   My writing moods have changed from intellectual thought, to depressing and anger at the world, as you can tell. I cannot help it, it comes directly from my thoughts. Enjoy these two new poems I have written :)    Mindful Warning   A shred of light, as it tears me apart, A feeling of courage with all that is myself, To be given the strength to go on each day, Relies strictly on my focus and effort  An indication of reliance, what is the point? Reliance is strictly trust, and trusting oneself can break apart. An imaginative highlight of the mind, a deathly pull on the soul. To encompass a true vision is somewhat impossible  To subconciously change a thought to what you want it to be, Is severity in it's worst form, and is meaningless devotion. A wish of paradise, searching for the likes, Affection is nothing but a pointless emotion  Depriving me of a thought I wish to share, On a level of intellect, I can search and find it To criticise my style, and way of wisdom, Is nothing but pure atrocity.  To animate the lives of everyone, To switch points and turn it against oneself, Is what makes this world, what it is, Disappointing misery, a changing toll of life  Mistaking a lie for truth, and mistaking the truth for the reality, Guilds us and bounds us to this place we call home, Surely it does seem the way that can be bad, Who is one to tell the difference?  Everything is overrated, everything is a lie Lying in bed at night, thinking of what will happen next The hill is growing steeper, We don't give a damn.  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  This poem basically expresses my disgust, in not only everyone else, but myself as well in that we do nothing to improve society and all of it's many flaws.    Doomed   A blissful realization; a tempest of doom Reactions are different; visions of gloom Pocket your thinking; notice the sight, Everything is melancholy; nothing is right, Escape from the fury, return to the hell, See through its lies; seek and do tell.  Atracting its prey; tolerating its movement Adapting to change; accepting it's testament Illogical messes; justifying grace, Virtuous fiction; leaves us with a chase Skeptics cause dysfunction; an imminent trait, Caressing the thought, we are nothing but bait.  Gracious contemplation; a result from the thought, Is that of a wise person; a wise person taught. Understanding the depression; comprehending the hate, The future of this world, relies on nothing but fate. The destroyed forces within, interested in our well-being Shouldn't care anymore, for what they have been seeing  We've gone to far, and dug ourselves in, too deep. With the effects of our actions, others, now weep.  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  This one is along the same lines as the first. Showing our struggle with reality, and the world itself, and how our actions affect everyone else.  I guess that's all I will write for tonight. The contemplative mood is still evident, as I can feel it. I will definately write some more poems later today.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Talk to you all later.
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hello, again...   I am in quite the morbid mood at this time. Here's a ramble of my anger at the world, enjoy :)   Respect lacks definition, Reward cries out for greed, This world is corrupted, Indirectly, we all bleed,  Deserving the misery, Withstanding the pain, What were we all thinking? What did we have to gain?  A life full of sin, A morbidly choice, As many as there are, We relied on only one voice,  To speak for oneself, Has been ruled out for good, Nobody gave it a chance, Especially when we could,  We are now doomed to live in this place, It serves us right I suppose, But why should we complain? This is the life we basically chose,  Requirements mean nothing, Thinking is a shame, The world is nothing but a mockery, And we treat it like a game,  To be yourself or not, Is a question in the same, Who can we pin the problem on? Noone; We are all to blame.  © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  I guess it's more simple minded than anything. I really don't care though. It was enough effort for it to come right out of the blue that I had to type it all out. I guess that about explains my mood at this point. Not so much, negative, but "morbidly ingenious". I feel like I am thinking in a positively bad way. In a way that doesn't effect my train of thought or sanity. I am in the mood to vent, so I think I should take advantage of it while I am comfortable and seemingly interested in it.  I just find it completely and utterly horrible that we live the way we do. Everything is so fucked up. I am not playing Mr. Perfect here either; everyone that is old enough to think for themselves in a "semi" mature way can blame nobody but themselves. We contribute to everything that goes on in this world, indirectly and directly. And whether or not it's good or bad, people just don't give a shit. Incredible, isn't it? Selfishness, greed, objectifications, cold hearted people. It is nothing but a fucking joke. I can honestly admit to myself that I don't enjoy these things, or get a rise out of the misery they cause. The world is too good for a kind like us. Humans have the ability to think; and even if it is used in the worst way, it doesn't mean we are stupid. We know too much. People toy with nature, they toy with life, they toy with humanity. Is it right?   Society is based on so much more than, "how we live". How we act, how we think, how we handle situations, are just practicallities. The basics of society are nothing but a mere infatuation. One of which I am into myself, but do I have a choice? I will admit, society has me, but I would still consider myself rebellious in most of its senses.   To think badly of your own society, is when the worrying should start. Us humans have no sense of decency, and in general we all deserve the consequences that lie after this life is over.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Sorry for that. I got all worked up and into this post. I don't usually get so carried away.  Goodnight.
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       And I Return...   Hey everyone, I am extremely exhausted! *Yawn* The past 2 days were right fun, but in turn I pay for it by being tired. It was worth it though. Canada Day rocked. I went all out, with tattoos, clothes, etc. I was a walking Canada. We all went out to the Marina until about 11:30 to watch the fireworks, then we went to a party afterwards. I didn't get drunk though, I had one Mike's Hard. Afterwards we went out to Robyn's camp and I spent the night, and yesterday there. I am so sunburned now. And heatstroken. :(  I am grateful for the fact that I don't work until Tuesday. It's a Godsent in my eyes :) July 4th weekend in the USA. Therefore, I don't have to work!  I feel like writing tonight, and I think I will. Helps me to get my mind off of so much, and the more I write, the more I understand. I never really understood how hard it actually is to understand yourself. Poetry is the wavelength that allows me to build a "bridge" between my thoughts, and how I can express them. My ability to write also relies strictly on my mood. I can't write anything "happy" if I am not. It's how I feel that determines the subject.   Sometimes I don't even know the subject until I start writing more in depth. I don't think, I just spill it all in large amounts and boom; another piece of work. I really think it is cool though, to speak directly from the mind without any hesitation. It's just an urge to let it all out. Whether or not it's inspiring.  At the time I have no feelings to write. I will post later.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   Later.
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       It's Canada Day!   Wow, I love this day so much. Andrea and I went shopping at Wal-Mart, I bought a Canada T-Shirt, Facemask, Hat, and Flag. I am planning to wear all of it, including tattoos and Canadian boxers. Yeah thats right, I will be the truly patriotic "walking Canadian". I honestly love this country so much and I am so thankful to inhabit such a place. People can complain all they want, but we have it so good here. Appreciate it.  I will be out at my cousin's camp for the next few days, I will try to post tomorrow morning, or when I get home from work. I work a 9 hour shift tomorrow so I may not have time. But, I will try :)  I did write another poem I'd like to share with you all. I am really beginning to learn a lot about the way I think and dream. It's as if poetry is the key to writing it out so fluently, even if it has some sort of metaphorical point to it. It just comes out of my head, and I don't even need to think at times of what to write next, poetry is truly the language of the soul and the heart. (By the way this one doesn't rhyme)    Listen. Understand. Do. Three undeviating words. Are you able to hear? Deep in its depths?  Addressing the situation, Believing in yourself. Are you able to correspond? With its meanings so complex?  Acting upon its message coherently, In a way that is justifiable. Are you able to perservere? In a postive manner?  To protect; to love; to cherish, To bring upon; and act accordingly, To care, and to respect, Are the goals of its influence.  Possessing and judging your very own character, Are you happy? Are you forlorn? To peer deep inside yourself, To learn your very own truth.  Having meritable, yet factual attributes, Invisible to the naked eye. To assist in bringing them to the surface, is the nature of; the soul.   © 2004 Tyler Kuhk  That is my fictional approach to describing what I think is our soul. Hope you enjoyed. I am off to sleep now.  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site   "Proud To Be Canadian"  
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everybody...   The last few days have been crazy busy for me. Overtime was approved pretty much all week so I was working pretty much everyday for more than I was scheduled for. It caught up to me though.  Christie left yesterday to go back to Toronto for school, and Geri & I picked her up around 4:00 am to take her for breakfast and drop her off at the airport for 5:30am. I then went back home and slept until 8 and headed to work after that. Then I worked my 10 hour shift being extremely overtired - so I slept like a baby last night.  This morning is actually good, I feel refreshed and back in the game. There aren't too many people here yet as most will come in around 11:30, but either way we aren't too busy today. Let's hope it stays :)  So basically I am just sitting here at the lounge with not much to do until 9:30 when I sign my life away for the next 10.5 hours - I guess I can cope though :)  I wanted to make a quick update - I have some poetry to post in here later.  .: Sinful Misery :.  urlLink My Site   Later, for now :)
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Once again, hello all....   It has been yet another day that has since passed in my life. Each day lately, I have been dreading the fact that school starts in almost 3 weeks. Life flies by much to fast for my liking.  Work was alright I guess today, our systems were down for pretty much the entire day so I didn't really put much effort into helping anybody because I didn't have the necessary tools to do so. They shoved a bunch of the supervisors on T-Mobile today into Target's section so I was away from all of my co-workers except for the 5 I was with in Target. I purposely saved  urlLink Christie  a seat today and within 10 minutes of my shift they shoved me away from T-Mobile society. A lot of shit is going on at work now as well, I could almost even refer to it as drama.  For starters, there is a new representative who has been giving some supervisors very rude and arrogant behaviour, and in turn, complains that the supervisors are being rude. So they took all of us and warned us all that other reps have been complaining on how us T-Mobile supervisors are being complained on for being rude. I understand that it needs to be relayed to us - but it bothers me that this even has to be brought up. Why would anybody in the right state of mind be rude to someone with no apparent reason? I know damn well I do my job right and I would never disrespect another co-worker - no matter how rude they are with me. I would deal with it in a much different manner.  Too many things get started around there as well, it's like a fucking soap opera - work style. I attempt to stay out of it all, but now that I work full time shifts it's hard not to see a lot of what goes on there. It's a job - and it needs to be taken that way. Save the drama for your personal time, because it's one thing I dislike.  I try my best to disregard that kind of stuff, I have seen and put up with enough in the past with friends and family - it's as if people like the rise they get out of it? I suppose each of us indirectly contribute to it, but even so - can you help it?  Anyways, back on to a different subject. I am kind of tired tonight as I lacked some sleep last night, which was kind of a stupid thing of me to do, but I tried my best to fall asleep.   In turn, I did happen to fall asleep a bit after 3 - then I woke up a 9:30, not too bad but still, tonight I will have to compensate.  I wrote a poem finally today as my mind was in that state. Enjoy.   Deprivation  Not a moment to spare, Never the time to waste, Wishing time could stand still, Wanting a moment to replace,  Withholding life's pleasures, Letting go of the pain, Strict effort and integrity, Allow me the world to gain,  An impact of relation, A worthless tone of hate, Grief and existence are continous, Next to nothing to refer to as great,  Wrath of wisdom's ways, Bliss of knowledge's power, Caring too much about it all, If not equal, then a coward  Lonesome deep at heart, Depths of a soulful ill, Pain is state of mind, Love is what fulfills.  © Tyler Kuhk 2004   Anyways, I suppose thats enough for tonight...  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Night all.
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Greets everybody!   That sleep last night was amazing. I had good dreams, and I feel so much more alive than I have the past few days.   I think I was a bit overtired yesterday at work, as I was much more talkative and hyper than I usually am. It's either that or I am bitching to go home because I'm tired - so I will stay with the overtired point.  I haven't really been writing much lately - I don't feel any sense to. Today however, when I woke up, I thought I may just write some more later as I think that now with everything levelling off in my life, I may have the perserverence to do so.   The other day as I re-did my thoughts page on my website, I edited a lot out and added some information in that I didn't have on my other site. My views slightly changed in some areas, but became much more specific than what they were in the original indications.   I just reflect on the changes my minds gone through in the last few months.... it's amazed me. I can admit to myself that I am true and that I have nothing to impress anybody else about. I love it though, I no longer need to waste my time on worthless matters that only end up blowing up in my face in the longrun. Life is much too short to dwell on what you can do to make yourself seem so much better than others.  The context in which "better" is used, shouldn't even be able to stand firmly for itself. It's not possible to be better than anyone. Everybody has their strong and weak points, and even though people tend to focus strictly on negativity - the positive and negative in each of us balances equally.   Equality, in my opinion is something that will never be fully accepted by everybody. I really dislike when other people discriminate against others for their race, religion, or beliefs. Who is ANYBODY to ridicule for such things? That's the problem with today - people are far too judgemental and ridiculing that if it's not done their way its automatically bad, wrong, evil or "uncool".  I tend not too care about what people say about me anymore because I rest assure each day that I am happy with who I am and I know that the people who wish to ridicule me for the way I think or for what I believe in, are obviously people I wouldn't be caught dead associating with anyway. Either way, I win in the matter.  A word of advice... your never going to be liked my everybody... keep your close friends close... and watch your back when your into a new crowd...  .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Talk to you all later. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Greetings all...   It has been since Tuesday, and tonight, I will be able to sleep, and in the morning, I will be able to sleep in. I am so excited its not even funny. It's going to feel so good as I need some rejuvention to progress any further this week.  Work has just been unreal lately - I have been putting up with the same shit everyday, and it has been so busy. Saturdays are usually dead, and very slow; but I took more calls today than yesterday - and yesterday was very busy. It's just been an irritable week.  The C.L.E comes on Wednesday - I still have yet to get my tickets as we are all going on the last night :) It should be fun I need to get my mind off of work and what not at the time...  I am dreading returning to school, and I hate to be saying that since its another month before we go back, but I have been seeing flyers and commercials already for it and it makes me even more sad because I am loving the summer so much. So relaxed and stress free. Besides work anyway :)  I still have yet to pick up my Zyban prescription...I would like to begin to quit smoking very soon. I am a little nervous to try the pill though because I have heard of some strange side effects. I suppose I will just look on the bright side - that way I make not overreact on account of anything.  Anyways, need to make this short. I am absolutely exhausted and I need my well-deserved rest.   .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Night everybody...
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everybody...   So once again, I am at my lovely place of work. I happen to be on my lunch break right now so I decided to get on the computer for a bit.  Works been fairly busy, I have been dealing with the same thing however since 9:30 this morning. Letter after letter for the same reason. I am getting disgusted with the same call every 2 minutes. I guess that's life some days though, eh?  I'm not quite keen on typing anything interesting right now so I guess I may have to blab about things that are on my mind...  I'm pretty pumped that I finally got my site up and running thru tylerkuhk.com. It cost me about $20 Canadian for two years. I still have much more to do, but at least the basics are done. I'm currently hosting it on my own server, which consists of the ever so famous Pentium 200 MMX. That way I don't have to worry about relying on any free hosting servers, or to have to pay for hosting. This way it's all done for free.  Other than that not too much else is new. I suppose I should head back because my break is finished in about 10 minutes.  .: Sinful Misery :.  urlLink My Site   Bye all.
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey everybody...!   It's been almost two months I have held this journal together, and I am now brought to my 50th post. And yet, what a grand time to make a post since I have slacked off in the blogging department lately.  Recently, I have been working like crazy. My job tends to schedule me really shitty shifts so I have been putting up with that for awhile now.  My move is now done - we are all settled in and I am quite used to living here now - in fact I am enjoying it dearly. This basement apartment makes me feel like I am living on my own - so peaceful, but yet I pay nothing :)  Also recently, I have re-designed my website and have recently registered a domain. My site can now be accessed at  urlLink http://www.tylerkuhk.com  Check it out :)  I re-did some of my life thoughts and have been coming up with ideas on what else to post. I have written some thoughts / opinions on suicide, friends, truth and trust. I will post them up shortly.   Anyways, just wanted to make a quick post as I need to get to sleep. I have a long, enduring 10.5 hour shift tomorrow.   .:Sinful_Misery:.  urlLink My Site  |  urlLink My Poetry Portfolio   Bye everyone. And don't worry - my blogger attitude is kicked back into drive :P
      
</post>


</Blog>