<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have achieved my first goal in my plan to get free books and get something published!  The  urlLink Journal of Political Geography  (which is much more exciting than it sounds) have sent me a copy of Clive Barnett's  urlLink new book  'Culture and Democracy: Media, Space and Representation' to review. I have to write 1000 words by the end of september, which I'm going to have to try and squeeze in alongside my dissertation...hmmmmm
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I found this crazy  urlLink story  on  urlLink Susan's blog 
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Independence  on Saturday night was double fat,  urlLink Friendly Pete  played 1st and then for a change I played mainly pumping techy house and some funky techno and it seemed to work really well....the wel ldone gold star has to go to the VJs tho....crazy visuals all night on a lovely new projector...looks like this night is finally taking off! Next month Sam Ball from  urlLink Club Class  is playing so that should be even busier, time to buy some new records..any suggestions?
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm trying to market a  urlLink conference , mainly online and I'm worried that I'm turning into a low-level spammer.  I'm trying to make it all as targeted as possible but eventually I'm sure somebody will want to kick my arse.... If anybody has any suggestions for people/organisations/communities etc that might want me to send them info about the conference, please let me know so i don't just spam them!
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Krafty Kuts  urlLink is playing  at Greenbelt! Just as I was thinking, "perhaps I'll get round to checking out greenbelt at some point, shame there aren't any DJs and only jingly-jangly bands are playing" then i go and discover that! Maybe its about time I sent them a demo CD? 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      after reading back, I have decided to put something more interesting on here to reward anyone who reads this blog :)  urlLink Here  is a link to the new book by Lawrence Lessig which you can download under a  urlLink creative commons  license (ie for free).  The book is about creative freedom and the internet, mainly....well worth a look.
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Following a link on  urlLink Dan's blog , which came from a link on  urlLink Liz's blog  I've come across the fantastic  urlLink music plasma .  I really like this site and have manged to waste the last 15 minutes playing with it and trying to catch it out (with limited sucess).  Unfortunately, it has given me a huge inferiority complex about some work i'm trying to do at the moment (which i hadn't even started and now may never try)where I'm trying to represent networked data visually.  I was planning to write some basic html-formatted text that worked through hyperlinks and colour, which I knew was super-basic, but seemed approprate to the task and my abilities.  Now I may give up for a bit.  Hopefully the sun will come out again soon and cheer me up! 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After a long time knocking blogs as being prone to developing into embarrassing social confessionals, I've decided that having one myself might be a useful way of trying to bring together the different things that seem to keep happening around me and perhaps a tool to help me draw the links between them.  Opening all of this up to public criticism should be interesting too, with any luck people will be able to point out the gaps in my ideas and kick me (gently) when i'm going off on a tangent...i'll have to wait and see.... 
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink This  is a 3am idea if I've ever seen one, even non cat-people will ahve to admit the wonderfulness of this little site. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I came across  urlLink the other's blog , which is well worth checking out.&nbsp; The other is an Iranian living in Los Angeles, described by a young Iranian lad i used to work with as  urlLink Tehrangeles  due to the fact that it puts out a gobal Iranian TV network and has a huge Iranian migrant community. 
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've realised that I don't often put links on here, so urlLink  here  is one for you all...a wonderful photo-blog.... 
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I believe I have now officially bitten off more than I can comfortably chew.  This week I have:  1. Taken on a marketing job for a venue in Ashford.&nbsp; This involves&nbsp;developing a new marketing strategy for them and being responsible for the music policy and communications for the venue.  2.&nbsp; Re-designed my dissertation to increase it's 'focus' and also, sneakily, to make it more attractive to future employers.&nbsp; At some point next week I'm going to attempt to put it up on here to see whether it makes any sense to anyone other than me..... 3.&nbsp; Accepted another  urlLink book  review, due in at the same time as my dissertation.  4.&nbsp; Tentatively agreed to start a new business with a friend.  5. Begun to apply for new jobs, in an attempt to end my commuting misery.  I'm beginning to relax about the&nbsp; fact that I seem to have bene living at 100mph for about 4 years and hope that my new-found interest in gardening will ease the pain....   
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For once, I can finally utter the words 'money is no object' about a tengo gig.....  I now have £1000 to book a 'big name' DJ for independence, I'm thinking Seb Fontaine or somebody of similar fame at the moment but all suggestions gladly taken....needs to be housey tho!  Ok, so i guess there is a £1000 limit, so not quite no object, but in this case money is a big fat expensive object that I am allowed to spend, so that will have to do!
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just sent an email to the  urlLink Holy See , who could have predicted that?
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      DCMS have done me a huge favour by publishing a  urlLink consultation paper  on the place of culture in regeneration strategies, just before the date I have promised myself to have started writing my introduction by!  I had been struggling with the whole foundation of my dissertation because I couldn't find a contemporary context to hang it on that wasn't just one of the same tired case-studies that everyone has been using for ages like Glasgow or Cardiff, so this has come along at exactly the right time.  Now all I have to do is locate my errant tutor and convince her to sit down with me for a bit to discuss it! 
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've spent that last two days at a  urlLink conference  in Oxford on 'The Changing Contexts of Migration'.  Apart from the usual badge, folder and notepaper, I have come away with the following thoughts: 1. My dissertation may not work! Consensus seems to be that it is 'too big' for an MA piece.  This means I have had to slim down my idea, which I will eventually post on here, to make it 'fit' better with the time I have available.  I guess the people I spoke to were right on this one, if I'm being honest, but it has made the whole thing a lot less exciting :( 2.  Academia does not welcome generalists. 3.  The schism between policy, practice and research (and 'ordinary' opinion) in Migration studies is too wide to be overcome through a conference like this, especially if the people involved in choosing delegates think that the answer is to have an academic conference to debate the problem. 4. That fried breakfasts are they way forward. But only in the morning.....and especially if they are on account. 
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Apparently  urlLink this test  will pinpoint you on the political spectrum.  I occupy the same position as the dalai lama, which is nice.
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night I had dinner with a charming friend of mine who wants to put on a massive party at the  urlLink julie rose stadium  in ashford, which holds about 3000 people.  Bizzarely, the local council seem keen on the idea and will put up some bunce for our trouble! I'm in two minds about this one...wicked party, ashford needs it, probably suitcases full of cash involved, but quite stressful...maybe I'm just getting old?
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Being married and fairly sedentary, I often find myself listening to Radio 4. Lat night on John Peel's 'Home Truths' program, I discovered something interesting about the location of the North-South dividing line. Apparently, the line is drawn in terms of motoraway signage along the M62..this leaves manchester, most of liverpool and loads of yorkshire in the south....  
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've just got back from a week's holiday in Derbyshire. I thought I was going to Yorkshire until I got to the house we were house-sitting in, which shows how little I understand the geography of areas north of the Medway Towns. Before we got to the house we stayed with my brother in law and his wife in Manchester. Basically, I take back every comment I have ever made to  urlLink Dan  about the rain in Manchester. It was proper hot, almost too hot and we had an excellent time, including sampling the delights of the d:percussion festival, which looked excellent and sounded fat, especially as they seemed to have come across a job lot of turbosound rigs to power it all with! After that tho, it rained...and rained..... I'm trying now to catch up on a week's worth of work that I've let slip while I've been away....updates on holiday to follow in due course :0) 
      
</post>


</Blog>