<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Happy Birthday sa iyo…     It’s DM’s birthday today! Hay..crappy day man toh, masaya pa din coz narinig ko na naman ang Katarungan’s own version of the birthday song. Happy Birthday again dear friend! I thank God for giving me a friend like you.     I therefore conclude…    You see, being with 2 bitches in a day results to one crappy day. The formula bitch + bitch = one crappy day is so damn true. Let’s name them bitch 1 and bitch 2. I just realized that I was saying vulgar words the whole time I was with bitch 1 and when bitch 2 sang. Shit on that 2nd bitch. She’s like a feeler! Like I saw the look in her face, the look that says hay-naku-just-because-our-voices-are-to-die-for-don’t-act-as-our-supervisor-coz-you-have-nothing to-do-with-us. Hell no. You’re wrong. “Nothing do with us” you say. More like NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU! You’re one shitless crap. You make me sick to the bones and you make me wanna kill you and your whole clan! And you’re SOOOOOO, and I mean SOOOOOOOOOO yabang pa! You talk in a pa-humble way pa pero it’s like you really want me to envy you! Hay…so what do I care? I don’t even care a little bout you. You look like my ex-yaya kasi! HMP! I HATE BITCH 2 MORE!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        THIS GUY  ...   This guy, he's from YFC. A senior student from San Beda. The president of YFC San Beda. Nice, God-fearing, dedicated and devoted to God, fun to be with, part of taekwondo in UAAP, a friend...but not a cutie...puh-leeezzeee....          Here's somethin'...     The thought of him makes me go giggly and yucky at the same time. Weird, eh? Because look, when a guy texts you "Can I call you na?" you'll be like "ohgodamnshittyassholoeaaahhhh!!" and all giggly until you remeber that he's UGLY....I'm not being mean or something...But, hell yeah if you see him. And Alex makes me tukso pa to him. Deng man! Alex knows that there's one and only HIM....So you think it's Joshua Garcia? No...Jesus Christ...hahaah! Now you think i'm in my most spiritual mode. But even I'm a "demonista" -- term used by my brotha' when I go oh-so-baddy-bad-bad-gurl, I'd still choose Jesus Christ to be "my HIM" para safe, right? hehe! Just playin'. Basta, it's not about being a psycho-obssessed-YFC-person.          ...I don't believe in love at first sight you know, i believe in taking a deeper look..... üüüüüüüüü   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so empty inside.. That's what I am now that this jam-packed day has already come to a close. I'm so damned tired that I simply want to just lay in my bed with my arms and legs spread across my abode's breadth. But of course, I can't do that because in life, slacking off is a sin. Therefore, I need to do something just to satisfy the psychological need of defeating idleness. But what happened today that made a twisted “girl” twirl? 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Adventure-ing    Grabe! Woke up 5 in the morning because of excitement. Not knowing that it's a long trip, we still went to the resort. I was with Alex and my dad who's driving our Revo. Haay..we thought we got lost, yun pala, straight ahead...Straight ahead? Eh, there's like two roads, good thing we made daan in the right "lubak-lubak" road noh.     Welcome to God's Love Farm Resort    Nice place. It's colder that what I thought. No signal. Now, how can I text the love of my life if there's no signal? We arrived there 9. And we were waiting for Ate Raine and company. No HS Based Ateneans came. Even Kuya Pao didn't come..darn!     Happy Birthday to you dear friend!    Yehey! It's Juan Antonio Maningat AKA Tonico's birthday today! Whew! Assumption pa toh ah! Yehey! We're of the same age na! But still, I look older. Is it my fault that I need to take Stresstabs? And is it my fault that he's a baby-faced "man"? Yeah, you read that right. Man. Grabe! Love namin yang si "Taquitos"! Haha!      We called him up using my phone and Alex was like kilig talaga! Then after greeting him, we simultaneously said good-bye to him [with a 1-2-3 pa]. Tapos, Alex got bangag after we greeted him! Haha! We were making pa-trip Alex. Hay..Alex is tripping...I feel it....hehe!     The New Guy    There's this guy [na naman?]...he's gwapo. From Claret. He looks a bit like my best friend's ex. Hay! Cutie!His name is James and he's in 3rd yr. Basta yun. That's all I know about him. Tapos nung mass, kaharap namin sya! Todo kilig na naman ako at that time! Tapos when we were asked to stand up [btw, it's so hard to stand up when you're in an indian sit] I got up first, tapos I stared at James kasi I can't really resist his luscious lips [yuck! haha!] kidding aside. Tapos napatingin siya sa akin, so na-feel siguro niya na-crush ko nga siya. Darn! Why didn't I made iwas my head nung tumingin siya eh!!! Tapos nung Our Father, kaharap ko talaga siya! Tapos I heard him singing! Haay...LALAKE KA!     this fucking gay....CARLO...   hay! may putang ina na bakla!! kasama namin nung mass!! di ako maka-concentrate sa mass coz she...ay...i mean he pala was so papansin and so ingay!!! fuck that devil to hell! tapos nung communion he said "dun tayo tumabi sa mga gwapo" then i made turo james and carlo was like "yuck ha!" yuck?! yuck?! sinong mas yuck sa atin ha?! at least ako di ako malandi!! lintik ka!!!! tapos nung after communion kinalabit niya ng kinalabit si JAMES!!!!!! tapos nairita si JAMES!! THANK GOD TALAGA!!! and carlo made an issue na bagay daw kami nung isang guy na mataba!!!! tang ina nya!! tapos carlo made another issue about me and JAMES!! at that time, i started liking CARLO! hahahaa! thanks carlo for making an issue about me and JAMES!!!     ~: oh dear JAMES....üüü :~  
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        schooL fiRst...    oh yeah! i went to school kanina pare! and what a mass, damn! was that a mass? some weren't participating and some 3rd yr weren't supporting the choir. they were just laughing because a loud and unprofessional singing voice was heard. tapos our dear principal, Ms. Cruz had a heart-to-heart talk with us HS students. and during a serious [a bit funny, though] talk, the funniest thing happened. there were about 5 girls running towards the gym and Ms. Cruz was counting up to....i dunno. then a friend of mine who was also running just fell flat on the floor! damn! and to think, everybody was looking at her! sooooo embarassing!!!!!       A SERIOUS MATTER: KANSER    wuhoooooo! i watched Noli! it's super saya! there was this actor pa nga whose name is Marcus Madrigal as Elias. and what a good Elias he was! damn! he's fine! heheheh! good thing nga it's not wowie de guzman. naku! i think i've seen him in some plays for the nth time! damn! i'm just so happy he's not in Noli.       tapos when we went to our seat, we saw Michelle Madrigal from Star Circle Quest, Jade Lopez from Starstruck, Pia Romero and Pauleen Luna. grabe! bigla na lang sila dinumog ng sangkatauhan! hehhe! not really! basta dinumog sila!      we were having fun and all until....   i saw this guy from a "jolog" [pero i think they're jolog just because they act like skwakwa people but their phones are nice.] school. haaaayyy...he's so cute talaga! he's mestizo, a bit chinito, a bit chubby. basta he looks a bit like my best friend's ex. He was wearing this black jacket. haaayyy...we were looking at each other...[nangarap na naman ako. but it's oh so true.]. syempre, di maiiwasang ngumiti. so yun! hahaha! i was smiling the whole time!      ayun, we went home na. tapos nakatapat namin yung bus nung guy na naka-black jacket!!!! damn!!! he opened his window then half of his body nakalabas!  yun. he looked stupid, but CUTE! Ting decided to call him PAPA BJ. Black Jacket. Get it? heheh!       ~: PAPA BJ PAPA BJ PAPA BJ PAPA BJ PAPA BJ PAPA BJ PAPA BJ PAPA BJ PAPA BJ PAPA BJ PAPA BJ :~        
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      thank God!  gonna go to school tomorrow. kinda feeling a bit crappy.  a little redness na lang and a bit itchy. but i insist going to schoool. doi! tomorrow will be the induction of leaders! and like i need to be there. and tomorrow's the play ng Noli! i can't miss it! it's like missing meals worth 5 days! i'd rather miss eating meals worth a week than not to watch noli noh!   ~: haayy...ang tagal niya dumating sa mIRC....:~
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         This is one of my favorite YFC Songs...It's astigin kasi eh. Anyway, here's the lyrics.  
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      oh yeah, i'm still absent. crap. i've missed 2 days of my education, and that's like 1/5 of my life!!!! maybe i'm just over reacting but it's gonna be our exams next week! how the hell am i gonna cope up with the new lessons! damnit! i'm gonna go back to school on friday. i'm just excited to go back to school!  every night, i pray to dear Lord that may He take off all the redness in my eyes...is that right? see what sore eyes is making me say?!  grabe, i even made hawa my yaya.  everything is so messed up right now just because of my stupid sickness!  ~: everythin's fuckin' messed up right now. so pack all your bags and leave me now :~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
           growing up     young versus old.   first crushes and first kisses..   barkadas and barkada wars..   love letters and n-millionth break ups..   term papers and book reports.   job hunting and jobs..   babies and weddings..   and now, more than ever, the order gets jumbled up in really insane ways!    ~: i don't want to grow up. please take me with you peter pan!!!! :~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        hoy! pinoy ako!        Thanks to bamboo for the pinoy pride song that makes everyone proud to be pinoy. When I was at the mega camp, the pa system played "noypi". Without any planning or prodding, the whole camp broke into chorus to the highest decibel levels..... "hoy!! pinoy akooo!"   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        hallur!     heya guys! this is something new. i'm so sorry to those who are reading my blogspot na yung URL is  urlLink http://ohmygoditsrianne.blogspot.com . I had to delete it because may problems and stuffs like that dun eh. I didn't really want to delete it talaga!          i'm...     hi everyone! i'm a junior from one of the best high schools in the Philippines. hehe! enough said...sorry, i'm just sad...      what a dilemma...     i'm so sad..bakit naman ganito kasi...sayang yung mga pinost ko na blogs!!! damnit! sana my dear nemesis din will have this problem too. haha! badd guurrll...bad meeee...        
     

    
</post>


</Blog>