<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I had dinner first with Nins, Anne and Mich in Good Earth then met up with the rest of our friends in Greenbelt. We don't usually go out that much anymore...I mean unlike our college days when every saturday meant being totally dressed and getting hyper to enter either Ponti or Pravda....gosh we even used to line up just to get in Pravda.  Nowadays...its like where are all the people we know....the crowd gets younger and younger all the time we attempt to go to the "happening places". hehe :)  But at times like these we dont really care who we see...coz we have a blast by just drinking and making kwentuhan.  Coz unlike college we don't see everyone as often as we used to anymore...so everytime we have a chance to be complete (with the exception of Cat and Ceds last night) its really noisy...there's always so much to laugh and talk about.  Some pics from last night.....   urlLink       I love the strawberry daiquiri in Segafredo!!!   urlLink      We asked the waiter to take our picture and all of a sudden he said "CHEESE" in a really loud and funny way...laugh trip...obvious ba...anne?! hehe    urlLink      
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got home from what was suppose to be just dinner ar Niña's house.  But whenever me and Anne are there its never just that....its a neverending kwentuhan of everything from the little everyday things to our dream vacation ideas...which is most often than not done over our favorite "steady" drink...Alize! :)  Tonight's topic however was mainly on reminiscing our 2-month-long-after-grad vacation in the States!!!  The three of us spent about a little less than 2 weeks together in New York.  It was the  funnest . :)   Found some pics in my pc....   urlLink    Me, Anne and Nins with Lou and Arv at the NBA store.   urlLink    Us again...   urlLink    at the Disney Store :)  Me and Anne spent the rest of the two months in California and of course a visit to our long lost friend, Tit in Missouri. This can take forever to talk about...we did so much, saw so much, and most of all experienced a lot of things that we will remember and laugh about forever.  All these stories and experiences led us to make a pact...in 2006 (wishful thinking but is a goal we'll work hard to achieve), the three of us will go on a cruise around Asia with side trips to Singapore and HK for shopping of course!!! :)  Its really fun to talk about things like this, I really hope it pushes through!  Travelling with friends is so fun...you all pretend to be mature adults...no parents!! :)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I never thought i'd have one of these but since i'm not doing much then what the heck?! To mar and bern....add me to your list but i'm sure you won't   stalk   me haha! I'm trying to figure out how to post pics, but then again we haven't had new pics taken that recently.   Hey i just finished reading "Can you keep a secret?" by Sophie Kinsella and its nice....guess where I got that idea from....basta one from our regular list hehe :) The fourth book of the Shopaholic series is out already but only the hard bound copy coz the paperback will only be released next year.  That's it for now...I honestly don't know whatelse to say...maybe tomorrow. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I've been a bum for a little over 6 months now...which probably makes me a certified bum already haha!! Its been fun...Ive never had so much time to myself...I get to go to the gym and attend any class I want just as long as I'm not tamad, I get to have lunch with my friends who are working without worrying about getting back to work, I get to go gimik on weeknights and drink a lot coz I don't have to wake up early the next day...which brings me to one more thing I enjoy the most...I wake up at around 10:30 every single day. Another thing I've been able to do in the 6 months was to READ READ READ para naman my brain wont get idle diba? Ive never really liked reading but now I love to read.      I've read the Shopaholic series: Confessions, Takes Mnahattan, Ties the Not and the newest addition .... Shopaholic and Sister.      urlLink       This book makes you wish Sophie Kinsella writes the next book faster...kakabitin!!! Its so entertaining...so light but so many lessons to learn too...like NOT TO BE SO OBSESSED with shopping :) Becky Bloomwood gets so irritating sometimes...gosh just a little self-control could make her life easier. Aren't we all victims of shopping escapades...its a girl thing we can't get enough...but hello ending up with 5 coffee tables..how useless?! Ok enough about her shopping....I loved what they did for their honeymoon though...10 months going around the world with the person you'll spend the rest of your life with, the one you love the most in the whole world....WOW how romantic...that's like an exxageration of wanting quality time hehe! :)    urlLink         The next book I read was The Alchemist by Paolo Coehlo. Actually I read this 2 years ago when I graduated from college. My best friend, Anne,   gave it to me for my birthday....it was also sooo timing coz we were about to graduate. You know when you are at the crossroads of life and you read this....it makes you think even more...waaah kaka sira ng ulo hehe! Well anyway I read it again coz once again I think Im at a crossroad in my life....more of a quarter life crisis ata. Ive been a bum long enough and it has come to me that Ive had enough I wanna work again and get my life back on track but I realized its not as easy as that. This time as I read the book again...I highlighted the theories and ideas that really struck me. The one I love the most was: "When you want something, all the universe conspires to help you achieve it." It was repeated all throughout the book. Its so nice to think that if somethings meant to be then its meant to be...so ideal but makes so much sense. Another was: "Remember that wherever your heart is, there you will find your treasure." Hmmm...i guess the hard part is figuring out what it is you really like..what you're really passionate about. That's why I think I'm in a quarter life crisis...haven't found that in my life yet. I hope soon though :)       The last book I've just read was Tuesdays with Morrie. Its been recommended to me a million times and a long long time ago but like I said I never really liked reading. I'm glad I got to read it though. Such a sad story but so much ideas that makes you think about the life you're leading. Morrie said it well when he said: "Once you learn how to die, you learn how to live." It's so sad isnt it...but all life changing events happen after going through a near death experience. We are more often than not so caught up with success and the bigger picture rather than appreciating the small everyday experiences. Or we often wait till its to late to show someone they matter a lot....the most important things are always taken for granted. Oh and gosh I hope no one will ever suffer from the sickness Morrie had...amyotrophic lateral sclerosis... it eats you alive and the worse part is, it happens little by little making the suffering so unbearable for sometime until you drown to death coz it has taken your lungs already.  
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Happy 2nd Anniv to our "dream" States Adventure Vacation Trip!!!!      Today two years ago, Anne and I got on a plane and started our 2-month-US-adventure grad gift. I felt like an adult...independence galore!!! Our first stop was California.  We stayed at my titas place and just went around.  Thanks to Lei, my sis for driving us around.  Shame on us older pa naman kami but she wouldnt let us drive since we didnt have daw insurance in the the states!! Hay anu ba yun?! But was cool no hassle...most of the time we were sleeping in the car.  After a week we were off to New York.  Met Nins in the airport then we stayed in the extra apartment of Anne's tito.  We got more independence here than in Cali...which was better since we could get around on our own diba! The highlight of the trip.....Niña missed her flight...yey she stayed longer...what was suppose to be 5 days became almost two weeks, she left a day before we left for the third and last leg of our trip...Missouri?! The land of our long lost friend...Tit!!! This is where our month long trip got extended to 2 months.  We wanted to get a job...but by the second week of our 3 week stay there we got homesick (ok anne got homesick first then i got hawa) hehe di rin pala namin kaya so we came back October 3. Talk about 3 weeks of eating our every single night...I think we tried all cuisines na...Thanks tit and kuya we had a blast! Till next time....Tit ready the credit card haha joke lang! Come home and visit na kasi so it'll be our turn! :)  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>