<Blog>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mom is here to save the week but as I am finding out the change of life is not very good to her.  Last night she not only had two fans on in the room but insisted on opening both windows to let the room get to a bone chilling 35 degrees and yet she still got up in the middle of the night to fan herself off from night sweats.  Is this what we have to look forward to!!
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it's been less than 8 hours and the queenbee has blogged 3 times and commented on everyone's page. I do believe she now understands why we have kept her in the dark for so long!! Welcome Queenbee, welcome. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Jen and I were clerks at a department store, we had the beehive hair and funky glasses chewing gum and talking about something then out of the blue a stranger with exceptional good looks came to my counter to purchase something.&nbsp; I looked deep into his eyes and he said "mommy I have to Pee"...what???? Then I realized it was just a dream and standing next to me with big blue eyes was Kylee, mommy I have to pee wake up.&nbsp; So I get out of bed, hoping that I can return to my dream, but that would just be to easy.&nbsp; Kylee decided that 2:30 was an acceptable time to wake up and stay awake for the rest of the night.&nbsp; Bart and I battled with her from 2:30 until finally at 4:45 Bart lost his cool, started yelling and cursing and slamming doors.&nbsp; It was an ugly sight but it worked.&nbsp; I think he scared Kylee half to death and she was to afraid to continue on with the fit of rage she was having for the past 2 hours so she just decided to go back to sleep.  Bart never did go back to sleep, me on the other hand was fast asleep before he returned from his mission.&nbsp; I went to get the kid up this morning and she told me she wasn't ready to get up and I needed to go away so she can get some sleep.&nbsp; I found this to be quite humorous and dressed her while she lay in her bed and moaned about how tired she was.&nbsp; Hair was a mess, teeth not brushed but I picked her up carried her to the car and brought her to daycare.&nbsp; She walked in, went to a corner of the room put her blanket on the floor and went back to sleep, I don't think I was even out of the room and she was snoring.&nbsp;   Ahh the good life, I once asked someone when will I finally be able to sleep through the night and the response was 5 years.&nbsp; I shook that off, there is no way that could be true.....I guess I was wrong.            
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I will have to tell anyone that is planning a trip to Sunny Orlando Florida in the middle of July not to go.&nbsp; 108 degrees and humid as hell, not the best place to be when you are 7 months pregnant or have a 2 year old.&nbsp; We had all of these great plans set up for Kylee to do, Sea World, Disney etc, we were going to have fun and spoil her rotten as the next trip to Florida there will be two&nbsp;Stanphill girls and not just one.&nbsp; But because of the heat we only made it to the&nbsp;back yard pool of Grandma and&nbsp;Poppie Stanphills house.&nbsp; Imagine a hyper kid like Kylee trapped in a small house for 5 full days...not a pretty picture.&nbsp; By Friday everyone's tempers were hot, Grandma Stanphill felt it necessary to insult me then storm out of the house like a 3 year old child but not before I got a few good ones in...good to be pregnant can blame the hormones on everything.&nbsp;   I have been trying to write this blog all day but as I re-cap on our 10 day stay in Florida I can't think of one exciting or even funny thing that happened.&nbsp; Kylee was a total Bitch, that was pretty funny but other than that it was a very boring trip.&nbsp; Sorry kids I guess the stories just are not as fun when there is no alcohol involved.             
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So we have the great vacation planned for this weekend and into next week.  Dear old hubby just called to inform me that 3 of the 5 days will be spent without him.  Ughhh what am I going to do with mother and sister-in-law for 3 full days!!! His boss is in the hot chair and is about to be terminated, Bart is next in line so although it hasn't been said it has been hinted that he will take over the plant once they get rid of the dead beat that is there now.  The area manager just called him and informed him of a meeting they want him to go to in South Carolina, he will leave Monday night, and fly back either late Tuesday or early Wednesday morning, we leave for home on Wednesday!! I swear I think he hates me.  Now I am going to have to listen to the preaching of mom-in-law of how I need to raise my second child as I have not listened to a single thing she said about #1 and it gets under her skin.  I am going to have to suffer through hours of bad advise and ridicule about how I could drop my child off at daycare every day blah blah balh blah...Calgone take me away!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am proud of myself.  I went to the pool this weekend at 7 months pregnant and still managed to look better than some of the un-pregnant women there.  My darling husband even made the comment that even with a skirt pregnancy bathing suit on with a popped out belly and big boobies I still looked better than most of the women sunning themselves. And of course Kylee received many compliments on her little boy short bikini I swear this little girl is the definition of pretty!!!  I just though I would tell you about this since this was the only pretty thing that happened to me this weekend.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I think I have finally seen it all. I can officially say I do not like Ohio anymore.  When we moved out here my husband decided he would build me a cute little house in a very nice neighborhood to keep me happy.  This has worked up until now, the house has been invaded and I no longer want to live there!!!  I had gotten word that here were "some" dead worms in the basement that came in through a crack in the basement floor.  My husband assured me there was nothing to worry about and he would take care of the problem.  I of course believed him and have moved on with other things.  Well last night I decided I would go and get some of Kylee's old stuff to get ready for the new baby and to my horror the "some" worms turned into HUNDREDS!!!!  What the hell has he been doing down there, why didn't he take care of the problem when he said he would?  Is it possible he will never do anything about them?  Should I just put on a space suit and clean them up myself, or should I make him do it since he was the one who let it go for so long?    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The people that live across the street from me are strange.  I was outside playing with Kylee, as I usually do, and my neighbor was cutting his grass.  One of his daughters came running out of the house wanting to walk with her daddy, he took her by the hand and walked her straight over to my house and told her to play with Kylee, never once did he ask me if I would watch her.  Anyway so I made some room for her at Kylee's water table and let the two of them play, next the oldest girl (4) comes running out and the same thing happens.  So now I have these two girls, that are not mine, playing with Kylee's stuff.  At this point Kylee is bored and wants to go in I told her we had to wait for the girls dad to come back before we could go in.  An hour later he finishes the lawn comes over gets the girls and walks away....what the hell was that about? 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it's been 4 days and I have been so busy at work that I have not had a chance to post anything. So here is my breakdown of the week Monday - battle with Kylee, break a nail, 30 minutes late for work leave 15 minutes early simply because I just don't care anymore Tuesday - daily morning battle with Kylee, this one was really fun. Broke another nail..damn, went for my 32 week check up was told I might have gallstones and needed an ultrasound to make sure all was fine with me and baby. Husband decided to start playing rugby again and didn't get home until 8:30 at night...Could have used a little help with Bart Jr. Oh and still have not gotten to sleep through the night because of Kylee's overactive bladder and fear of sleeping in her room alone. Wed - Again, deal with Kylee and her "Princess Mood". Went to ultrasound, saw little Sasha that was very, very cool. No gallstones just a very active baby kicking the crap out of me, came to the office, talked all day did nothing, got caught. Got a wake up call at 12:00, mommy I got to go potty, 3:00 mommy I can't find my stool...what???? 4:40am, mommy where's daddy?? Enough child please sleep through the night already!!!! Then there is today Thursday, closed a couple $20,000 deals in France and India feeling pretty good about the day and have decided to take a breather. Oh yea and battled with Kylee and broke another nail...damn again!! When is someone coming out to visit me again, someone's got to get that child of mine under control because I am to tired to do it and Bart is to sore to do anything. There should be a law against a 37 year old man playing Rugby. Bless his little heart. Last but not least I have been reminded, once again, that my birthday is upon me and I will no longer be in my 20's. The thought of 30 is more than I can handle at the moment and the fact that I will not be able to party in style is yet another downfall to the big day. I think I will sit on the couch, eat icecream and pray to the sleeping gods that my little girl will actually make it through the night without the routine 3 trips to my bedside. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need your help. I have a friend at work that has been battling depression, knee surgery and back surgery. We have already come to the conclusion she is absolutely addicted to the pain killers the doctors keep giving her (oxycotton) . This is one problem but not the worst as she will have to be on these the rest of her life. The big problem is her massive weight gain in the past 5 months. She has put on at least 30 if not 40 pounds putting her at close to 80 or even 100 pounds overweight. Because of this her depression has become worse, the pain in her back and knee have become worse and I am concerned about her health. She is a wonderful person and I want to be able to help her as everyone in her family just calls her fat and moves on but no one takes the time to really give her some advise to follow. Now I have never had this type of problem so it is all new to me, any advise would help.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I not pretty, I a princess. Sorry Laura I have been trying but she won't budge. She insists that she is a princess or sometimes I will get "I is beautiful and I have beautiful hair" You can't really argue with her on that one. We got her hair cut, about 4 inches off, so now her hair is shoulder length and she absolutely will not wear it up anymore. She says she looks better with her hair down...again who am I to argue with that. I can't stand her, what a lover!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      10 - It's way to Far 9 - My boss is a ass, loves to pick on me because I am from Jersey and not Ohio 8 - They pay me nothing, so I pretty much do nothing 7 - They take as many sales away from me as possible and give them to other sales people to make them happy 8 - Did I say my boss is an ass??? 7 - No one here likes what they do so everyone is always unhappy 6 - There are no pretty people that work here - except for the intern and his last day is Friday 5 - The vacation Nazi has been on my case all week, I just might slap her 4 - We have the overweight, unhappy snitch that loves to listen in on everyone's conversations then go and tell the boss 3 - Getting in trouble for talking to the receptionist (3rd grade stuff) 2 - The VP is ALWAYS here and loves to look through all of the paperwork you have on your desk on even in your desk and the #1 reason I really can't stand working here is - The VP is always touching himself and adjusting the privates right infront of me...yuck!!!  8 more weeks until Freedom!!! 
     

    
</post>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Laura, this post is for you for being such a great friend, sister and roommate.   #10)  She goes grocery shopping with me then arranges all the food in pantry by size and substance so they are easy to find.  #9)  She takes care of the Dog when I'm late coming home or have to go away for the day.   #8)  She keeps me company when John is doing man things in the garage.   #7)  She makes we watch cheesy soap operas but turns them into drinking games to make them more interesting.   #6)  She comes with a whole differant wardrobe & a large supply of books, movies and beauty supplies that I can borrow at any time.    #5) She buys dinner when I don't feel like cooking & goes to pick it up.   #4) She always does the dishes  #3) She goes shopping for herself and brings home little presents for me (and sometimes the cats, dog and John too)  #2) If I'm not feeling well, she makes me a bed on her couch, makes me some soup, pops in a movie and rubs my head, feet or back.   And the #1 reason why I love living with Laura is.....  She always makes me feel pretty, even when she catches me napping with my mouth hanging open and a little drool coming out.   Thanks Laura, your the best!!!   
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thanks for the e-mail Laura. The next Harry Potter Book will be called "Harry Potter and The Half Blood Prince". No word on when it will be released. I wonder who the half blood prince is? Lord Voldermort or someone new??? Lord V is a mudblood right? BTW - how did Tom Riddle get into Slytherin if he's a mudblood, I thought they only took pure bloods. That is a question that has always weighed heavily on my mind. Oh that Harry, what will he do next? 
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Men are gross. They proudly share toilet stories, participate in belching or farting competitions. They feel the need to show others a particularly gory picture that they found over the internet, or an extremely perverted one.  Take my husband for example. He is the king of toilet humor. He also tips the scales as the most disgusting belcher, often bringing up more then just a burp which I always have to clean off of him because he does this while driving. So why is that the smallest of things can really gross him out. Like the time I stayed home from work b/c I had the flu. I drag my sick ass down the stairs around noon to search for some gingerale and to my horror I find a pile of cat shit on the couch and a pile of puke on the chair. So I call my husband to find out what the hell happened and it turns out that he accidentally closed the door to the cat boxes so the cat shit on the couch which grossed him out so he puked on the chair. Then he decides that he is too grossed out to clean it up so he leaves it for the poor wife who is delirious with 103 fever. Thanks dear.   And they call us the fairer sex, go figure.
      
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What is up with Stalkers? I mean, I know that I'm pretty and people want to be around me but really, can't you guys take a hint. Take Nick for example, here is a guy (kid really he's only 23) who once went out with a friend of mine, she dumped him because he was a mamma's boy and a snooze and now he's bothering me. Why, you might ask, well I'm not really sure. I recently saw him at a wedding and spend most of night avoiding him until he showed up at my hotel room later that night with 3 bottles of champagne. My husbands plan was to beat him up and steal the bottles of champagne but since he is a friend of my sister, I couldn't let him do that. Anyway, he spends most of night trashing my friend and trying to hit on my sister in law while my husband and sis-in-law's date just open fire on the guy and verabally abuse the hell out of him. Did he take the hint, noooooo, he came back in the morning to give us his business card so we can call him. Of coarse, we don't call him although we do contemplate signing him up for bed wetters anonymous. Anyway, that was 2 weeks ago, today I get an e-mail from him inviting us (and Laura of coarse) out on his boat. First of all, how the hell did he get my e-mail address!?! Second of all, if I get stuck on a boat with this kid, he's going overboard.  Go Away, Stalker!!! 
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My dog is big. Really Big. He just turned 1 and he weighs approx. 165lbs. His head is 3x's the size of mine & easily rests on my hip when I'm standing (I'm 5'7"). He will top out at 230lbs when all is said and done.   My dog is gross. Really Gross. He farts, snorts, burps, snores, wheezes, drools, foams and leaks drippy white stuff from his yoohoo (even though he is fixed). I have brown slime on my floors, walls, ceiling, funiture, clothes and car.   My dog is stupid. Really Stupid. I threw him in the lake and he sunk like a stone. He didn't even try to swim! His ass was bobbing up and down on the surface while his head was completely submerged. I had to jump in to save him.   I love my dog. My dog loves me. That's all that really matters. 
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is what is going to make me rich so that I can stop sitting in traffic 3 hours a day to go to a job I used to like but has since sucked the life and joy out of me. A book written by me and Laura teaching people how to be pretty. It's a fairly simple concept. If you belive you are pretty, then you are, no matter what the rest of the world thinks of you. I think the number one rule to being pretty is to always have someone to help you when you don't feel pretty. For example: I got pulled over and the cop gave me a ticket. I went home to Laura and told her that I didn't feel pretty because the cop didn't let me go. Her reply: "He must have been a real dork in High School and he had a crush on a pretty girl that looked just like you, he asked her out and she broke his heart. Now he is bitter and resentful seeking his revenge by pulling over pretty girls and giving them tickets." Thank you Laura, I feel pretty agian!!   So keep your eye out for this book, Laura and I will work hard on it so that all women can be as pretty as us. Well, maybe not AS pretty but close enough. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      OK people, I'm taking down the Out Of Order sign. Not because my computer is fixed but because I simply can't stand not blogging. The overwhelming desire to share my every thought has far surpassed any technological inconvenience I have to endure.&nbsp;&nbsp;I have decided to share just a portion of last night with you all. Last night was not a special night, nothing out of the ordinary happened, it was just an average night at Casa de Pretty and it went something like this......   It was pouring rain when Laura and I simultaneously pulled into the driveway around 6pm. We work 5 minutes away from each other and usually arrive home around the same time, but for some reason never actually drive the&nbsp;hour+ commute&nbsp;&nbsp;together. Anyway, we go in to rescue Goof from his crate where he is patiently waiting with his&nbsp;bitch in&nbsp;his mouth and&nbsp;the tail going a mile a minute. After much coaxing he finally drops his bitch and heads out the door. Laura grabs a handicapped umbrella in a feeble attempt to keep dry while making the trek to the mailbox. Her attempt is wasted and she arrives back in the garage soaking wet and looking quite silly holding the twisted, half open, inside out&nbsp;device that was supposed to keep her dry.&nbsp;&nbsp;Guinness does his business in the rain then spends the next 10 minutes "Goofing" in the yard and trying to catch the water pouring&nbsp;from the drain.&nbsp;He then runs in the garage, lips dripping with&nbsp;slime and wipes his mouth on Laura's work pants.&nbsp;We dry the dog, spray him with febreeze and go in the house.&nbsp;   After slipping into something more comfortable, we meet in the kitchen to discuss dinner. Van Morrison is playing in the background and dinner plans are quickly forgotten as Laura & I decide to prance around the living room and sing for awhile.&nbsp; We take a break to get a drink, wine for me and captain and Ginger for Laura, before commencing with the dancing and singing. As 7:30pm approaches we discuss dinner once more. The man of the house should be home anytime now and we really should feed him since he worked late and will be hungry.&nbsp; Chicken and rice are on the menu tonight so we take out the chicken to defrost. This is followed by more dancing, singing and drinking. We also have many discussions about Dave, John, blogging, lesbians, porn, marriage, Guinness, the cats, the mighty girls,&nbsp;sex, drugs and rock and roll. 8pm rapidly approaches, dinner has not been started, John is not home yet&nbsp;and the dog needs to Goof again. By 8:30 the dog is &nbsp;freshly goofed and&nbsp; consuming his meal. We start our&nbsp;dinner just as John walks in the door and loudly announces that he had to work late and now feels like vacuuming the entire house. He is clearly drunk, I guess working late isn't so bad after all. The next 30 minutes are spent preparing dinner and discussing the phonetic alphabet. The clock strikes 9pm just as we are sitting down to grilled chicken, rice and creamed spinach (also know as Charley Sierra).   The next hour is spent eating, drinking, and cleaning&nbsp;with more dancing and singing. John&nbsp;is welding the vacuum like a pro but feels the need to stop every few minutes to suck the dogs lips into the vacuum hose. Laura and I, quite buzzed already, decide it would be fun if Laura walks on my back. I lie down on the living room floor with my head under the coffee table while Laura jumps on my back using the table for balance. She's quite skilled at the art of back walking and is soon digging her bunions into my sore muscles. Many grunts and moans escape me as she does this which greatly upsets the dog. He thinks that Laura is hurting his momma and lays down next to me with his head under the coffee table and big furry body pressed against mine. He then proceeds to whine and grunt while blowing farts at Laura in a&nbsp;half ass attempt to knock her off balance.&nbsp; We take a break to clear the air and let Laura stretch, apparently back walking is quite a workout for her.&nbsp; John finishes up the vacuuming and gets his back walked on which does not upset the dog at all.&nbsp; He then retires upstairs to "hang with mammers" which actually means that he is going to fall asleep on Laura's couch.&nbsp; Laura and I stay downstairs and after refreshing our drinks, settle in to an exciting episode of General Hospital. Goof is in rare form and is grunting and humping his bitch with a vengeance. Unfortunately for us, the more he humps the more he farts, and he is one horny bastard so the farts are just flying out of him. Laura and I decided to make the dog farting a drinking game and are soon throwing one back every 5 seconds. By the time GH is over the dog is spent and we are toasted. We say our goodnights (I think) and&nbsp;retire to our separate sleeping quarters. John has already found his way to the bedroom and is anxiously waiting&nbsp;for some "Sierra Lima" before&nbsp; allowing me to fall into a dream filled slumber.&nbsp;&nbsp;   That, my dear readers, is a typical night at Casa de Pretty.   &nbsp;    
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My computer sucks!! It is 11:00 am and I have been trying to check blogs all morning but my computer is refusing to cooperate.&nbsp; I fear that this may interfer greatly with my blogging.&nbsp; I am now working on the boss to purchase me a new computer so that I can be at my blogging best. I tried using John's computer but his office resides next the Indian guy's office and I was soon overpowered by the smell of curry and egg farts, not to mention the string of unintelligable jibberish coming from his direction.&nbsp;  So, it is with a heavy heart that I must declare this blog out of order for the time being.&nbsp; I hope to be up and running agian by the end of the week. If I can locate some kind of gas mask then I may attempt using hubbies office agian but&nbsp;I am in no hurry to&nbsp; subject&nbsp; myself to that kind of torture.&nbsp; For now, I bid you all a fond farewell, keep up the good blogs and remember to stay pretty!  
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a general message to all in the pretty club, You Are Pretty!!! I am leaving this message to you all because I will not be available via blog today. It's a sad day I know, but it must be done. There are several deadlines to meet today if I want to leave by 2pm to start my weekend&nbsp; at sleezeside early. On top of all my deadlines, I still have my little redheaded slave to boss around today so I will be&nbsp;very busy as I intend to make him do everything from&nbsp;rearranging my office furniture to getting my coffee. I am also considering teaching him the fine points of giving a woman a neck message but as he's only 14, I'm pretty sure I can be arrested for that. &nbsp;Anyway, I hope you all look and feel pretty today. Have a great weekend and I'll blog you all on Monday.   
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          Holy Crap, It's like I'm on crack or something. Not that I know what being on crack is like but I'm pretty sure it's something like this. Last night &nbsp;I decided to celebrate my b-day is style by doing way too many shots of tequila with one too many of everything else, you know the drill. Anyway, needless to say I was feeling a little tired this morning so I stopped at the gas station for a red bull. Nope, no red bulls, but they did have something called stacker 2 energy drink, so I figured why the hell not. Then, I decided to stop at Dunkin Donuts for an iced coffee with lots of suger, just the way I like it. This all went down around 8am, now at 10:15 I'm like freakin Bevis. I'm fairly certian that I've annoyed all my coworkers with endless unintelligable chatter. I've gotten out of my chair so many times that I'm starting to feel like I'm doing a buns of steel video. I want to run, I want to dance, I want to paint my office red. It's going to be rough when I come down in a couple of hours.&nbsp; Maybe I will go raid the principals office, he will have some liquid crack! I am the Great Cornholio!!!       
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          I only get better with age. Today, on the 27th eve of my birth, I'd like to take a moment to reflect on all the things I have accomplished in the last 26 years.  &nbsp; Age 0 - 10 years: Born in NH, moved to Idaho, moved to Texas, moved to upstate NY - became an expert packer.&nbsp; Never broke any bones (mine or anyone elses). Avoided being flushed down a toilet by my 2 evil stepsisters(he he). Mastered the art of blaming everything on my sisters and making them do most of the housework. Spent most of my time engaged in early morning G.I. Joe wars or dogging heavy spit fire from my sister, Denise.&nbsp; Spent the rest of the time annoying everyone else.  &nbsp; Age 11 - 15 years:&nbsp;&nbsp; Experienced extreme culture shock when we moved to Guido land, aka East Hanover, NJ. Spent way too much time teasing my hair and wearing stupid looking pants.&nbsp;Saw every episode of Beverly Hills 90210.&nbsp;Took dance lessons and made everyone I knew watch me shake my booty to&nbsp;the musical stylings of MC Hammer.&nbsp;&nbsp;Pranced around stage as big bird at my dance recital. Got my first dose of real heartbreak.  &nbsp; Age 16 - 18 years: Experienced culture shock agian when we moved to Newton, NJ and&nbsp;none of the boys were making out in&nbsp;the hallway. (It's a guido thing).&nbsp;Had a&nbsp;few identity issues&nbsp;but finally managed to find myself. Never got&nbsp;knocked up or arrested. &nbsp;Wore a size 2 dress to my prom. Graduated HS without repeating any grades. Made a few very good friends. Fell in love with one of my very good friends older brother.  &nbsp; Age 19 - 21years: Became an Auntie for the first time. Got engaged to the love of my life. Spent alot of time just hanging out and working. Planned a decent size wedding. Broke my back trying to break into John's bedroom window 2 weeks before my 21st b-day. Spent my 21st b-day in a body brace. Sued my future in laws for hurting myself on their property. Moved out of my parents house and into my first apartment with soon to be hubby.&nbsp; Married the love of my life and went on a very nice honeymoon, thanks to the before mentioned lawsuit.&nbsp; Became legal drinking age - yeah!  &nbsp; 22 - 26years: Moved out of apartment and into a nicer townhouse with new hubby. Spent alot of time drunk. Made some friends, lost some friends, and realized the true meaning of friendship. Managed to move up the corporate latter without the benefit of a college education. Became an Auntie agian. Built my dream home with my loving husband. Had some really really good times.  &nbsp; The last 12 months: Developed a stronger relationship with my sis-in-law when she moved in with us. Got a really really big dog. Didn't see my hubby for 4 months while he built&nbsp;Laura her room. Celebrated 5&nbsp;wonderful&nbsp;years of marriage. &nbsp;Became an Auntie for the 3rd time.&nbsp;Spent way too much time hyped up on hormones. Went on a fabulous&nbsp;vacation. Broke up with yet another&nbsp;set of friends. Realized how much prettier I am now then I was when I was a&nbsp;size 2 thanks to the pretty club.  &nbsp; The next 12 months: Only god can tell but I&nbsp;sure hope they are fun! Happy 27th B-day to me! &nbsp;      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, my neighbor the woman beater invited us to his house for a party. John wants to go for neighborhood politic reasons but I'm not so sure I want to go. The only time we ever hung out with this guy he got drunk (my fault) and punched a woman in the face (not my fault). Granted, she was big ugly butch "woman"  who probably out weighed him and she punched him first, but it still didn't make for a good first impression. Plus, he made it a point to tell me to wear my bathing suit so I think he just wants to see me in a bikini, not that I blame him, I do look stunning in a 2 piece. :-)   I really wouldn't mind the guy so much if he didn't apoligize every time I see him then make some really inappropriate comment or gesture, like raise his fist to me, that sort of thing. He's just wierd and I try not to hang out with wierd people, only pretty people. Any guy who names his daughter Treasure can't be right in the head. 
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It brings warm feeling to my heart when I think of all the pretty girls (and even some boys) out there who have been touched with the power of pretty because of the pretty club. Who knew it would be so popular? The terms "I feel pretty", "It was very pretty of me" and "Boys can be pretty too" have become a part of everyday conversation. I feel like we should be going to schools and teaching young people the power of pretty. The youth of America needs us. Think about all the eating disorders, teenage pregnancies and suicides we can prevent. Laura & I have already started recruiting new members to the pretty club. We have a mall date with two 8 year old girls on friday. We are teaching them confidence, positive self image, how to love and respect themselves, and most importantly, how to be pretty. Of course, we are also teaching them proper ways of dealing with the unpretty which I feel is a critical part of the training. Oh where was the pretty club when I was a skinny, akward looking teenager with low self esteem and little self confidence. I always new the pretty girl was inside me but I didn't actually meet her until after High School. Now that I have found her I will never let her go. Girls (and Dave) embrace your pretty self and feel the power that being pretty brings! 
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      4:00am Sunday July 11, 2004   Dear Diary, Dude, I can't sleep agian You Know. I took like 5 sleeping pills an hour ago with 1/2 a bottle of rum so it's only a matter of time before I pass out cold you know. I hope I can fall asleep because I only have one more pack of cigarettes to last me until morning & it will be really fucked up if I run out you know. I can't figure out what happened to all my cigarettes, just yesterday I bought a whole fucking carton and they are gone now. Dude, I wonder if like my kid is smoking them or something. Dude, that would be like so fucking cool if my 8 year old daughter smoked with me. At least I'd have someone to talk to you know. Dude, I can't wait until she gets a little older and starts hanging out with kids that do drugs so I can like raid their stash and shit, that will be so fucking cool you know, then I won't have to take all these sleeping pills you know. Well Dude, I'm going to try and get some sleep you know. I'll talk to you later. PW  4:30am Sunday July 11, 2004 Dear Diary, Dude, I'm like totally freaking out. The sleeping pills I took before aren't fucking working so I took 3 more, finished the bottle of rum and smoked my last cigarette. What am I going to do Dude, I don't have any more fucking cigarette's and the stores don't open for like 2 more hours. I'm going to go out to my car and see if I can find some butts to smoke.  PW   4:00am Monday July 12, 2004 Dear Diary, Dude, you won't believe what happened yesterday. After I wrote that, I went out to my car and found a whole other pack of cigarettes, I like totally forgot that I bought those, you know, it was like so cool. Anyway, I have to tell you something really fucked up. We went to the lake house to visit the Aunt and Uncle of those users that I wrote about and do you fucking believe that they were there!!! That is so fucked up, they knew we were going to be there and they had no business being at their own families house when we were going to be there you know. Dude, how fucked up is that? Anyway, I got back at them by totally ignoring them the whole time I was there. After they left, I told their Aunt and Uncle all this really bad stuff about them and some fucked up shit that they said and I think that I got the Aunt and Uncle on my side. Why wouldn't I, I mean, I'm the one who is painting their basement for them so they have to pick me over their own niece and nephew you know. Anyway, I'm feeling really good about the whole thing because I know it's only a matter of time before those users come crawling back to me apoligizing. Dude, I can't fucking wait, it gonna be so cool, you know. I'm sure I'll be writing all about it later. Until then, I'm just going to sit here and smoke and wait. Maybe I'll go do a whip it. Later Dude. PW 
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't feel well today. I'm not sick, I'm not hungover (that much anyway), I don't have my "friend"- No, what I have is so much worse then that. I suffer from a horrible affliction called mastiffgasitis. You see mastiffgasitis is a fairly common condition that affects just about anyone who enters my house. It's caused from sitting in a room filled with noxious mastiff gas for too long. Symptoms include nausea, gagging, dry heaves, watery eyes and the uncontrollable urge to call the dog an A-hole.  I woke up in the wee hours of the morning and hubby was gone from the bed, so was his pillow. As we hadn't gotten into a fight before bed I knew this could only mean one thing, the dog farted. I buried my head in the pillow and went back to sleep. I awoke hours later to a smell so rancid I thought maybe I'd died in my sleep and had gone to hell. Nope, turns out the dog farted again. Dry heaving, I ran from the bed and escorted the dog outside to rid his bowels of whatever evil thing had crawled in there and died. After his extraction, we went back in the house to wake up hubby who was sleeping in the guest bedroom. He got up, called the dog an A-hole and commented on the greenish hue that my skin had taken on during the night. I assured him that the problem had been taken care of and we went about our normal morning routine. 30 minutes later I left the bathroom, freshly showered and looking pretty now that my skin had returned to it's normal color. I was not prepared for the horrendous smell that assaulted me as I left my bedroom. Searching for the source, I soon found a disgusting pile of green poo smeared all over the welcome mat by the front door. Trying very hard to keep the OJ that I drank earlier in place I quickly picked up the welcome mat and stuffed it in a garbage bag. If it had been the most expensive mat in the world I don't think I would have tried to save it, luckily I got it from walmart so in the trash it went. Now, sitting at my desk hours later I still feel very nauseous and am dreading what may be waiting for me when I get home. All I can do at this point is nibble on saltines and pray. 
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      That is the song hubby started singing last night after Laura left to hang out with the new man she's been talking to. At first I thought he was hinting to me that I would be expected to perform the love since we had an evening alone. Then I realized exactly what he was singing. He was sitting at Ohmar belting out "If she falls in love tonight, it can be assumed, her carefree days with us are history, our trio's down to two"! Then he pretended to cry. (Like Pumba in the movie) Isn't that sweet? 
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As I sit at my desk and look at the ever increasing mound of paperwork, only one thought goes through my mind, blogging. It's a sickness really, an addiction that can only be satisfied by spending hours at a time reading and re-reading what my fellow bloggers are up to. Everything I do, see, hear or smell in life makes we want to blog about it. I want to tell the world that I got flipped off this morning because I cut off some fossil who was struggling for 20 minutes to get his head out of his ass but still couldn't see because he had shit in his eyes. Fuck you too blue hair, what the hell are you doing driving anyway? I want to blog about how stupid my dog is for sitting in a camp fire over the weekend and burning an inch off his tail thus making the 1/2 hour he spent trying to catch it last night all the more difficult. I want to blog about how funny Laura looked yesterday with her hand down her pants trying to locate the mosquito bite she thought she had on her ass after I told her I had one. It's like crack. I worry about not having anything interesting to say and missing out on my fix. I worry that one day I'll go too far and start blogging about things that I really shouldn't share with another living soal. Is there a cure? Do I really want to be cured? 
      
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      No, am NOT talking about housework, I am talking about getting rid of all the shit in life and letting go of people who make my life more complex. I've done it before and I'll most likely do it agian. There was the best friend in High School that slept over my house every night just so she could wear all my clothes, ride in my car and steal all my boyfriends. She was trash and I discarded as such. Then there were the "couple friends", the ones who would come over on a Friday night to hang out but wouldn't leave until Sunday evening when all the beer was gone and there was no food left in the house. The ones who would demand to know every detail of our lives just so they could broadcast to the rest of the world what we were doing and how it was wrong. The ones who felt the need to trash us behind our backs to whoever happened to be around, even if that person was hubby's own sister. Broke up with them at a bar, see ya. Most recently, we have hubby's best friends psycho wife. The girl I pretended to like just so that hubby could hang out with his buddy. This actually worked for a couple of years until psycho wife decided to make me her new best friend. The job description for being PW's best friend includes being able to sit in one room from 11pm to 6am & listen to her talk about the same thing over and over and over agian while she chain smokes 6 packs of cigarettes. One time, to keep from going insane, I tried to make "talking" to pw more interesting by taking a drink everytime she said the words "Dude", "You Know" or "Fuck". This actually worked b/c I got so drunk that I puked on her shoes and passed out cold less then 2 hours after starting this game. After that, I decided to cut the drinking game down to just "Dude" which still enabled me to get drunk enough to pass out on her without actually blowing chunks. After putting up with this and other pycho behaviour that I won't mention here, I come to find out that she has been talking shit about me to my hubby's aunt. Apparently, I didn't appreciate her and she thought I was rude for not staying up all night 4 times a week to listen to her babble while she tried to slowly kill me through second hand smoke. So, in light of recent events and in the interest of keeping my liver and lungs intact, I have once agian decided to give the old heave hoe. Goodbye pycho wife, you will not be missed but the smell of smoke in my basement will linger forever. 
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I brought Guinness to work with me today because my boss isn't here and it's half a day anyway. He's being really good except he keeps blowing farts at me and it's really stuffy in here & I have no window. Luckly my receptionist had a coconut candle that is trying it's hardest to mask the smell but not doing a very good job. All my co-workers are in love with him and have forgiven him for sliming up thier work pants, it's a casual office anyway. I just hope the fed ex guy doesn't come walking in with packages in his hands, Goof doesn't like it when people come toward me holding stuff. That is how the whole dragging incident happened in the first place. BTW - I went to doctor yesterday and my ankle really is infected, stupid dog. I'll just have to be careful not to go in the lake tonight, it's firework night. Good thing John installed that toliet on the sailboat or else I'd be screwed.  Well, I hope everyone has a great 4th of July, it really is the best holiday of the year. 
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As most of you may know, Laura is getting me a tattoo on the small of my back for my 27th b-day. In her attempt to explain how it would feel, she came at me last night with a steak knife and told me to "bend over". Thanks Laura but I think I'll wait for the real deal. I don't really need you to stab me in the back with a steak knife, I actually have a tattoo & know what it feels like.  Anyway, I am trying to decide on what to get and have been looking into celtic designs. There are a few differant ones that I like but they are very detailed & I think I want something simple. Click on the link to see the Triquetra, it is an ancient celtic symbol for fertility and the power of 3. What do you think? http://www.irelandsown.net/triq.html
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear Fellow Bloggers,  I will not be blogging for the rest of the week due to the fact that I am taking a few mental wellness days away from work.  If anyone should be looking for me, I will at home slapping random colors on my walls with wild abandon in a desperate attempt to turn them from mental institution white to something more zen like.  John will also be taking a few days off although his peace keeping activity of choice will be digging gaping holes in the backyard with pieces of very large machinery. Wish us luck, I'm sure we will need it! 
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have this "friend" her real name is Flo but I used to call her Scarlet. I never really considered her much of a friend even though we used to spend several days every month together. She was always rude, pushy, demanding, moody, sloppy, and she smelled a little funky sometimes. I used to get stressed out when I knew she was coming for a visit because her constant nagging gave me a headache and usually made my face break out. She was so clingy that, when she did visit, she had to be with me 24/7. I couldn't even go to the bathroom without Scarlet up in my grill the whole time. My husband absolutley hated her and would avoid her like the plague. The problem is, she hasn't been visiting me lately and I'm starting to miss her. She's been with me every month since I was 13 and I feel a little lost without her. I don't really know what happened, she just stopped visiting one day. I kept on thinking that she would eventually come around so I continued to stalk up on all the supplies she always required , but she hasn't come and my cupboard is now overflowing.  Even hubby has noticed her absence and has stated his concern for her welfare. I contacted an investigater to help find her but so far they have no idea where she is. The gave me some special pills that they thought she couldn't resist (she really likes pills) but so far she still hasn't made an appearence. I'm worried that I may never see her agian. If anyone sees her could you please let her know that her old friend Jen is looking for her and that I miss her. Thanks. 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Because I'm being walked all over. Some of you may remember my ramblings about my crazy, pill popping, space cadet of a receptionist.  Well, she has done it to me agian. She approached me yesterday as I was leaving, hysterical crying (as always) saying that her boyfriend got last minute tickets to a Phish concert in PA and she REALLY had to go because it's a reunion tour and they probably won't ever play agian, blah blah blah, sob sob sob, whatever. Now, keep in mind that this girl is NEVER here yet we have been paying her for 40 hours a week since she started 2 1/2  years ago.  These are just some of the reasons why she hasn't been at work: Car Accident - 3 times Flat tire - Monday this week Phish Concert - Today Muffler fell off 2 weeks in Aruba- 3 times Panic Attack -  2 times Drug Rehab - 2 weeks Miscarriage Dog bite Family problems Boyfriend problems Stomach pains Headaches Flu - 5 times Cold - lost track Bump on leg (no joke, she thought it was a blood clot & was dying) Court - 2 times No Insurance &amp; can't drive to work (one week)  Not to mention the numerous times she had to leave early becuase she had doctors appts for her ADD, Ulcer, STD (negative), Blurred Vision, and most of the problems listed above.   She also really sucks at her job, she cost the company 4 million dollers b/c she was probably high and sent a really important bid to the wrong address even though the right address was highlighted and circled in black marker.  This girl is a piece of work, I really need to find a new receptionist    
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For all my fellow bloggers who have been waited with baited breath for me to post a new blog, please forgive me.  I currently have a strange man sitting at my desk looking through all my previous cookies as he tranfers all the useless info to a new computer. I can only hope that all the porn has been properly erased. I suppose it doesn't really matter since the only time I looked up porn at work was when my boss wanted to see the Paris Hilton video, what a waste of time that was. Anyway, I am currently sitting at John's computer while he is off doing something else and will try to sneak off periodically to check everyone's blogs. I can only hope that everyone stops coming in and saying stupid things like "Hey John, looks like you need a hair cut" or "John, when did you get so pretty" or "Wow John, I never knew you looked so good in that shade of pink". Whatever morons, it wasn't funny the first time you said it.  I'm a little moody today, can't you tell?   
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          The waxing last night was a success and David's back is now as smooth as a baby's behind. What a stud he was last night with not one, not two, but THREE hot chicks waxing his back. The evening starts out with a nice pasta dinner and a few shots of tequila. Next, Laura takes Dave upstairs for a back washing while Stacey and I heat up the wax. After his washing, we lay him out on the bed and start trimming the hair to a more acceptable length. Now it time for the waxing to start, I position myself on the left side while Laura gets the right. I spread a thin layer of wax on a small area, apply the strip, pull the skin taunt and 1,2,3 pull the strip off in one quick fluid motion. Then I apply a cold wash cloth to the area to relive the sting. Ahhhhh, that wasn't bad at all! Now it's Laura's turn. She slaps on a bit too much wax and spreads it around until the hairs are slowly and painfully being pulled out by the roots, then sticks the strip on and just rips it off with a flourish. OWWWWW! That stung a bit! OK, my turn agian.... 1,2,3 Ahhhh, not bad. Laura's turn.... RRRrip OWWWW, that freakin hurt, and this time there is blood. This pattern continues for awhile until I finally take pity on Dave and boot Laura out. She goes off to search for some booze and Stacey takes over her side. Stacey is doing a steller job and we manage to get most of his back done before the bottom falls out of Stacey's technique and she starts drawing blood. OK, your both banned now, I'll finish it myself. An hour later he is done and his back looks very red but very smooth. To top off the evening and sooth his tortured skin, Dave receives a back washing with an exfoliating sugar scrub from all 3 chicks, then some cooling aloe  applied by 6 pretty hands. Totally worth it!      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          Tonight's the night, my big date with fellow blogger and male pretty club member, Dave. What's that you say? A date? But Jen, your married and Dave is your sis-in-laws boyfriend!!! Not to worry dear bloggers, it's not what you think. While this date may involve lots of alcohol, removal of clothing, some sweating, a little hot wax and possibly some screaming, it's totally innocent I swear. Perhaps I should start from the beginning. Over the weekend I was witness to an event that had me second guessing Dave's membership in the pretty club. The event was shirtless Dave.  Was it the lack of breasts, you ask? Nooooo, we don't point fingers at little breasted club members because I really hate being pointed at. It was the hair on  Dave's  back that had me ouisting him from the club. Pretty club members just don't have hairy backs, it's simply not allowed. So, in order to insure his membership, Dave agreed to let me wax the offensive hair off. To prepare for this event, I went out last night and purchased the finest wax that Harmon's had to offer, then rushed home to find a subject to practice on. Hubby would not allow me anywhere near him. Even the promise of some "Sierra Lima" couldn't convince him to give up some leg hair, so I had to move on to someone else.  An inspection of Laura turned out to be a dead end as she proved to be quite smooth, although she did offer to let me use a bikini test area. Sorry Laura, I'm not hitting that my first time out of the gate, I'm thinking practice is in order before I'm ready for bikini area hair removal. Luckly, just as I was contemplating giving Rair a smaller set of pantaloons, my friend Stacy showed up and offered me her lip to practice on. I spread the hot wax on the little blond fuzz she called a moustach, rubbed the piece of cloth over it and just ripped away! It was actually quite fun and Stacy didn't even flinch. Of course, I'm pretty sure the baby fine hairs on her face came off easier then the hair nest on Dave's back will, but it was good practice just the same. So, wish me (and Dave) luck tonight, I'm sure it will be a story to tell tomorrow!      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
             I was talking to a friend the other day and she asked me how I liked my job. I answered with my usual response of "It blows, I don't want to do it anymore" in which I was expecting the normal reaction of "I know what you mean". Instead I got "So why are you still doing it"? Hmmmm, you know what, I don't really know. Maybe I'm scared to quite because I've been here so long and I'm comfortable. Perhaps it's because I work with my husband and I really enjoy spending all my time with him. It could be that I'd probably have to take a pay cut if I left and I don't want to give up any of the comforts that I'm accustomed to. Whatever the reason may be, that one little question has really got me thinking.  What would it be like to wake up on a Monday morning excited to start my day? What if I got to spend every day doing exactly what I wanted to do? What  would I choose to do If I could do anything I wanted? The sad part is that I don't even know.  If someone were to ask you what you wanted to be doing with the rest of your life, could you answer right away?  Would you still be happy doing it in 20 years? What would it be?        
</post>


</Blog>