<Blog>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Agar hai koi HARYANEY ka, to khoob Daba ke Khaney Ka, 
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To all,  Plzz make sure that no body make excuses now onwards, excuses dont serve the purpose what mwtters is only the + work, so guy and gals keep woring.
      
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Inovations is all encouraging new thoughts.so please keep encouring thoughts.
      
</post>


<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        My Business Exercise Romance/Adventure:-   Today I have been assigned a job of getting self employed and understand the retail business.  I was determined that I will not wander away to many shops for getting a job, The first shop I visited was a Dress material shop “Century Textile” whose owner is a  Mr. Dinesh (a Marwari). Firstly when I explained him the whole exercise I am interested in carrying out at his shop, he bluntly refused to assign me any such job and asked me not to waste his as well as mine time, but I was firm and tried to convince him by saying that if he can allow me then I am interested in coming back after an hour so that he can finish his monthly end financial cash records. There he got convinced and form that one hour I stood outside the shop on footpath and observe the movement of people on the footpath, it was 10 in the morning and mostly gents were outwitting ladies in strength, Funny thing is Business was moving very slow that time, as it become 11 am movement of ladies get increased and the clear cut picture shown on the sales from the showrooms. After and hour I approached Mr. Dinesh requested again, this time he assigned me with the Show room Manager Mr. Dhiren Sanghvi, he told me about the 50-50 % partnership between Mr. Dinesh and the Century Textile, the material being sent by Century Textile, Mumbai on consignment basis, and the showroom have to pay for the transportation  expenses. While giving a close look at Showroom, I found that the place was ample but there were no display of products, so suggested Mr. Dinesh for displaying Kurtas (there specialty). I interacted with customer’s came to the show room and helped in selling goods worth Rs.1,000/-. But found that Mr. Dinesh is a pakka Marwari and will not pay me the incentives later, but I had to take it somehow, I tried below mentioned tricks to take out money from him:-  1) At lunch I offered him to have lunch with me in a restaurant, so that he will at least pay the bill afterward, But he refused the proposal bluntly.  2) I prepared a farzi Business report and showed the showroom as one among the very best in the city, and there after I requested him to counter sign the report and also give some comment, he refused that too,  3) Finally at the time of leaving the showroom I said to him sir I worked for you for hours, so you will definitely like to pay me at least Rs.25/-, But friends instead of paying me he said, I gave you an chance to understand the business and therefore you should pay me instead of I to you, that was more then enough, but I was also determined and I tried 4th option of psychological pressure,   4) I said sir, if you are not paying me then its ok but if somehow somebody asked about it please say that you have paid me Rs.25/-, and gentlemen what happen next…………….  He immediately said no problem I helped you in the morning and now also I will help you, I will tell to your supervisors that I have paid you Rs.25/-, you need not worry, Take care, bye.  Business I learnt from him:-  1) If there are so many shops of a same commodity & you have planned to enter into it, then make sure that your brands is totally different from others,  2) Always try to capture centre point of market on the main road,  3) Try to avoid paying money as much as possible,    
    
</post>


<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My institute (SIMS) organising an Seminar "4Tghought" keeping an eye on Competitive Advantage in the business world. Our Guest of honour for the Seminar is Mr. Baba Kalyani, CMD, Bharat Forge.  Making this seminar a success SIMS is trying to reach almost all the corporate houses in the pune and our council members (2nd Year stdnt.) have formed a team of marketing executives, Me one among them.  Till now i have called so many corporates and found the  general view against attending it, reason being they are not focused and they cant even imagine that by attending such an event they can not only get an advantage in getting recognition  among the corporates but also in understastanding the need of the business. Sometime i may feel they are just  about to loose an great opportunity their way.  But some one has rightly said "some will remain peions and others excell them easily and be called as CEO of next generation".
    
</post>


</Blog>