<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok well i am just gonna dedicate this blog section to saturday nite cuz i figured i rant too much about my intellectual and spiritual wanderings but oh wellz...... okee well..i was gonna talk about saturday nite cuz I HAD the GREATEST time in such a long time...well it was a*n*e bday...we went to ESM @ Front St....and met d*m*y's bf and his friend... who apprently had some type of interst in me?..meh dunno he was a funny guy tho and we had a bit in common ..but oh well nothing will probably happen...any whoo..the food was great i had lasange..and 2 spicy ASS chicken wings...sat beside drama queen hung and princess...it was fun...princess was ahppy as anything and queen was jus gettin happ after braking up wiht that weird looking bird girl..its all good..had great convos and jokes..sat across from 'jax' and rey...hmmm jax seems to think shez in our little gorup thing cuz she was so possesive when i said i was gonna do something with trisha..but shez stupid..blah wahtever...chilled a bit..played with the condom machine in the bathroom..hmm and after wards pretending to be foreigners..and getting a free sketch from some artist psycho named robert burns because i am a 'beautiful chinese gurl' haha ..that was such an ego booster .. then stupid rey gettin mad for attracting psychos..stupid guy..hez jsu mad and depressed..whatever... ooh then we walked down to the skywalkk where a bunch of drunk whities were actin stupid..then we walked to lakeshore and to harborfront to see the fireworks...it sall good it was FUN....  Ok back to being cynical realist/pessimist... well i failed to be a good person again..went back to the old ways for a bit...but i kno i gotta be stronger than that...i am so easy and numble .. soo stupid..i am not open minded and won't except it at any level......i am so stupid...   the sunlight blinds my face as a i walk through a forest but something is a little bit different this time the path way seems to have accumulated more mud and humus  leeching out a foul but familiar unidentifiable smell the trees cool me off with their flappin leaves  and the grass looks like a cold treat ready for me to relax on  i keep on walking not knowing where i am going and soon i hit a bridge overlapping a pond it cuts off in the middle and leads to two seperate places: the beautiful yet materialized city and the peacefull and calm forest my feet begin to carry me to the middle of this bridge should i exit back into society..or stay with the genuine beauty of God?    hmm jsut a little free flow of mind..trying to improve on it but whatever..there is a lot of symbolism in this..so yeah...oh wellz nuff i with the ramblings i'm out..peace  [recovering]    
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        'No one who put his hand to the plow and looks back is fit for service in the kingdom of God.' (Luke 9:62)         Many people who are willing to follow Jesus nonetheless worry about future uncertainties, hence their faltering footsteps and mindless fellowship. Jesus does not change His tone in spite of their lack of security; in contrast, He emphasizes that He is not one who is too concerned with personal security. He says, 'Foxes have holes and birds of the air have nests, but the Son of Man has no place to lay his head.'     Jesus wants us to understnad that to be overly worried about everything is not beneficial to anyone at all, since this readily weakens the fervour of devotion to life. That is why He syas, 'No one who puts his hand to the plow and looks back is fit for service in the kingdom of God.' Jesus also says, 'Do not worry about tomorrow, for tomorrow will worry about itself. Each day ahs enought trouble of its own.'    Following the Lord requires courage, perseverance and trust in Him. when you are certain about the will of God, be not afraid; rather ,just follow Him one step at a time, work hard to go forward, and sucess shal never elude you.    DAMN..tht was freaking inspiring..actually it was sort of like the answer to a question I didn't ask but was sort of in my sub concious...well that whoel thing up there was sort of like one of those things that GOD purposely sent for me....But still heres the problem:  - I really don't have enuf faith at all to sometimes beleive that God sent me that for  me - I am too proud to admit to who I really like or to even stick up for things I know   that I as a Catholic have to defend - I have a SHITTY temper - I am a little bit insecure although people think I am so confident  - I am too secretive to really appreciate what real friendship can do for me - I am too realistic to really think outisde the box and have trust in GOD..  man the list goes on...but I PROMISE I will try to have more faith...cuz at the end of the day..thats all really got...  [faith]
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hmmph so i was staying up last nite doin my before the bed ritual and everytime i do sit there on my bed thinking..how in the world do u tell between ur OWN voice and what GOD is trying to tell you?....like man i tried it and i tricked myself SILLY doing it by beleiving what i was hearing was really GOD when it was really me trying to do what I wanted..which was a bad thing.....well that taught me a big lesson....its not always what u want that HE wants even if it seemed so freaking good in HIS prespective..weird eh? but I was sooooooooooo sure and naive that i was gonna get what i wanted cuz it jus seemd over the top like a positive experience....something that would of made me a better person..but i guess there were other 'better' things in store.....maybe that place wasnt' rite for me..but like i learned GOD only gives u what HE feels best..and so cuz HE knows BEST....but like what is the meaning of it all then u kno wat i mean?..and of course we have our own free will to do whatever the hell we plz to do .. ok well back on topic here...the queston was  how do we tell between GOD's voice and will and our own?   I guess you CAN tell between the two althought it is hard...i guess if ukno if GOD is talking to you .... u kno its not ur own voice cuz its totally something you wont' expect to hear....something that can scare you..or maybe even clear up the obvious for u..the obvious as in something u are contemplating that u kno that shoudl be but u just dont'wanna except..so u sort of deny it and stuff like that and BAM! God tells u wat to do and it freaks the living shit out of u but u kno wats going on...well i don't think u get scared....but moments liek those sort of confuse u the over all existence of GOD and what not...like u sort of beleive in HIS existence but at the same time you are shocked and u question urself and say  holy shit did that really just happen or is my mind playing tricks on me again?   then again if u didn't hear HIM speaking to u...would u even beleive in teh existence of GOD at all?..I know I wouldn't..well like I beleived that GOD was real and existed just the fact taht I didn't think that HE would want to exist in my world cuz i was such a screw up and rebelled against my conscience...dammit for even a while..i considered myself the  FATE REBEL  and i guess that was why i was so down..cuz i questioned everything that happened to me instead of just beleiving that everything happens for a reason....man like I hated the fact that something liek being CATHOLIC would like just make me lead a blind, dull and planned out life..i thought that there was no point in following GOD cuz HE knew everything that was going to happen so why in the world would i wanna live like that? if i knew someone knew my whole destiny why in the world did i want fulfill it out...well damn i was freaking wrong....thats when i heard of something called  FREE WILL . Like I heard about it all the time..it was 24/7 in my face all the time sort of ting but i never really bothered with it..i was and still am naive..like free will is basically something like GOD gave us the power to make our own choices and to either   a) follow HIM  or  b) follow what WE and the WORLD want  So with all that cleared up I understood more...and thats why i came to the conlusion why the world is SSSSSSSSSSSSOOOOOOOOOOOOOO screwed up... everyone says they don't beleive in GOD cuz there is so much pain and suffering and if their was a GOD why would he let it all happen..u kno why these things happen and everyone is' suffering'? cuz these SOBs don't turn to GOD...they use the b)part of the God's free will and so they do whatever they want..and still even if U R suffering u can turn to GOD for help...suffering is not neccesarily bad... it can teach u so much things and ultimately draw u closer to GOD....like i think everyone should try to turn to GOD...like the barber story   Barber to customer: I don't beleive that God exist Customer: Why? Barber: Do you see that homeless man out there? (points to homeless man with long dirty untrimed hair) If God existed then there wouldn't be problems liek homelessness.. Customer: Well then in that case, I don't beleive that barbers exist neither Barber: (laughing) But I am a barber and I am cuttin your hair Customer: So if barbers existed, why would poeple like that homeless man that walked by still dirty unclean and uncut hair Barber: Because the homeless man doesn't want to go the barber's i guess? Customer: Exactly!..Its liek God...people have all these sufferings and pains but the problem is...they don't turn to him for help     NUFF SAID..GOD does exist..problem is..would u turn to HIM? [confused.but.still.a.beleiver]
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      *sighz* i remember a little bit back on august 28 (me bday!) 2003...i read the horoscope in the paper that morning and this is what it said:     Virgo! this is your year to shine. Jupiter has moved into the house of Virgo meaning luck, properity, happiness and anything you can wish for! You may not see it now but surely it will light up your future later in this year so keep your head up!! This occurence ends at the end of next year on August 28   BULL SHIT! I must say this has been one of the worst years in my life..lets see:  1) I practically grew away from my friends 2) I almost got arrested TWICE 3) I got dejected from that SCHOOL  4) I never felt so depressed in my whole entire life during half the month of Feburary 5) My friends turned stupid and got into hardcore drugs and alcohol  6) A nice big hopeless romantic spell still goes on... 7) That nice big suspension for 'illegal substances' 8) Having a mental breakdown  9) Just feeling that plain old empty feeling all over and over for NO reason at all 10)Having issues with my self esteem / confidence 11)Feeling stuipd and lonely and like a misfit 12)Figuring out that majority of my friends just have low self esteem problems and do not look forward to the future as much as I do  But then I looked around and found this :    While Virgo is traditionally a modest and disciplined sign, having upbeat and expectant Jupiter here can bring you into line with your greater potential. Expanding your experience through study or travel, or the adoption of a new philosophy on life, are all possibilities. Driving these is a more futuristic and optimistic outlook. The effect of that will be to attract more confident and beneficial associates around you. This is a once in twelve-year opportunity; your generous benefactor has arrived, so move with it. The downside would be doing a Captain Bligh and ultimately landing in the drink.   Dude! Can I ever agree on this. As shitty as my year has gone from the above list...I DID get a new outlook on life...check this list out:  1) Taking philosophy DID give me a new out look on life. Especially the question:      What is life?   I figured I wanted to be a doctor..or some health care      professional 2) I found GOD..something I thought i never would of and through the weirdest time of hardship of this whole year.  3) I travelled to RI in the USA and met so many cool people 4) I never knew I was that outgoing and funny and had 'leadership qualities that can do great things for me'  5) I never knew I was that well like by a bunch of strangers I met for 6 days 6) I have this new plan of taking a year off after grad and travelling around the States and Mexico with a few 'religious professionals'  7) I made new friends and got closer to acquantinces  8) Relay For Life let me know I was NOT alone in my weird social journey 9) I am going back to my homeland where I was born and to Australia, possibly Brazil and Atlanta 10)Possibly and hopefully going to Germany next year for WYD with some American friends 11)Wore a dress for the first time in a couple of years (yes its a huge breakthrough =P) 12)Started becoming more open with myself to myself 13)Finished every single course..well except for Bio..but still 14)I met a few people with the same goals and philosphies as I had  Man the list can go on..I guess I did have a shitacular year but the shit just made me grow up...I guess without everything that happened this whole year, I wouldn't have had learned half the things I did...I guess liek they say ..thats life...i just wish everything was as easy and simple as it was but then i am growing up so problems had to come sometime....well i kno i figured one ting..as much as i am cool with my firends rite now and having such a good time, i kno i dont' wanna be stuck with them forever...i wanna meet new people and see a different side of the world..they are so paranoid about not making friends cuz they are so ashamed of themselves..why? i dont' kno .. my theory is that if u act urself..what is there to be a fraid of?...sometimes i guess peopel are afraid of themselves but honestly i think if eveyrone acted liek their real true selves .. i think that they woudl be even cooler...they jsut gotta realize that..man to be honest..i think i am sick of them sometimes...or maybe i just need time alone to figure things out...it wasn't like that before..i used to LOVE chilling with them..it was so much fun..so somewhere along hte line either  a)I changed and 'matured' b)they changed and 'matured' c)we all changed and 'matured' d)we jus dont' click anymore cuz I havedifferent direction  I say its d). Another thing I know that wherever my life takes me..i just wanna kno that GOD is with me liek I am doin what HE wants me to do..even if it is not what I wanna do..I found God and I dont' wanna loose HIM.   On the other hand here..the horoscope...is it something we shoudl beleive?..soudns freaking beleivable but apparently it is 'evil'...liek so many of the things are beleivable when it comes to personality traits and stuff like that. so that makes u beleive the daily horosope crap like the ones above...half of that stuff has liek happened already...are we lettin the horoscope take over our lives?..liek say we read it in the morning and live our days out..liek we would have the horoscope thing on our minds all day and let wahtever it is happen..then say we read it when the day is over..would the horoscope still make sense?...i don't get it either...liek some peopel put so much trust into these daily horoscope things its ffreaky. In my opinion there is no point to living life anymore if u kno wats goin on. Its liek ur just there to feel teh emotion of it..if u get wat i mean..  [meh..ce la vie]
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well it was 10 am in the morning today and I flippeed on the TV to watch Maury...it was kind of entertaining for a while cuz it was about that same old paternity test thing and blah. I actually felt sorry for a few of the people cuz everyone was booing at them and they were just crying and stuff... then i began to wonder..why the hell do poeple watch talk shows anyways?...it is so damn degrading liek why is it our business to watch someone's sufferings? its not like we know them or anything and like we want to help them out.. so why watch it? cuz u kno why?..we are all parasites...we take from people's sufferings feed on them make fun of them and make our selves feel better from the current life we have and in the end, we do nothing good for the people on the show..we compare our own miserable or not so miserable lives to others so we can feel so much better but in the end we are not that much better off then them. we can make fun of them and holler at them and yell but what is the point?..we are degrading someone else's lives and plus, talk shows just make society look all more messed up then it usually is. like half the things we see on the shows sound so unreal which makes u think, what the hell has our world come to. man i sit there and i would LOVE to think that there is a script behind all the 'realityness' but chances are, even if there was a script behind it, cases like the ones we see are just as real as they seem.  another thing that doesn't make sense to me is why newspapers and stuff liek that print out advice columns?  like chances our some of the stuff the people send in won't happen to us so why do we bother reading them?..meh..once again we are just feeding off someone's misery which is a real sad ting cuz i kno i do it myself...u kno wat i kno i dont' have a bad life..like some people would want to be me but:  1) they don't really know me and how i REALLY think 2) I would love to be in someone else's life myself 3) they have no idea what the hell i am going thru rite now  like my life isn't bad..i am just very udnerappreciative and sensitive. and thats wat the talk show made me realize. its kinda sad that it was MAURY POVICH that made me realize taht.  but here i am bitchin and mopping to myself how i wish i was somewhere...i wish i could realize that things happen for a reason and if not the BEST..but i don't want to accept that..i wish everything could go MY way but then, that would take the challenge out of life.. but sometimes i rather be bored with life then put up with my stupid desires..liek i jsut want to sit back sometimes and have things i would want even if did feel bored out of my mind...i KNOW i don't have a bad life...and i wanna try to appreciate things rite now but i can't cuz i am too used to things that i have and i can't imagine that they will ever dissappear cuz i take so many things for granted...and i don't wanna be one of those people who will appreciate these things when they are gone cuz then it will be too late...damn just can't wait till i graduate from the crack hole i call school...i jsut want time alone away from everyoen and thinga nd meet new poeple and have a new outlook without that stupid empty void inside of me that i kno i can fill if i tried to appreciate....ooh also talkin on the phone today..i realized something..us stupid teenagers are always trying to live the fast paced life..liek from one year to another we are COMPLETELY different .. we try new thigns that aren't good for us or we try to be 'grown up'..why?..i realized i was caught into that too..trying to be all like grown up and stuff and indulging into grown up stuff but why?...for one thing it can make u look cool and stuff like that but we ALL hafta realize...we are all still young..we shouldn't be taking life that damn seriously at this age..so screw drugs, sex, alcohol and even relationships..we're not in a rush to get married so why apply on the pressure to get a significant other when WE DON'T NEED ONE...and to explain that empty feeling everyone gets?..well its a little sign for everyone to fill that empty hole that only GOD can fill..sounds churchy...damn rite..honestly i don't think i can handle a bf rite now..damn and even if i did get one..i kno i will still feel a lil empty..its jsu so intimidating seeing everyone else 'fall in love' and just me sittin in the back ground watching..maybe i will find mr mr SOMEDAY..like i wanna kno how it feels..i just kno that i still wouldnt' feel complete...  [thankfull?]
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      wellz....hmm what can i say....don't know how I am feeling these days/sometimes I feel like I am on top of the world..sometiems..just stupid and lonely...i hate feeling these things and i seriously hope its like ragin hormones or something...this whole relation ship thing is confusing me..the letter i wrote..i wonder was today a step towards me to gettin something? don't kno ..then again its all for the best as learnt down in the ri. man this is ridiculous..i dont' even know if i can trust this stupid blogger thing..i dont' want anyone to come across this.. and hopefully they won't cuz i would die..i don't want ANYONE to know how I really feel...see liek I need a really close friend but like no one clicks thsese days...everyoen bussy backstabbing and stf or just plain untrustworthy..it sucks...people tink i am so extroverted but i am NOT..i am introverted and thats how I like it..makes me feel more independent...then i get stupid and insecure over tings from teh past liek that whole december incident where i had to tell EVERYTHING and lie about it...which still kicks me in the ass to this day..maybe i should forgive myself..cuz that someone thinks i didn't say shit...i was buzzed i don't kno?. and that is why i am so glad i am gone for the summer . so i can think and see what the hell is going on with me...i want to be a better person..and i want to kno what God wants me to do..but the problem is  I FREAKING don't...and htat is what scares me so much. what if it is not what i want?...there are many things I don't want but at the same time I do..i have a general idea of what it is...i just wish i got it confirmed..u kno wat i mean? i don't got enuf faith...and i wish i had all the tonnes more but I don't./ sometimes i jsut feel like hiding myself and not want to go out at all..liek agrophobia..cept i am not insane. i just hate what society ahs made today SOOO SICK of it..not even funny .... thats why I LOVED that school so damn much..cuz everyone was so liberated and hilarious...i wish I was like them but NNOO i am not going down there cuz i perfectly know its not meant to be and everyoen does too...whatever I'm out..can't wait to get me own comp in my room    [lord.willing]
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      so i ask myself..what is life..?..i have asked many people this question but i get this very common response :  its what u make it ...ok herez the problem with the answer. it is freaking shallow....how do u make life? u can't just sit there until something exciting happens....so basically we are suppose to get up and run around and make something exciting...like what tho?...ee i lived in the city for SSSSOOOO unberably long..and no doubt .. i love toronto...all those crazy cultures and street parties..but those can only last for so long..eventually u will get sick of chillin...i mean last week i went out 3 days in a row...to the mall and the next two to like downtown...i mean for the first two days, it was like WOW i am have so much much incredible fun but the 3rd was liek..dammit give me something new..i can't stand chilling for the rest of my life cuz i am sick of it already..man i wonder sometimes i am liek i want to become a doctor....but i dont' kno, theres liek an empty element to the whole profession. ok chances are u WILL get married but think of it this way...ur stuck in teh hospital treating people which is fun and rewarding for liek 14 hours a day..then u go home to ur kids and hopefully the HOT husband..try to cook a meal with all the energy u have left and go to sleep..wake up the next morning (or before the pager from the hospital gets u) and same shit all over..i can't stand that..i need something, something more i would say..liek saving lives is ABSOLUTELY cool and making all that difference in someone's life physically and hopefully mentally is even better but like the whole routine sounds so repetitive..medicine itself is not repetitive but the whole concept of it is..liek it is probably going to be a HUGE emotional roller coaster which makes life challenging but the whoel make money to feed ur kids thing is VERY VERY repetitive and i absoutely HATE repition..argh....well liek any job liek htat is today..most peopel just need to feed their kids and some poeple enjoy what they do... its like the feeling i always feel..of always wanting MORE..i can have the best time in the world but i go home i feel the same old way empty and grasping for more..i mean dont' get me wrong for the time being while i am caught in the moment i am having fun...but i dont' completely enjoy it..cuz i want MORE.....so waht is MORE i ask myself..liek i hope MORE for me is like living in abandonement outside the rules of society....i kno i like to travel but not for the rest of my life....hmm what do i want?..nothing seems liek it can fill up the weird MORE feeling..like friends i have and they make me laugh although i wish sometimes i had different friends..more like people who know how to have innocent fun rather then smoking it up and gettin high and doing all these weird illegal things....ahah it would be cool to be a secret agent of some kind..u kno liek the ones with guns and hi-tech gadgets and run around to get like secret information of some kind..aaahh u get the drift....i have a family and all though i dont' have a sister and we are a bit financially retarded..i am just fine with them..sometimes but meh....i dont' kno..like i have everything that some people would want...but i still want more..i don't kno..i can't get enough of anything...i figure now that i look at it..throughout my life..i was never truly happy...like i never have felt true happiness and everyone can come around me and tell me ooh ur so lucky man u are probably the happiest person alive that i know...am not....i may LOOK happy...but lots of stuff goes on inside..my quest for true happiness...i am trying to think of an event that has made me the happiest for a while...hmm going back to RI in May was wicked..i got off the car and everyone was like AHHH UR BACK !! and it was great to see everyoen again..i had the biggest grin on my face that day...such a great time..thousands of miles away from everyoen and thing that could cause me happiness and at the same time sorrow....is this feeling  a result of :   a) being an underappreciative brat b) taking everything for granted c) a gift from GOD?  for so long i wanted this weird I want more feeling to be a gift from God..almost liek a vocation..i want it in a weird weird way..but at the same time i am scared and confused about what it really can be...i mean for a while i thought it was a gift....like rey he starts to feel liek empty but hez happy when he finds a love interest...liek everyone else..but for me its different..i have felt it all my life...as long as i can remember....i never had a true feeling of satisfaction...could it be...love? i don't think so..i reall dont' feel any romantic interest for so far....i haven't mr mr..haven't really been attracted to anybody for a long period of time enough to want...ok well i have...but like deep down i kno i don't want one.but at the same time i do..jsut to see how it would change me...like to fall in love..but i dont' think it is possible to fall in love at this age....meh..sighz..someone i need to be inspired   complex noises and high pitched buzzes constantly fill my ear these are the sources of joy but also, great sorrow my exterior may show a very strong iron layer of exuberence but really, it is just a mask,  to cover up the pain that i don't even know why i feel the layer is really just a thin cheap porcelain  and if you look carefully into it you will feel the romance of my emptiness  [just can't get enough]  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      HHHEEEEEEEEEELlllllllllllooo..well not feeling like i am up to snuff...but hey i am feeling sort of happy ... kind of had a good day..woke up at like 10.30 and had like burgers for brunch..my sides are numb from sleeping cuz it happens to be my women's week so thats why i was so freaking cynical ahah...hmm well miriam called today..and shez not continuing for gr 10..poor girl...i kno something is wrong jus can't get my hands on it..well hope her the best cuz she so young and innocent..hmmphs...oh well yesterday i go the book of LIfe of Pi..and its pretty good..comparing animals to liek religion and human nature..ahah sort of comedic but COOL...erks i figured i am gettin into reading..liek screw friday nitez out..frdiday nitez IN reading...man they are so cool and open up ur mind....wel oooh yeah the hosue is gettin renovated..so its gonna be prety..man so much money to spend ...feel sorry for dad.... [PMSing]
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         identity is to encourage them to look inside themselves, rather than outside, for the answers. This is not always easy. With one client I'll call Mary, it took great patience and lots of long, uneasy silences to begin to separate out her true desires from those of her peers and parents. But if she continues to do this, and withstands pressure from others to conform, she'll be a much healthier young adult with a strong sense of her own identity.    apperently as me friend told me...people from ages 16 - 18 go through some identity crisis..and then from 18 -20.. the find their true selves...? makes sense sort of considering the fact i am turning 17 and thorughout gr 11 i didn't kno wat the hell was going on and i acutally got depressed...but anyways..i came up with the question after hearing that..who am i anyways? like i really dont' know..and i thought i knew...liek i thought i was: funny, hardworking, trustworthy, friendly pssibly in a mean blunt way, tomboy ish..but some how sort of sensitive in a feminine way?...i dont' kno anymore like...it was almost as if i was aiming towards those traits...maybe that is what makes me ME...finding what i think to be the best trait and trying to be that..but then it will not be ME...so if i jsut sit back and try to go with the flow it wouldnt' work cuz in every situation..we need to bring up some type of trait..liek pessimistic, optimistic, mean, kind, calm, relaxed, manic, pisseed or hwatever...but u kind of decide (well at least me) according to what will give me the most attention or power...so does that make me a spotlight lover and power hungry? (I sound like a Leo).. I dont' know..maybe i am jsut imature or soemthing like that..have no idea ..so then apprently according  to this identity crisis we are suppose to look up to someone ..liek a role model...and thats how i figured that i wanted to have an older sister..or even a younger one so maybe she can somehow look up to me...but i prefer an older sister..u kno..even if we may fite all the time..i kno that it would definitely have a HUGE impact on me...maybe to be more 'girly'..i don't kno...see then i have this wierd desire to be mroe girly..but i don 't kno if it would be me....like sometimes i wish i would start puttin make up on.. .but i am too scared cuz i got that little crazy tomboy image..and it would seem weird...and i hate it when everyoe dotes on me for having these weird 'girly' coments. hm so i figure..i do wish to be more feminen...weird..ok also i think the reason i am so addicted to emode..cuz it tells me so much about myself..sometmies it hink that i conform myself so i would meet those traits cuz according to that site, i am some crazy bubly person..i mean i guess i do like meeting people alhtought i have this weird shy trait about me...well i kno for sure that i liked to be looked upon as someone who is funny, and a good friend, and somewhat deeply intelectual and knowledgeable on politics..meh but that is what i am trying to do but i sometimes jsu don't freaking kno...meh...argh..and they say we are suppose to have fun at this age..not that i am not..but liek after 3 days in a row goin out...i started getting bored of that HIGH feeling of happiness and carefreeness in teh world..like i want something more....i can't get enuf of it...maybe it is GOD?..probably..but like i want MORE MORE MORE.....i am not even if like love from someone i wnat bad can fil that weird void up...i mean face it ... i sort of got everything that like a teenager can want compared to some...family, friends, stuff liek htat..but i still feel stupid....and i still want MORE MORE..i am starting to find materialistic things  make me happy ..but then they only last for a whiel..and u get bored of them and u just wnat MORE MORE and MORE...hmm and these days..i am not as strong willed to my opinions as i used to be..i get shot easily and jsut sink and turn red...doepz    the blood shot sky fades towards the nite every creature on the earth nests towards home where they belong and don't have to worry about a thing because lucky for them, God intended them to be different from humans wihtout minds, without fate   hehe still trying to improve on my poetry skills  [confused]
     
    
</post>


</Blog>