<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HI EVERYONE,  WELCOME TO ANIL MAHADEV'S BLOG ON DATABASES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES.  IAM A STUDENT OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, DOING MY BACHELORS DEGREE IN APPLIED INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY FROM SIKKIM MANIPAL UNIVERSITY.  MY PASSION IS READING, WRITING ARTICLES AND HAVING FUN WITH MY FRIENDS AND FAMILY.  HERE IS A LIST OF MY FAVOURITE IT TOPICS  {  SELECT * FROM FAV_TOPICS WHERE TOPICS LIKE 'D%'  OUT PUT :) DATA DATA BASES DATA MINING DATA WAREHOUSING  }  KEEP VISITING AS I WILL B UPDATING MY BLOG EVERY WEEK. 
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well the answer could be many things.  We could take it in two different perspectives.     From a Business Point of View   From a Developers Point of View   I will discuss From a Business Point of View today and tomorrow From a Developers Point of View.  We are in a age where Time is Money and less Time means losing Money.  Therefore Appropriate Information has to be given to Business Analysts , Managers and othwer Top Level Executives in order to make the right decisions.  This is where Business Intelligence comes into perspective.     Best Regards Anil Mahadev  Applied Information Technology Student  Aptech/SMU   urlLink http://www24.brinkster.com/anilmahadev/architect.aspx   My BLOG   urlLink http://enterpriseinformationarchitect.blogspot.com   {  Software Innvoation is my Passion  }    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why User Interface Design is Essential for The Ultimate User Xprerience ?    &nbsp;  Hmm!!! If muy Blog was not UI Friendly would u have come and visited it again, no right !.    &nbsp;  In todays complex world of Software One must put themselves in the shoes of the users and think, Why this has to be like this and why not like that?    &nbsp;  Therefore, one must make sure that UI is the prime concern of any S/W Development Process.    &nbsp;  One cannot assume the User knows !!!, but dont develop software thats too easy to handle as well ;).    &nbsp;  We have to follow the guidelines given to us by our Team Architects and Leaders etc .     &nbsp;  And we must meet with the customer from time to time and discuss other issues involving the UI Design&nbsp; Phase.    &nbsp;  Next we all can sit comfortable coding and going thru the QA Cycle etc.    &nbsp;  What do you think?    &nbsp;  Send me a mail to    &nbsp;  urlLink  anil_mahadev007@hotmail.com     &nbsp;  on the above matter.    &nbsp;  Best Regards  Anil Mahadev  Applied Information Technology Student  Aptech/SMU    urlLink  http://www24.brinkster.com/anilmahadev/architect.aspx    &nbsp; My BLOG    urlLink  http://enterpriseinformationarchitect.blogspot.com    &nbsp; {  Software Innvoation is my Passion  }    &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       &nbsp; Dear Friends  All of u in Business Intelligence must check this out    urlLink  http://www.databasejournal.com/features/mssql/article.php/3305411    &nbsp; Hope this helps :). Best Regards  Anil Mahadev  Applied Information Technology Student  Aptech/SMU    urlLink  http://www24.brinkster.com/anilmahadev/architect.aspx    &nbsp; My BLOG    urlLink  http://enterpriseinformationarchitect.blogspot.com    &nbsp; {  Software Innvoation is my Passion  }  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Atlast Freinds,  Exams r over, but not far from my project thatsgonna start from tomorow . Iam planning a Student information system using VB.NET and SQL Server.  Wait and Watch 4 more Listing  Right now I have holidays till August 15.  So after Independence Day, I hope , I willget crackin more and more for Software Independence.  Anil ;)  
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hi folks,  Its been quite a busy week 4 me.  So Iam just thinking on what to start blogging about.  For starters, I have started to re-tune my math skills for computer science.  Watch this space 4 more posts on Database Technologies.  So watch out for them.      Best Regards      Anil Mahadev      Applied Information Technology Student        Aptech/SMU        urlLink  http://www24.brinkster.com/anilmahadev/architect.aspx       My BLOG       urlLink  http://enterpriseinformationarchitect.blogspot.com       {      Software Innvoation is my Passion      }   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        As promised, I will discuss From a Developers Point of View.        Developers today have too much on their hands, than to sit and work out BI Solutions, unless there are in the business.      From a developers's perspective, One should consider the following.        Appropriate BI Knowledge     Effective use of BI Tools like COGNOS,BUSINESS OBJECTS,MICROSOFT BUSINESS ANALYSER and other products.     Listen to the customer , their Team Architects and Leaders as to how to go about a BI Solution thats right for them.(The Customer).     And most importantly is Training, A crucial area in any part of I.T. .     Well for more info, I will be covering Business Intelligence in detail in future posts.    So watch out for them.    Best Regards Anil Mahadev  Applied Information Technology Student  Aptech/SMU    urlLink  http://www24.brinkster.com/anilmahadev/architect.aspx     My BLOG    urlLink  http://enterpriseinformationarchitect.blogspot.com     {  Software Innvoation is my Passion  }  
    
</post>


</Blog>