<Blog>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hello,     &nbsp;   I'm Jewls. I'm trying to change who I am, but I'm kinda scared of what it will be like its been so long....    For the past couple years I've been smoking pot on and off. More on than off. At first I did it because my big sister wanted me to try it with her. She really seemed happy that I did it so I kept doing it. Then I started to like it. My mom told me its a gate way drug but I didn't believe her. I knew I didn't want to do any other drugs; at least not at the time. That same year when I was 14 I got drunk for the first time. I drank half a bottle of vodka! I was drinking with a friend of a friend and he didn't tell me when to stop drinking. I trusted him because my friend did. Big mistake! I eventually threw up profusely. My mom made red velvet cake that day...He thought I was throwing up blood. I had a severe case of alcohol poisoning.&nbsp;When&nbsp;he&nbsp;thought I was dying he called my mom. She came and picked me up, she was&nbsp;a little drunk that night too. I remember stumbling through the garage and falling on bicycles. I passed out&nbsp;with my head on the toilet and&nbsp;red throw&nbsp;up all over myself. I've never gotten that drunk since. About a year after that I met a girl that became my best friend. Her name is Ashlee. At first we just smoked weed together, then she started to spend the night with me on the depressed, and I started doing awful in school. My mom sent me to a rehab but it only helped for a little while. I knew all along I had weekends. She was in a screwed up relationship with a skaterboy. They fought constantly. It seemed like when they weren't fighting they were having sex. She told me about a cough pill called Coricidins. She said if you took 8 they would mess you up. To get them you had to steal them from the store. We decided to do them. She'd done them before but I hadn't. She wanted me to steal them so I did. I didn't even care that it was a transgression. It was all down hill from there. I stopped caring about things, I got to want to change on my own. The decision couldn't be forced on me. The person I am is so bland. I could be doing so much more. I hate the thought of wasting my life.        
     

    
</post>


</Blog>