<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was able to download pictures, as you can see.  After downloading new software that works with the blog, it was much easier.  Spending the money for it is worth it.    One more day till Joe gets promoted.  I've sung the National Anthem at least 10 times today in preparation for tomorrow.  This was all while driving in my van today-to get a haircut, pick up the cake for the reception tomorrow and buy a pitch pipe!  That's so I'll start in a good key and not get too high or too low in the song with many notes!    Granny and I enjoyed the movie The Notebook very much.  It did deviate from the book some, but the movie was still good-with very pretty scenery and very appropriate music.  Afterwards, we ate dinner at 316 Oyster Bar and then I went to Joe's softball game which didn't even start until 9:30.  His team won-14 to 12!  So they are still undefeated!  
      
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    my two pretty girls, Gracie and Ellie&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Ellie and our Golden Retriever, Sadie&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Still having trouble posting pictures, which is the reason for some posts just being one sentence long.  The one picture that did make it was a lucky break and I have yet to be able to repeat it-even though I thought I was doing the excact same thing.  I'll keep trying! 
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A number of new things will happen this week-the most important being that Joe will be promoted to Lt. Col on Thursday afternoon.  We're very excited about it.  Joe deserves this recognition and I'm very proud of my husband.  He asked me to sing the National Anthem for the ceremony and I said I would.  But I haven't told my family yet, who will be attending the ceremony.  I'm glad some of my family will be able to be there.    Joe's Mom will arrive tomorrow to be here for the promotion.  I'm playing for Diane West's wedding Saturday morning.  She is one of my Granny's best friends.  Sunday is July 4th, as well as the day my Great Aunt Lena Belle and Great Uncle Vernon's ashes will be committed at a service at Highland Church.  Life continues to be busy......the girls are spending tonight with their Mo and Papa, ( my mom and step-dad), so Granny and I are going to see the movie The Notebook tonight.  We've both read the book and both loved it.
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ellie and our Golden Retriever, Sadie.
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The last post was supposed to be a picture of our girls.  It didn't work for some reason, so I'll keep trying to figure that out.  Today we went out to breakfast as a family to Cracker Barrell.  Something we don't usually do on a week day, but Joe was home this morning because he's flying tonight.  Gracie was in a bad mood.  She actually took a nap shortly after Joe and the girls returned home.  I went to the PX and commissary.  We're having friends for lunch after church on Sunday.  We live in the same town but hardly ever see them, so I'm glad the date worked for both of us.   The mother of a girl from my high school class came by today with her daughter's twin daughters.  They are almost 5 years old and very cute and polite.  Ellie wouldn't talk to them-as usual, and Gracie warmed up to them after a few minutes.  It can be very frustrating for me when ELlie doesn't talk to others.  Thankfully we've seen some progress in her since this all started about 5 years ago.  I can only hope and pray that we'll continue to see more progress.  In many ways, I feel I've turned it all over to God, because He is the one who can take care of her in all situations.  I just have to stop worrying about what other people think.
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Ellie being silly by our pretty pink tree this Spring.  We don't know what kind of tree it is, but it certainly was pretty for a few weeks in April. 
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My daughters, Gracie and Ellie.
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      After reading other blog sites, I was inspired to start one of my own.  I spend a lot of time at this computer, probably too much time some days, and I thought this would be a good way to keep a journal, get down my thoughts immediately,rather than thinking I'll write it down later and then forget about it.  Hopefully I'll be creative and interesting, but most of all, learn more about myself in the process. 
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Joe is now a Lt. Col, his Mom has come and gone, we celebrated 4th of July and the girls are now at the beach with Mo and Papa.  They've waited a long time to get down there again, so I'm glad they could finally go.  The promotion went well.  I was mostly pleased with my singing, but I know I can do better.  It sounded soooo good in the shower that morning!  I was just nervous and emotional.  My biggest mistake was looking at Joe near the end and letting my emotions come out even more.  But I received a lot of very nice compliments and Joe is still receiving compliments.   Church on July 4th was amazing.  The orchestra played and we sang The National Anthem ( choir and congregation), America the Beautiful and Battle Hymn of the Republic. It seemed that everyone felt very patriotic and very proud to be American.  Joe wore his uniform and looked great.  A few others wore uniforms too.  After church, we went to Highland Pres for a committal ceremony for Lena Belle and Vernon's ashes.  It was a nice service despite the heat.  Lunch at Granny's was fun.  Joe and my Dad played horseshoes with Ellie and Gracie and they all had fun.  Gracie would yell out " YA-HOO "every time she threw one.  The visit with Joe's Mom was typical-she talked a lot and she spent time with the girls, helped Joe in the yard, kept the girls for Joe and me to run errands go see fireworks.  She stayed a week and I think she even realized this time it was too long. But she means well and things could definitely be a lot worse.  Now I'm getting the house ready for the new carpet to be put in next week! I did take a break yesterday and shop some, as well as go see the movie The Terminal.  Tom Hanks was great in it, as usual. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've now had no caffeine for 3 days and very little sugar and also a headache for most of those 3 days.  But I feel good about what I'm doing and looking forward to making progress in changing the way I take care of myself and losing weight!  Here's what I've eaten since I started this new regiment:  Wednesday Breakfast: Toasted Oatmeal Cereal with Almonds and fresh blueberries 1%milk whole english muffin with strawberry jelly and margarine decaf tea with splenda Wednesday Lunch: Small amount of Lasagna and Salad Root Beer ( thought it would help my headache)  Wednesday Dinner An apple with peanut butter Water  Thursday Breakfast Ham and Egg Biscuit Water  Thursday Lunch Grilled Chicken Sandwich Small Fries Water  Thursday Dinner Pasta with lots of vegetables Water  Friday Breakfast whole English Muffin 2 pieces sausage Toasted Mini Wheat Cereal Water  Friday Lunch 2 hot dogs Water  Friday Dinner Trout Almandine Mac and Cheese Green Beans Watermelon Water  And I cut the grass tonight-back yard and front, so my energy level is getting better and I got some good exercise!   
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We returned today from a long weekend in Savannah, GA to celebrate my Granny's 77th birthday.   It was a fun weekend with, at one time, 19 family members plus 2 babies!  Ellie and Gracie had a great time being with their newest cousins, M and S. They are my cousin H's stepdaughters.  It really helped Ellie come out of her shell and she spoke to many of the adults there and it was wonderful for Joe and I to see her that way.  Could it be a start of something new? I know many people are praying for Ellie and her anxiety.   Most of last week, I stripped wallpaper  in and painted our foyer.   It hasn't been an easy task and I'm not done yet, but I hope to be soon.   Some of the paint peeled off when I took the tape off and there's some green paint on the white trim-I also didn't get all of the wallpaper backing off and it's very obvious in some places.  At least I love the shade of green I chose.  I spent almost an hour trying to decide a color and then what shade of that color at Home Depot last weekend! 
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Gracie in and on pink&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>


</Blog>