<Blog>


<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well today my family celebrated Grandpa's 80th birthday. But his real birthday isn't for another week! What the heck?! O well. So yea, I was stuck at a house with a bunch of old people. They kept like ordering me around. One lady was like "Missy, I seem to have misplaced my napkin..." And I'm like... 'and?' But then Mother came and said, "Livi would be glad to get you a napkin." Like the old lady couldn't have gotten up herself! Grr! Then I was in charge of giving cake to everyone. They treated me like I was a slave. And Grandma was introducing me and my 13-year-old cousin, Lizzie, to everyone. The old people were like "I remember this one (indicating Lizzie), but not this one (indicating me). We gave Grandpa a toast and had sparkling grape juice. Jon, Lizzie's 12-year-old brother, acted like he was drunk. It was actually quite funny. It was very nice that Sister was hanging out with Danielle, my 8-year-old cousin.   You may be wondering why the title is Einstein's Great Fall. Well, Lizzie and I got bored and went up to the toy room. One of the windows didn't have a screen, so I opened it. Then I saw some Barbies lying on the floor. Liz and I started playing around, tossing them out the window once in a while. Then Brother and Jon came up too. We decided to make a movie of the Barbies. It is so funny! Filming dolls being thrown out the window... The little doll's hair was sticking straight up so we named her Alberta Einstein. My favorite quote from the movie is: And this is my pet machine gun, Fluffy! Yes, we probably WERE drunk from the sparkling grape juice. But of course, Sister and Danielle realized that we were up to something so they made my aunt tell us to put them in it. Grr. I don't like little people. In the end we just gave them the part of screaming when the Barbies fell out the window. We showed the finally masterpiece to the entire family and they were laughing so hard! It was great fun.  Now, about the whole Jack thing. This is Livi's blog and Livi is going to write what SHE wants, savvy? If you don't like it, don't read it. Livi loves all of you dearly, but you have got to understand that not everything is going to be in your favor. I know what that one adjective is that Jack thinks you are, and I agree with him totally. Please, lay off!  Bye!
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My family has been lake oriented since as far back as I can remember. When I was little, I would always go to Grandma and Grandpa's lake. They had a nice little paddle boat and a sprinkler that I would always play with. Mother's friend had a lake cottage that we always went to also. There I would play in the sand, go swimming, go tubing.. stuff like that. About six summers ago, my family finally bought a cottage of our own, on the same lake as Mother's friend. The lake is called Snow Lake. We go up there every weekend during the summer. The cottage is really nice, 4 bedrooms, 2 1/2 baths, and a nice boat. We go tubing ALL the time. It's like our life. Even if it's freezing cold and cloudy, we are out on the tubes. At night we go to the ice cream shop, play cards, build a fire, make smores. Sound fun to you? I bet.  Let's play use-your-imagination again. One weekday you get an invite to a friend's pool party which is on Saturday. You ask Mother if you can go. "No, we'll be at the lake." You beg and you plead, but it's still no. So Friday afternoon, you pack your things and head to the lake for another fun-filled family weekend. Before you get in the van, you ask one more time if 'Best Friend' can come too. "No." So there you are, stuck in the van with Family. Dad, Mother, and Sister are having a very LOUD conversation, Brother is playing his Gameboy with the volume on high, and you are trying to read. Imagine the annoyance! But this is just the beginning. After driving for 45 minutes, you finally get to the cottage. You hurry and grab your bag, run up to your room (which is practically a closet in Sister's room, no joke), hurry back down the spiral stairs, and do your job of sweeping spider webs off the porch and dock. Once that's done, you grab your book and plop a squat on the couch. Finally, some reading time.. WRONG. Brother and Sister run in and turn the TV on to some stupid cartoon show. You try to take refuge in Brother's room (your room is only used for changing), but the door doesn't close all the way and the volume is up as loud as it goes. You give up reading and put your swimsuit on because you see Dad taking the tube to the boat. So now here you are, on the boat, FREEZING, and they are going to shove you on an inflatable piece of plastic and drive you across the water. You take turns with Brother and Sister, it's still cold, but it's not bad. You're sitting in the tube, Sister talking away next to you (2-man tube) and you start to think of what others are doing. You wonder what it would be like if 'Best Friend' was there too. Now it's time for dinner, not so bad. And now you get to do the dishes while everyone else has fun doing something else. When you're done, you walk into the TV room to find Brother and Sister lying on Mother, the babies. You go up to Brother's room (your favorite room) and read. After a while, "Livi, come down here! We're playing cards now!" You go downstairs, sit down, and play a couple rounds of Progressive Rum. At the end of round 3, Brother starts crying and throwing a fit because he has to count his cards. So the game ends. Now you get to go get ice cream! You get back and Dad starts the fire. It's nice and warm. You look at all the stars that you can't see at home, and you think about Jack and how you wish so much that he was there. You can't take the loneliness anymore, so you go inside and go to bed in Brother's room. You don't sleep in closets even if there is a bed. Brother usually sleeps on the daybed downstairs anyway. You say your prayers and get all comfy and- Brother comes into the room. "Out." You must protest. "No, I'm sleeping here." "Fine, but I get this side of the bed." He indicates the side you are on. You move over to the other side, but you take the good pillow with you. You need SOME good thing. After Brother kicks you about 50 times, you finally go to sleep. But only to wake up to: Brother snoring, Brother kicking you, Brother lying on your shoulder, or Brother waking up at 7 and turning on the TV. At 9:30 (way too early) Mother wakes you up for a nice breakfast. You eat, take a shower, and put on your suit. You are ready for a morning of tubing! You step outside and- IT'S REALLY COLD! But Family is pushing you out the door and into the boat. Finally the sun comes out and it's nice enough to swim for a while. You suddenly remember the party you were invited to. It's taking place right now and you're not there. You think about all your friends and how much fun they are having. You think of Jack and how you could be with him right now if it wasn't for your lake! On the way back to the cottage, you spot Mother's friends. They come back to the cottage with you and you are in charge of making the food for them. You make the food, join them and suddenly the boat takes off and you are stuck for the afternoon. You drive around the three connected lakes for a while. Warm when the sun comes out, cold when it goes away. You stop here and there to visit people who know you but you have no idea who they are. At one of the stops, you stay in the boat while the adults go talk to the people in the cottage. You see on the porch a boy about your age. He is blonde, and sitting in a wheelchair. You look at him more closely and realize that one of his legs is missing. Suddenly you recall the story from last summer of that boy who got ran over by a boat. That was him. You feel sorry for him and then beg Mother to take you home, you're bored and burned. You go home, eat dinner, do the dishes again, blah blah blah. Then you try to read, but have to play cards again. After cards you sit down and watch TV, fighting here and there on what to watch. After a while, you get bored and go up to Brother's room and listen to music. You sit on his windowsill and look out at the lake. You see a bright star and start to think of Jack again. How you wish he was here! When the CD is over, you go to bed. Thankfully Brother is sleeping on the daybed this time. The next day is pretty much like the last. Tubing, boating, TV, cards. FINALLY it's time to go home. Brother and Sister want Mother to sit in the back seat with them, so you are stuck in the front. You turn the music on and all the songs that remind you of Jack come on. You miss him so much. You try to listen to the music but Family is having a discussion about road rules. Grr.. how they bug you! Good. Now you are home, on the computer, and back where you are loved. Thank you for playing use-your-imagination.  Bye!
      
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Don't we all have issues? Of course we all have issues. And everyday I am faced with some of them. Issues range everywhere from books to dance. If you disagree with any of my opinions on these issues, by all means, flame.  Harry Potter Romances: I support Harry/Hermione all the way. They are like perfect. Christina doesn't see that, but the book won't tell everything. Some things you just have to figure out yourself. You may think that they can't be together because they are friends. Well, if you watch As Told by Ginger, you would see that Ginger and Darren are together and they have been friends since they were babies. All good couples start out as friends. Jack and I started out as friends and look at us! We're perfect! The girl Harry cares most about is Hermione. And the boy Hermione cares most about is Harry. Well what about Cho and Viktor? Cho and Viktor are Harry and Hermione's CRUSHES. There is a MAJOR difference. We all know that Harry looks like his dad, right? And we all know that Hermione is Muggle-born like Lily, right? And we ALSO know that history likes to repeat itself in Harry Potter's world, right? Right. IT IS FATE! If you, like Christina, support Ron/Hermione, you should think again. Ron and Hermione fight NONSTOP. Do you know what happens to couples who fight NONSTOP? They break up! They get divorced! Ron and Hermione just DON'T FIT! And Ron doesn't like Crookshanks. 94% of women would dump their boyfriend if they didn't like the pet. HARRY/HERMIONE ALL THE WAY!!!  Other romances I support: Ginny/Neville Ron/Random girl (Parvati maybe) Draco/death (though I know it won't happen) Ernie/Hannah Jack/Livi Dobby/Winky Percy/Penny (I think it's cute) Hagrid/Madam Maxime Crabbe/Goyle (it would be extremely funny to add gays to the books) I better get on to other issues.  Initials: We are going to play use-your-imagination. Pretend you are a girl who walks into Kohl's to find a cute purse to take to Vegas. You like those initial purses that everyone has, so you decide to get one of those. Now think of your name... good... now the first letter of your name. That is called your I N I T I A L. Now that you have that letter in your head, go look for a purse with that letter on it. You search and search and search, but you can't find that letter. There must be a mistake. There HAS to be at least ONE.. somewhere. You search some more, but you CANNOT FIND ONE. Your heart sinks, your hopes are gone, so you by a black purse instead to match your mood. Then you leave the store wishing you had a different name. This is how I feel EVERY TIME I WALK INTO A STORE. There are no purses with the letter "O" on them. But your name is also Livi, by an "L". NO. I want my O's! "O" is not the only letter left out either. I have a very good friend named Hillary, and she can never find anything with an "H" on it. Without are O's and H's, we would be nowhere. This book here that I'm reading for the 3rd time would be called: Arry Ptter and te Gblet F Fire. And Santa Clause wouldn't be able to say "Ho, ho, ho!" To all the neglected-letter names, I feel your pain!  Teen Couples: I don't know about Jack, but I get put down all the time. People don't understand how serious I am when I say I love him. They think it's pathetic and stupid and stuff. They don't think we can make it a long time, but I think we can. I know we can. Others think we are too young and just having a "crush". Yea, I'm young, but I'm getting older. And THIS IS NOT A CRUSH. This is real, I know it is. How can I make you people understand? *sigh* You'll see in time, I know.  Dance a Sport? Yes, in my eyes, dance is a sport. Yea, I know, there is no NDA (national dance association) but it is still a sport. Most sports are played using balls, like basketBALL, baseBALL, volleyBALL, but not all. Swimming is a sport, but it doesn't use balls. Cheerleading is a sport too. I don't like many cheerleaders, but I have to stick up for them on this. It IS a sport. I am just as dedicated to dance as the rest of you are to your sport. I give most of my time and money to dance. Dance is the only thing I do. There are three things that I think all sports have in common. Practice: You have to practice every sport to get better at it. Dance is no easy task. You have to learn balance and posture and technique. You need to learn motions which turn into steps which turn into dances. It takes a lot of time and a lot of concentration. And along with practice is dedication. If you weren't dedicated, you wouldn't practice. Next time you are with me, watch me. If I get bored, I'll start dancing. Practice is as must for a sport. Sweat: Yea, I sweat in dance. I sweat a LOT. Some of those costumes are like an oven. And the lights are like a tanning bed. And THEN you dance. A sport is usually something that gets your heart rate up. And usually when your heart rate goes up, you sweat. Sweat is a must also. Competition: What is a sport if you don't compete? In basketball you have all these tournaments, in track you have meets, and in dance you have competitions. You travel around the country to get scored on how well you dance. It takes a lot of teamwork to make the dance perfect. It's just like tournaments, you want to get first place. You want to be the best. Without competition, where is the sport? With these three things: practice, sweat, and competition, dance can be classified as a sport.  A note to all: Dad is taking the computer away now. I have no idea when I'll get it back. I will try my best to find other computers to raid. I will miss you all. Talk to you when I get it back.  Bye!  
      
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hello all, and welcome to my life. My name is Olivia Analise Schnyder. I am 14 years old and will be a Freshman this fall. I have no writing ability unlike one of my best friends, Christina, who can write perfectly about anything at any time. I have two other very close friends who come up in my life a lot. Their names are Mit (it's his nickname), and Jack. But before I get into the things with all my friends, I will talk about the smaller things in my life.  Family Dad: He favors the rest of the family, thinks I'm on the computer too much, stuff like that. Also very irritable. Mother: Mother loves me... I think. She kinda understands the importance of my beloved computer. Also favors everyone else.. figures. Brother: He is 11 years old and he is ok most of the time. Except for when he thinks I'm on the computer too much. (Wow my family is like me/computer oriented) Sister: VERY annoying. She's like always bugging me and always crying. Being 10 years old, she is the youngest so she always has to have her way. GRR.. Dogs: I have two beautiful boxers. One is retarded.. but she is SO CUTE! The other is on a diet, like the rest of my family.. except me of course. My name: Since my family named me, I'll tell you about my name. I was named Olivia for my Italian grandmother and Analise for my German grandmother. Christina likes my middle name.. she's like obsessed with Anne Frank whose name is Analise. She oddly shares a birthday with her..  !My Birthday!: My beautiful birthday is July 6, 1989! Less than 2 weeks! I'm almost 15. Maybe since I'll be older, people will give me more respect. Who knows. Christina would know, she's already 15 and doesn't let anyone forget it.  Dance: I dance. I have always danced. I love dancing. I do 4 kinds of dance: tap, ballet, jazz, and lyrical. I also compete dance. I compete tap and jazz. Every other year my studio goes to the national competition. This year it is in Las Vegas, in 2 WEEKS. I leave July 5 and get back the 12. I have 6 dances going. I hope we do good. I think we will. I have named my shoes. (yes I know I'm weird) Their names are Annie and Caprice.    Ok, now, to my life. I have lots and lots of friends. Three in particular: Christina, Jack, and Mit. At one point, months ago, the four of us were known as the US Group. After having a Civil War (also known as The Big Fight) we kinda lost the whole group thing. Everyone thought of it as a clique. Of course IT WASN'T! It was just a group of friends who had a name! JEEZ PEOPLE! People bug me sometimes. Well ok, onward. Everything got worked out with the "war" and all was good for a while. Then one day- hold that thought-  Jack is my boyfriend. I love him VERY VERY much. I won't go on about it in here because NO ONE WANTS TO HEAR IT. *sigh* But we have been going out for a good 5 1/2 months. *happy sigh, daydreams*... o yea-  Then one day Mit got on Jack's nerves. To make a VERY long story short, Jack won't forgive him. It is a mess. Jack won't talk to Mit, Mit won't talk to Jack. "Our lives are a freakin' soap opera!" - Christina. It is truly horrible. I have hope though, one of my curses-  My curses: Compassion, Patience, Hope, Faith. They haunt me.  Well it's late, so I better wrap it up. I'll be back tomorrow or so to talk about more things. Unless Dad takes away our virus-filled computer.. if he does, I will be back as soon as possible.   Bye!  
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       This day was so horrible. I would rather die than live this day again.   &nbsp;  I got up at 6 to go to stupid band camp. It was so boring there. I'm in the pit. All we did was learn all the scales on the stupid marimba. And the people in the pit are just nerds. I mean NERDS. They don't know how to read music or anything. There was this one girl who plays the clarinet like me. But she left the pit after lunch because of Mit. There's this big whole in the formation where Mit would be if he was still doing band. So she left, and now I'm stuck as the only girl in the pit. I hate it! So there we were, 10 hours to do something. 10. I was so bored out of my mind. And I missed Jack so much. He's out there marching, and I'm stuck inside playing scales. I've always wanted to be in the marching band. And actually MARCH. I have to go through this for 2 straight weeks. And then the rest of the year during practice. And then the rest of high school. I'm gonna be sad my whole life because of this. Don't tell me to quit band because this is what I've always wanted to do. I just need a hug.
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a fun weekend, a VERY fun weekend. It was so much fun if you didn't guess. It all starts Friday. I had my last softball game of the summer. We won because the other team had to forfeit. It was a fun game though. Then I had to go home and pack for the weekend. And then I left for Chantal's house.   I went to Chantal's house to drop of my stuff because I stayed with her the whole weekend. Then we went to a surprise party for my friend Isabel. She's moving to California! Where it's always hot! It's so not fair. But we're all gonna miss her very VERY much. The party was a lot of fun. I got to see some friends that I hadn't seen all summer. There was a water balloon fight, some people swam in the nasty pond. It was great. We went for a couple of walks too. And those of you there know what made my day on that second walk. Hi Jack! *waves* Feisty!Livi came out and tried to kill Christina with a water gun. That was SO funny, and you know it, Christina. And Mit, please take my mother's advice and BE NICE. Then at the end of the party, we just all sat and talked. Some of them stripped, but that's another story and shall be told another time. Then when I left, my day was again&nbsp;made. Hi Jack! *waves* That was such a fun party. We're all gonna miss you, Isabel!   Saturday morning I got out of bed at like 6. I took a shower, blah blah blah. Then Chantal's mom drove me and Chantal's siblings, Pete and Kate, to our high school. Today's the parade! Yay! We got there like right when we had to board the buses. And I couldn't find my marching shoes! So I was like the last one to board my bus. I didn't know which bus Jack and Mit were on, so I just got on the closest one to me, and luckily they were on it. I sat across from them. I sat with this girl whose friend was behind her. They were making up these hilarious songs which I will NOT repeat. And for breakfast I had flavored cardboard. After a couple hours we got to Peru, the Circus City. We did our warms ups and stuff. Then we had a while to just talk and whatever. There were all these circus animals. Jack wouldn't let me pet the tiger. He said it would bite my hand off. I got to pet the asses though. Mit said they looked like my mother. He is SO mean sometimes. I tell ya.. So, then we marched in the parade. It was cool. After the parade, we got to walk around the midway for a while. Then we went to the circus. It had a bunch of kids in it. It was so cool to watch them do everything. They did like everything. It was amazing. After that, we got back on the bus to go home. On the ride back, I sat next to Jack, and Mit sat next to those girls that I sat next to. I dropped my bottle cap underneath Mit's seat. That started EVERYTHING. I was so bored; I had to do something to entertain me. First I poured water on Mit's head when he was sleeping. Then I asked him for my bottle cap back. He wouldn't give it back, so we made this big deal about it. It was so funny. I tried to act all sad and all, like I really wanted the thing back. I'd say that I'm a pretty good actress. No matter how hard I wanted to laugh, I kept my sad face. But it was so funny! We were fighting over a bottle cap. A  bottle cap.  In the end Mit made&nbsp;a compromise with Jack and I got my bottle cap back. Thanks Jack! You're the greatest. And oh man. I had to go to the bathroom SO BAD. And the driver kept driving on the shoulder of the road, where its all bumpy. It was horrible. Then we got back to the school and I ran to the bathroom. THE GIRLS' DOOR WAS LOCKED. I like panicked. Then a bunch of us girls ran into the guys bathroom. The whole day was rather funny. Had-to-be-there moments. Tomorrow (Monday) starts band camp. Yay!!! (that was sarcasm) Then I went to the lake with Chantal's family. They have a cottage right by ours. I went to babysit these kids with Chantal. It was great fun. The kids happened to be her ex's siblings. After the kids went to bed, we got tired and fell asleep in Chantal's ex's bed. It was quite funny. And no, he wasn't there. I was so tired. I had all these strange dreams, but of course, I'm known for my strange dreams.   Sunday was fun too. We got up and went to church like good little Catholics. Then we came back and went skiing. We had four people up on the skis at the same time. It was me, Chantal, Kate, and Pete. We all got up on the first try and we all stayed on until we decided to all let go. It was SO awesome!!! Pete was next to me and he kept spraying me with he ski. And every time we turned a corner, Chantal got whipped out of the wake, but she stayed on just fine. We are all such good skiers. Kudos, kudos.   Now I get to read this stupid book for school. I really don't wanna read it. But I have to. Oh well. And I have to get up early, so I better stop typing and get on with my life.   Bye!   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, let's see. What should I talk about? I am currently very sad, but I know I'll be out of it by tomorrow. I think I'll start by talking happy... then I'll talk sad.   Yesterday I had some people up to my lake. It was Jack, Mit, Chantal, and me. We had a great time. We went tubing and swimming and eating. We belched a lot and had fun talks. The tubing was the best part. We all fell off a lot. One time specifically... Chantal and I were on the lay-down tube, and Jack and Mit were on the sit-in tube. We hit this big wave and at the same time hit Jack and Mit's tube. As Mit put it: 'It was like Jack was the driver and I was the passenger. Suddenly Livi and Chantal came flying. It was like Livi hit the windshield and bounced off, and Chantal went under the tires....' Oh, it was great fun. When Chantal and I were on the tube alone, she asked the most hilarious random question. I was laughing so hard that I fell off the tube. I won't repeat what she said, but it was HILARIOUS.   Ok, enough with the happy.. onto the sad.   I was in marching band. But I can't be anymore. I have dance the same night as band practice. It may not seem to mean a lot to you, but it's really gonna kill me.&nbsp; I want to be out there performing with everyone else. I love performing. And I love being in band. All the people are really cool and the songs are cool too. They may be hard, but I need a good challenge. I'll just be sitting who knows where watching the band perform without me. Watch them move around the field playing Machine and the other songs. Watch them go to competition without me. Watch them win without me. *sigh* Oh, when the Saints go marching, I'll have to watch.   And in better news, I still get to march in a parade Saturday. That should be fun. Jack and Mit will both be there. We'll have&nbsp;a grand old time.   Sorry about my mood. It'll all be better next time.   Bye!&nbsp;     
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hello all! Livi is back. Sorry it’s been so long. I was in Vegas, then I got busy with stuff. But I’m here now, never fear. While I was in Vegas, I only took notes. So if you have any questions about anything, please ask.   - It is very HOT there. Not humid hot like Indiana, but dry hot. My hair didn’t even curl. It got up to over 100 every day. Every time you stepped outside, it was like a hairdryer was blowing in your face. Even at night it only went down to like 80. HOT HOT HOT.  -We walked the strip just about everyday. No not strip as in take your clothes off. The strip is the long line of hotels/casinos. The whole strip is like 2 miles long and I like walked it every day.  -The casinos are cool too. Each one has a different theme. But if you are under 21 you had to stay on the red carpet and keep moving at all times. Blah blah blah. Here is a list of all the casinos/hotels I went into:  Riviera (I stayed there)  Paris  Aladdin  Circus Circus  Venetian  Mirage  Caesar’s Palace  Bellagio  New York New York  MGM Grand  Flamingo  Excalibur  Treasure Island  - Now some of you might think that hookers just come up to you on the street. NO. The hookers have Latinos working for them. They stand on the street and hand out cards of topless women with little stars on their boobies. The cards are all over the ground and stuck in signs. It’s like gross. - Lesbos, gays, drunks… It’s nasty.  - Moms in mini-skirts = BIG no-no.  - Right outside my hotel window was this little wedding chapel. I watched all these people get married. Aww!  - Since it was Vegas, Mother bought all these drinks and stuff. I got to have a Virgin strawberry colada. It was really good. Mother bought a bottle of rum and she let me sniff it. She also let me try her margarita at Margaritaville. You know, like that song. “Wasted away again at Margaritaville. Looking for my lost shaker of salt. Some people claim that there’s a woman to blame. But I know, it’s nobody’s fault.” No one I was with got overly drunk, don’t worry.  - Two stores that I like a lot were at the very other end of the strip. And we walked there twice. There was the Coke store and the M&amp;M factory. They were so cool! I got Coke and M&amp;M’s all in one day!  - Circus Circus was really awesome. They had all these midways and a bunch of acts. There were these two really really strong guys who would like balance on each other. And then there were these acrobats. It was cool. - Now as a lot of you might know, some of my friends and I are totally into a couple musicals. Mostly Wicked and RENT. Well, at the competition there was this raffle. One of the days you could win four posters. Two of them were Wicked and RENT. I went all excited. I didn’t win though. Oh well.  - While in Vegas, I went to some shows. One of them was at the Treasure Island. It was this pirate show with girl pirates and boy pirates. First, one boy pirate climbs onto the girl pirate ship. Then the girl pirates like strip dance for him. Then the boy pirates come to save him, but the girl pirates fight them. (with like dancing and singing) Then they blow up the boy ship and it sinks. And the boy pirates come onto the girl pirate ship and dance. Yea… Another show was La Cage. This one is the female impersonators. It was HILARIOUS! The main guy was dressed up as Joan Rivers, and each time he came onstage, he had on a new dress and a new joke. I didn’t get a lot of it, but I think that’s ok. Then all these other guys would come on as famous singers and imitate the girls. Some examples are: Jennifer Lopez, Madonna, fat Madonna, Bette Midler, Judy Garland, Whitney Houstan, Cher, Celine Dion, Britney Spears, Dolly Parton, Michael Jackson, and more who I either forget or can’t spell their name. It was great…  - I was with my friend Gabby the whole time because we shared a room. Now, these adults are dragging us kids into casinos where we can’t do anything. So Gabby and I had this game. We would rub our feet on the carpet and then shock our mothers. Oh, it was great fun! I mean, what do they expect us to do? Be bored?  - On the last day there, we went to downtown Vegas. It’s not like a downtown here. There aren’t any tall buildings or anything. It’s one street filled with a bunch of little gift shops. It was cool, I guess. Really old though.   That’s all about Vegas in general. If you have any questions, please ask.  Now for dance. The whole competition was way messed up. The judges gave all the bad dances first places. They didn’t place teacher’s choices. It was SO messed up like you wouldn’t understand. Half of the dances from my studio didn’t place when I KNOW they should have. I got two 1st, one 2nd, one 4th, and two 5th. Let me tell you, that’s BAD for my studio. But oh well. The next nationals are in Orlando, Florida. Can’t wait!   Convention was fun too. We had the one ballet teacher again. This time we had to do faces and be fun-key. We also had to “pet our pussycat.” Please don’t ask. The little kids thought it was great fun. We learned some cool dances. If you want, I’ll teach you the Tanto. Yay Tanto!   Well yea, that’s Vegas for you. I’ll be updating about my life later. My life’s too confusing now.   Bye!   
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sorry that I haven't written for a while, but I've been busy! Getting ready for Vegas and all. I leave Monday and I am so excited! I shall miss you all dearly though, don't fret. Wish me luck! (and a happy birthday)  Well, about this full moon effect. Thursday night there was a full moon, and it has effect like a lot of things. I first saw the moon on the way to band practice. At band this girl kept running around screaming, "It's my birthday! It's my birthday!" And then this NEW director guy, who was NEW, never seen him before, knew everyone's name! It was like creepy. So the moon effected those two people that I noticed. Then I went to Jack's baseball game. On the way there I just stared at the moon. It was so big and bright. When I got there, I sat down next to Mit. All he did was talk. Talk and talk and talk and talk. I think he talked about stuff he wasn't supposed to. But I don't know. It's the moon! The moon makes people go crazy. The next day I went to el lago. We almost reached the highway when I remembered that I left my swimsuit at home, so we went back to get it. Mind you, I don't get effected by the moon. At all. On the ride to the lake, I noticed a big number of dead raccoons. A lot more than normal. I think the moon got to them, and they said, "Hey, let's go get ourselves killed tonight." So they all went into the street and died. They are all lunatics, literally. Luna = moon. So the word means "crazy in the moon". Be warned and watch out for the next full moon.  ~*~To Jack and Mit~*~ Family got on my nerves. I wish you would have come, but if you did I would have gotten in trouble. So either way it was screwed. All I did was lay on my bed and listen to Wicked. And *Mit stop reading* I thought of you, Jack, the whole time and I wondered what you were doing. I wish I could have been with you, but I knew you were having fun, so I wasn't so sad.  Well, that's all I've got for now.  Bye!
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yes, I call it Bad Camp for a reason. It's horrible. You'd think we'd all have fun just playing our instruments the whole time. But it's a lot of work. And it's like affecting everyone.  Like I said on the second day, it's boring. For me at least. I have music now. And I have to play about five different things. The bells, two cymbals, chimes, and a bucket. Mit is in the pit now too. So I guess it's not as bad for me now that I get to talk to him. He has these two mallets that I guess resemble me and Jack. He likes to do little puppet shows. *rolls eyes* The songs we play are really cool. The ballad is kinda slow, and I don't get it. But it's really pretty and "powerful". The opener and closer are really really fun to play, and I love the melodies.  There's like this director guy. He directs the pit. He's like harsh. He's in this rock and roll band but he always talks about classical music. He has a ponytail and he can't hear real well. I think it's because of all the years he's been beating timpanis. He likes dynamics. And he likes to show off. He's cool, but he bugs me at the same time. And there is this kid who was in the drumline, but he decided that marching was too hard. So he joined the pit. He can't read music, and he's always off. I think he's trying to hit on me. He wears to much cologne, and he always tries to do little things for me like putting my mallets away and carrying my stuff. It's rather bugful. I should mention to him that I have a boyfriend who is in the band. Maybe he'll back off then.  Poor Jack. Poor, poor Jack. He is so stressed. My poor baby. Marching is like hard. And it takes a lot of work. They have memorize their sets, and their music, and their everything. I just stand there with music in front of me. But I would much rather be in the band with the rest of the clarinets. I don't care how much work it would be, I wanna do work! And the director told us all today how much we suck. Yea, real nice, I know. This whole thing is making everyone so stressed. We are all like pissed at everything. Some worse than others. Well, there's only one more day. I'm sure we'll get better. We're gonna be the best band ever! Because I said so.  Well for some adventures... I already mentioned the puppet shows. Well, I had one of my mallets represent Mit. One day I was playing the cymbal with this mallet, and it broke. It just snapped in half. There goes Mit. Dead as a mallet. Beheaded he was. How sad... And today, Mit brought in the ingredients to make my famous dip. I call it My Dip. Because it's mine. And there is this microwave in the band room that everyone uses. Well, we made the dip, but the dish didn't fit in the microwave. So there we were, stuck. Well, we decided to use the plastic container that Mit brought the cream cheese in. It worked, and we got our very yummy dip. Some people tried it and they loved it. I think I should have gotten a watermelon for that. Seriously...  Running sucks, just leave it at that... Why would anyone run as a HOBBY. Seriously people. Do you enjoy like killing yourselves?! Don't answer that...  I'm tired. Can you tell? I should be in bed, but I'm not. So I'm leaving.  Bye! 
      
</post>


</Blog>