<Blog>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yes, this is the beginning...my blog, my life, my weirdness. It'll all be here. Whatever I am thinking, whatever I am worrying about... Which brings me to the first topic...Mom. We are waiting to hear her test results to find out if she has breast cancer. This is a pretty freaky thing. Her little sister had a lump removed a few years ago, so it is not outside of the realm of possibilty here. I feel bad because my freak level ont his isn't just over Mom. Don't get me wrong, I love my mother, but I am also concerned about the ramifications if my mother is diagnosed with breast cancer. That means my chances are even better than most that I may develop it as well. That would be pretty rough for the girl who has prided her bust as one of her best features since she was about 15! Women are made to find so much of themselves wrapped up in their breasts by society, fashion, etc...to have them become diseased is kind of like having your sexuality or identity become diseased as well. I know that is not the reality of it, but it is the way society reacts to it these days! It can feel that way....anyway, that is one of the big things going on right now!  

						
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So mom is OK! All is well on her health front! That's a relief! So now on to all the other concerns of the world...LOL!!!!  Well, the holiday weekend came and went without too much hoopla. I guess that's good considering there was a birthday in there for me as well. Yup, that's right, I turned 33 on Saturday. And you know, it's actually been pretty depressing to tell the truth! I keep looking at my life and how much I have NOT accomplished and how much I want to and how far off in the distance it all feels! It's enough to drive you nuts! But I guess it isn't all crap...afterall, I have two wonderful little boys that I adore, who seem to be doing very well, despite me! LOL! THey are pretty smart, big and strong and very happy, so that's good. They seem to be the only consistant bright spot in the world for me right now. I am working on finding some others out there as well, but it takes time!!!!!  Speaking of such things...I have purchased a new work out tape that I think might do very well for me. I am hoping that it will strike me as a hobby more than a work out, so I am excited about it! I am taking up belly dancing! I think it will be fun and I know it will work all of the areas that I have trouble with, so that is a good thing! If only I can actually get myself addicted to doing it, then it will be a very good thing! If I really like this tape, then I think next month I might order the next 4 in the series and really get a good workout routine put together for myself! I am looking forward to going home tonight and trying it out! I think it will be fun....  I know that if I am able to start feeling better about myself, losing some weight and just looking better, that will help with some of my other issues, like the whole men thing. I'd really like to have a relationship again, but I don't seem to be meeting many men and even the ones I know that seem to be into me, seem to be a bit scared off or something. I think a lot of it has to do with the walls I have built for myself. THe first layer came when I was pregnant and didn't want anyone to come between me and my kids....that one is still there a bit....ok, a lot! lol! Then the second came after the Patrick incident. I was working relaly hard at letting the guards down for him and then he went and stepped all over me! His treatment of me was awful!!!! But even more so is the fact that I have been dreaming about him and there seems to be some sort of a pull toward him again! This is not a good thing! I do not really want him, I think this is just a symptum of being a bit lonely and nothing more. Either that, or I am on a self-destructive route, which needs to be bypassed! Anyway, I think if I can get my body image stuff under control and gain a bit more self-confidence, the I think the men thing will fall into line a bit more. I'd kind of like to see something a bit more happen with the Brent thing, but I think he got scared when we had our little sex thing a few weeks ago and it went less than favorably. I mean, it started just fine, but it ended abruptly......as can be the case at times. We'll see if anything ever happens there again or not. Maybe I'll check in with the fairies and see what they have to say about the whole thing when I get home tonight....... 

						
</post>


</Blog>