<Blog>


<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone. I'm amina a.k.a amino acid. i'll be writing in this here blogspot because I feel like it. I don't know what to write about quite yet, so i'll write later! amino acid
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey everyone. i hung out with kristen yesterday and last night and we went to the mall and terrorized wal-mart like no other. we toilet papered people's house (including hers...lol) last night. when we were at walmart, we threw things over the aisles and we got carts and put junk in them and then left them and the prodigal "straw that broke the camel's back" was getting these boxes of condoms and putting them in random people's carts when they weren't looking. it was fun. one of the store security guards went nuts and like chased us and yelled at us. it was great. but he killed my fun. oh well...me and corey were the ones doing the condom thing and kristen and josh were just hangin around i suppose. so yeah. then after that we went to randi's and had a blast. we were all sittibg in her room and then we went to DLM (dorothea lane market {sp??}) and then grater's where we stole a buckeye...lol...cha. then we went to the park. then we were swinging. then we saw these kids and they were talking to us...and they had cookies!! i *heart* cookies. so...corey and kristen and josh and i were supposed to leave to go back home at like 10 and it was like 9 22 or sumthing...so me and rando wanted to hang out with these kids and have some cookies. so coral and k-risten and jizz-osh-izzle left. and we had cookies for like 2 minutes. then we left. i feel bad for having cookies and then up and leaving, ya know? well, they didnt have a lot of cookies like maybe 7? and there were 4 ppl that wanted some. but they said to come back to the park and they'll bring more. they were good so maybe i'll buy some next time too. yeah. it was fun. me and rando ran back to her house like halfway. coral was a little pissed, but he got over it. yup. then rando said something about taking this stuff out of a pill and snorting it...and we cracked up.&nbsp;it was great. i loved it 100 times. p.s. i made coral change his sn to say," a hundred" yup. i am ONLINE! woot. so, anyway, i snorted that crap and it made my nose run bright yellow snot for like 3 minutes. then we went home. now thats where i am. im gonna get some ice cream in a sec. yeah...ice cream. bleh. i'll write L8a..yo. *hearts*   --*amino acid*-- 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey everyone. i havent written in a while..but it's not like youpeople check this out everyday and anticipate my every word. so. lets catch up on the last since whenever i wrote in this. i met that jon kid. he's a lot cuter in person. i got a webcam and pics now...woot! this one kid told me that he printed out my pic and put it in his wallet...how creepy is that?? just some random kid on the i-net....::shuddering:: hopefully he threw it away (i asked him to). but yeah. it creeped me out. then, lets see...i went to pki w. corey and l-ray and hydle. we met kristen there w. troy (her b/f now YAY!) bleh. i went to cd connection. no one interesting was there. ::sad face::&nbsp;oh yea. i didnt get a discount off&nbsp;those CDs either. there really was a sale. don't i feel salty now?? (wtf does salty...in that context...mean anyway???) bleh. i still kinda have a thing for him. i still have a big kinda thing for frank. ::blushing-sad-i-miss-frank face:: ouch. i just definately stubbed my toe. i saw the lion king broadway style. i drove. working on getting that license. cha CHING! i need a job. yo, i just watched Bad Santa. well, like a few hours ago. and ya know,....lean in close y'all...i find billy bob thornton to be very&nbsp;strangely attractive. i dont know why. but...SHHHHH!! you can't tell anyone!&nbsp;k? lol...so yeah, what else did i do...? oh, i met corey's "fake cousin" josh. he's pretty cute. he has a g/f. i hung out w. rando a lot! it was fun!!! i *heart* hanging out with rando! lol we're gonna go party soon...or so i believe. hmph. i went to the cellar saturday evening. me and rando and cordizzle got bored and went to burger king where i proceeded to win a french toast thing. i guess that was exciting. me and rando "stole"&nbsp;a cart from kroger's (stole meaning took it out of the parking lot). rando pushed me in it...and since im such a fat ass, she got tired...lol. i said that she could ride in the cart the next time. we went back to the cellar to wait for rides and i wrote "SATAN" on the sidewalk and "Dogs fucked the pope. No fault of mine." on the parking lot. Some ghetto girls got into a fight. and I'm betting bored writing about all this junk. I bet you guys couldn't care less, eh? i agree. well, i'm gonna keep writing until this dumb picture thing downloads. i guess the picture thing is to let me post pix on my blog w.o just posting a link. i dono. well....blah blah blah. bleh bleh bleh*** ooo, just hit my head on the chair. not cool. i need money like no other. i kinda want some cookies too...lol. not those kind. not like choco. chip, man. im talking about the real junk. lol...i think im gonna eat a reese's cup. woah...download's almost done...92% yo. i'm gonna make another quiz and make the world take it. i'm gonna try to make it into a forward everyone does. yeah...that'll be it. 94% almost! 95%! bleh. im listening to NIN and some other band on the radio at the same time. i like NIN better. lol 97% ooh, i got my horoscope. neat..i'll check it out. p.s. it's like 2:13 a.m lol 99% !!!!!!!!! oh yeah, download complete! well, that was a waste of time.&nbsp; i don't understand the point of that...bleh. who tf knows.i'll try to post a pic....just a sec... does this work?     &nbsp;   sry if my pix suck. or if they don't work. but yeah. i'm going to bed. ::tired:: good night y'all. *hearts*    *--amino acid--*    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yo, i just got back from miniture golfing, well, putt-putting. it was for jessica's b-day party...she turned 11...wooo jessica! (she's my neice) yeah. i met that jon kid today...for like friggin 30 seconds...seriously. he's going to ozzfest. what do i think about this kid? well, from talking to him last night (well, this morning...) he seems pretty cool and corey says he's pretty cool...and that's cool cuz corey wouldnt lie and tell me he's cool if he's really a jerk or whatever...but yeah. he's cute too. if he wanted i'd prolly go hang out with him or "go out" with him if he wanted...yeah. bleh. i wanna go to cd connection like nothing else. i wanna see if my buddy's there. i wanna see if he talks to me (like usual...out of his way...lol). i wanna just see him. that's not weird, is it? .....ouf... i wanna stop thinking about him and such cuz i'm too much of a pussy to say something to him. i mean, i wanna just go up to him and be like, "hey, do have any idea that the reason i've been in here so often is so i can see you?...." i dono. i just wanna kick myself. he's the reason i'm not sure about jon. if i didnt wonder if maybe he was interested in me, i wouldnt have any "qualms" about getting with jon. but i dono. it all goes back to "there are no wrong or bad decisions or mistakes. only the things you do and the things you don't," thing. you learn something for everything you do. if you never do anything you can't learn from it. and it's not a mistake if you learn that what you did was an unpleasant experience...you still learned something. i dono where i'm going. if anyone knows what i'm talking about say sumthing so i can make sure i'm not insane. but yeah. i dono. im going to see the lion king tomorrow (broadway style!). hopefully getting my license soon. hopefully getting a job soon. bleh. hopefully a lot of junk. lol. well, im done for now. ttyL8a *hearts* --*amino acid*--
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have decided that I am going to try to write in this hardcore...like nothing else. Ya know, like everyday...but wnayway...I'm gonna take a shower in a few cuz I'll prolly take 2984584967094357242139841 hours to get ready...even though I'll only see this kid for about3 minutes....::discovery:: Girls are stupid. We take hours to perfect our look even when no one will see us.  >. ::listening to "Memory" by Sugarcult:: ::checking out a Tarot reading:: ::coughing like crazy:: Bleh. my eye hurts...and I'm tryting to make a b-day card for Jessica, but I dono what to put in it...I think I've said "i dono" more in the last 8 hrs 35 minutes than ever b4....im heading out..taking a shower *hearts* --*amino acid*--
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yo everyone who keeps up with my junk. bleh. i dono what to do with myself. this guy, jon  > and i started talking today cuz corey told him about me i suppose. so yeah. we talked and had a blast talking and having a fun convo and all. it was really fun. i migt meet him tomorrow. prolly will. i feel like i should be more excited though. i just, i dono. i can't really be much more excited cuz well, i just dono. there's this guy. i've seen him a lot, especially recently. i used to see him at school, now i see him at cd connection...since he works there and all...but yeah. everytime i go there (if he's working) he'll go out of his way to come up to me and talk to me, or compliment me on my clothes or the cd(s) i'm buying..and the last time i was there, he even gave me 2 dollars off when nothing was on sale...but eh. i dono what to think. i mean, maybe he's just being cool and wants to keep customers coming back, or maybe there's more...or maybe, i dono. i never know. and if this is a case where he is just being nice, then i must pose the question...why is it i can go out and make other people start to like me, but the one who really matters can't see it? uffffhhh...i dono what else to say. i'm speechless. i am excited about going to meet jon, but now as excited as i wish i could be...or maybe i am and i just have to meet him to really know. i dono...like i said so many times before...eh. Yeah, here's this awesome quote (or near quote) from the movie _Unfaithful_...."There's no such thing as a mistake or a bad decision. In life, there are only the things you do and the things you don't." I suppose I live by that...or try to at least. yeah, i'm goona go...my mom's gonna be checking on me soon...ttyL8a. *hearts* ::confused:: --*amino acid*--
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bleh bleh bleh. im so friggin bored with a capital B, O, R, E and D. I'm talking to rando and cor-dizzle and ignoring everyone else cuz I feel like it. I'm wearing my hot new tongue ring....the one with the ring on the top...I'm having fun playing with it...lol. i have huge pants. seriously. i can fit my BODY into ONE pant leg. and we all know how huge I am...so that says something...and there's actually even a little more room in the pant leg....it's nuts. I got 2 pairs. One's blue with popples on it and the other is black with spongebob on it. yo...anyone ever wanted to know what "pjkawerhgjfrhgjktnae" is? well here it is....striaght from Dr. amino acid the cook's mouth..."uhm, ok...pjkawerhgjfrhgjktnae is a GREAT eastern chinese dish, if you're into sushi and seaweed...you have your richly salted pacific seawater seaweed mixed perfectly with raw salmon sushi...add a teaspoon or so of soy sause and BAM! the best pjkawerhgjfrhgjktnae you've ever tasted." I bet you are very excited and can't wait to try that dish.....(EWWWWEWWWWEWWW!) i dont know what to write at all. I'm no longer baby-siting that jerk---no BITCH--- Ally. I'm so glad she's gone...I was so under paid for watching her sick ass. She has some seriousl issues...honestly...she's fucked up, and I'm not sure there's a cure...but "at any rate" (as my art teacher always said) I watched like 1987489235498208545845778462656248181828282823443764674646456 million movies this weekend. It was nuts. All the ladies in the house say...::incoherent mumbling::. lol...it's a Yahoo thing... but anyway..i don't have anything interesting to say except I want some cookies....lol...that's all. I'm heading outta blog for today...tty'all L8a. *hearts* --*amino acid*--
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woah, my blog IS working...and has been working i just didnt know... lol..i feel dumb.eh, whatever. i cleaned this lady's house today and got $24 worth of candles (2 candles 12 each) and $30  too! woot. i didnt do much, and tried to give some of the money back, but she wouldnt take it...eh. im 30 dollars richer. i got a corey hart cd and if u dont know who he is, look him up. i dont feel like telling u that hes and 80s scene singer who did sunglasses at night...okay! lol...when love and death embrace  amino acid p.s. i hate harley! and i dont even know him!
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yo, im writing to see if this is finally goona work. yes. goona. harly's being a shitface ass-cockless-jerk-fuckface-sorry tourettes--shit mother fucker dammit asshole needs to crease...uhm, he's being a jerk. poor rando. i wanna kill him for her cuz he makes her sad even though he makes her happy too. ugh! pook. well i'll see if this works. lylab/s i s'pose. *hearts!* amino acid
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yo, I got back from Illinois 3 or 4 days ago! WOO! It was crazy...we did some crazy stuff....but not too crazy.Rando commando's b/f is being a jerkhead guy. pshh. eh, I got this crazy cold like 2 days before we left Illinois and I still have it! kinda.I was supposed to get online last night but I fell asleep and I didn't. :( oh well. I suppose I'll just tell cordizzle and rando that I fell asleep. well, I dont really know what to write about for now, so I'll write L8a. *hearts* amino acid
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey hey hey. well, its been a while, eh? ive decided that im moving to canada when i get out of high school. i got moulin rouge. its a great movie. ive seen it 7 times in 5 days. "the greatest thing you'll ever learn is just to love and be loved in return." i *heart* that quote like woah. t *heart* that whole movie like woah. yeah... oh, and randi hates me. over harley. yahoo face. hardcore. i dont understand. they broke up. cor-dizzle todl me since rando wont talk to me....cuz ya know, the block button can solve all the problems in the world. *sarcasm @ randi*if she wants to hate me, i'll let her. i can find new friends. oh yeah, and she told me that i was fat, emphasizing my extreme obesity more times than was absolutely necessary. corey said she was only trying to make me mad, but whatever. she says i'll never get a b/f cuz im so hideous and fat...once again emphasizing me being overweight. i suppose she thinks it upsets me, but i know that she's way more upset about her relationship with harley (if you could even fucking call it that) than i am about her calling me fat over and over and over. yeah. i figured the world would like to know that tidbit. i think shes way insecure. but thats just me. idk. well, i dont wanna waste my life talking about her. i have so many other better things i could focus on. like i said, i can get new friends. well, im bored like woah. im going to warped tour and thats way awesome. and xfest. that'll be pretty cool i think. i have to babysit this week. i finished my driving too! whee! i have to get my license tho...but i suppose i wont get it for now cuz i have no car so no reason to get it. yeah. well, hm. oy. i go back to school soon. im getting my hair dyed like avril lavigne...lol. i love her hair like woah. i went to cd connection the other day and i saw that kid. yeah. he's neat. well, im gonna go. tty'all later. (aka write later) *hearts*  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey. n2m going on. me and corey got in a little quarrel with rando. i wish she would listen to us. i bit my tonge too. it's way annoying. i bought party monster, romeo and juliet, moulin rouge, and avril lavigne's new cd. yes. i really did. *yahoo face* i saw the godfather, and the godfather part 2, mona lisa smile, and bowling for columbine. i went to the movies (2 dollar) with kitchen, corey, and rando. we saw garfield. it wasnt too bad. but then, it wasnt too good either. liuba moved which makes me sad. i hung out with her the day she left. i gave her phillip. hes this cow i made in art 1 frosh yr. he was my fave thing ever. ::yahoo face:: idk what to write. i think i should go to bed. i have to drive with my instructor tomorrow. we're on the highway. for 2 hours. i dont wanna do it. im gonna fuck up. i know it. then he's gonna fail me! then i'll cry. i still need like 30 hrs of driving before aug. the 11th. i wont have them. but i'll tell my dad i do. so i can get my license. i wont have a car anyway. eh. where would i go anyway? and for those who care...which is prolly no one who reads this....i went bra shopping the other day and got 2 new bras...lol. now you all know. well, i guess i'll go to bed now. i dont wanna fail to hard tomorrow....*today*...see y'all. *hearts* +--amino acid--+  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>