<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, we found another vehicle to take to Utah! Praise God! Andy & Colleen Kryder are letting us borrow their Suburban for the week, so we're thankful to them and to God for providing and answering our prayers. Keep praying as we try to solidify housing arrangements for our trip out and back. Some things have changed and we're in need of a place to stay on the way out this Saturday night, now. Churches seem to be hard places to get ahold of. I know ours is, too, with just a part-time secretary, but it seems to be the same way every place I've called out in Wyoming. Anyway, as soon as we've got it nailed down and God has provided, I'll be sure to update the blog and let ya know.  Also, don't forget about the Concert of Prayer tonight at the church. It begins at 7:00 and should be a great night of worship and seeking the Lord's face together. Hope to see you there!
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For the week of June 27-July 3, here are some specific requests to be praying for each day: • Pray for the organizers of the Challenge Conference, that their hard work will reap great rewards in the lives of students. That loose ends will begin to come together and God would be glorified. • Pray for the physical/transportation needs of our group. We still need one more vehicle and hopefully a small trailer for luggage. Pray that God would provide both soon!!! • Pray for our leaders that God would prepare their hearts to minister to students. • Pray for safe and timely travel on Saturday, July 3. • Praise God for providing for us in so many ways in preparing for this trip to date, especially financially. • Pray for out attitudes as we travel together. • Pray that God would build a great expectancy in our hearts to meet Him next week and seek His face. • Pray for God to move in mighty ways among our youth, that He might be glorified. • Pray for the Concert of Prayer on Wednesday, June 30. 
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thank you for your willingness to partner with us and pray! We’re excited about the ways in which God will be using you as He works in the hearts of our youth.  For the week of June 20-26, here are some specific requests to be praying for each day: • Pray for the organizers of the Challenge Conference, that their hard work will reap great rewards in the lives of students. That loose ends will begin to come together and God would be glorified. • Pray for the physical/transportation needs of our group. We still need one more vehicle and hopefully a small trailer for luggage. Pray that God would provide both soon. • Pray for the students of our group as a whole, that the teaching we’ve been going through as a group would prepare them for the conference. Pray that God would be preparing their hearts even now. • Pray for one of our students, Matt Mueller, that he can find someone to work for him July 2, 3, 4. He had a very recent and unexpected conflict with work come up. Pray that God might provide a way for Matt to join us and that Matt would see God’s hand in working things out for him to attend. • Pray for our upcoming fundraisers, that God would continue to be faithful in providing funds for us to attend. Praise Him for His generosity already!
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, here's the first post to the Challenge 2K4 Blog. I'll be posting Challenge–related updates nightly while we're in Salt Lake City and also calling in from my cell phone to post audio blogs that you can listen to from this site. You'll even be able to add your own comments on each individual entry. If you're a Challenge Prayer Partner, you'll be able to check for daily prayer requests from your students here as well. Hope it works well for ya, I'd love your feedback!   – Pastor Josh
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, we made it! It's late Thursday night right now and everyone is back in the hotel crashing. I'm not sure how many more updates will get posted before we get home because I'm not sure we'll have internet access again after tonight. Thanks again for all your prayers and support of the youth, it's been a great encouragement and God has been using it. We bought DVDs of the main sessions this week, so if you're curious and want to check out some of the teaching here, in a couple weeks you'll be able to check the DVDs out from me at the church.  This post will be short and sweet 'cause I need some sleep! :-) But here's an update of our itinerary on the way home beginning tomorrow...  We'll be leaving the hotel at 8:00 A.M. local time and headed for Park City, Utah where we plan to go white water rafting at 9:30 A.M. By 12:30 we hope to be done and on the road for South Dakota. I can't remember the name of the town right now, it's on a piece of paper in the Suburban, but it's just north of Rapid City, SD. On Saturday we'll get up and visit Mt. Rushmore, then make our way across South Dakota to Iowa. Saturday night we'll be staying at my home church in Alta, Iowa, Summit Evangelical Free Church (www.summitefc.com). Sunday morning we'll attend the Worship Celebration there then take off after lunch for a small church in Chicago. The kids from Summit who attended Challenge (28, I think...) will be leading the service there Sunday morning and sharing what God did in their lives here this week. Monday the plan is to spend the day at Six Flags Great America, then get back to WCBC sometime around 9:00 P.M., maybe a little later.  Thanks again for everything, and we'll see you all again soon! If we can't post any more written messages here, we'll at least try to post some audio ones again before we get home.  Later.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After the session Wednesday night, I had the kids write about 3 things. (To read more about the subject of the session, look at the last entry posted early this afternoon) First, I had them write out things they were good at and/or enjoyed. Basically to make them think and reflect upon how God made them. Second, they were to write a short sentence or two prayer of thanksgiving to God for the way He's blessed them with those things. Third, they were to write out a prayer request that God would somehow use those gifts in their lives for His glory. That they'd be able to make decisions that would allow them to most glorify God in their lives in light of the way He created each of them individually. Continue to pray for the kids that these sessions and the things God has been working in their hearts on and teaching them would impact them far beyond this week in Salt Lake City. We start the journey home in the morning, so pray they'd begin to think of how to pack it all up and take it home with them even today.  So here they are, in no particular order, and in their own words...  Kayla Trump A few things I enjoy doing are... riding horses, helping sick animals, and working with people that have disabilities. I think that I could do all these things and still glorify God. My job is an important decision I know but God doesn't care what job I do as long as it isn't a sin and I'm still glorifying Him. Because in the end, I will spend eternity worshiping and praising Him and His name.  Hannah Marshall I absolutely love teaching little kids gymnastics. Just to see the look on their face after they've accomplished a goal or a new skill just warms my heart and soul. Please pray that God would somehow use my love for gymnastics to glorify Him. And that maybe someday I could impact kids lives by simply teaching gymnastics.  LauraEllen Burtsfield I enjoy volleyball, entertaining people, acting. I thank God for these talents and that I can use them in my life. Pray that I'll be able to give all I can give to Him and use my talents to glorify Him.  Jessica Myers I really love playing volleyball. I'm so happy playing it no matter who I'm with. I also love singing and just being with friends. I thank God everyday for each and every one of those things. There are a lot more things that I love and thank God for but sadly there is not enough paper! I would really appreciate it if all you back home would thank God for what you love doing and to use my gifts in His ways to honor Him so He and I can enjoy them.  Wes Kaiser God has given me a few gifts like basketball. I am good at it and enjoy playing. Also I'm good at soccer. I just want to thank the Lord for giving me these talents. Since tomorrow [Thursday] is our last day here, I would just like for the Lord to allow me to take some things home.  Travis Juif Riding BMX bikes is something that God has given me the ability to do and I don't know if it's my purpose in life to ride bikes but I thank God for the abilities He has given me. Riding has helped me through many hard times. Thank-you God for all You have done.  Carmen Myers I absolutely love to sing and do art! I also love loving other people. I also love playing with my puppy that I've always wanted! Thank-you so much, God, that You've given me these awesome gifts. Tonight I found out that I can do what I love to glorify Your name. i don't have to be boring and dull. Thank-you so much, Lord! Help me to use them to glorify You. I don't know how I could use my art and my voice together in my life. I know that I can continue to love people despite their flaws, or at least try. So if you could just please pray for a way for me to find a way to use what I love doing in my future. He is awesome and He will answer.  Alisa Gamauf I enjoy anything that has to do with people. Talking to them, getting to know them, witnessing to them. There is no high like knowing that you've played a part in leading someone to Christ. It is like no other feeling. Music and dance are also my "passions" - but no career awaits me in either. :-) I thank you, Lord, for the abilities and passions I have in my life. i pray that you will help me to always keep You at the forefront and my #1 passion! I thank You for those around me that are in my life as well as those yet to come. May you use me as a vessel to shine Your light for others to see. Let others always see your Son in me. Thank-you, Jesus!  Emily Leismer I love working with kids. And more and more I come to find I like talking to strangers to get to know them. There are so many jobs out there and I can't possibly come up with one. But two that keep coming up are teaching and business. But I also really really love music. And since I can't really sing that well, so I play instruments. I thank God for my abilities in music and writing. I'm so blessed with a talented family to influence and guide me. I couldn't ask for a better life. I need these things to be lifted up in prayer: self-confidence in all I do, a closer relationship with God, help with staying pure, and that I can open up more to people and make new friends throughout my life without being embarrassed.  Ashley Sharp I like talking to people! I like playing sports and playing around. I like to pray. God has just placed these things on my heart and in my life that I like to do! The speakers have been throwing things at me and I have been taking those things into my life. I know I need to take those things and use them in my life and I know it will be hard cuz of what my life is like!  Phil Tinkey God helps me build stuff like airplanes, jets, cars, windmills, merry-go-rounds, etc. I thank You, Lord, for giving me the ability to build stuff. I hope, Lord, that I can become better, Lord. In your precious name. Amen. (Josh: Pray for Phil that God would clarify gifts and abilities in his life that He can use and enjoy to glorify the Lord.)  Dannielle Leismer I enjoy acting. I love it! Every time I get off the stage and hear the audience clap and rave about a production I feel awesome. I also enjoy band. Granted, sometimes I loathe playing my clarinet, but I love band. You get an awesome feeling when you go to a competition Saturday and you march the best show of your life. Even if we get last place, I enjoy the people and the friendships that I make. I ask you to pray that I would glorify God in all that I do whether it be acting on stage, playing my instrument, or singing praise to Him on Sunday morning. Thank-you, Lord, for everything you have allowed me to do - and the talents you have given to me.  Lissa Steffen These past two days have been so amazing. God has totally worked in my heart. Tuesday night we had an open worship session. They laid out crosses and little bowls. There were little hearts (representing your prayer and love for another person), pieces of reflective paper (to represent our self-image and reflection of who we are to the world), rocks (to represent the burdens in our lives), stained pieces of cloth (to represent our sins being like dirty rags). We were able to go and lay down or burdens or sins at the cross while we worshiped, and that was so awesome. I really enjoy doing interior design and decorating. I thank God for giving me this skill. I would ask that you pray for my heart to stay on fire for Christ as we return.  Tonya Dewart I love working with kids, helping and teaching them. I praise and thank God for allowing me to work in a field where I can do what I love everyday and for giving me the ability to work with the great kids we have in our youth. I pray that God would help me to always keep my focus on what will glorify Him.  Lance Hostetler I love telling people about God. Not just telling, but teaching, encouraging, edifying, etc. Please continue to pray for the unity of the group and our fellowship with one another.  Hollie Sharp I enjoy playing softball and hanging out with people from church and my friends. I also enjoy playing basketball. God, I want to thank You for everything You did for us. It's just so awesome to know you are there whenever we need You. I pray that You will help me use my talents You gave me. And God, I pray that You will help others use theirs too.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was an incredible day - last night especially. Louie Giglio, the founder of "Passion" conferences spoke on "Real Purpose". What is the purpose of our lives? What is God's will for it? He used some powerful illustrations of the universe we live in and how it all exists - including our lives - for one purpose: to glorify God forever. John Piper, if I remember right, (and he may have quoted it from the Westminster Confession...) says in his book "Desiring God" that "the chief end of man is to enjoy God and glorify Him forever." That truly is the only purpose for our lives. Wondering what God's will is? It's simple, glorify Him.  Everything in creation is a part of His story, they all tell about Him in some way. For each of us, we have the opportunity to either be a part of that eternal story, to tell a part of it, to tell of God's glory with our lives...  or, we can be all about ourselves and focus on "our own story" that will only last a few decades on this earth. What's your choice? Want to follow God's will? Then do what glorifies Him!  God has created each of us with unique gifts and interests. We all have desires and dreams, things that we're passionate about. For some it's art, for others it's music, some it's sports... you name it, someone is passionate about it. God didn't create us with these unique passions and gifts and abilities by accident. He created us with them that we might use them to tell His story! To proclaim the glory of God! Paul writes in 1 Corinthians 10:31, "...whatever you do, do it all for the glory of God." That is God's will, do all things for His glory. If what you're doing doesn't bring glory to Him, don't do it! That's how you discern God's will. WHATEVER you do, do it ALL for the glory of God. Not just some stuff, not just "church" stuff, but WHATEVER you do! Whatever you enjoy doing, whatever you're good at doing - God has blessed you with those gifts and those abilities so that you would enjoy Him and His gift to you by using them to the fullest of their potential so that they might tell of the glory of God!  The will of God and our purpose for life, as I told the kids this morning, is a bit of a "soap box" issue for me personally because I think it is so mis-taught in the church today. So many Christians have been decieved into thinking that in order to be truly valuable and precious to God they have to be a monk in China or something and give everything up to follow Him. They'd be right in saying that you need to be willing to give everything up so that it's not bringing glory to you, but you should take up everything God has blessed you with and use it to bring glory to Him! That's why He created it to begin with! His will isn't as specific as so many like to think, at least it's not if you're basing what you believe about God's will on what Scripture teaches us. It's very vague and general in Scripture. God gives us freedom to do so many things in our lives, our only obligation is to do them to His glory!  Ok, i'm gonna step down now, but I could probably write a book on this. Who knows, maybe someday I will. Be praying, though, that our kids would understand that God created them as they are, precisely according to His plan with different gifts and desires and abilities. Pray that they would seek to honor God and bring glory to Him by doing that which they're good at and what they enjoy, and that as they make decisions in their lives that they would make decisions that provide for them the greatest opportunity to use their gifts and enjoy their abilities in a way that would bring the most glory to God. That's His perfect and pleasing will!  We're heading into some evangelism/ministry training right now, but I'll be posting some of the prayer requests and things I had the kids write down last night along these lines. Your prayers are being used! God is working and I'm fired up to see how He might use a lot of this week to impact WCBC over the coming months. (Also, if you want to get in contact with us and/or encourage the kids, click the "comment" link under any entry and leave a note there for them! Or just e-mail me.)  Later.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! Sorry for the lack of updates today so far, we've been busy, and this one will be short. Last night was a great night of worship and letting the Holy Spirit work in the hearts of individuals. You'll have to wait until later, though, for a full explanation, but God is doing some neat things in the lives and hearts of our youth.  This morning Francis Chan continued his study with us through 1 John, today in chapter 3. We dealt with forgiveness and the need to let go of baggage we have towards others because it hinders our love of and relationship with Christ. John writes in chapter 3 that anyone who has hatred in his heart for another believer isn't walking in fellowship with Christ... A humbling thought in light of how easy it is to be bitter or hateful towards another believer when you've been wronged.  This afternoon we had a 2 1/2 hour session with Josh McDowell. He basically gave the condensed version of his "Beyond Beliefs to Convictions" book. He laid out for us how to defend the validity of God's Word - it's historical accuracy, and why the gospel accounts of Jesus Christ are true. It was a good experience for many of our students.  Continue to pray that God is faithful in the work he's doing in our hearts this week and that as we travel home we would be safe and that the things learned and experienced here in Salt Lake City would carry over and have a tremendous influence back home.  Sorry for being so short with this update! We'll have prayer requests from everyone again tomorrow morning. Until then, though, here's some more pictures (Many, though, are blurry... the kids haven't grasped the whole "auto-focus" thing on the camera! ;-)):  urlLink http://homepage.mac.com/joshuacw/PhotoAlbum27.html"   Later.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's more prayer requests/testimonies...	again in their own words...  Emily Leismer These past few days I've realized that I act different with different groups I'm with. it's one of the things I need to work on. But by praying and spending time with God I know it will be easier to just be real around everybody. And just a random fact: the worship so far is amazing. It's not boring, it just makes you want to jump up and down and raise your hands.  Carmen Myers I think it was Barbara Francis who spoke about the many different  mirrors of how we see ourselves. When she talked about the one where you see all your sin and shame and you can't see yourself any other way, I could relate. I struggle constantly off and on with a low self image because i see all my mistakes. i want to see myself ONLY how God sees me, and let ONLY that vision matter. I also have a problem with simply and truly believing without a shadow of a doubt that I am forgiven. I need to forgive myself. I need to realize and truly believe God has completely forgiven me. They just seem so huge and impossible to forgive and forget.  Chad Hoffert I've identified the following as areas in my life I would like to concentrate on in my Christian walk: 1) Purity in thought. 2) Consistent acts of love towards my family and others. 3) More diligence in prayer and Scripture reading.  Kayla Trump I have learned a lot in the past two days. We have learned from wonderful speakers. A few have said amazing things that made me think. Thanks to all who are praying for us. God is doing some amazing stuff in my already.  Jessica Myers I have learned quite a bit on this trip. Along from the conference I have learned to cope with people that are a little bothersome (when I'm tired). In the conference I have learned that you don't have to lead a perfect life in order to become a good Christian. God has already helped me stay focused on what I need to do and want to do and what not to do. He helps me look at both sides of the argument and take into consideration other peoples feelings. He helps me see what's good and bad about what I'm thinking on doing so I can make the right decision.  Dannielle Liesmer In the purity session Dannah talked about how sexual wit is everywhere. How you turn on the TV and it's right there in your face almost constantly. It makes you realize how much little things can affect you and how hard it is to stay fully pure. It makes me want to strive harder to censor what i put in my mind. With shows I watch, to the music I listen to, to how at ease I am with what people say around me.  Tonya Dewart The speaker last night spoke of our relationship with Christ and the importance of always striving to grow closer to Christ. This spoke to me because reminding me sometimes it's easy to get comfortable where I am in my relationship with Him. I am going to work on constantly spending more time in His word and in conversation with Him. Keeping the excitement and not ever becoming satisfied with where I'm at in Him.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey! It's 8:00 Tuesday morning, the kids are getting breakfast here at the Salt Palace and I'm typing into my laptop! Yesterday was a great day. The morning sessions with Francis Chan working through 1 John are going to be a highlight of the week. He went through studying God's word for what it said, and brought it home in a powerful way to our students. The teaching here so far has been very very practical and down to earth. The far-fetched "super" - Christian stories (as I call 'em, probably better said as "fakey-Christian") from many youth conferences that do nothing more than fire kids up and leave them to fall the next week are non-existant. We're being TAUGHT skills to take off our masks and be real before each other and our mighty God who loves us so much.  I'm not going to give as much of a play by play like I did yesterday, because I don't have as much time and because I have some of the students prayer requests to post. The rest will come later in the day, so keep checking. Before I post the prayer requests, though, here's a few pictures you can check out from yesterday:  urlLink http://homepage.mac.com/joshuacw/PhotoAlbum26.html   Here's the prayer requests, in their own words...  Hannah Marshall Today, in a lot of the messages, the speaker really emphasized the point of where is your heart. Where is your mind focused? It really got me thinking of how many times I focus so much on bad things and things of the world that I miss out on a lot of good things. Please pray that God will help me to have a positive attitude and that I won't dwell on the negative but look for the good. Also pray that when I get frustrated or impatient with some of the other kids that I wouldn't give in to that but I would let God handle it and like I said before, the I would just stay positive. :-)  Lissa Steffen The speaker that we had Sunday night was awesome. He really encouraged me by telling us his testimony. He also challenged us by his message and testimony. We had a prayer concert Monday morning and Monday night which was AWESOME. We thanked God for who He is and the awesome things He does in the morning. At night we confessed our fears to him and asked God to change us. God has really been working in my life. Its just amazing. I just want to thank you all for helping support me by your prayers and thoughts. I really appreciate it.  Phil Tinkey I'm excited for the speakers. It's been encouraging. Please pray for my attitude towards others, that I don't feel left out. (Josh: Pray for Phil's mindset. He's in need of seeing things more clearly. Kids are being accepting of him, but Satan has programed his thinking in such a way that he just can't see it. God is great, though! And He can break any stronghold, pray that He would do this in Phil's mind!)  Ashley Sharp Don't be afraid to let people know that you have a mighty God! The first speaker we had today, He (the speaker) really gave me a lot of confidence to speak out for my faith. It teached me a lot! (Josh: Pray that Ashley will continue to grow this week and that God would help her to become a bold witness for Him. The potential for her young life is great, God is working.)  LauraEllen Burtsfield Pray that I will just be myself. I'm a poser. I can't do all I want to do for Christ because I am totally afraid of humiliation. i would like people to pray for me to be strong and to have an open mind to all the speakers have to say at night and in the morning. i am really looking forward to our "girl" talk tomorrow (Tuesday) afternoon with Dannah Gresh.  Alisa Gamauf I'm learning in an incredibly way already this week God is definitely in this place. I am learning how to worship and praise God on new levels and in new ways. I am learning and being reminded of how truly complete, sufficient, and whole I can be in Christ. He is EVERYTHING and all we need in this life and for eternity. My heart is being moved. I am learning a great deal about these kids and where the are at in their walk with Christ. The teach me more than they know and make me want to grow. The one thing mentioned by one of the speakers here that has stuck out for me was the line (during the purity seminar) that marriage - someday for me - is to be a "portrait of God's love". I have never thought of Christ love in that respect. He is to be our FIRST love – we are to be "married" to Him first. I am learning. Learning to love Christ in new ways.   There ya have it! I'll post the rest after lunch, I've gotta run for now. Starting today, there will also be automatic posts added of prayer requests for the conference as a whole. I'm trying to get it set up, too, that each of these posts would automatically be forwarded to your e-mail address, but not sure if I can get it set up or not.   Thanks for your prayers – God is working! In my life, in the leaders lives, and in the students lives, praise Him for it!   Later.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We made it! We finally arrived in Salt Lake City around 4:30 yesterday afternoon. All in all we made good time, it just took a little longer than originally planned since we had to go through Denver and the mountains, it tacked a couple hours onto our time. The trip was LONG but good, the kids really got along well and there were no major clashes, so that's a blessing.   After arriving in Salt Lake the kids got checked into the hotel while Chad and I hiked up to the Salt Palace Convention Center to get registered for the week. About an hour later we made it back with the name tags, bibles, and other stuff for the kids. Our first session started at 7:00 so by the time we finally got some showers and cleaned up, we were moving again back up to the SPCC.  The worship was great. Chris Tomlin (www.christomlin.com) is leading all week - we sing many of the songs he's written both in church on Sunday mornings and more with the youth. His style and ability to guide people into worshiping Christ while taking attention away from himself and the band is a great gift. After the worship was some drama and then the main speaker for the night, David Nasser.   David shared his story of fleeing Iran with his family as a young child, running for their lives, and coming to the United States. It left a very bitter taste in his mouth towards God as millions of people were killed there in the name of religion. He shared a powerful testimony of the influence that his peers had on him through high school and how easy it is to do anything just to feel accepted and not alone. He fell into the "in crowd", drinking, partying, etc., and it wasn't until a year or so after he graduated high school that he came to know Jesus Christ.  His family, being Muslim, was incredibly hostile to his faith. At first they let it go for a couple weeks, assuming it was just another phase. But as they found out this whole Christianity thing in his life was real, attitudes changed in a hurry. After being baptized he was disowned by his father and kicked out of the house. Five months later, David's sister came to know Christ...  then his mother...  then his brother... soon it was just his father left, and he remained incredibly hostile towards him and his faith.  To make a long story short, David's mother, who had heart problems, came to the point where she needed some major open-heart surgery and was given only a 30% chance to make it. Through some phenomenal events there at the hospital, David's father finally came to put his faith in Christ after realizing - by watching his family - that Christ was in fact God. That he was real. The faith that his family had wasn't just an on again, off again game that many people in the church like to play... where on Sundays God is great and so are they, but during the rest of the week their lives are not much different than any non-believer.  The kids were challenged last night to make their faith real. To understand that real truth is a person - Jesus Christ. As we got together as a group afterward last night I challenged the kids with this: No more games. That really sums up all the issues that many of us, and certainly most of our high school and junior high kids, deal with in our walk of faith in Christ. So often we hear and know the truth, we even believe Jesus and the Bible to be real, but the problem is we never put it into practice. It's like taking a shower and believing in soap, knowing it has the power to cleanse our bodies and wash away the dirt, but never taking that bar out of the tray and applying it to our bodies. In the same way many of us never apply the truth that we profess to our lives, and it makes life miserable. We know the power in it, but we leave it sit there off to the side.  So that sums up last night and leads to the main prayer request to come out of it – pray that our students would do just that, quit playing games. No more games. That their lives would be real and authentic and the truth the know to be real in the person of Jesus Christ would be applied to their lives and downloaded to their hearts.  Pray also for our sessions today... This morning we begin a week-long study of 1 John with Francis Chan. In the afternoon the guys and girls will split up for a session on purity, then this evening the focus of the main rally is "Real Purpose".   Pray for the leaders that we too would have our hearts in tune with Christ and be challenged in our walk. That the games we play would be put aside and our relationships with Christ deepened so that we can even more effectively minister to our students.   Praise God for safe travel and good attitudes.  Pray for me personally that God would give me the rest I need. I'm exhausted! :-) But God uses us many times in powerful ways when we're weak and all of our strength is drawn on from Him. Pray that He would be my strength!  That's it for now, after tonight I'll start posting specific requests for each of our students so you can pray specifically for them.  Later. 	
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, everyone. Satan seems to always pop his head up at the worst times to try and mess with our minds and schedules, especially when we're doing God's work or when there's potential for God to do great things – like during our trip next week. Well, my PowerBook is on the fritz right now, there's something messed up with the power connector on the laptop and it doesn't want to recognize that it's plugged into the wall and has juice. I've got some info on there that I need to get printed out that's just sitting on there now... Also, if it doesn't get working, we won't be able to post many messages–if any–with prayer requests here on the website. (That's where I'm convinced it's Satan working...  God does great things through specific prayer and Satan would love nothing more than to mess up our communication and make it harder to keep in touch.) So if you get this, pray things would start working so I can get the info I need off my laptop and that it would work out for sending prayer requests and/or that we'd find an alternative!  Thanks!
    
</post>


</Blog>