<Blog>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As a child, I grew up in a family where we explored the world around us often.  Hershey Kisses on lamplights in Hershey PA (and the chocolate factory), Amish cooking in PA, Bush Gardens in VA, Graduation Ceremonies in Annapolis MD, Royal Gorge in CO, Ghost Towns in AZ, Knotts Berry Farm in CA, Disney Land in CA and Disney World in FL, Bear Lake in CO, Redlands in CA, MoRanch in TX, Camp Mystic in TX, James Avery in Kerrville TX,  YMCA of the Rockies in Estes Park CO,  all the memorials in Washington DC, lights and sounds of New York City NY, Natural Bridge Caverns in New Braunfels TX, Cascade Caverns in NM, etc -- among many adventures along various roadways and highways across the United States.   This doesn't include all the adventures we had in Acapulco Mexico, West Germany (before the fall of the wall) and the Rhine River, Switzerland, Austria, and Lichenstein.  Bringing up my daughter, I shared some of the excitement of the adventures by taking her to MoRanch in TX, Talledega in Birmingham AL, Dinansour Tracks Safari in Grand Prairie TX, Noah's Ark Safari in Bastrop TX, and as much as I could afford (and as time off from work would allow).   Times were tough, but we had additional adventures in our move to and from South Carolina, as well as during the time we lived there, including the sights and sounds of Charleston, Sommerville, Beaufort, Myrtle Beach SC and Savannah GA.  Hwy 95 offered us additional adventures driving up and down the east coast to and from CT, and one time we took a side adventure down the Skyline Parkway of the Blue Ridge Mountains.  Recently, I couldn't standed it any longer and added a mission trip last summer to the beautiful country of Guatemala (See my blog on  urlLink Bluebonnet Missions  for additional information about that trip) to my adventures.  I plan to add additional mission trips in the future, as well as opportunities to explore Canada, other Latin American countries, and much more...  Hopefully, through this site, you will be able to join my adventure.   With respect to Roy Rogers, "Happy Trails" to us all!! :)   
     

    
</post>


<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If you never have been on an Walk to  Emmaus , you should take it to consideration as part of your renewal process in your faith.  Mine was taken in 1999 and was truly an amazing and remarkable journey.  The Walk to Emmaus is told in the Bible in  Luke 24:13-34  and entails a journey of two people who end up walking with Jesus, unbeknownst to them at the time.   An Emmaus Walk  is further defined in an article as:   "The Emmaus Walk is an exercise in which prayer and scripture run together in a walking meditation. The specific goal of this exercise is for two believers to walk together in fellowship and in silence, allowing the risen Christ to minister within and between them. It begins in a group meeting, providing the context of silence, scripture and prayer, then breaks up into couples for the actual Emmaus Walk, and returns about an hour later to share the experiences of the walk, and to offer it to God in gratitude and praise."   For further descriptions of the Emmaus Walk process, please see the article,  An Emmaus Walk .  Perhaps, the crux of the Emmaus Walk can be summed up in the following two passages from the Bible:    Luke 24:31  (After Jesus explained the passages from the writings of Moses and all the prophets, explaining what all the Scriptures said about himself and broke bread with the travellers:) "Suddenly their eyes were opened, and they recognized him.  And at that moment he disappeared!"   Luke 24:32  "They said to each other, 'Didn't our hearts feel strangely warm as he talked with us on the road and explained the Scriptures to us?' "   When speaking to a friend of mine today about the Walk to Emmaus, she reminded me of this song...from the  Casting Crowns  website:    If We Are The Body  Song based on James 2:1-9     Lyrics by Mark Hall    Music by Casting Crowns  It's crowded in worship today As she slips in trying to fade into the faces The girls teasing laughter is carrying farther than they know Farther than they know  Chorus: But if we are the body Why aren't His arms reaching? Why aren't His hands healing? Why aren't His words teaching? And if we are the body Why aren't His feet going? Why is His love not showing them there is a way? There is a way   I will never ever forget the journey I took in 1999 nor the people I met on that journey.  Their faces are forever engrained in my mind.  Everyone experiences the Walk to Emmaus in a different way; and, when you begin participating in the putting toIf you have strayed away from your beliefs or want to make your faith even stronger, such a walk is certainly recommended (please note:  this walk isn't only for adults, there are Chrysallis walks for the youth, and Genesis walks for pre-teens; their missions are all the same!), for example:    urlLink What is Emmaus?   urlLink Emmaus, Cursillo, Chrysalis, TresDias, Ect   urlLink Mt. Wesley's Emmaus Page   urlLink Emmaus of the Rockie's Emmaus Page   urlLink Purchase Area Fourth Day Community's Page  urlLink Good News re Emmaus Walks   urlLink Alabama Emmaus Community   urlLink etc, etc    My Emmaus Walk in 1999 has, though, lead to a greater meaning and experience to my trip to Guatemala during the summer of 2003, four years later.  Without my Emmaus Walk in 1999, my Guatemala trip may not have been enhanced so greatly.   I am looking forward to sharing with you more about my Guatemala trip.  Stay posted.      DECOLORES!!    
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This time last year I was unwinding from a mission trip I took to Guatemala which forever affected the way I think I think about the world outside of the comfort zone.  Guatemala is a beautiful country -- beautiful mountains, beautiful Mayan temples/pyramids, beautiful culture, and so much more.  I loved meeting the people there and I missed not going again this year due to my own financial situation this year; however, I have many photos that were just amazing and memorable that I reflect on often.  I have many tapes that I recorded sounds and voices of meetings and discussions that we had during our mission trip.  I hope to be able to get them slowly translated through the Monday Mission Minute series I will do on this blog site.  I really am looking forward to sharing reflections and transcriptions with you.  If I can figure out the photo inserts on these blogs, I shall be sharing those with you as well.  The trip involved meetings with other preachers and Church programs,  CEDEPCA ,  CESSMAQ , a women's coop making Guatemalan fabrics, a Mayan Priest, and many noteable villages.  The trip was sponsored by the  Presbytery Mission .  It was a trip that I will certainly never forget the faces of the people I spoke too and saw.  I am looking forward to sharing with you my memories of the Guatemala trip.  I wish I had known about these blogs back then; I would have certainly created my Guatemala diary log back then... :)  Hasta la vista!  ps  I have decided to make this series its own blog from the original blog  Bluebonnet Blooms !  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "June 7, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    Wow! so much has happend in these last few weeks with my cousin in the hospital (Mom says that this next week she will be moving to the recouperation area -- yea!)  Passport arrived on Thursday a week ago, money started falling into place this past week for the trip, was beginning to get things wrapped up for work, getting things wrapped up for school, getting [my daughter] centered, etc., etc., etc.  Thursday (June 5th) was the longest day in history waiting in anticipation of the trip - opening a new door of opportunities & experiences that I haven't explored.  Amazing.  Sylvia & Bob dropped me off oat the airport at 4pm -- Sharyl arrived closer to five, but I had already checked in & she was at the back of the line still.  I went on through security w/o even and waiting for others at the gate.  Our flight was delayed since Houston rained that afternoon & there were a backlog of flights gettingoff the runway.  A bus from Casa San Jose was there to meet us at the airport [in Guatemala] when we arrived at 11:30pm & took us to Casa San Jose. We unloaded our bags & got into our assigned rooms.  We were to leave to Tikal at 5:30am so before going to bed we had to pack up for a one night stay at Tikal.  To do so, we were to get up at 4:30am!  The trust I had to leave part of my stuff behind was something in itself, but we did so.  The flight there was fairly uneventful, but as soon as we arrived the humidity was noticeably more so than Houston and we all began peeling away sweaters & what we could.  A bus from the Tikal Inn picked us up from the airport in Flores and drove down a long highway past a naval bases.  Our Tikal Tour guide was there as well and introduced himself to the group.  Our rooms wern't ready yet so we changed into our shorts, ate a brief fruit plate, filled up our water bottles and started on our trek to the ruins.  We started by visiting the visitor's center & off we went.  He introduced us to the allspice tree, & the sweetgum tree, and the ants.  Along the way he also introduced us to the ceiba(sp?) tree which is their national tree. I have no idea how far we walked, stopping here and there to talk about the nature (fauna and animals) as well as various ruins we approached.  The worst was this endless hill that seemed to go straight up.  I ended up with charlie horses in my legs and waited for them in the plazas while they explored more before the rains came tumbling down.  I rode back down in a truckl.  Even the truck had problems.  If the truck was having problems, I knew I would have.  I had already been slipping and sliding in the mud up there!  We ate at approximately 3pm and had free time until around 8:30pm.  During that time I had washed my sweaty clothes and slept.  I read my book outside & in the dining room until the others arrived.  Lights out & electricity was out completel at approximately 9:30pm through 11:00am the next day.  (Electricity was also out from 4-6pm [in efforts to conserve that precious commodity in the jungle])  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 25, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    Wow!  What a rollercoaster ride I've been on during the last few days -- emotions encircling and keeping me from being as organized as I should be.  On Friday, I had off to go to San Antonio, but I actually didn't get to leave until Saturday morning (had to get my camera & contacts from the office, oil changed in my car, log in new assignments to a spreadsheet, etc., etc).  Saturday morning was more of the same centering around from my garage door not closing & my pants tearing by catching on the pitch of the doorway.  It was really comical that I even got out of The Woodlands area at all!! When I finally made it to San Antonio!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 22, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))      HOROSCOPE, Thursday, May 22:   Your style may be a alittle fast and loos for timid bystanders.  The Stars let you move easily through the world without regrets or restrictions.   Your views of the moment could be totally different tomorrow.  This is what I am expecting from the trip in a sense.  Actually, I have no real expectations; therefore, I leave a lot of room for excitement & very little for disappointment!  I am so very looking forward to this trip!! There is a glimmer of hope for my cousin  - she is beginning to respond to the sound of her husband's voice last night!! I'm thinking that this [following] prayer might be nice to use if asked:   O God of love, we pray thee to give us love:  love in our thinking, love in the hidden places of our souls;  love of our neighbors, near and far ; love of our friends, old and new; love of those whom we find it hard to bear, and love of those who find it hard to bear with us; love of those with whom we work, and love of those with whom we take our ease; love in joy, love in sorrow; love in life and love in death; that so at length we may be worthy to dwell with thee, who art eternal.  Love, Father, Son and Holy Spirit, for ever and ever.  Amen.  -- William Temple (1881-1944) The following is just a great imagery:  "Imagine life as a game in which you are juggling five balls in the air.  You name them - work, family, health, friends, and spirit are made of glass.  If you drop one of these, they will be irrevocably scuffed, marked, nicked, damaged, or even shattered.  They will never be the same.  You must understand that and strive for balance in your life."  -- Brian Dysonn, CEO of Coca Cola Enterprises from 1959-1994  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 21, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))     O God,  forgive the poverty, the pettiness, Lored, the childish folly of our prayers .  Listen, not to our words, but to the grownings that cannot be uttered; hearken, not to our petitions, but to the crying of our need.  So often we pray for that which is already ours, neglected and unappropriated; so often for that which never can be ours; so often for that which we must win ourselves; and then labor endlessly for that which can only come to us in prayer . . . O give us to love thy will, and seek thy kingdom first of all.  Sweep away our fears, our compromise, our weekness, lest at last we be found fighting against thee.  Amen.  -- William Edwin Orchard Sometimes, our prayers can seem quite petty -- especially when, at our lowest of times, we have much more than out global neighbors might have.  I think, though, that our fear is that we may get in the same situation as them.  Thank goodness that most of us have our good health.  I am worried about my cousin though & hope that God is hearing our prayers for her. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 18, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))     O, God, we ask you not to lift us out of life, but to prove your power within it;  not for tasks more suited to our strength, but for strength more suited to our tasks . Give us the vision that moves, the strength that endures, the grace of Jesus Christ, who wore our flesh like a monarch's robe, and walked our earthly life like a conqueror in triumph; we ask it for his sake.  Amen.  -- William Edwin Orchard (1877-1955) Wow!!  I have a lot of tasks which often demonstrates my strength but perhaps my strength is actually that I have the ability to do so many tasks?  Very interesting.  I'm excited about the upcoming trip and look forward to the tasks ahead of me - both during the trip and afterwards.  I have lots of ideas and ambitions to do while I am there.  I wonder if my thoughts will drastically be forever changed during the trip... "Every oak tree started out as a couple of nuts who stood their ground.  - Anonymous  "A visionary is one who can find his way by moonlight, and see the dawn before the rest fo the world."  - Oscar Wilde I consider myself a visionary in many aspects with many hopes and dreams and ideas to achieve my goals I set forth.  Sometimes though it seems that "getting there" can be an upward battle with never ceasing hurdles & challenges to overcome, all the while knowing that God remains by my side.  I know too that my hardships will be greatly minimized in comparison to what the Guatemalans are dealing with on a day to day basis.  I am wondering what new visions will find there & what impact that will have on my life...I wonder...In the meantime, my cousin remains at the hospital in critical care.  I hope God is hearing our prayers. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 19, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))      Truly I tell you, whoever says to this mountain, Be lifted up and throughn into the sea! and does not doubt at all in this heart but believes that what he says will take place, it wil be done for him.  For this reason I am telling you, whatever you ask for in prayer, believe (trust and be confident) that it is granted to you, and you will [get it].  -- Luke 11:24  A global society grows from common human experiences?  Hmmm... are we a global society about to embark upon some common human experiences?  This verse seems quite profound in light of the trip ahead & my cousin in the hospital.  Any doubts that I may have should be immediately anilated and a greater emphasis to be put upon the words:  GOD CAN!   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 18, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    I checked my emails as soon as I woke up & my mother sent me an email that was quite disconcerting -- my cousin was having brain surgery this morning.  I prayed hard this morning and struggled between going to San Antonio and missing my ordination or going to my ordination.  I turned to God & asked Him.  What I heard from Him was that [my cousin] was in his hands and He was watching over her; I should go to my ordination & installation as a Deacon.  I also had the t.v. on at the same time and Joel Olsteen from  urlLink Lakewood Church  was speaking.  One thing that stood out was:  "I have the favor of God."  I took that as a confirmation of my decision to stay today.  I'm glad I went becuase I really got the opportunity to know some of the people so much better.  It was so comforting to be surrounded by so many friends while inside I was praying feverishly for the success of the surgery.  What a blessing it is to have the Church to turn to in the times of praises & of needs.   "The fruit of the Spirt is love, joy, peace, patience, kindness, generosity, faithfulness, gentleness and self-control.  If we live by the Spirit, let us also be guided by the Spirit.  Let us worship God."  -- excerpts from the  urlLink Woodlands Community Presbyterian Church .   In the call to Worship, this really spoke to me and a reminder of what may have well been the motto and inspiration behind my Grandma - my life role model - and probably should be adopted by myself as well as everything I do in life is to live by the Spirit and affect others with my catagious love for Christ.   BRANCHES OF THE VINE .  What a perfect sermon to have on this day of all days.   We are the branches supported by the life line of our God.  I had never quite thought about it quite that way, but it makes perfect sense.  In the children's sermon, the lady made an analogy between the fruit & flowers of the plant being equated with our talents.  I liked that analogy very much. . . .  "The church is founded on Jesus Christ.  We acknowledge that Christ chooses to be known in the world  through this community of ordinary people .  Christ is the foundation of the church, therefore it will not fall.  The church is marked by the Holy Spirit. Across the centuries since the church was founded, the Spirit has formed and identified it.  We recognize the true church of Jesus Christ whereever the work of the Spirit is evident :  in preaching and sacraments, in the new life and continuous growth of believers, in the sharing of spiritual gifts and material things, in mission and service to the world." I loved reading this Statement of Faith today -- especially, in light of the upcoming trip to Guatemala.  I am hoping that I will be able to see the work of the Spirit being evident in Guatemala in spite of their strifes they have had during the past decades.  I am so interested in seeing the workings of God in the rest of the world beyond the comforts and confines of my own home.  Seeing the world as it is and not as a tourist fantasy is important to me. This song [following]is sung to the tune "Morning Has Broken"...a beautiful song:   God The Creator   God the Creator, you in love made me, who once was nothing, but now have grown.  I bring the best of all my life offers, for you I share whatever I own. O Christ the Savior, you in love called me, who once was noone, lost and alone.  I pledge to go wherever you summon, making your will and purpose my own. O God the Spirit, you inlove move me, who oce was noshere and felt unknown.  I know my need of you for companion, all things can change when not on my own. And with the people summoned together to be the Churhc in which faith is sown.  I make my promise to live for Jesus and let the world know all are his own. This [the following song], in a sense, is the signature song of our Church as a result our committment to our sister Church in Africa.  It brings back such good memories from their visit to our Church last fall during our stewardship campaign.  It is very moving (in every sense of the word).  We Are Marching -- author unknown, sung by members of sister Church in Africa   We are marching in the light of God, we are marching in the light of God. We are marching in the light of God, we are marching in the light of God. We are marching, ooh! We are marching in the light of God. We are marching, ooh! We are marching in the light of God.  We are singing in the light of God ...   We are praying in the light of God ...   We are dancing in the light of God ...  We are marching in the light of God ...  Perhaps, I will be able to bring back with me some songs from the Guatemalan culture as wel.  This trip is the most exciting thing I have done in such a very long time.  How will God demonstrate His blessings on this trip?  Only time will tell.  We will be leaving inless than 3 weeks away. I checked in with my parents and my cousin survived the brain surgery.  She is in ICU now but not completely out of the woods just yet.  I continue my prayers for her. Dear God:  Please place your warm hands upon her and let her know that you are with her and assure her that her work on this Earth is not quite done.  Please also place your everloving arms around her entire family and comfort everyone as [my cousin] continues through her recovery process.  In your name, I pray.  Amen.   Another coincidence? Horoscope for Sunday, May 18th:   "A movie or an overheard conversation makes unusual sense although it's in a foreign language.   A global society grows from common human experiences.  Everyone recognizes a good opportunity."   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 17, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    Today was eventful as I set up a separate account for my sideline income.  I travelled to Brenham, Conroe, The Woodlands, and North Houston seeing to some business evaluations.   I stopped at a place to check on a car that they had on their lot.  They wanted way too much for it.  I think it is because of the poor economy that they have gotten so insane with making money for themselves.  I am desperate for a newer car, but not that desperate. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 16, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))      O, God, who by thy Son Jesus Christ hast set up on earth a kingdom of holiness, to measure its strength against all others:   make faith to prevail over fear , and righteousness over force, and truth over the lie, and love and concord over all things; through the same Jesus Christ our Lord.  Amen.  -- George Wallace Briggs  Hmmmm...liked this prayer today. I think many of us don't trust our entire faith to God.  Any doubts, questions, etc. of the unknowns on this trip  must  be anilated by our complete faith in Him to guide us through everything.  He probably has the only clue as to our faith journeys we are about to embark upon.  I am real excited -- so much that my sleep schedule is completely off.  I doubt that I'll really rest until I have my passport at hand and I'm on our 3-hr flight to Guatemala City.   3 weeks from yesterday, we will be on our flight there!  How exciting!! (SMILE) 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 14-15, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    Busy work days @ work. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 13, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    How much more on cue could this prayer be on the trip we are about to embark upon?  More than 40 yrs after Mr. Parson's death, we are still praying for peace among the nations.  No telling when the prayer was actually written.   Almighty God our heavenly Father, guide the nations of the world into the way of justice and truth, and establish among them that peace which is the fruit of righteousness, that they may become the kingdom of our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ.  Amen.  -- Edward Lambe Parsons (1868-1960)   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 12, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    A good prayer to remember as we embark on our upcoming journey:   Grant to us, O Lord, the royalty of inward happiness, and the serentity which comes from living close to thee.  Daily renew in us the sense of joy, and let the eternal Spirit of the Father dwell in our souls and bodies, filling every corner of our hearts with light and grace; so that, bearing about with us the infection of good courage, we may be diffusers of life, and may meet all ills and cross accidents with galiant and high-hearted happiness, giving thee thanks always for all things.  -- Robert Louis Stevenson      The Weaver - Author Unknown   My life is but a weaving, between my Lord and me, I cannot chose the colors, He weaveth steadily. Oftentimes He weaveth sorrow, and I in foolish pride Forget He sees the upper, and I, the underside. Not 'til the loom is silent and the shuttles cease to fly, Shall God unroll the canvas and explain the reason why. The dark threads are as needful in the skilled Weaver's hand As the threads of gold and silver in the pattern he has planned.  This is something I had posted on my website a while ago; however, it seems very appropriate to include it with my journal as I prepare for my faith journey to Guatemala in June since Guatemala is known for their finely, tightly woven goods.  This poem adds such meaning & depth to the looms & woven goods we are about to see. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 11, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    MOTHERS' DAY!  -- a day of rest for me & a day of joy talking with my daughter.  (Note: Remember to bring her back something red or blue.) 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 9, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    It is the night before our orientation and I'm anxious to meet the other folks I'll be going on this trip with.  So far, we have been emailing each other during the past few months.  The countdown has begun as I have also mad my passport application today.  I will finally get to put faces with those people with those people I have been talking to and get some more answers about our trip itinery and journey, as well as tips on dealing with the customs, lores and faiths fo the Guatemalan folks so as we don't offend anyone during our travels and sightseeing.  I pray that people in Guatemala are as excited about us coming there as I am about going there and gaining the opportunity to understand their culture even more! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 10, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :)) BR>    SATURDAY, MAY 10, 2003 ARIES HOROSCOPE:  A committment you made is uncomfortably calling you.  Perhaps volunteering will make you a better person, but the troubles occurring today have more to do with needing to be in two places at once.     Funny!  Some things are more insightful than others.  I'm very excited about today's orientation, however, I am torn between getting someassignments completed or cutting my orientation short!?!!  I am often amazed how on cue these horoscopes can be.  On the way to the meeting, the radio sings, "Feel the Spirit!"  The orientation meeting was informative and insightful through handouts, videos & slides.  I enjoyed getting to know most of our group (I believe that one or two people couldn't make it).  We have been given assignments for devotionals on certain days; I've been given Tuesday.  My devotional is based upon Matt 2:12-13.  In reviewing the devotionals (mine & others'), it appears to me that this trip is going to be as impactful as my Emmaus weekend was in Sept 1999!  We'll see; in the meantime, the excitement rises and I'm looking forward to giving as much as I am receiving.  Before leaving the orientation, the Northwoods Presbyterian Church invited me to [be] commissioned along with them at their Church on June 1st @ 9:30am.  We also agreed on a date fo July 10th for our post trip review! 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JOURNAL NOTES -- "May 8, 2003"    (NOTE:  These notes were taken prior to and up to my first mission trip ever in another country!  I will be sharing these posts with you on the upcoming posts.  I hope that you will enjoy and share the excitement that I felt as I embarked upon this new journey! :))    It is a few days before our "orientation" meeting to meet the others in the group.  We've received more notices about what to bring and what not to bring.  My mind is racing with excitement and some jitters of heading into unknown territory for me -- out of my comfort zone, working and living in the States.  I wish [my daughter] could be going with us but everything got so confusing as to whether or not she would be having her wisdom teeth out at the same time.  I pray that things will be going well for her while I'm in Guatemala. 
     
    
</post>


<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is tough to diet when you are on an very tight budget.  If one is forced to go through the food pantry, foods available are not necessarily very healthy foods.  (NOTE TO SELF:  If at a point in time I am able to be on the giver to the pantry again, I am going to concentrate on healthier food options.  It is so welcomed when a case of bottled water and/or fresh veggies/fruits are available as alternatives to canned veggies and beans.  I think more considerations should be given to things to cook with as well -- oil, butter, milk, cheese, etc. to provide flavors to those that are food pantry recepients.)  If one is forced to buy inexpensive foods at the grocery stores, it is sad that most of the inexpensive items are the most caloric options.  Why is that????  In reading an article on the net today,  urlLink Snacking: Which foods are healthy, which are not -- 9 snacks that might surprise you , it was certainly an eye-opening viewpoint.  For example, I had always thought bagels were a good alternative; according to this article, it might not be the wisest choice.  Right now, I am hungry for some grapes -- anyone got any grapes to share???? 
    
</post>


<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						                                                                      Professional Objective:	   To obtain a challenging and rewarding long-term role within a progressive organization best utilizing my advanced communications, as well as innovative decision-making and paralegal/criminal justice background and skills.      Paralegal/Legal/Customer Service Skills Highlights: 	   Austin, TX   	2003 (Dec) -current, Adecco/Harte-Hanks (xBox Tier 1 Technical Suport & Customer Care)  – began as a temporary for the Christmas Holidays for the rush of the calls involving the xBox console and fielded many hardware and hookup/installation related issues; converted to regular employee status on January 8, 2004, and continued to receive training on other types of issues/calls to field as a xBox agent.  Increased opportunities occurred in May 2004 with the SASSER worm event when we answered incoming support requests for removal of this virus, as well as in June 2004 technical knowledge was expanded to cover xBox Live and wireless issues.  Have been known to jump in to assist in moments of temporary crisis (i.e. when there were over 15 computers out of commission directly before a new shift flow was coming in, when had to get new versions of a software quickly loaded into each to get people operational).  Also, I have been a pinch hitter in many situations and accepted overtime whenever asked.   	2004 (Jan), ATR/Volt/ AMD (Contract Paralegal Temporary)  --  corporate litigation involving an array of legal issues before, during, and after one of their paralegals was having rotator cup surgery; worked with subpoena gathering process; worked with some HIPPA guideline issues; met with outside counsel and clients regarding various litigation issues, notarization of affidavits, and deposition preparation process.   	2003 (Dec)-2004 (May), ACS/BPS (Data Entry Clerk) – (the new Texas Medicaid Vendor)  -- began as a regular employee during the transition period of the old vendor to this new vendor of processing Texas Medicaid claims; worked in the Data Entry Department processing many types of claims and correspondence issues through a high tech system during the 3rd shift and moved later to the weekend shift mid-January and back to 3rd shift.  I left due to their incentive compensation structure and the company taking back the benefits of those working on the 3rd shift.   	2003 (Sept-Nov), EuroSoft /NHIC (Insurance Analyst Contractor) – (the old Texas Medicaid Vendor)  -- began as a temporary employee during the transition period of the this old vendor to the new vendor of processing Texas Medicaid claims; worked in the Torts Department as an Insurance Analyst processing and determining many Torts Claim amounts; working closely with many personal injury attorneys and Texas Medicaid clients; prepared files for transition to the new vendor.                                                                                               	  The Woodlands, TX/Conroe, TX  	 2003, Adecco/A Professional Image (Special Projects Temporary)  – asbestos litigation document management via eCounsel and other specialized legal programs at corporate legal department of Waste Management; data entry and contact with Call Center for credit card conversion for Citibank at Home Depot Grand Opening through custom program, etc; Staff Support Specialist cover at Tri-County MHMR and working on HIPAA Compliance issues.   	2002-2003, Whisenant & Associates (Paralegal/Office Administrator)  – in small law office, draft pleadings and other legal documents; calendar timelines and deadlines on TimeMatters; log in time via TimeSlips; supervise Receptionists/Secretaries; transcribe correspondence and document tapes from Attorney; legal research and investigation including some skiptracing and corporate/bankruptcy issues; focus on family, collections, product liability litigation, personal injury, real estate, and general civil litigation law matters in County, State, and Federal District Courts;  act as liaison with federal defense attorney’s office on transference of immigration litigation matters; file/client management; prepare and notarize affidavits; client contact and retention responsibilities; deposition summaries;  vendor coordination; special projects coordination; coordination of process serving on various cases; accounts receivables; coordinate and schedule depositions; responsible for basic computer maintenance and training of peers with various computer software programs; HR/Office Manager duties and responsibilities.    Houston, TX   	2001, M.D. Gibson & Associates, P.C. (Paralegal/Office Manager temporary)   - in a small law office, brought office up to date on TimeSlips billing system, equipment contracts and replacements; establish office flow with supplies process; collected on some past due accounts receivables accounts; prepare and notarize affidavits; transcribe correspondence and document tapes provided by attorneys; coordinate lender package turnarounds with various lenders; coordinate trust activities between financial trust provider and trust clients; assisted in legal clerk duties on real estate, landlord-tenant, and business start-up/corporate matters; filing of documents in County and State District Courts.  	 San Antonio, TX to Houston, TX	1997-2001, SBC’s Southwestern Bell Telephone (Manager OSP Construction Analysis) – maintained Technician Performance Scorecard for Texas regions, prepared 58-slide PowerPoint presentation for VP’s road tour announcing merger realignment, coordinated rollout processes for GPS installations & panic alarm updates for the $32.25 Million South Texas’ vehicle assets, litigation research for previous GPS vendor issues, coordinated Tech of the Future $7.5 Million computer rollouts for development, installation, and software updates in technician vehicles; PC Coordinator over $6 Million inventory in South Texas region; worked in relationship with legal department regarding damage prevention and litigation issues; trained peers and superiors on customized computer programs. 	  Charleston, SC   	1994, Adia Temporary (Special Project Paralegal)  – in a large law firm, perform document review of breast implant litigation for relevancy in suit against Dow Chemicals; deposition summaries; computerized documentation system updated for ease in filing and retrieving specific information.   No. Charleston, SC   	1994-1996, Gonzales & Gonzales (Paralegal)  – in a small law office, brought law firm into computer age & served as paralegal regarding prepare and coordinate real estate matters for closings, including drafting related documents, drafting municipal ordinance issues, draft and prepare family and probate law matter documents; filing documents in Municipal, County, and State Courts; some exposure to asbestos issues; coordinate and schedule depositions; prepare and notarize affidavits; lots of client contact; receptionist backup; trained peers on computer software programs; coordinate office supplies.  Interestingly enough this was a father-son law firm, both had been State Representatives of South Carolina and the father had founded North Charleston.  The father was, as a result the attorney involved in many of the City of North Charleston’s decisions and ordinances, and many litigation matters for other North Charleston businesses.   While there, the father ran for Mayor of North Charleston.   Charleston, SC  	 1995-1996, Guardian ad Litem of Charleston County (Guardian ad Litem Advocate)  – in a non-profit agency, investigate issues surrounding child abandonment, neglect or abuse cases; perform diligent searches for missing parents; review case records at Child Protective Services; prepare court reports which were turned to the various attorneys involved on the case, as well as Department of Human Services and the Court Judge; advocate for the child’s best interest in the courtroom. 	  Austin, TX   	1993-1994, Texas Department of Transportation (Special Project Department Secretary)  – in a State agency, assisted in development of Registration Tag System for the State of Texas; trained peers on computer software programs; coordinate office supplies.   	1991-1992, Ronquillo & DeWolf  (Special Project Paralegal/Office Manager)  – in a large (but small local) law firm, aided in a savings & loan litigation case on Lamar Savings & Loan Association closure through document organization, bate-stamping, recording and preservations; coordinate and schedule depositions; work with another attorney on insurance matters; deposition summaries; trained peers on computer software programs; coordinate office supplies.   	1991, City of Austin Law Department (Intern Paralegal)  – in a medium City law department, draft ordinances; attend City Hall meetings; legal research focused upon municipal, real estate and water/wastewater arbitration and litigation issues; deposition summaries; trained peers on computer software programs; responsible for finding a point of law which saved the City of Austin $450,000 on a real estate arbitration issue.   	1991-1994, CASA of Travis County, Inc. (Paralegal Internship/Court Appointed Special Advocate)  – in a non-profit agency, investigate issues surrounding child abandonment, neglect or abuse cases; perform diligent searches for missing parents; review case records at Department of Human Services; prepare court reports which were turned to the various attorneys involved on the case, as well as Department of Human Services and the Court Judge; advocate for the child’s best interest in the courtroom; brought into light a mistake that Department of Human Services did, which they were reprimanded in the Courtroom by the Judge; assisted juveniles in their Courtroom cases; successfully placed first abandoned child case with adoptive family and found many missing parents.   	1990-1991, Pope, Roberts & Warren (Legal Secretary)  –in a medium law firm, transcribe tapes provided by attorneys to prepare correspondence and legal documents & pleadings regarding various general litigation issues; deposition summaries; coordinate & schedule depositions; receptionist backup. Next step was pursuing the Legal Assistant Program at The University of Texas.   	1989-1990, Stewart Title of Lake Travis & Stewart Title of Austin, Texas (Escrow Assistant)  – in Texas established Title Company, reviewed files submitted for real estate closing, which included, but not limited to, coordinate surveys, pest control inspections, and other activities necessary for completion of closing; prepare documents and affidavits for closings; close contact with clients; notarize affidavits; assembled closing documents along with loan documents received from lender; post closing involved preparation of documents for clients, lenders, and documents to be filed with Travis, Williamson and Hays County Courts, as well as disbursement of funds to all parties involved in the transaction.   	1988-1990, Burnett Staffing (Legal Secretary Temporary)  – in a staffing agency, temporarily placed for legal secretaries as they went on their vacations, maternity leaves, etc; transcribe correspondence and document tapes provided by attorneys on various general litigation matters; coordinate and schedule depositions; file management; answer phone calls assist attorneys in some special projects; training peers on computer programs; worked for various sizes of law firms, including but not limited to Graves Dougherty and many others.          Education:    * 	In pursuit of a Criminal Justice degree, including focuses in Investigations and Victim Advocacies to improve my legal/private security background/knowledge.     * 	Possess a Legal Assistant Certificate from the University of Texas in Austin, TX (1991).   * 	Obtained HIPAA Compliance Certification.   * 	Texas Commission of Private Security – Level I (92.5) & Level II (85) testing.     Computer & Other Skills:   These encompass a sound working knowledge of a variety of business productivity-enhancing software packages, especially:  Microsoft Office Pro (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Publisher, Access), WordPerfect, Quicken, TimeSlips, TimeMatters, Business Objects, Business Warehouse, SAP Gui.  Have prepared many types of analytical reports which have included complex histogram and other graphs to illustrate process, progresses, or special emphasis points.  Have organized and coordinated order processing, credit and customer service departments as 13th employee in start-up companies like PC’s Limited (now known as Dell Computer Corporation) and Cactus Communications/Doctor’s Exchange, in additional to many years of experience in the retail market providing sales, cashier, and customer service roles (Oakdell Pharmacy, Foley’s, University Coop, etc.) as well as seasonal returns analysis roles at the Internal Revenue Service.  Further, have ability to read blueprints through some drafting/architectural training received at San Antonio College and The University of Texas at Austin.    Related Volunteer Activities:   Williamson County Crisis Center, 2004 – present (Round Rock, TX)  Montgomery County Genealogical and Historical Society & Research, 2000-3 (Conroe, TX) Advisory Board Member of Child Watch of North America, 2002-3 (Houston, TX) GAL of Charleston County (Guardian ad Litem), 1995-6 (Charleston, SC) CASA of Travis County (Court Appointed Special Advocate), 1991-4; 2004-present (Austin, TX) Girl Scout Workshop Facilitator on Child Abuse Awareness & Responsibility Issues, 1993 (Austin, TX) Documentation Exchange @ University of Texas, 1991-4 (Austin, TX) ProBar, 1991-4 (Austin, TX)    Professional Memberships:   American Society of Criminology (Member), 2003-present Toastmasters International (Greenspoint Area Toastmasters & Spring Ahead Toastmasters), 2000-3  National Legal Assistant Association (“NALA”), 1991-present Capital Area Paralegal Association, 1991-present   

						
</post>


<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... I imagine myself, sometimes, with the images of Elliot Gould, Angela Lansbury in Murder She Wrote, or Steven Cannell as he types the final at the end of a show he has worked upon, or even with the image of my own Mom creating her masterpieces (fiction and non-fiction; adult and children; prose and poetry) as I was growing up.  She would often have the "midnight oil" running (just kidding, no oil, but the image sounds more surreal than with a lamp on the desk) throughout all hours of the night.  Perhaps, that is where I get that from typing, now on the computer, until all hours of the night from?  Can that be a generational thing???  This blogging thing has been quite addictive.  In fact, it has been so much that my friend's son says that now I have become a bloghead.  Is there such a thing?  I realize that this has been going on for many years before I have jumped on the bandwagon during the past week, but I have so much to say that it has been interesting to blog away!!  My landline phone was disconnected today; I have rent due tomorrow; and I need to take an online defensive driving class -- yet, I am typing my thoughts and words down as if I were already an aspiring writer.  Well, maybe someday I will be! In the meantime, I am enjoying the beginning of this ride!! :)  Be sure to check out some of my friend's sites:   urlLink Books by Len Grossman (an self-published author in Connecticut)    urlLink Anton Dvorak's Memoires  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have had to take a defensive driving class recently for the improvement of my auto insurance records.  I hadn't taken one in many, many years.  Defensive driving classes (during the last time I took them) were taught primarily through community education programs and driving instruction schools.  Throughout the years, the list has been expanding to reach out to the community through offering them in comedy workshops, restaurants, online, and - the one I chose to do - through video rentals.     urlLink Take Home Traffic School  is available from  urlLink your local Blockbuster video store . (Note:  not all the Blockbuster stores offer this; you will have to call your local Blockbuster store to be sure!)  Other sites to refer to for additional informaiton, see:   urlLink Comedy Defensive Driving School   urlLink DMV - Defensive Driving   urlLink American Defensive Driving School   urlLink Driver Campus  urlLink Online Traffic Schools  urlLink Traffic School  urlLink I Drive Safely  urlLink Web Traffic School    There are many other avenues -- no excuses now for a person to save off of their insurance or get a ticket dismissed through a Defensive Driving program.  These options will fit even the person who has the strangest working schedule on Earth!! :)    Hope everyone will be driving safer on the road!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "Trust your hunches. They're usually based on facts filed away just below the conscious level."    Dr. Joyce Brothers  Psychologist and Television Personality   Trust is an underlying factor in every relationship.  The other day I spied a young couple at work sitting in cubicles next to each other; the woman heavily involved in her work; the man heavily involved in his work, but exploring the Y! personals while he was talking to customers in a minimized screen format so as to not be obvious.  Is it my responsibility to tell this young woman that her beau is perusing other possibilities??? I don't think so.  The young man's actions will catch up with him eventually -- especially, if they are even remotely dishonorable.  Perhaps, he is just exploring the possibilities before he asks her to marry him.  They make such a perfect looking couple. She has kids from a prior marriage and they are all living together.  I don't want to rock the boat if he is just looking to see what might be out there before he makes the life-long committment.  Hopefully, though, she won't be oblivious and distracted too much to see this behaviour and to not be in touch with her own instincts.  Trust is the foundation towards any relationship and if you cannot have that trust built firmly into your relationship, you truly don't have a relationship that will last.  Relationships built on distrust and deceipts can never last.   Ephesians 4:14 -- "Then we will no longer be like children, forever changing our minds about what we believe because someone has told us something different or because someone has deverly lied to us and made the lie sound like the truth."  Ephesians 4:15 -- "Instead, we will hold to the truth in love, becoming more and more in every way like Christ, who is the head of his body, the Church."  2 John -- "the truth that lives in us and will be in our hearts forever."   Part of finding a soulmate is largely determined by the amount of trust one can trust in the other, which is largely fully trusted until proven wrong.  Once proven wrong, it is difficult to truly rebuild that trust completely.  If any counselor is telling you that it is possible to rebuild that trust is only telling you that to build your confidence in the opportunities of rebuilding a relationship, but isn't being completely truthful to you.  The only time this because more than just a mere possibility is when both parties reside themselves to being completely honest and truthful to the other in order to rebuild the trust that became wavering.  The only thing to truly trust is your instincts; they are rarely wrong.  Any flags that are being sent up should be acknowledged and dealt with directly and head on before the situation escalates and becomes out of control and/or a relationship is inadvertently built upon lies and deceipts.  Prayers go to the couple that was observed the other day and anyone else who might be living lies and non-truths through distrusting and deceiptful ways of living.  Life is too short to waste in untrustworthy or deceiptful ways of living!! :)   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                    If You Hate Forwards, Read This!**    For all of you who delete fwds before you read them, this  is for you. I had not seen this before, but I am glad it fell into my lap from a friend.**    A man and his dog were walking along a road. The man was enjoying the scenery, when it suddenly occurred to him that he was dead. He remembered dying, and that the dog had been dead for years. He wondered where the road was leading them.  After a while, they came to a high, white stone wall along one side of the road. It looked like fine marble. At the top of a long hill, it was broken by a tall arch that glowed in the sunlight. When he was standing before it, he saw a magnificent gate in the arch that looked like mother of pearl, and the street that led to the gate looked like pure gold.  He and the dog walked toward the gate, and as he got closer, he saw a man at a desk to one side. When he was close enough, he called out, "Excuse me, where are we?" "This is Heaven, sir," the man answered. "Wow! Would you happen to have some water?" the man asked. "Of course, sir. Come right in, and I'll have some ice water brought right up."  The man gestured, and the gate began to open. "Can my friend," gesturing toward his dog, "come in, too?" the traveler asked. "I'm sorry, sir, but we don't accept pets." The man thought a moment and then turned back toward the road and continued the way he had been going. After another long walk, and at the top of another long hill, he came to a dirt road which led through a farm gate that looked as if it had never been  closed.  There was no fence. As he approached the gate, he saw a man inside, leaning against a tree and reading a book. "Excuse me!" he called to the reader. "Do you have any  water?" "Yeah, sure, there's a pump over there" The man pointed to a place that couldn't be seen from outside the gate. "Come on in."  "How about my friend here?" the traveler gestured to the dog. "There should be a bowl by the pump." They went through the gate, and sure enough, there was an old fashioned hand pump with a bowl beside it. The traveler filled the bowl and took a long drink himself, then he gave some to the dog. When they were full, he and the dog walked back toward the man who was standing by the tree waiting for them.  "What do you call this place?" the traveler asked. "This is Heaven," was the answer. "Well, that's confusing," the traveler said. "The man down the road said that was Heaven, too." "Oh, you mean the place with the gold street and pearly gates? Nope. That's Hell."  "Doesn't it make you mad for them to use your name like  that?" "No. I can see how you might think so, but we're just happy that they screen out the folks who'll leave their best friends behind."  Sometimes, we wonder why friends keep forwarding jokes to us without writing a word, maybe this could explain: When you are very busy, but still want to keep in touch, guess what you do -- you forward jokes. When you have nothing to say, but still want to keep contact, you forward jokes. When you have something to say, but don't know what, and don't know how, you forward jokes." And to let you know that: you are still remembered, you are still important, you are still loved, you are still cared for, guess what you get? A forwarded joke from  me.  So my friend, next time if you get a joke, don't think that I have sent you just a joke, but that I have thought of you today and wanted to send you a smile.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A friend has forwarded me this quip that was sent to him:   Smiling is infectious, You catch it like the flu. When someone smiled at me today,  I started smiling too.  I passed around the corner, and someone saw my grin.  When he smiled I realized, I'd passed it on to him. I thought about that smile, then I realized its worth.  A single smile just like mine, could travel the earth.  So, if you feel a smile begin, don't leave it undetected.  Let's start an epidemic quick, and get the world infected!   I seriously believe in smiles as they are truly infectious.  They can even be seen through the phones.  I talk on the phones for a living so I know.  Even the must riley of clients who have a beef about this or that are often joking with me by the end of the conversation.  Some say I have a gift or talent in getting a good raport with others.  Tell you a little secret though -- SMILE, you will make someone's day and do your part in generating smiles across the world!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This time last year I was unwinding from a mission trip I took to Guatemala which forever affected the way I think I think about the world outside of the comfort zone.  Guatemala is a beautiful country -- beautiful mountains, beautiful Mayan temples/pyramids, beautiful culture, and so much more.  I loved meeting the people there and I missed not going again this year due to my own financial situation this year; however, I have many photos that were just amazing and memorable that I reflect on often.  I have many tapes that I recorded sounds and voices of meetings and discussions that we had during our mission trip.  I hope to be able to get them slowly translated through the Monday Mission Minute series I will do on this blog site.  I really am looking forward to sharing reflections and transcriptions with you.  If I can figure out the photo inserts on these blogs, I shall be sharing those with you as well.  The trip involved meetings with other preachers and Church programs,  CEDEPCA ,  CESSMAQ , a women's coop making Guatemalan fabrics, a Mayan Priest, and many noteable villages.  The trip was sponsored by the  Presbytery Mission .  It was a trip that I will certainly never forget the faces of the people I spoke too and saw.  I am looking forward to sharing with you my memories of the Guatemala trip.  I wish I had known about these blogs back then; I would have certainly created my Guatemala diary log back then... :)  Hasta la vista!  ps  I have decided to make this series its own blog at  Bluebonnet Missions !  Look forward to seeing you there!! :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It seems that not too many people share faith in God instead of wasting their lives away worrying about what the tomorrow will bring.   Matthew 6:30  and  Matthew 6:31    Matthew 6:32  and  Matthew 6:33  refers to God knowing our needs and Him supplying what we actually need on a daily basis as we continue living our lives for Him.  My own Grandma and Big Mama (ironically called that because she was Grandma's mother; she was extremely tall and skinny!) served as prime examples and role models of living their lives for Him.  Without fail they both taught Sunday School each and every week of their adult lives in a small Christian Church in a small Texas town, raised vegetables and fruits and shared their wealth through baking breads and jellies to share with others, made their own quilts, sewed clothes for the grandchildren, had patience while teaching others about gardening and sewing, and lived very simplistic lives.  I think many of us tend to forget our roots and look for the same glimmers in the materialistic world that never seems to satisfy us as a whole.  Mansions are great -- but would be better served in housing the homeless, perhaps.    How much is too much?  The answer to this is probably when it consumes your every moment for existence on this earth to achieve the greatest wealth of all, when all we need to do is look at our own hearts and understand the wealth we achieve each and every day -- especially, when we help others to improve their quality of life (empowering them to help themselves through a variety of resources in the communities), when we get ourselves involved with helping others (there are so many non-profit organizations that are just clammering at the bit for volunteers), and when we are just being prepared to listen to our friends, family, and strangers that we encounter (not necessarily in that order).  Many people quote  Matthew 6:34  without realizing that they are quoting it directly from the Bible.  It is appropriate, though, to end this blog with the words from the verse of  Matthew 6:34 :  "So don't worry about tomorrow, for tomorrow will bring its own worries.  Today's trouble is enough for today."  Isn't that a great thought for today???    
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As part of my re-learning process, I have been focused today on cleaning up my blogs a bit by cleaning up the URL references I have made in the prior blogs and typing, for example   CASA  instead of making the actual URL reference (www.nationalcasa.org).  This process certainly adds clarity with the blog.  Right now it takes a little extra time to do; however, I am hoping that it will become as second nature as to typing this blog in the first place!  As I become more adept with the HTML, perhaps you will get to see other fancy developments with my blog. :)  Laters...
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Courts have always set precedences for various caselaw on a diverse array of matters.  It is quite difficult to keep up with all the law changes; even if you got every digest publication produced and put on the shelves.  Within an organization that I am involved with in Williamson County, Texas, they are considering getting a Court Watch group organized.  Court Watch is a group of volunteers that go to various court rooms and write up what they see in the Courtroom.  The primary focus would be domestic violence and sexual assault issues; however, these groups could easily have focuses on a variety of issues.  It is said that there are statitics on increased conviction rates where the Court Watch group volunteers are organized.  It seems like a good idea in order to ensure that those who abuse, neglect, abandon or sexually assault others dont end up getting a mere slap on the hand.  The people in this Nation have come a long way since the 1980s where it became more of a focus upon the awareness of these problems existing.  Statistics are now seeing a decrease of domestic violence in many areas with the increased awareness; however, we have to ensure that the courts do their job and not let these violators get away with their criminalistic acts.  To break the cycle, the victim isn't the only one that needs to break the cycle by not becoming a victim anymore; the cycle needs to be broken through many spokes of the wheel to ensure complete anilation of the problem (or, at least, as complete an anilation as one can expect).  It may never be completely wiped out of existence, but we can certainly strive for it -- right???  Some other websites to check out (just to get you started)on these issues:      Eagle Forum's Court Watch   Court Watchers Changing Courthouse Rules   Supreme Court Watch (Holt, Rinehart and Winston)   Results of Silent Witness National Initiative       
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I lived in a pretty naive world growing up.  While I was familiar with people controlling others, I was not familiar with alcoholism and a variety of other addictions that normal, everyday people have in the world.  It was simply not discussed and we had rose colored view points on society growing up.  In my first marriage, I was not only introduced to someone very controlling but an alcoholic as well.  This certainly burst my rose-colored viewpoint on the world; one that I was certainly not prepared to deal with.  Now, almost 20 years later, I have been well educated about the real world and have left that marriage a little over 10 years ago.  I have progressed in being able to be in a position to help others through the same adversities that I had experienced in my first marriage.  Not only have I been involved in  CASA (Court Appointed Special Advocate  and GAL (Guardian ad Litem) programs for the abused, neglected and abandoned children in the court systems, I have been involved with  Toughlove ,  Family Eldercare  and Crisis Center programs to aid the elderly, domestic violence affected, and sexually assaulted, or battered men and women.  I hear constantly about people being controlled, abused, neglected, or abandoned emotionally and physically all the time.  With all the new laws enacted, this has not been anilated by any means; however, we can do all that we can to help.  No one deserves to be controlled by another person.  A marriage should be a team effort where one is not better than the other; but, where each other compensates for each others weaknesses to have a strong united marriage.  Anything less is working against the grain of the wood and will only serve to heed progress throughout the life.  Each person deserves to be respected and treated as a human being no matter what his or her disabilities or weaknesses might be.  Everyone has the right to be empowered to do the best that they can be.  Have you empowered someone you love -- or even a stranger* -- today?  Look around you...empower another person not to be controlled by others, but to be in control of their destinies along with the aid of their network of spouse, family, and friends.  Make the connections possible.  Provide them resources available -- numbers of crisis centers, local Churches, samaritan counseling centers, neighbors, safe houses, etc.   Let them know that they are not alone.   * Hebrews 13:2:  "Don't forget to show hospitality to strangers for some who have done this have visited angels without realizing it!"  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While I just stumbled upon this venue the other night, I am discovering that people have been blogging for years!  That is definately news to me!  Where have I been????  I thought I was uptodate on everything in the computer world; this only goes to serve that I definately have no clue about the truer scope of the technological world.  I had thought myself to be very computer savvy.  While there remains a great vastness of people out there that are still far less computer savvy than myself, I am slowly discovering a new world out there when exploring a way to access the new Beta of the GMail being produced by Google.  In an absorbed exploration mode, I discovered that there are as vast a number of blogs created as varied as the bloggers are themselves.  Some are extremly creative in their blogging; while others utilize it to do their daily journaling.  I have passed along the information about how to build a blog page to several of my friends yesterday and one of them has reported back to me that he has created his own.  As soon as I get his exact blog URL, I will certainly share it with you all as well.  UPDATE:  This is  Anton's URL  -- check it out.  He just started it today!!  If you are still unsure of whether or not you would want to blog, I suggest that you go for it -- after all, what do you have to lose? You certainly have much more to gain from it - a venue to demonstrate your creativity; a venue to meet others with the same interests as yours; a venue for you to share what is on your mind; a venue to post things that may be of interest to others; a venue to brush up on your writing skills ... the list could go on for-ever!  I hope that you all become happy bloggers!!  If you do choose to have this as one of your missions in life, I hope that you will share your URL with me as well.  Looking forward to seeing more happy bloggers.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bicycling has become a more an popular sport throughout the years -- especially, with Lance Armstrong winning the Tour de France for the past few years.  I was in the United Way office today and they had a Williamson County Bicycle Map available. It was interesting because it not only mentioned the pathways designed specifically for bicyclists in this region, it also specifies the safety features of various roadways and highways throughout the county.  It does have a disclaimer that it "was developed to aid bicyclists in finding their way safely through Williamson County.  This is not a map of existing bikeways, but an evaluation of Williamson County's street and road network."  This particular map was produced through a company called ProLinks (Productivity Links, Inc.).  I would suggest contacting them to see if they have such a map designed for your county as well --  ProLinks .  Special note:  This same company, its corporate offices strategically placed in The Woodlands TX, has been involved with organizations such as the Montgomery County Genealogical and Historical Society and the Taminia Community with projects involving GPS mapping of various cementaries in their county.  Their projects are limitless and have many more listed on their website; be sure to check out  ProLinks !! :)   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It has always been my motto to focus on the good and positive in things, as well as try to live my live in accordance with Timothy II 2:15, "Work hard so God can approve you.  Be a good worker, one who does not need to be ashamed and who correctly explains the word of truth."  I am not perfect by any means; if anyone claims that he/she is, they are not being truthful either to themselves or to those who are around them.    My approach to life has been to empower others.  Empower.  I love that word because it implies of great strength.  As such, I try to instill strength in others through boosting their own esteems as well as providing them guidance to finding the resources that they need to succeed in their lives.  To me, there is no greater fulfillment than to see others being empowered to achieve their successes and for them to actually achieve the successes that they were empowered to do.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, yesterday was my daughter's first day of her senior year at high school.&nbsp; It is a significant year for her -- and for me.&nbsp; We have been through a lot with each other throughout the many years and without each other much for the last couple of years.&nbsp; We have had many good times and many rough times, but seem to hang in there together in the end.&nbsp;  Last week began my college courses online as well.&nbsp; This will be an interesting term with my working and my college courses, as well as her in her senior year at school and taking a college course or two as well....  Hopefully, neither of us will have our hair pulled out in the end..... well, I think we can make it so long as we don't have any major kinks in the road (ie my car died on me tonight after taking her to purchase some school supplies -- nothing like God placing more hurdles for us to cross when it just seems like we have had enough hurdles!!).&nbsp; Please say your prayers for us that we maintain our sanity -- okay??? :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A conversation I was having with someone the other day said, "So, you are a techie?", after I was explaining some of the things that I am involved with.&nbsp; Me????  &nbsp;  What did this mean?&nbsp; Was he trying to say that I am a Nerd??? Hmmm... I am not sure that I would "resemble" that remark; however, come to think of it....  &nbsp;  I started in 1984 working for Michael Dell when he was operating as PC's Limited, and nearly every job that I have been involved with has involved a great deal of software applications and teaching others computer usage in some form or fashion.&nbsp; I have a logical mind that feels challenged by some critical thinking processes.&nbsp; But, does that make me a techie???? hmmm...  &nbsp;  I also have a creative side of me that is often challenged by the endless possibilities that can occur within any particular software program, but needs far more than what the computer/technological world can supply me for resources of creative media.  &nbsp;  Additionally, I probably am the only girl that can attest to helping her Dad with putting together Heathkit TVs, etc (back in the day), having a Lionel train set up on a large plywood board table, a playable victrola, a library full of books on two walls of the room, a handmade radio and turntable made with visible vaccum tubes, and extra stored gidgets and gadgets that could not be placed in anyother part of the house but my very own bedroom!! :)&nbsp; Perhaps, I was destined to be a Geek, Nerd, Techie -- or, whatever the label is these days by mere osmosis of being around my Dad????&nbsp; Who knows.  &nbsp;  However, if being one of these labels, means also that I can master some critical level thinking skills, then I guess I am fitting the bill to the -T.&nbsp; In this day and age, it would be unrealistic to say that technology never affects our&nbsp;everyday existance and means for living; in fact, it is quite clearly the opposite that is true.&nbsp; I yearn to see what might be coming about in the future of our world.&nbsp; I have seen technology advance by leaps and bounds.&nbsp;&nbsp; I am so excited to be a part of the growth and expansion process by providing technical assistance to callers calling into the center regarding an assundry of issues.&nbsp; Why, in just the last 25 years, there has been an incredible advancement made in technology; I am so&nbsp;excited to see what the next 25 years will bring that I am quite literally sitting on the edge of my seat!!&nbsp; Technological advancements are only limited by our own imaginations.&nbsp; Just imagine where we will be!! :)  &nbsp;  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay... I am at it again this morning. I did another movie review -- this time on one of my favorite movies that many people probably missed,  urlLink Return to Me . Let me know what you think!!   I am off and running to my other less creative jobs... :(   More to follow soon. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       For one of my classes this term, I had to write a paper already.  Hope you enjoy reading it!!!   	 What do I want to be when I grow up?   That is what you are actually asking, isn’t it??? I still don’t know; therefore, this project is difficult to do.  I am studying Criminal Justice because it is fitting with my background of a paralegal (a field of which I have worked throughout the past 15 years).  I don’t necessarily want to be working in the police department (the first career people think is your goal when you mention you are studying criminal justice), but I do want to be employed in a position that requires best utilization of my investigative and deductive reasoning skills.     These skills were used to a degree with my role as a paralegal; however, I am looking for something a little more rewarding – for example, I have volunteered as an advocate in the CASA (Court Appointed Special Advocate) Program; Child Advocates; and GAL (Guardian ad Litem).  All of these experiences were definitely rewarding in working with the children involved in the Courts as a result of abuse, neglect or abandonment; the problem is that working as a volunteer doesn’t pay the bills.   As a result, I have considered the options of being a director of one of these programs, or a similar program, in the future; however, it is somewhat a competitive market to be in because these programs aren’t just a dime a dozen, especially those that pay an income that one can live off of.      Alternatively, I am looking into owning a security business with a friend of mine that has more than 25 years of actual security experience in this area.  The idea is that the combination of his experience and my background as a paralegal and office management would be a combination that would give us an edge on most of the security companies in the area.  Learning the management of a security office would be new to me in that it would be in the security industry; however, I am not new to managing offices and/or various projects.  I am well skilled in those areas.  Management of a security office requires a license in this State though, therefore, my title would be that of a receptionist.   Although the title of receptionist would seem minimal and not worthy of my level of skills and abilities, it is going to provide a great jumping board to learning the field, obtaining a split of commissions for contracts that I would help to bring on board to build and sustain the company, learning the rules and regulations of the Private Security Commission, etc.  These roles would enable me to see the whole picture being developed.   In the future, my friend and I hope to be able to set up our own security business.  We have already talked with members of the Board and they are keeping an eye on us because of what we can both bring to the security industry when we do begin our own company.  The would be the ultimate goal for us to accomplish so that we can eventually work not as hard as the worker bees and be able to enjoy life a little bit more; however, that probably won’t be seen for another 20-30 years at least.   Other avenues that bring interest to me include being able to persue studying how to capture identity thieves and other computer related issues.   There is another whole avenue waiting to be explored and accomplished.  I would love to be on a team exploring those capturing options as I already thoroughly enjoy all sorts of computer aided research and writing, web developments (see http://Bluebonnetfields.blogspot.com and other links stemming off of that one), and so much more.  Between all my diverse skills and abilities, I am certain that someday I will figure out “what I want to be when I grow up”!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Interesting.  Checking out some  urlLink Yahoo venues  after checking my  urlLink Yahoo ,  urlLink GMail ,  urlLink Earthlink  and  urlLink DonEasy  email earlier this morning and discovered that I can also  urlLink write Movie reviews  through there.... and, we all know, that I am loving to write so much that I am seemingly turning into a bloggerhead ... hee hee....  I (pant, pant) must t y p e my blogggggggeerrr....(zzzzzzzz)...... (even if it is 2am when normal people are sleeping!!!) just kidding....  Even so, I have made an attempt at a review on  urlLink Finding Forrester  earlier today before heading off to work.  Let me know what you think.  Would I make it as a movie critic?  Does it inspire you to aspire to see the movie????  Any suggestions for future reviews???? 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Met up with my brother yesterday afternoon.  He brought with him, Brandi, who who just absolutely perfectly personable and interesting.  Anyhow, they told us about how my brother had taken her to the prom in High School...and about 12 years later, they are happening to meet up with one another once again.  Who would have thought that someone who lives in NY could meet up with this TX gal after not seeing her for more than 12 years?  It must be fate.    The sparkles in their eyes, the friendly banter they had going, the caring actions they did for one another was fabulously grand and, hopefully (don't want to jinx them though) this might lead on to a longer relationship???? Only time will tell.  In the meantime, I am keeping my fingers crossed....they are such a cute couple. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is amazing as the summer digresses and the Fall starts to appear around the corner (well, after we get through August), we are all finding ourselves surrounded with three people under one roof all involved with some aspects of school -- (1) I am working on my Criminal Justice degrees through  urlLink Kaplan College , as well as training for local Crisis Center and  urlLink CASA , (2) daughter in her senior year at a local Charter School and taking some courses at a local college, and (3) a friend's son being enrolled through a Software Applications degree program through  urlLink ITT Technical Institute .  Things are a little rough getting everyone settled in, as well as focused upon their respective needs; but, hopefully, we won't end up being three bald folks by the time this upcoming semester is complete!!  That, certainly, won't be a pretty site!!   Right now, it is complicated by the fact that my daughter has lots of spyware programs downloaded on her computer through various sites she goes to download the documents.  We are running around fast and furious to make sure that it doesn't bring my computer down as well.  I have had enough down time during last term; I certainly don't want a repeat of that...  Pray for us??? at least, for all of us to keep our sanity.    My academic advisor forwarded this to me yesterday -- it is certainly well appreciated and applicable to our concerns at hand.      The other side    When your skills are challenged, you can become far more capable. When your beliefs are challenged they can become immensely more compelling and persuasive.   When your intentions are challenged, it can make you more determined and committed. When your faith is challenged, it can grow even stronger.   The downside of challenge is that it can be difficult to go through. The upside of challenge is that it's great to have been through.   When you arrive at a challenge, take a moment to look at it from the other side. Imagine all that will be gained by working your way through it.   The bigger and more imposing it appears when you first encounter it, the more value you'll have gained when the challenge is behind you. And that will set you up to conquer even bigger challenges, and to enjoy even more substantial rewards.   Give your best to the challenges. And what you get will be even better.   -- Ralph Marston  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Very interesting!&nbsp; The setting up of the wireless system wasn't quite as involved as I had anticipated.  I called the   urlLink Time Warner  tech support a couple times and viola! it was done.  Amazing....  Technology happening at an accelerated rate!  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        PRAYER:  Set before our minds, O heavenly Father, the example of our Lord Jesus Christ, who when he was upon earth found joy in doing the will of him that sent him, and in finishing his work.  When many are coming and going, and there is little quiet, give us grace to remember him who knew neither impatience of spirit nor confusion of work, but in the midst of all his labors kept a tranquil heart, at leisure from itself to serve and sympathize; through the same Jesus Christ our Lord.  Amen.  The Book of Worship of the United Methodist Church   There comes a time when assistance is needed to be asked for in order to complete a task to meet the bigger picture of the goals set forth and one should not be afraid to ask.  After all, have you not heard the buzz going around at someone's funeral wherein they were saying, "Why didn't _______ (you fill in the blank), just ask for help? We would have been glad to help them?"  People are just afraid of asking for help -- feeling like that it is downgrading to admit that they need assistance and/or just plain ol' too proud to ask.  Part of being humble though is knowing just when to ask for assistance.  There are many organizations available to provide assistance for when you need that little extra to get you through a particularily rough period of time.  One of the more widely known charitable organizations is the  urlLink St. Vincent de Paul Society ; there are others more locally known which can be found through your local Churches and/or phone books.  I am not sure who coined the phrase, "Be it ever so humble, there is no place like home", but that phrase seems to eminate that being of a humble heart is truly a home.  One must remember that when things start getting rough and you are trying to keep a home together, it is best to start by humbling oneself to ask for assistance.  There is no time like the present...  Have a humble heart -- Have a humble home!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I must admit that I have been fighting from making this huge step -- argumentatively due to the budgetary reasons. However, now that my daughter is back home with me and she has a computer of her own, it is now necessary to consider the wireless option because  she will be starting school next week  (  urlLink Time Warner  was going to charge me double for adding another modem to the account, or only $15 more for getting a wireless router, not to mention that they couldn't install it for another 3 weeks with the back to schoolers already lined up )  and we live in an apartment  ( no need to have wires being strung throughout the house to get us hooked up unnecessarily !)....They have asked me to bring in my old modem (which I have only had for a couple of months) to exchange it for the wireless router and equipment; I am wondering why though, because one would still need a modem, unless they had a gateway (including the modem with the router).  Well, I'll see in a little bit....  If you don't see me back on line posting my daily postings, you can probably be assured that the wireless set up that they are giving me today is not working right.  They  say  that it is pretty much plug and play.... we'll see how accurate that is!!    Wish me luck . . . :)   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         "It is good to have money and the things that money can buy, but it's good too, to check up once in a while and make sure you haven't lost the things money can't buy."  George Lorimer 1867-1937, Editor of "Saturday Evening Post"   Volunteerism, a act of committing time towards a project benefitting others who need assistance -- making ends meet, feeding a family, fighting for their own rights, etc.  God mentions throughout the Bible to "work hard"; however, does that necessarily mean working hard only if you get paid for it?  I don't think so.  I believe that while money is a necessary evil to get exist in this world (ensuring a roof over the head, food on the table, etc.), it isn't meant to be everything.  "Working hard" to me also includes looking out for one's neighbors and community.  It surprises to me how many people you ask to help in a particular situation ask if they will get compensated in some way for helping and/or ask what will they benefit from it.  To me, it is not a matter of what I will benefit from it; but, rather, how can I best benefit others.  The greatest pleasure can be obtained from helping others -- and no money can ever buy that.  I guess that I just can't comprehend such a response since I have volunteered many, many hours to political campaigns; being an advocate and voice for abused, neglected and abandoned children (as a  urlLink CASA  and Guardian ad Litem volunteer); being an advocate and voice for the elderly (as a  urlLink Family Eldercare  volunteer); being an advocate and voice for the abused, neglected and abandoned women and children (as a Crisis Center volunteer); being a delegate to another country for assistance with their programs to those trying to improve their quality of lives (through the Presbyterian Missionary Program); and so many other opportunities.  If you haven't ever volunteered, I would suggest you contacting your Church, local  urlLink Red Cross , and other non-profit organizations to see where your best fit might be.  If you still have not a clue, you can also go online and sites, such as  urlLink Volunteer Match  or  urlLink Taking It Global  (for a more universal approach) will aid in matching you up with a best fit scenario before you lose out in not realzing during your lifetime the things that money can't buy in a million years!! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "You don't get to choose how you're going to die, or when. You can decide how you're going to live now."  Joan Baez Singer/Songwriter   Life is full of choices.  That is what I have been preaching to my daughter since she was little.  I have tried to enstill that in her -- sometimes, I think she hears me; sometimes, I think she doesn't; or, perhaps, she is choosing not to listen.  Whatever the case, I am hoping that she learns from her bad choices and thrives on the good choices.  I'll be the first to admit that I am not perfect by any means.  My daughter, at nearly 17 years old now, should be fully aware of that.  I have made no bones about it; however, I have continually moved on learning from those bad choices to get where I am today.  I choose to live for the moment and the future rather than dwelling upon what I have done wrong throughout my life.  If asked, I will gladly share my past with others so that they can learn; however, that is a far cry from dwelling upon it.  In fact, I have been asked to speak on behalf some non-profit organizations to share with others my history so that I could inspire others into knowing that there is hope for change to occur.  Today, from the small Church I attend here, the pianist there is celebrating her 96th Birthday.  Being that I am only 45 years old today, I know that I should have at least another 45 years to go, if not  much, much  more (my maternal Grandfather was 96 years old, my paternal Great-Grandmother was 98 years old, etc. when they died). Here is to hoping and praying that my next 45 plus years are less traumatic and more celebrating of life's good pleasures and moments! :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Life certainly does take its twists and turns.  Since I moved here last Fall, I haven't been back to where I had been living for three years prior much.  However, one very cute older couple's daughter visited the small Church we attend nearby with them today.  This daughter had been one of my many friends I had at the prior Church; it was nice to be able to see each other again.  Although our reunion was dampered by the discussion of our beloved pianist at our old church dying recently of a sudden death.  The pianist's funeral is today and neither of us are able to attend.  She shared though with me the shocking events that took place recently:  the pianist's husband leaving her last Fall, her diabetes kicking in strong, some seizures, and rumors of some sort of cancer that was over taking her body.  One of the General Session members went to her house and found her dead.  Having found my own husband dead in our apartment nearly two years ago, I know the rush of emotions he must have felt and probably still feels even though the pianist wasn't his own wife; however, we are a close knit group.  As such, I am sure the rush of emotions were just as strong as if it were his own wife.  What then makes this day glorious?  I think today's sermon helped to make today glorious as serving as a reminder to be humbling.  The pianist was very humbling and never let it be known to the congregation that she had diabetes or other ailments, yet she served God in bringing music and joy to others. She never once complained and continued to serve God to the best of her ability.  Do I think that she was, perhaps, wrong in not letting others know of her ailments?  Yes, to a degree; she just didn't want to come off as a complainer; however, sometimes things need to be shared with others, and that in itself can be a very humbling experience to admit that one is not perfect.  One particular verse stood out among the others being read today --  Philippians 2:3 :  "Don't be selfish; don't live to make a good impression on others.  Be humble, thinking of others as better than yourself."  I really like that verse for some reason, in addition to my other favorite verse 2 Timothy 2:15.  I think I will add that to my creed.  My Grandma seemed to live in this accordance; she certainly didn't care what others thought of her impression upon others; she was simply herself and thrived on helping others out.  My life has been modeled after that; I hope any pray that I can live up to my Father's expectations, as nicely summarized in Philippians 2:12-17 . . .  "Dearest friends, you were always so careful to follow my instructions when I was with you.  And now that I am away you must be even more careful to put into action Gods' saving work in your lives, obeying God with deep reverence and fear.  For God is working in you, giving you the desire to obey him and the power to do what pleases him.  In everything you do, stay away from complaining and arguing, so that no one can speak a word of blame against you.  You are to live clean, innocent lives as children of God in a dark world full of crooked and perverse people.  Let your lives shine brightly before them.  Hold tightly to the word of life, so that when Christ returns, I will be proud that I did not lose the race and that my work was not useless.  But even if my life is to be poured out like a drink offering to complete the sacrifice of your faithful service (that is, if I am to die for you), I will rejoice, and I want to share my joy with all of you.  And you should be happy about this and rejoice with me."       A Prayer:   Thou who art over us, Thou who art one of us, Thou who art: Give me a pure heart, that I may see thee;      a humble heart, that I may hear thee;      a heart of love, that I may serve thee;      a heart of faith, that I may abide in thee.  Amen.  Dag Hammerskjold, Sweden, 20th century.      A Prayer: 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Everything works out in the end. If it hasn't worked out, it's not the end.  -  Unknown    As I was reading my email this morning, I came along this quote.  Funny, it comes after a month of turmoil because I am not bringing in enough income to make ends meet and the day after my interview for the promotion at work.  I sure could have things working out for me in the end for a change.  It would certainly be a long time coming.  I did get my daughter back in with me; this is good.  I had the interview at work; this is good.  I have a friend's son focused upon working towards a career in computers, with an appointment at a technical school next week; this is good.  I am helping the women's shelter get a much needed interior paint job next week, as well as getting trained on their phone systems; this is good.  Recently I discovered a way to take Spanish for virtually free (just paying $8 to the senior center, and they'll let me in without qualifying as a senior, and $11 for the workbook); this is good.  A good friend of mine reported to me last night that she got the job she had been vying for during the past couple of months; this is good.  Are things really going to work out in the end?  Hopefully, the "end" is not all that close for me, however, I certainly wish for more good coming my way than not for now!!  Is that asking for too much????  I don't think so.  In fact, good things are already starting to come along my way.  Life can be good!! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today brings a little excitement in that I am scheduled for an interview today at my place of employment for a position that will give me progressively more responsibility.  Duties will include administrative needs for the Operations area where I'll be able to utilize my statistical and analytical background.  In supporting myself and two others, I am hoping that it will also include a significant pay increase; however, I am going to be thankful for any level of pay increase at this time.  Times have been tough during the past few years where the economy has seemed to have slumped to an all-time low.  I have applied for several positions at my place of employment.  If it isn't meant to be for me to have this particular position, I truly hope that this will be the first of many interviews to come and that I will find the perfect niche soon!! :)  Say your prayers for me today...  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Men!  A friend of mine called yesterday to tell me that he FINALLY went to the doctor's office yesterday, reporting that, not only did he have bronchitis and a severe kidney infection, he nearly was put in the hospital for more than a month!!  I have been telling him for months to go see the doctor...  My late husband refused to go to the doctor's office too...and, look where that got him.  Actually, his excuse was that he was waiting for the insurance to kick in, which he was only about 2 weeks from the insurance kicking in.  So sad.  That doesn't really say a lot for our medical insurance programs.  The affordability of the health insurance programs has been just insane (along with, of course, the costs of auto insurance programs).  Don't get me wrong.  I am not for socialized medicine at all; however, there should be a happy medium somewhere in between that the health insurance program becomes more affordable for all & not just those few that can afford it.  Who are the underwriters of the insurance policies to choose between who can have a quality of life and those who can't?  It seems strange to me that they act like Gods and create most of the policies way beyond the reach of the typical, average American individual.  Can you tell that this is one of my pet peeves? Well, enough of my soapbox -- well, for the day!! :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I opened my email up yesterday, I was notified that she was incredibly ill; today, I opened up my email and discovered that she went on to be with the Lord today.  My jaw just dropped.  She played piano at an old Church that I had attended while living in The Woodlands.  I got to know her through my late husband who sung in the Choir that she accompanied nearly every Sunday and special events.  I continued to have opportunities to get to know her a little better as I met her in other activities at the Church as well.  I had told her (for example) that I, too, had loved to play the piano but I didn't have the opportunity to play it since the time that I left home for college (many, many, many moons ago).  She offered to teach me to bring back my "swing" in the piano, if I would find a piano of some type to practice upon.  Our paths would cross often here and there, and she would ask if I found my piano yet?  Sometimes, she would add that maybe I could just practice on the piano at the Church sometime.  Other emotions resurfaced as I began to think about her kind heart and how she accompanied the choir who sang at my late husband's memorial service.  It meant so much for me to have them there at my late huband's memorial service, especially since singing in the Church was a passion for him.  My husband will have been gone to be with the Lord in just a few months from now (on November 11th) for two years.  I didn't think I would be quite so affected still from my husband's own death.  It clearly is something that I will have to continue to deal with for many years to come.   Dear God:  Please sound the trumpets for Laurie who so passionately played in the Church for you and make room for her to play for You in Heaven.  Please wrap your everloving arms around her, remove any degree of pain or suffering that she had endured here on Earth, and make room for her to play for the angels who sing for You.  In Your name, I pray.  Amen. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My daughter and I were very close while she was growing up.  We did a lot together, and were each other's best friend.  She confided so much to me and I would advise her what I would do, etc.  Things got crazy in 2001 though.  Both her own father (I had been separated from since 1989 and divorced officially since 1991) and I had found other people to get married to.  Her father had been out of her life for many years prior to that and started showering her with gifts.  She was beginning to think that the grass was much greener on the other side and started throwing things like, "My daddy will buy that for me", "Daddy would let me do that", etc.   I wasn't in a position to give in or compete and I did the hardest thing for me to do -- take her to her Dad's to live @ 14 years age.  Last September (almost a complete year after my husband I was married to in 2001 died from a heart attack), she had asked me to move back to Austin, and again I was faced with a little bit of competition, i.e. "I'll move in with you if you will buy me a pillow top mattress" etc.  I, again, was not in a position to compete or give in; so, I did not.  Tonight, she surprised the heck out of me by announcing that she was going to move back in with me!!  I was pleasantly shocked and amazed.  My little daughter is actually growing up.  I had hoped that I would hear her utter those words long before now; however, I don't want to jinx myself yet.  Right now, she is asleep in my bed.  I love having her back...  Sometimes, I guess, a little firmness in a stance actually does pay off in the end.  I pray to God that he blesses her soul for some good decisions that she has been making recently and continues to watch over her as she proceeds onward with her life journey. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bicycling in Austin, Texas, has become more popularized through the notariety of Austinite, Lance Armstrong, through his urlLink Tour de France  feats.  A more up to date tracking of the race can be found through the  urlLink Tour de France 2004 Live Result Tracking .  Athletes have taken championships in sequential years noting a great ability to endure great odds; and, Lance Armstrong has managed to do so for the last 5 years in a row.  What a remarkable man.  Will he be able to pull the #6 year of being a Tour de France champion is anyone's guess.  It is fortunate that he has been able to achieve the 5 years in a row....in the meantime, Austinites and fans throughout the world are cheering him forward.  Go, Lance, Go!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink Guatemala Journal Notes . . .    can be interesting tidbits to read.  These Journal Notes were written in my Journal last May and June in anticipation of my first mission trip outside of the United States.  I have moved them to my  urlLink Bluebonnet Missions  website in order to be able to share them more readily with others.  This is, also, just a quick glance of the excitement leading up to my Guatemala Mission Trip.  Plans are for, in the future, to add to my  urlLink Bluebonnet Missions  website other notes and information received during the trip, as well as translations of tape records that I took while there.  I understand that I may actually be able to record those sights/sounds and discussions on the website directly.  As soon as I am able to figure all that out, I will certainly keep you uptodate on that as well...  It was such a wonderful trip; it would be a shame not to share that information and knowledge with others.  Hope you will enjoy!!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry for being so late in wishing a very Happy 4th of July, but I had to work overtime for the greater portion of the day.  It just didn't quite seem like a Holiday for me because I have been working overtime since Thursday and will be thru Tuesday.  I missed the fanfares, the celebrations, my family's BBQ, and all the firework displays -- especially the one with the symphony playing in concert along with the extravaganza!  *sigh* Perhaps, next year, I will be able to take advantage of this???  We'll see....  In the meantime, I hope that everyone had a very Happy and Safe 4th of July this year!  Be sure to comment on yours, if you would like.  (See the below link for adding your comments following this post.)  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got home tonight from work and happend upon a public broadcast station's documentary about the creation of fireworks -- one in particular is the famous  urlLink Zambelli Fireworks , which are displayed throughout.  Comprised of rich  urlLink Zambelli Family  secrets yield to generations of secrets and traditions.    What I didn't see the show emphasize though (perhaps I had come in too late in the show?) was the fact that the  urlLink Zambelli Family  were not alone; there are other families -- i.e., the  urlLink duPonts at the Longwood Gardens  and others, as well as more recently developed firework companies (like the  urlLink Phantom Fireworks  and  urlLink Alonzo Fireworks .  Some fireworks have even made their mark in the  urlLink Guiness World Records !  Years ago when I lived in South Carolina, I attended a fabulous fireworks display at  urlLink Patriot's Point  in Mt.Pleasant, South Carolina.  Growing up, I remember the firework displays in  urlLink Ft. Sam Houston  in San Antonio, Texas,  urlLink July 4th Fireworks  in Annapolis, Maryland,  urlLink HEB Austin Symphonic Fireworks  in Austin, Texas, and so much more.  This year....well, this year I am finding myself having to work, although I believe that I am getting the day following off.  Unfortunately, they don't have fireworks on the 5th of July!! :(  Perhaps, I will be able to a Fireworks display soon.  I miss the grandeur of the sights and sounds that go along with it, as well as the awestrucking amazement that is beheld in each firework going off in a very systematic fashion.  To those who read this on the 4th of July 2004, may you all have a very blessed and safe 4th of July!! :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Several years ago I was making up to nearly $50,000 (ended in 2001), then I had to sacrifice and work for less @ $31,500 (ended in 2003), and now I am barely getting paid enough to cover the essentials of living.  Something has to give!  My parents tell me to learn to budget.  I tell them you have to have something to budget with.  It is a vicious cycle.  If I don't work 2-3 jobs, I don't have enough income to spread to support my family; however, then, I don't have enough waking moments to share with my family.  What is a single Mom to do with daughter heading off to college in about a year???  Life can certainly be very frustrating....  Hopefully, the economy can get on an upswing....  Maybe even our employers can soon offer to match the cost of living that we so struggle with.  Perhaps, they are hoping that the cost of living comes within the range of the wages; I just don't see that happening anytime soon...  Perhaps God will shed some light to offer more hope to everyone???  One can only hope and pray....    PSALMS 18:25-19  (New Living Translation)   To the faithful you show yourself faithful; to those with integrity you show integrity. To the pure you show yourself pure,  but the the wicked you show yourself hostile. You rescue those who are humble,  but you humiliate the proud. Lord, you have brought light to my life;  my God, you light up my darkness. In your strength I can crush an army;  with my God I can scale any wall.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      At work, I am quite amused by the foreigners who are there to answer technical questions from people who only speak foreign languages calling into our center.  There is one in particular I have been talking to in passing or about work projects -- a man from  urlLink Morrocco , home of  urlLink Casablanca !  Never thinking twice about it, but watching him sometimes while I am on the phone and being quite intrigued.  Yesterday, he surprised me by coming up and talking to me directly.  I was shocked and flattered simultaneously...a lot due to the fact I don't normally get THAT personal with others at work.  My daddy taught me long ago to never mix work with personal relationships....  After work we spent some quality time talking to each other and before we seperated our ways for the evening, he first kissed my hand and reached over for a kiss. WOW!  Am I going to have my own personal  urlLink Humphrey Bogart ?? or, just a short-lived moment??  Stay tuned for more details to come?!?!? 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While growing up, I was raised in  urlLink San Antonio ,  urlLink Texas , where the majority of the culture was not necessarily the  urlLink Hispanic Culture  but, over the years has seen an increasing  urlLink Hispanic Influence . Spanish was spoken mostly in the rural regions; no  urlLink ESL (English as a Second Language)  classes were taught while I was in school; however, by the time I moved to  urlLink Austin ,  urlLink Texas , and substituted through the  urlLink AISD (Austin Independent School District) , it was clear that Spanish was becoming more prominent as they had  urlLink ESL Programs  in all the schools within the  urlLink AISD  system.  That being said though, I returned to  urlLink San Antonio  in 1997, I discovered that, while waiting in the lobby of my bank the Hispanic influence had become even stronger.  I picked up a brochure while waiting in line for something to read, only to discover that it was written entirely in Spanish!  Additionally, I discovered that the Hispanic population had become so strong that the job hunting process was stymied by the employers asking, are you bi?? (and they meant, "are you bi-lingual??).  Job hunt after job hunt after job hunt during the last subsequent years (more than 7 years now) consitently turned me down because I wasn't bilingual.  Suddendly, I was on the recepient end of being discriminated against.  One of my greatest pet peeves is that, if they are suddenly going to make it a requirement for employees to be bilingual, then they should be offering "SSL" (Spanish as a Second Language) to help those who never took Spanish and/or need to brush up on it (like me) because they never used it on a regular basis throughout the years for free  -- just like they implemented the  urlLink ESL Programs  in all the schools within the  urlLink AISD  system.   Being back in the Austin area, I may have found an answer to a free program being taught in  urlLink Round Rock ,  urlLink Texas .  Their Senior Center is offering free classes -- just pay $8.00 to the annual membership of the Senior Center AND about $10 for the workbook.  Not a bad deal!! :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My Picture Taken in July 2004  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                  txbluebonnet (bluebonnetfields@yahoo.com) has invited you to look at pictures together, using Hello.   txbluebonnet said:  add to profile   Hello is a free program that lets you share pictures while you chat online, over a secure direct connection with your friends.  It's as quick and as simple as dragging and dropping files.   To download Hello and get started sharing photos, click on this picture, or go directly to our  urlLink sign up page .  You'll be able to select a username and password, and before you know it (it takes about 30 seconds to download), you'll be sending and receiving pictures too.  You can learn more at  urlLink www.hello.com .       &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp;         (are you still using email to share pictures?)        &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp;     &nbsp;        If the links above do not work, you can copy and paste this link into your web browser:  https://secure.hello.com/download.php?do=redeem&ticket=DLwLApJuHrd9JywI7tBt4onON    Picasa will not sell, share or in any way distribute your email address or personal information. To learn more about privacy and security in the Hello network, go to  urlLink http://www.hello.com/security.php          
     

    
</post>


</Blog>