<Blog>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My sister rented the movie "Spirited Away" at Blockbuster and it's totally my 4th favorite movie (behind the 3 HP movies of course) Anywho, it is   SUCH   a good movie. I really recommend you buy it or rent it immedietly. I saw it tonight and I'm buying tomorrow morning. That's how good I thought it was. If you want to rent it, I'd recommend going to Blockbuster, obviously. If you want to buy it, I'd go to Wal-Mart, or if you don't want to leave the house just order it from Amazon.com. I've provided links for the DVD and VHS versions of it:  VHS:  urlLink Click Here  DVD:  urlLink Click Here   Again, I really recommend it. Such a good movie. Well, see ya next time and ttyl. Byezo!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, today at  urlLink Hogwarts Castle  I had a nice chat in the Slytherin Common Room with a couple of friends. One of my friends loves it when I change into my Animagus Form (a golden retriever puppy) because she thinks I'm so cute. Hear that? I'm cute.   Anywho, today is her (the one that thinks I'm cute)'s birthday! Yay, let's through a party!   (See that smiley? One time my friend Allen's dad said that Allen looked like that smile.) Hehe. Anywho, I've been reading this thread about this battle between TDE (The Death Eaters) and OotP (Order of the Phoenix) and it's kinda bloody   but quite interesting. If you wanna read it, click  urlLink here . Well, again I will say, if you haven't signed up with H-C than you REALLY need to because it's one of my most favorite Harry Potter sites! When I get on the comupter every morning I go to  urlLink Mugglenet  (it's set as my homepage) and then I check my mail, and then it's off to school at Hogwarts Castle. I beg of you to sign up. I know you will like it. If you don't, you can personally post rude comments about me in my comments box of this message (I can always delete them anyway.  )  Well, I'll ttyl. Byezo!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, since it's obviously, the best thing in the world I thought I'd do a whole article on it. So. My favorite Harry Potter links:  1.  urlLink Mugglenet  2.  urlLink Hogwarts Castle  3.  urlLink Mugglenet Interactive  4.  urlLink CoS Forums  5.  urlLink J.K.'s Official Site   Numbers 2, 3 and 4 are HP Forums but oh well.    Okay, my top 5 favorite HP characters:  1. Fred Weasley (so funny, so funny) 2. Remus Lupin (great guy, Moony) 3. Sirius Black (you gotta love him) 4. Ginny Weasley (so misunderstood) 5. Draco Malfoy (such a git! and played by Tom Felton!)  More faves:  Books (in order): Order of the Phoenix, Prisoner of Azkaban, Goblet of Fire, Chamber of Secrets, Philosapher's Stone. Movies (in order) Prisoner of Azkaban, Chamber of Secrets, Philosapher's Stone. HP Food/Drinks: Butterbeer, sugar quills, treacle fudge. Couples: (serious)Ron & Hermione, Harry & Ginny, Hagrid & Madame Maxime, Dumbledore & McGonagall (funny) Draco & Me! Percy & Pain!  More later. ttyl. Byezo!  P.S. POST YOUR COMMENTS!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, dear god. I got the school supply list for next school year today and it is  SCARY . There's 2 coloums(sp?) of stuff and it scares me. *cries silently in a corner* Sorry. It's just really freaky. Anywho, I just had some popcorn and so I'm kinda full. For some reason, we have popcorn like every night. I got on  urlLink Hogwarts Castle  (we'll just call it HC) and had a nice chat at the Ravenclaw Table (even though I'm a Slytherin, lol.) For some reason, Slytherin Table is always deserted. Well, it's not always deserted: it's not as bad as the Hufflepuff Table where no one has posted in like the last few  days . So my mom took me back to the pool at like 6:00 but they were having a swim meet and I got really mad. Grrrr! Well, that's all I have to say. ttyl! Byezo!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well you guys, I'm off to the pool! I'll probably get back around 3:00 or so but you know. You know what sucks though? I wear goggles at the pool so when I'm floating on my back in the water, I get a tan everywhere except for around my eyes! And it looks  really  freaky. We had to buy some sunless tanning stuff to put around my face. Well, anywho, ttyl. Byezo!  UPDATE: Well, turns out 10 minutes after we got there someone barfed in the pool. Luckily, I wasn't in the pool when they did. I had just gotten out to go get some water gear from my dad. But they said it would take 30 minutes for it to clear up and then when the 30 minutes were over they were going to have a 10 minute break so I went to get on the slide and the line stretched out down the stairs and onto the sidewalk. Finally, after waiting in line for 5 minutes, I got to slide  ONCE  and I was like, "Jack this, I'm goin' home." So I got back at 2:20 and started reading my magazine that came in the mail.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to Libby's World of Fun! Yay for fun! And boo for not fun. Sorry, I'm crazy. You might want to leave now if you get freaked out by people like me. =D Anywho, This is my first blog so I don't really know what I'm doing. lol. Anywho, a little bit about me: Harry Potter is like the best thing in the world and I would die without it. If you don't like Harry Potter than may you be shunned by the whole world. May bad luck and misfortune be spread upon thy. Again, signs of craziness. Anywho (I love that word) I also am in love with Tom Felton. You can visit his site  urlLink here . He plays Draco Malfoy in the Harry Potter movies! Another reason why I like him, he's in the best movies based on the best books ever! Well, I just had a ham sandwhich and some Flamin' Hot Cheetos (those cheetos will probably come up a lot since they are my favorite food ever!) I just got off the best Harry Potter RPG site in the  WORLD!  It consists of forums, where you roleplay like your in the Harry Potter world. The address is  urlLink http://www.hogwarts-castle.com . Well, I hope you check out Hogwarts Castle, because it's AWESOME! Well, I'm out. ttyl (which means talk to you later.) [Your going to have to learn internet lingo so you can understand what I'm saying sometimes. I might provide a post that has a guide maybe. lol.] (laugh out loud) Byezo!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>