<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      today is kinda a normal day for me... i went to the library after sch... the stupid sch say got seminar den in the end only first 5 classes got only and mine is tomorrow wad a waste of my time lor... den after i did some chem at the library and we sat at the kids sections and the seats were so low lor... my legs aint short and it was very uncomfortable for me... after that on the way to parkway i saw someone from chung cheng but then she purposely walk off in the other direction wth... at nite the north and east of singapore people experienced a major power cut and the whole thingy lasted for 1.5 hours sia lucky my house never kena... and i realise that rachel from chung cheng is a bitch!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      AH!!!!! sch reopen already... now my sch has no more subject room basis but change to form room basis le... is it good? is it bad? well i dunno because i have gotten used to both systems... anyway first day i was rather quiet and my physics teacher even thinks that i very sad... haha she so cute~! anyway when i reach home, i felt stressed as the whole day the teachers have been stressing bout the number of weeks left to O LEvels SHITS! i didnt noe wad to do... instead i juz taking out my things and stare blankly... at nite after waking up from a nap i also dunno why but i juz felt so happy and great! is it a good omen? i juz feel stress whenever i hear abt the results thingy...  i muz aim for VJC manz.... anyway gtg sleep ... wan an 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      it is only a few hours to sch reopening and i dun reali give a heck abt it cos it is like i didnt do my holiday hw at all... sLAck ritez? i always regret it at the end of the hols but i still have this bad habit... i feel like an idiot manz... i feel that i m getting very very sensitive, am i? i dunno, maybe i am... but i hope yu can forgive me if i am... i'm feeling very vexed abt this~~~ wher is e love manz??? 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Although it is a day away from sch reopens, i did not feel any excitement or any pressure at all... now i am in sec 4 yet i do not feel the need to study hard... what is the world getting into manz? i have been feeling very f*cked up this few days not juz because of sch and also because of other reasons... i feel that in a way or so, i m being betrayed... i also dunno why suddenly the world seems to change completely, i m actually ignored by somebody... yet i do not know the reason, i reali wanna know the reason and i dun wan that somebody to actually dao me... i hope to regain the friendship manz... 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       wa liao i today felt so fucked up man... i sleep at 5.30am and early morning my parents juz came in to the room and wake me up ... what the fuck! they say wad everyday wake up so late... they dunno wad is called sch hols wan sia, cant even sleep a bit longer... i hate people who disturb me when i having ample rest wan sia. FUCKING no REspect!  but then luckily i simmer down ... after that i went for a hair cut... and now my hair is damn short ah!!!! but i juz think that i look great in short hair~
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      heyhEY~ hello kids i have no idea wad i'm doing here but i guess it is all destined for me to have a blog ya? anyways reali wan thank SOME people ah who always ask me to go to their blog to take a look and stuff.. now influenced me to take up this blog thingy liao... anyways since this is my first time and 1st post. let's juz hope that everything will be smooth-sailing for all my frenz? it doesnt matter who yu are , but wad yu do...   fr3nz for3v3r ah !     sAyo~~~~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      wow time reali travel fast yeah? for the whole week i've been stressed with the time left before we face o levels... THIS whole thing is killin me manz... i noe this is our last lap but it is very tiring ... however i have already started studying so i muz continue at this rate before i take my O's... i reali wish to go VJC and to see some people there... but then i dunno whether i can or not... anywayz today i went chinatown then i went plaza singapura... and yu know wad ? i got a new study lamp and it's real cool man... i hope this lamp can motivate me to study reali hard... cya 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>