<Blog>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, everyone has a blog, webpage, forum, or local BBS.  Do local BBSes still exist?  If anyone sees a local BBS for the Baltimore/Washington D.C. area, drop me a line.  I'd love to get involved in one.  Not that I need another hobby to half-ass, but I really miss Bulletin Boards.  And I'm not talking about that TELNET crap, I want a real modem dialup-    I just realized I don't have a modem anymore.  For anyone still using a modem, I'll let you in on the secret that the rest of the internet community with it's flash-induced pages assumes you have broadband connection at this point.  If not cable service then at least DSL.  Boy can I get off the subject.  Alright, a BBS in Maryland or D.C. with TELNET access we be alright too, but I'll hook my modem back up for a dialup board.  Anything else?  Pretty good for a first post right?  This doesn't mean I'm giving up on my webpage, just that this is easier for me to do from whereever I want.    I'll add the blog link to my website sometime this weekend.  Got a few other things to add this weekend too: my slightly procrastinated short story and my letter to the Command Sergeant Major (if you are in a very political military climate, or the 902nd, this letter will be entertaining).
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, so I'm back in the habit of trying to write again.&nbsp; Not here mind you, but a short story I've been working on since... oh July of 2001.&nbsp; It started out as a bunch of brief stories independent of each other.&nbsp; It turned into a "novel in the works" after people commented on how well they thought the stories were written and that I should do something with them.&nbsp; So why am I telling you all this? &nbsp; It's REALLY starting to get to me.&nbsp; Remembering back to certain moments hasn't been the easiest.&nbsp; I have to refer to my journal, my friends, people who aren't my friends but were sober enough to remember what actually happened.&nbsp; Not that the actual events matter mind you.&nbsp; It's based on my experiences but it's vastly warped in order to fit in the realm of fiction.&nbsp; Well, that and I have to fill in the memory gaps with something. &nbsp;I might as well embellish what I still remember to make it a bit more interesting in the process, right? &nbsp; Sadly though, when people who were involved in the situations read it, they instantly take what I wrote as what happened.&nbsp; People who weren't even there comment on how funny that day was, and people who were&nbsp;involved comment on how they wish they could've been there.&nbsp; It's like the guys who constantly rewrote history in Orwell's 1984.&nbsp; Were they the Ministry of Love? &nbsp; I don't&nbsp;always seem to have a choice when I'm writing as to where I take it.&nbsp; I find a path and my fingers do the rest.&nbsp; Then I go back many times over to make what my erratic fingertips performed to look a bit more sane. &nbsp; So I'm going to start again.&nbsp; Haven't even started on being a father yet, that could almost be another book/short story/novella/essay/book report.&nbsp; Someone please try to keep me on top of it.&nbsp; If procrastination was an Olympic event, you can bet I'd be on the U.S. team. 
    
</post>


</Blog>