<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got home from the first tournament baseball game that Ethan and I had. The game was so close. IT was the top of the last inning we were up to bat and were down 6-5 we hit 1 home stole 1 home and Ethan walked 1 home. So now we are ahead 6-8 it was getting dark so we were afraid that they would call it for darkness. Our pitcher walked one who stole his way to third. We have two more people to get out. The next batter hits a grounder to second, and the guy on third gets home but we get the batter out at first. And finally we struck the last batter out! We had won! So now we continue in the tournament with a game tomorrow. 
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After Josh woke up from his dose of LSD we were laughing about all the weired jobs people have at hospitals, like the first lady they talked to asked "This was an accident right"? Josh was thinking "no I go around and break my arm on purpose. and another lady wasant allowed to say he had a broken arm even though it was obvious because she wasnt a doctor so she had to put "posible break". Another guy they talked to whose job was to make shure that women that are in labor are realy suposed to be at the hospital. Its just realy weired.
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I woke up and was laying in bed and Josh came in with this big splint on his arm. I was like josh what did you do? He said that he had gone to somebodys house to work on their hay loft, and it fell, and he fell, and he screamed, and his arm snaped. So now Mom, Dad, and stacey are on their way to get his arm operated on.
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today Ethan and I Had our last double header baseball game. We lost the first one and won the second. Yesterday Trenton and I went to the skatepark. I saw someone bust their board right in half. The Guy had oleyed up to grind and when he landed on the rail cracked right in two.
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is my new blog
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I haven't posted for such a long time because Dad was running a phone line down to staceys room out of the computer jack.&nbsp; we are done with the dry wall, and have started with the mudding.&nbsp; this morning I got up and helped Mom get ready for the garage sale, then after it started I went down stairs and helped dad with the dry wall until lunch time then I ate lunch then I went to the tennis tournament, and won my matches, then I came home and helped Dad with the dry wall some more and now its almost time to eat, and after we eat Mom Nicole and I are going to go to a graduation thing at church.     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was much like yesterday except instead of work at church I worked with Dad, and insted of a thing at the library I had tennis. so thats about all I have to say. By now 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up, ate, and helped Dad in the basement. Then at lunchtime I ate again. At two I had this thing at the library where they showed you how to make stuff out of duck tape. Most of it I already knew. I brought my duct tape pants along, and the lady teaching thought they were so cool, and she was going to another library to put up a display and she asked if she could put my pants up so I was like sure. They,re at the College park library. Then after the thing mom took me to work day and then I came home and ate and now I'm here.                                                                                                                                 Question: whose blog would you be more likely to coment on, Mine or Joshe's?
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi this is K_bob what's up?  urlLink Stacey's  going to show me how to link. It ought to work this time. On Sunday I had Trenton over after church and we skated and watched all the big battles on lord of the rings. On Monday I bought a roll of duct tape and made a pair of pants, and we started on Stacey's new room in the basement. If any body wants to buy a pair of pants let me know they're $5. Today I am just sitting around doing nothing. It's quite fun you ought to try it some time. 
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today Nicole had a swim meet so I got up early to go to that. Then we got home, ate lunch, did chores, and now we are about to eat dinner. Stacey and Josh are at a CYA so after we eat I will probably go take a shower, sit around till I feel tired then I will try to go to sleep, then I will wake up, and it will be morning, and I will be happy. THE END. Oh by the way the link to Joshe's blog didn't work so don't even try it. Good night.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry it took me so long to post so this will be a long one. Check this out I'm going to try to make a link  to  urlLink josh's  blog! I hope it works. On Friday I had a ball game which we won, then on Saturday I went to the Owens. I was supposed to have another ball game on Saturday but it kinda got rained out. On Sunday I went to church and came home and went to church and after church we took the Magnuson downtown to watch the fire  works. We parked at the top of a parking garage, and Trenton and I had brought our skateboards so we skated around and watched fire works. It was really fun. Then on Monday Ethan and I had A baseball game which we lost. Then after I got home from the game I went around with some of my friends and blew stuff up with bottle rockets, that was a lot of fun! Then on Tuesday I wasn't feeling well so I slept most of the day. On wednesday I went to workday since I didn,t have a ball game. So today I am Just sitting around doing nothing. In the baseball tournament we ranked four out of thirty-two.        today's poll: Which is better STAR WARS, or Lord of The Rings?
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night we won our game against the River Dogs. Now we have semi finals tomorrow. We killed them in our game, the final score was 20 -10. In the last inning there was a pop fly right out over the shortstop, and he threw his glove at the ball. When you do that the runner gets to advance two bases, but if he had hit the ball the runner would have gotten three basses. Everybody except the coach thought it was funny. 
    
</post>


</Blog>