<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (Carmen San Diego?) woops, sorry--I got side-tracked...my blog?  Well, my blog address is trebloc.blogspot.com.  I know what you are thinking, "t-r-e-b-l-o-c??? WTF?!?!?!"  Here is the story behind this seemingly odd name:  As most kids around the age of 6 or 7, you and your best friend spend a lot of time together.  My best friend Ryan and I first met in first grade during "movie" time.  Our classrooms were connected by a door, and the 2 classes frequently did activities together such as recess, movie time, we were all one team for field day, etc.  We also lived in the same neighborhood (I first made my Christopher Columbus-like discovery on one of my many bike rides around my neighborhood--I was a workout freak even then..LOL).  So, since first grade, we were inseparable.  We spent the night together at each others houses every weekend.  We carpooled together to and from school.  We played together after school.  His mom was my second mom and mine his.  His dad was a father figure to me.  He "inherited" a sister from me and I "inherited" a brother from him.  We went on vacations together.  Bottom line:  we were ALWAYS together!  Spending so much time together, we thought that we would be the clever little rascals that my mom said we were and devise our own language.  We would talk in this language when others were around just to baffle them.  Our secret language...(gasp)...was to say words backwards!  Ok, ok...I know you are laughing at this point saying that this is just "Pig Latin" and that a lot of kids do this.  We didn't have a clue at the time that our seemingly ingenious language was anything less than original.  We thought we were soooo cool.  Who knew?    Anyway, T-R-E-B-L-O-C is just my last name backwards--COLBERT.  Clever, eh? (or the lack there of)
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those of you who know me in the slightest know that I am a HUGE workout person.  I do not mean this in the same context as say Arnold Swartzenagger (sp?--didn't come up in spellcheck), Brad Pitt in Troy, or The Incredible Hulk (I mean, just take a look at me--LOL).  I workout mostly because it is good for your body, to maintain my physique (albeit, I'm not to be confused with the forementioned rock-hard bodies), and because I really do enjoy it (seriously!).  Having said all this, I am in the gym everyday.  Ok...here are where my observations begin...  Have you ever been resting between reps or walking to get some water and just look around?  I mean, come on people...what is with the workout couture?  Just look the next time you are at the gym.  There are some with (gasp) spandex--ok, I have to stop and make a point with this one.  I reserve spandex for women who do aerobics or people who are into serious, I mean serious, cross country biking.  Some should know that they really shouldn't be showing all of what spandex allows one to show.  Period!  Next, you can see some in a full sweat(or wind)suit.  Is one really THAT cold whilst working out?  Then some are in "normal" workout attire--athletic shorts and a t-shirt.  And of course, there is all of the imaginable workout attire in between.  Next, there are usually 4 types of people you will see:  1-"Gym Bunnies"...these people are really, REALLY buff, lifting heavy weights, sometimes spandex-wearing people. 2-"The Regulars"...these are the people who are at the gym regularly, what to get into shape (or maintain), just "normal." 3-People who just want to be seen...they think this is social hour, look like they are working out while trying to look good--usually the sorority-type (sorry to stereotype).      Side note:  Notice I didn't say sorority-type "girls" because a gay guy can be a sorority-type! 4-"Once in a Whiles"...as this name suggests, these people only go to the gym once in a while, whenever it is convenient.  It really is interesting surveying your fellow gym patrons.  Give it a try the next time you are working out!  P.S. Please feel free to comment on any workout couture or types of people that I might have omitted. P.P.S.  FYI--I would fall into the category of a "regular" who wears "normal" workout attire.  (Am I saying that I am "normal"???  I think we can all beg to differ on this--LOL)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I have gone the WHOLE weekend and a couple of days without blogging and I almost went crazy!  Well...ok, that was a little dramatic...I just kept thinking about it.  I went to my mom's house in Gainesville for a couple of days and it was a nice break.  I'm sorry I don't feel like typing right now, but I promise that I will make it up to the 2 or 3 of you that visit my blog--LOL;-)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW--I have now entered the world of Blogging!  Who knew that my life would lead me to this very moment?!?!?!  Here is the story behind my journey to "The Blog":  I visit Natalie's blog daily to see what crazy, literary stories she has given us the pleasure of reading.  Also, Angela has just started her own blog and I am now compelled to read hers, too:)  Well, Natalie, Angela, and I were at Halo drinking our cocktails, looking at the cute guys, and discussing various topics.  Then we start to talk about their literary talent for blog-writing.  I am showering them with compliments at this point when they suggest that  I  should start a blog.  **Ponders**  **Could I be as literarily(sp?) gifted in blog-writing as my present company?**  The night wears on.  We start to talk about Natalie's earlier gentleman admirer who wanted her to stay at her present location.  Uninterested in his invite, she tells him that she is going to Halo to meet some friends and he says, "Halo...isn't...it...uh..."  "Gay night," Natalie replies, "but I'm the hag."  That is when the 3 of us start to talk about the labels that people use to describe a certain person or group of people.  And, ta da, that is how we came up with my blog name:   Twinkie, Potato Queen  (For those of you who are unaware of this label:  Twinkie = yellow (asian) on the outside, white (white..LOL) on the inside and Potato Queen = an asian guy who likes white guys)  So, having already come up with a blog name (it's all gravy from there, right?), toying with the notion of my very own blog all morning, and having just a little too much free time on my hands on a Friday afternoon at work, a new blog is born!  So, here it is...ENJOY!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok....this is the saddest blog EVER!!!&nbsp; :(   ...sadness and melancholy...   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and by "BritS" I am referring to...Britney Spears. I am a huge fan (Love her!--to get the full effect, you have to use Jack's voice from  Will and Grace ), but come on. She is making some jacked-up choices right now. First, her 55 hour marriage to Jason Alexander. Next, her engagement to her loser guy, Kevin Federline (who is a dancer, has a kid and one on the way...enough said!).  Plus , her decision not to get a pre-nup!!! Pregnant???--who knows!  Come on Brit...THINK, THINK,  THINK!!!   What will the Britster do next??? 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The "it" that I am referring to is Reality T.V.!!!    Like most people, I have t.v. shows that I HAVE to watch.   Friends  (re-runs and dvd's now),  Nip/Tuck  (a recent addition),  QAF  ( Queer as Folk --for the gay-challenged readers--LOL),  Sex and the City , and the occasional reality show that peaks my interest--just to name a few.  So, I was channel surfing last night when I came across  For Love or Money .  This show can suck you in like no other.  Here is the premise:  One guy, 15 girls, whoever he picks has to pick either him (love) or the money ($1 million).  I know this sounds like a dumb show (this was my exact thought when the first one aired), but it somehow sucks you in.  Then, almost immediately after the show ends (usually the next week at the same time/day), they have a  For Love or Money 2  with the girl that ultimately, and greedily, picked the money over love.  This show is in it's second season.  Here is where it sucked me in...  I didn't watch the first show with the guy and 15 girls because I know how it can suck me in, and I didn't want to be committed to another show.  But then, last night...the first episode of the second show aired.  This time, instead of just the greedy girl who chose the money over love returning as the "love" part, there were... 2 girls!!!   They were both one of the last girls remaining and they  hated  each other.  So, they meet the 15 guys and they have to have an elimination the next night.  The twist:  the   guys   vote off one of the girls!!!    And ...all of the guys who chose the eliminated girl leave too!!!   This is just good t.v. people...
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After enjoying a pleasant dinner last night with 7 other friends, I made an interesting observation.  We had had 4 bottles of wine throughout the course of the evening, so most of us were feeling "good."  Isn't it funny to see people's personalities alter after drinking?  I know that this is not a new topic or Earth-shattering discovery, but it makes for a good blog entry, don't ya think?  Here are some of the more common after-drinking behavioral changes that I observed:  Some get:  mean, loud, bitter, truthful, quiet, tired, nostalgic, sad, happy, horny, analytical, depressed, funny, talkative, obnoxious, affectionate, etc.  Any combination of the above behaviors can be quite interesting.  So, the next time you are enjoying a night out with friends (accompanied by alcohol of any kind), sit back and observe what kinds of drunks you and your friends are.  Isn't it funny?    P.S.  Feel free to add any of your observations of the intoxicated that I might have left out. P.P.S.  What kind of drunk are you?  FYI...I am usually a loud, happy, funny, talkative drunk;-)
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Preface: I have been watching A LOT of home decorating shows lately (by lately, I mean   Conversation this past weekend:  Sis: Come here... Me: Ok... Sis: (points to a wire shelving rack in her kitchen) Me: Ok...what about it? Sis: I want you to build me a cabinet to replace this wire rack... Me: HUH??? Sis: Stacy (her husband) doesn't have time with work and all. Me: Like I do??? Did ya forget I work, too?!?!?!? Sis: Well, you can do it on the weekends (smile on face).  ...'cause I have NOTHING else to do???  GEEZ... 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...about Friday the 13th...    Fridays are considered bad luck.  Examples from the Bible--They had different calendars back then, but Christian tradition says Jesus died on a Friday. It also holds that Eve tempted Adam with the apple on a Friday. Same with the Great Flood.  And 13? God (or the gods) again: There were 13 at the Last Supper. The Norse god Loki crashed a dinner party of 12, making 13; he then tricked Hodur into killing his brother Balder, the god of light and joy, with an arrow poisoned with mistletoe. The 13 months of the pagan lunar calendar meant the number was cursed by God.  In combination, Friday and 13 have special resonance: When Frigg, or Freya, the Norse goddess for whom Friday is named, joined a dozen witches, she transformed them into a coven of 13. Fridays used to be reserved for public hangings in Britain; traditionally, there were 13 steps on the scaffold.  Most authorities say Friday the 13th earned its notoriety on Oct. 13, 1307, when King Philip IV of France (known, oddly, as Philip the Fair) ordered the dismantling of the Knights Templar, the warrior monks who were the scourge of Islam during the Crusades.    And a final note:   The Olsen twins are born on Friday, June 13, 1986 (you know I had to add some sort of celebrity fact--hehe).   So there you have it, some interesting facts about Friday the 13th...  ***info provided by MyMSN:)*** 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm honestly not trying to be mean, but...  ...at what point do you think that this man thought he was overweight???  People kill me! Everyone is on this diet fad or that one. Low-Carb this, Low-Carb that.  PEOPLE!!! The key is MODERATION and EXERCISE!!!  This isn't rocket science. Lord! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...RUNNER! For those of you who know me, this is like telling a blind person that he can't see. Hrmmm...my second reference to a blind person??? Interesting, eh?...but I digress...  One of my ultimate life goals is to run a marathon. I have been running ever since I can remember. One of my early childhood stories that my mom shares is that the flight attendants said that I ran up and down the aisles the whole flight from Korea. I started to run for my high school when I was in 8th grade and the rest is history. I run on a daily basis for exercise, therapy, "me" time, and cause I just plain like to run. It makes me feel good. "Exercise releases endorphins...endorphins make you happy...happy people just don't kill other people!" (an ode to  Legally Blonde)  Plus,   ever since I heard that Oprah did one, I KNEW I could/had to/needed to/should/would do one.!  I have run numerous 5K's and 10K's, but never anything else.  Well...I am a step closer to my goal.  Today, I registered for my first...  wait for it...  HALF MARATHON!!! (the crowd cheers!!!)  Anyway, it is the Annual Atlanta Marathon/Half Marathon on Thanksgiving Day. I will keep you all posted on how my (continued) training goes!  Wish me luck! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...a love quiz. Here is how the story goes...  A woman and I share an office at work. She usually just rambles on about various topics and I usually just ignore her. On occasion, I will interject with my ageless wisdom and then go on about my work.  SideNote: I must describe this woman. She is a tall, black woman who is raising 2 kids on her own. She is in her mid-30's and lives near the airport. She was in the Army and could beat the heck out of me!  Today, she was rambling on about why she doesn't have a man, how she is a good catch, how she isn't happy cause she is alone, etc. I told her that she just needs to stop looking for love and it will find her; that she has to be happy with herself before she can make someone else happy; that she can't rely on others to make her happy--only she can make herself happy. (examples of my ageless wisdom). At that very moment, I remembered that I had seen a link on my MSN homepage that was titled, "Quiz: Why Are You Still Single?" So, we both took the test.  Results: You're a pretty normal guy (girl). Being single is a short-term situation for you, and the current run of bad luck probably won't hold. Keep it up, and be sure that your lonely nights don't allow you to slip to the next rung.  HRMPH! About as helpful and insightful as a blind person trying to read a newspaper:(   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Isn't it funny how the little things that occur in your daily life can be the exact things that you look forward to? Here are a couple of mine:  ~A hot cup of coffee on my way to work--with flavored creamer:). ~Smelling the gum through my car air conditioning vents when I drive by the Wrigley Gum Plant on my way to work. ~Running (I know this might sound weird, but to those of you who know me very well, this seems oddly normal). ~Reading my book during lunch while I eat the same thing day in and day out.  ...for tomorrow, I will look forward to these little things all over again... *smiles with contentment* 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I was at the gym this morning when I witnessed a brave act. I must preface this story with a little background information about the gym that I attend. I workout at LA Fitness--mostly at the Ansley Mall location. This location, if you don't already know, is considered the "gay, cruise-y" gym. I have gone to other locations around the Atlanta area, and I find this to be true. I, of course, go to workout...but hey...the eye candy ain't bad! LOL! Anyway, on with the story...  I was sitting on the bench--resting in between sets--when I caught something out of the corner of my left eye. A guy walked up to another guy and asked him his name. These 2 particular guys are regulars that I see every morning. They exchanged names and continued with the standard introductory conversation:  I see you in here all the time... What do you do here in Atlanta? etc...  After this introductory chit-chat ended, they both went back to their prospective workouts without phone numbers or the possibility of anything more than just "meeting another friendly face." But...I thought to myself (by "thought" I really mean that I look like a crazy talking to myself in a muddled tone), "I would NEVER have the balls to go up to someone (at the GYM, no less) and ask a guy his name that I thought was CUTE!"  To this brave guy: I salute you!:)  So, I'm a wuss...what will I do??? 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...when my 3 year old niece and 2 year old nephew looks at me and says, "Uncle, I love you!" ...when they hug me so tightly and won't let go. ...when they only want to sit next to me when we all go out to eat. ...when they ignore everyone else (their mom, dad, nana) when I am around. ...when they give me a kiss for no reason.  I could go on forever, but I guess I am trying to say that every moment I am around my niece and nephew is a humbling moment for me:) It's amazing how the little rascals can make you feel...
     

    
</post>


</Blog>