<Blog>


<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hardcore Holly vs Akio (my prediction... Hardcore Holly will win)   What a way to kick off a show with Hardcore Holly.&nbsp; The crowd seemed to be really behind Hardcore Holly.&nbsp; Some great moves occured.&nbsp; Akio got some nice heel kicks, and also our favorite Korean movie star pretty much made the match a good match.&nbsp; Hardcore Holly got some great Hardcore Chops, and a nice kick to the mid section on Akio.&nbsp; Hardcore Holly then nailed some great clotheslines on Akio and then did the best dropkick in the buisness.&nbsp; Toward the end Akio tried another heel kick only being caught by Hardcoe Holly and was set up perfectly into the Alabama Slam.&nbsp;   My rating:&nbsp; **1/4.  Most people would rate it: &nbsp;1/2* to a *.  Up next was a short photage of JBL and the Undertaker.&nbsp; This was some good stuff.&nbsp; The look in JBL's eyes when he saw Taker, he looked so scared yet he still had to brag about himself.&nbsp; Undertaker then chokeslamed JBL, and quoted "You... Me... Summerslam!"&nbsp; It was a huge shock to me, cause i dont see Smackdown and yet it was a great little promo.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 2.&nbsp;&nbsp; Danny Basham vs Johnny Stamboli (My prediction... Johnny Stamboli will win)  Match wasnt as impressive as i thought it was going to be.&nbsp; Johnny Stamboli being my favorite of the two, got some great moves in.&nbsp; I however just happened to wake up right before Velocity started, and almost fell asleep.&nbsp; Anyways, Stamboligot some good offense, then got thrown out of the ring, and Doug Basham through Stamboli in the turnbuckle... this is where Bill DeMott and Josh Mathews really went at it, arguing over if Doug Basham was part of the match or not. (I found it to be funny to see two people argue over pointless thing.) Nunzio then went and got in Doug Bashams face for interfearing and then Danny Basham attacked and through Nunzio in the turnbuckle.&nbsp; Danny Basham then tried to perform a move but got caught into a&nbsp;sunset flip&nbsp;by Stamboli, giving him the victory.  My rating: &nbsp;* 1/4.  Most people&nbsp;would rate it: &nbsp;3/4* to a *.  Up next was some more great stuff.&nbsp; Vince McMahon made an apperance and talked about how Kurt was throwing his weight around. an how he fooled the fans, wrestlers, board of directors, and worse of all Vince himself.&nbsp; Vince told Angle that he was going to do what he did to alot of other people... this happens to be my favorite quote Vince uses... "YOUR FIRED!".&nbsp; However Kurt was only fired from his GM spot, and is now an active wrestler.&nbsp; Vince said that he will have a match at Summer Slam.&nbsp; The match happened to be Kurt Angle vs Eddie Guerrero.&nbsp; (Yet again Smackdown has been impressing me latel and i am not even seeing it!)  &nbsp;&nbsp; 3.&nbsp; Rob Van Dam vs Rene Dupree (My prediction... Rene Dupree will win)  Great match with two great athletes.&nbsp; Rob Van Dam seemed to have most of the match under control.&nbsp; I however had to leave and take out the garbage.&nbsp; I happened to miss pretty much the whole match.&nbsp; But i did catch the ending which was great.&nbsp; I saw a perfectly performed Rolling Thunder by Rob Van Dam.&nbsp; And that great dance taunt thing that Dupree does.&nbsp; However Seemed that Dupree taunted with the crowd a little way to much and took his time causing a turning point.&nbsp; Rob Van Dam then i think kicked Dupree causing him to bleed from the mouth, then he went for the 5 star Frog Splash for the win.  My Rating:&nbsp; **.  Most people would rate it:&nbsp; * 3/4 to a **.  &nbsp;  Overall I think this was one of Velocity's greatest shows... I loved Hardcore Holly this week, and Akio impressed me alot.&nbsp; Rob Van Dam actually put on a great match that i actually liked suprisingly.&nbsp; And Stamboli was good.&nbsp; However Bashams and Rene Dupree didnt perform to well... Bashams just suck and need to leave for good, and  PERMANENTLY  quit wrestling for good.  
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yet another Onimusha game i have yet to play... Kinda reminds me of Super Smash Brother... but instead you get to play as everyones favorite Japaneese hero... Samenosuke and Jubei... even characters like Marcellus, Oyu, and Kaede... and of course everyones favorite enemy... Nobunaga.&nbsp; It is a four player game... and is a must play.&nbsp; However there isnt enough starter characters to intrest some people... and seems like playing 2 player or 3 or 4 player will bore you after a while... however again... single player in story mode in the other hand is very fun indeed. there are some storylines for each character and yet you have to raise your stats.&nbsp; Overall gamespot rated it a 6.5... but i think Gamespot can be an ass sometimes... even though that sie is probably the best gaming site ever, i would have to rate the game with a 7.5.&nbsp; It is not quite a 10 because they used horrible voices... they dont even sound like the original characters which ruined it... however graphics, and using the true storylines... gets it higher then a 6.5... Overall the game kicks ass... and i suggest you to get it if you have a PS2. 
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I may have no seen Smackdown.&nbsp; But i am going to judge the match on how i would have been if i have seen it... However i did read about the matches and ill guess what it was like... after all its Smackdown... cant be to hard to predict, right?     Josh Mathews is a new Announcer. (... Well now thats an improvement for Smackdown! At least he is better then Tony Chimel.)   &nbsp;   Spike Dudley&nbsp;vs. Chavo Guerrero&nbsp;vs. Jamie Noble.&nbsp;&nbsp;Spike pinning Guerrero with the Dudley Dog to become the number one contender for the Cruiserweight championship.&nbsp; (Seems like it was a great match.&nbsp; After all Spike does diserve the Cruiserweight title more then Chavo.&nbsp; But i would have liked to see Noble and Spike duke it off for the number one contenders title. After all they both are well gifted athletes If i were to rate it i would have probably went with a "**1/2" or maybe even a good solid&nbsp;"***" depending on how well they all did.&nbsp; This may possibly be Smackdowns best match.)   &nbsp;   Backstage, the Divas come up to Kurt Angle and complain about being misused and underutilized. Angle agreed and announced a Fatal Four Way Lingerie match for later on with Sable vs. Dawn Marie vs. Torrie Wilson vs. Miss Jackie. (Wow Kurt, That was your chance to get a woman, yet you blew it!... In my mind this match wont be too bad.&nbsp; At least all of the women are hot... I personally want Sable to win, but i am going to predict Miss Jackie on this one.)   &nbsp;   Dudley Boys had a promo about ECW saying it sucked and all calling it "Extremely Crappy Wrestling".&nbsp; (I guess its good for a heel response from the crowd.&nbsp; I personally liked the very few matches i have seen in ECW such as Tommy Dreamer vs Justin Credible for the ECW title.&nbsp; Too bad i never got to see Crash Holly&nbsp;or Stevie Richards in it.)   &nbsp;   Scheduled for tonight is Luther Reigns vs. John Cena (I'd like to see Luther kick his ass...&nbsp;maybe even see how he wrestles... but i aint watching it... so what goes goes.. i dont care about this one.)&nbsp;and John Bradshaw Layfield’s “Rocky Challenge.” (What the fuck is that!?)   &nbsp;   Billy Kidman vs Bubba Ray Dudley (Already seems very crappy, possibly a DUD or a squash.&nbsp; But i already have chosen Billy Kidman to win... even though most likely after the promo the Dudley's played... seems like Bubba will win. Seems like a "*" match. Maybe a "* 3/4 " match)&nbsp; Bubba Ray Dudley pinned WWE Tag Team champion Billy Kidman.   &nbsp;   Funaki interviewed Booker T and Kurt Angle. Angle told Booker that he was going to name him the new United States champion next week once he had it cleared with the Board of Directors. Funaki said that that wasn’t fair, so Angle fired him for not knowing “how to speak English.”&nbsp; (Now that is funny as hell!!!!... but it seems good because&nbsp;Funaki may go to RAW!)   &nbsp;   The Dudley Boyz came up to Spike Dudley and noted how they all have title shots next week. Spike blew them off and said that he didn’t want anything to do with them. They promised they wouldn’t interfere next week as long as Spike didn’t interfere in D-Von’s match with Rey Mysterio later tonight. Spike agreed and walked off.&nbsp; (After reading this i think even if Spike doesnt interfere, the Dudkey's will still interfere in Spikes match.&nbsp; Lets hope if Dudley's do interfere in Spikes match, Spike will be able to take&nbsp;both them on and still win the title!)   &nbsp;   WWE champion John Bradshaw Layfield came out and said that since he’s in Philadelphia, where the Rocky film was shot, he was laying out a Rocky challenge for someone to try and defeat him and if they did, they could have a title shot at Summerslam. Out came Mike Kruel (USA Pro/ECWA who has worked a lot of dark and TV shots for WWE) who Layfield beats easily. (Figures Bradshaw won!) &nbsp;Layfield says that he guesses he doesn’t have a match at Summerslam. The lights go out and the Undertaker gong hits. Undertaker comes out and faces off with Layfield. Undertaker chokeslams Layfield and takes the ring mic. “You…me…Summerslam.” He says and walks off.&nbsp; (HOLY SHNIKIES!!!!! TAKER VS LAYFIELD!!!!!!... I am going to predict Taker in this one... even though Bradshaw is impressive as WWE champ as i see it.... I rate the match with bradshaw as a "DUD".)   &nbsp;   The divas came down for their Fatal Four Way Lingere match featuring Sable vs. Miss Jackie vs. Torrie Wilson vs. Dawn Marie. Kurt Angle came out and fired all of them.&nbsp; (WHAT!? This seemed like a good match to me!!!!!!.. i knew Kurt was a queer!.. maybe they will all go to RAW, Home of the Divas... match rating "DUD")   &nbsp;   Rey Mysterio&nbsp;vs D-Von Dudley (Seems like an ok, decent match, but i deffinately want D-Von to win. I would give the match a "*1/2") Bubba Ray Dudley tried to interfere but Paul London and Billy Kidman came out.&nbsp; Rey Mysterio beat D-Von. (Spike should have interfered and helped out the Dudley's.. that would have been a good highlight in the show!)   &nbsp;   John Cena&nbsp;vs. Luther Reigns. (The match&nbsp;I care less about, maybe Luther will be the winner... then i might look and read more on this match. "1/2*")John Cena pinned Luther Reigns after Booker T attempted to interfere, but it backfired.&nbsp; (Booker... Just give up already... you suck! and you are even boring as a heel! but if you are going to vs Cena... then beat him cause i hate Cena as well!)   &nbsp;   Kurt Angle came to the ring and called out Eddie Guerrero, telling him it was time to apologize because “You don’t cross the boss.” Vince McMahon’s music hit and he came to the ring. McMahon told Angle that he lied to all the fans about his injury, but more importantly, he lied to Vince. Vince said that he was going to get a humanitarian award for making a handicapped person a General Manager, but that is out the window because Angle lied. He told Angle that he was fired as General Manager, but was back on the active roster. McMahon announced he would be facing Eddie Guerrero at Summerslam. Guerrero came out in his low rider. McMahon got in the car and made it bounce.  Guerrero left and McMahon came back to the ring. He told Angle that he had to apologize to everyone he fired tonight, and brought them out. Angle apologized to Funaki and Tony Chimmel but refused to apologize to the divas. Vince told him he was going to have to join the “Kiss My Ass” club for the divas. Angle refused and offered to kiss Vince’s Ass. Vince said No because he has a “Special Ass.” He gave 10 seconds to kiss or apologize. Angle apologized. Vince said that Angle now has to apologize to him. Angle got on his knees but instead low blowed McMahon. Everyone checked on McMahon as Angle escaped. (Seems to be a good angle right there... however Vince didnt diserve to get low blowed!)   &nbsp;   &nbsp;Note: This is way to long to read so i copied and pasted for you to read for me! and i kinda edited the rest of the matches and segments... sorry... maybe if i saw the show i could type it in my own words.&nbsp; And Credit&nbsp;to Gerweck.net)   
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As many of my few duranged and demented fans know by now i am going to be posting some stuff in my poorly put together blog.&nbsp; My schedual consists of....   Sunday  - thoughts on each match on Sunday Night Heat/PPV   Monday - thoughts of each match on RAW... and Talk about Joe Schmo Show 2   Tuesday  - Post a Wrestler of the Week and then talk about Silent Hill   Wednesday  - Talk about whatever and let everyone know how cool i am   Thursday  - Even though i dont see SD i will post what i think the matches will be like... and i will post what happens   Friday  - My thoughts of NWA-TNA Impact   Saturday  - Thoughts on Velocity matches 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For this week's Wrestler of the Week has got to go out to someone that has impressed me over various occasions.&nbsp;&nbsp;This wrestler has great agility, Speed, Power, and is a great technical wrestler in my mind.&nbsp; Even though i tend to like the heels of wrestling, this isnt the case.&nbsp; This weeks wrestler is a great tag team wrestler, and certainly one of the best Intercontinental champions ever in my mind.&nbsp; This wrestler hasnt shown as much as he should in WWE and if he has he would be one of the biggest stars in the buisness.&nbsp; The crowd gives him a HUGE pop.&nbsp; For this weeks Wrestler of the Week, it goes out to one of my favorite wrestlers.&nbsp; He is a total of 260 pounds, and 6'3''.&nbsp; From Las Vegas, Nevada.&nbsp; Former World Tag Team Champion, Intercontinental Champion, and European Champion. &nbsp;Please consider the first wrestler of the week to be none other then... Val Venis... HELLO LADIES!!!!!   &nbsp;      urlLink        &nbsp;  Val Venis has great performance and timing.&nbsp; He may only be used on Heat, but he steals the entire show with a great performance.&nbsp; Val Venis also has one of the best finishers in the buisness... The Money Shot.&nbsp; He also teases the ladies by walkin down to the ring with a towel&nbsp;then asking one of his "Lucky Ladies" to come to the ring and take his towel off of him.&nbsp; The lady is then kissed by Val Venis (one fuckin long kiss) and then usually interupted by his opponent.&nbsp; However now he just gives the towel to a lady in the audience and kisses them on the cheek if anything.&nbsp; But still Val Venis is also one of the best heels the company has to offer.&nbsp; My personal favorite gimmick he used was Chief Morley.&nbsp; Then again WWE didnt see it going to last too long, so they brought him back as Val Venis.&nbsp; Either way Val Venis is one of my favorite wrestlers and should be used more.&nbsp; 
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For this weeks wrestler... I chose someone that had to be one of the worst wrestlers ever... Ill explain why in a second.&nbsp; This is by far makes the jobbers of wwe look like the HHH.&nbsp; The following facts perfectly explain it:     Tall as fuck  Funny to watch  English kicks ass  Shitty finisher  Tall as fuck again  Always gets DQ'ed  Wants a US title shot  Needs a translater  Deffinatley needs someone to carry the match (Even Billy Gunn for that matter)  has never been in a&nbsp;0*&nbsp;star match (all his matches are always in "-*****" from what i hear he sucks.)  Umm...... (Holy Shnikies&nbsp;i am wasting time even listing things about him.)   All these things mean he is deffinatly a Smackdown wrestler.   urlLink     HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!  WOW! even his picture is funny!!!!!!!!!  Talk about an entertainer!!!!        
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Not a bad start for this weeks RAW.&nbsp; First to kick off one of the hot sexy diva's.&nbsp;   1.&nbsp; Diva Elimination (My prediction... Michelle McCool)   Johnathan Coach paced a few, only stopping at Juli, one of the twins, and eliminating her.&nbsp; It wasnt a huge shocker at all, after all there were two of them, only can choose one, and besides they both arnt that hot.   2.&nbsp;&nbsp; 20 Man Elimination (My prediction... Stevie Richards)   This was obviously my number 1 match of the night, since i am certainly not lookin forwards to that iron man match.&nbsp;   In order in placing:   20th: William Regal (laugh at his attire)  19th: Tyson Tomko  18th:&nbsp;Chuck Palumbo (Eminem Wannabe)  17th:&nbsp;Val Venis  16th: Matt Hardy  15th:&nbsp;Hurricane (My 2nd pick)  14th: Rodney Mack  13th: Stevie Richards (#1 pick, cool yellow tights)  12th: Rosie (3rd pick and Congrats... Nice attire!)  11th: Robert Conway  10th: Sylvan Grenier  9th: Tajiri  8th: Ric Flair  7th: Rhyno  6th: Kane  5th: Maven (Too bad he wasnt eliminated sooner)  4th: Batista  3rd: Edge (Now that was a shocker he lost)  2nd: Chris Jericho (DAMNIT!!!! YOU HAD TO BEAT ORTON!!!)  Winner: Randy Orton (You fucker!)   My rating: **** 3/4 (I just LOVE any elimination type matches!)    Now this is something to give you a scare... who can that mystery, former WWE Superstar be... Ill tell you, Kamala!!!!!.&nbsp; The object is to have all the remaining Diva's "seduce" Kamala verbally. I personally found this entertaining as fuck.&nbsp; Carmella, just kept laughing, and some of these diva's screamed when they first saw him.... BOOYAAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!! Up next was a comercial of this old peice of crap book known as Ric Flair's... I had no interests in it.&nbsp; Actually the book doesnt seem to be half bad for his fans.&nbsp; Hopwever i am not a fan... therefore i just walk off.   Ivory had a microphone and talked to Lina McMahon and Stacy Keibler.&nbsp; Ivory the hot babe she is... had to let the CEO old hag talk... which ruined the fun part of jerking off... (You didnt read this.)&nbsp; Linda talked about why young 18-30 year olds should vote... and then told Stacy to give some examples.&nbsp; Stacy wants better paying jobs and i forgot the other one... i kinda spaced out when Ivory and Stacy were all close together like that... or i imagined them like that... (again you didnt read this.)   The Diva's came out in bikini's... all looked hot, and yes i have to say it, even Tracie, the only black chick was hot too.   3.&nbsp;&nbsp; Triple H vs Chris Benoit (My prediction... Triple H)   Ok, just as i tought it couldnt get any worse they wast a whole hour of good wrestling on Benoit.&nbsp; Im sorry but a whole fuckin' hour is way to much.&nbsp; Now Benoit did pull some great moves and yes Triple H did better moves, but an hour!&nbsp; Match went decent, kinda slow, but actually good wrestling and yes i did watch it.&nbsp; Benoit with over a dozen Crossfaces and Sharpshooters.&nbsp; And Triple H with over a doven Pedigree's... The only thing good about the match... Benoit did a suicide dive... to bad he wasnt successful.&nbsp; Around the end, HHH had a total of 3 points, Benoit with a total of 3 as well... and out of nowhere the damn crowd reacted as Eugene came in.&nbsp; Eugene immediatly attacked HHH, Flair, and Batista.&nbsp; Then hit HHH with a steal chair.&nbsp; This set me off.&nbsp; Then something got to me even worse... Eugene put the ref in the ring.... (WELL FUCKIN GREAT THE FUCKIN GUY PUT THE REF IN THE RING AND THE REF HAPPENED TO GET UP WHEN BENOIT WAS PINNING!!!!!!!) 1.............2..............3. with a total of 5 seconds left before the 1st count.... it was over no matter what....   My rating:&nbsp;Do you even want to know!?&nbsp;&nbsp; fine, my rating is:&nbsp; -***** for eveolution's interferance and for Eugene... however the match was rated a: ***3/4 in my mind. Blame Eugene for it all.   (Ok i officially hate Benoit, Eugene, Flair, Orton, Batista and yes i hate HHH right now for not kicking out, i hate both the ref's, i hate bischoff, i hate the fans, i hate the camra man, i hate the timer dude, i hate whoever aired the match, i hate spike tv, i hate the writers of RAW, i hate the fat man in the black shirt in the crowd, i hate that title belt, i hate the iron man match, i hate raw, i hate my t.v., i hate me for even watching it, i hate those diva's who just wasted time and didnt show STEVIE RICHARDS, i hate rosie for eliminating STEVIE, i hate Jericho for not beating orton, i hate the chocolate chip cookie i was eating, and i hate edge cause i always have hated him, and oh yah... I hate rock... and I&nbsp;BLAME EUGENE for me hating all of them!   Over all show was good.&nbsp; I have to thank WWE for having a fantastic show because i happened to be happy... Stevie was at least on raw.... pissed because Eugene cost HHH the title... and excited to see Ivory and Stacy fuck inside my head... (you didnt read this.) overall the show was great and a 60 min. iron match was even worth it even though the ending ruined it from being a ***** match.   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1.&nbsp;&nbsp; Stevie Richards vs Val Venis (My predictions... Stevie Richards)  Stevie Richards and Val Venis put on one hell of a performance.&nbsp; Val Venis got some great shoulder blocks and even got that mov he does when he thows his oponent into the ropes and uses his knee to his oponents gut.&nbsp; Stevie got some great neckbreakers and a Stevieplex.&nbsp; He tried for his Stevie T like 3 times, yet everytime it was countered.&nbsp; Val Venis went for the Money Shot and hit, but Stevie KICKED OUT!?!?.&nbsp; Val Venis then knocked him back down and went for it agin only this time nailing it and getting the three count.  Winner: Val Venis  My rating: ***  2.&nbsp; Chuck Palumbo vs Maven (My prediction... Chuck Palumbo)  Maven really sucked like usual... The only thing that i liked about Maven was him getting his ass kicked by Chuck.&nbsp; Chuck pulled a good performance in my opinion, even though he is an Eminem wannabe, and yet still is better then Eminem... so does that make Eminem the wannabe? or is Chuck much better with the Eminem look that Eminem wants to look like Chuck who coppied Eminem?... hmm... whatever... anyways Chuck got some great kicks to Mavens back... thats pretty much the only good thing that happened in the match.&nbsp; I thought Chuck won it when Maven got the Crossbody on Chuck then Chuck rolled over pinning Maven, and i jumped to my feet only to see Maven kick out. (so i got mad and went to get a drink of water).&nbsp; Ends up Maven won the match when i got back, so i wasnt to happy to see Maven win.&nbsp;  Winner: Maven  My Rating: -*+ 1/2* =&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; -1/2* (Maven won... so it had to suck thats why it is in the negatives.) Nah, actually it is a 1/2* match  3.&nbsp;&nbsp; Victoria vs Jazz (My prediction... Victoria)  This should be an interesting match... too bad i forgot to pay attention and missed all the moves.&nbsp; But Victoria had a very hot entrance, and she wore PINK!.&nbsp; Okay, this may seem kind of grose, but Jazz also looked kinda hot.&nbsp; I mean, who cant resist a lady with her hair all messed up and looks like a gorilla even with makeup?!?... okay, that was just fuckin nasty.&nbsp; Anyways, i did catch Jazz with a few submissions and Victoria going over the top rope. Then Stevie's crossdresser attire came out and attact Jazz... (WHO IS THE CROSS DRESSER!? I WONDER!) The "lady with abnormally red hair and wears grandma dresses" reminded me of the girl from the ring.&nbsp; i have no idea why, i thought i knew just a min. ago... but oh well.&nbsp; Well Victoria came in the ring and pinned Jazz.&nbsp; Victoria looked as if she didnt know who it was. Stevie.. i mean "the abnormally red haird lady" had a smile on "her" face... hmm.   Winner: Victoria  My Rating: 3/4* maybe a * cause of Stevie's apperiance!  Which reminds me... I may have missed Joe Schmo Show 2 on last Monday.&nbsp; Too bad the Wheeper lady left.  &nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This weeks RAW started off with HHH in the ring.  He talks about how he went and lasted 60 minuets in the ring with Chris Benoit, Yadda Yadda Yadda.  He then talks about Eugene, how he is a moron, idiot, and a simpleton.  He then calls out Eugene like eight or nine times.  But instead he gets William Regal.  Regal says that Eugene isnt here today.  And then he says that he was the one who sent Eugene to attack HHH.  Regal then blabs on about how HHH and him were tag partners and talks about how "evil" they were.  Regal says this one cool line, but i cant remember it... something about venom in his veins.  1.   Diva Elimination (My prediction... Christie)  Evidently i was wrong again... Cammile one of my favs of the 9 diva's got eliminated.  Oh well.  2.  Rhyno and Tajiri vs Robert Conway and Sylvan Grenier (My prediction... Rhyno and Tajiri)  Over all the match was great.  Very fast paced.  However way too short.  I think they would be great tag team champs with the pop they got from the crowd, also they are really good in the ring as a tag team.  I wish i could have seen what they were like in ECW. Rhyno gored i believe robert conway and was attempting to gore sylvan.  Tajiri then got Sylvan in a pin and won the match.  My rating - **  Interview was made with Randy Orton.  He talks about how he won the battle royal. He says that Lesnar won the title at age 25 and that Orton will be the youngest... He said it as if he wanted a fued with Lesnar. (Lesnar would kill him.)  He then mentions off people he had taken out... This list consisted of Shawn Michael, Mick Foley, Sgt. Slaughter, and Steve Austin. (When did he take out Austin.)  Lita was talking to Stacy keibler backstage talking about Trish Stratus i would assume.  Then Matt Hardy came in.  Matt asked Stacy to leave and both wished Stacy and good luck on her match.  Matt tells Lita he wants to be with her.  And Lita tells matt the same.  (This kinda ticked me off to see these angles of romance... i just cant stand that shit.) Matt then says he wants to get married as soon as possible. (I plugged my ears because i dont wanna hear him say that to my bitch... to bad i unplugged them at the wrong time and heard them mention marrage.  3.   Tyson Tomko w/ Trish Stratus vs Rosie w/ Stacy Keibler (My prediction... Rosie)  Great match i thought. I noticed something in this match...  Tyson really sucks.... and his name keeps reminding me of that toy car... Tonka!!!.. Rosie did some great moves such as the top rope leg drop and then Stacy did a cartwheel!!!!.  Trish got in the way and distracted Rosie.. Tomko then got the big boot.  My rating - *1/4  Jericho's Highlight reel took place.  Edge obviously wanting to know why Jericho eliminated him.  But before they got to that Jericho said that at Summerslam it was going to be a triple threat match.  Batista vs Edge vs Jericho.  Chris Jericho and Edge got into eachother's faces a few times.  Edge hopefully a heel.  Then they duked it out a little bit.  Some good stuff.  Edge attacted Jericho unexpectedly.  Then Jericho attacted Edge unexpectedly.  4.   William Regal vs Triple H (My prediction... William Regal)  William Regal attacked Triple H during his entrance.  Regal reall took it to him, he tore up the announcer table.  He just literally beat the fuck out of HHH.  Then out of nowhere Triple H hit Regal with brass-knucks.  The ref saw it and DQ'd HHH.  Regal won the match.  Triple H then grabbed his best friend... The Sledge Hammer, and tried to attack regal with it.  but regal countered and grabbed his brass-knucks.  HHH counters.  HHH then finally hits Regal wih the hammer, causeing him to bleed even more.  JR about this time went crazy.  Regal had to be put on a gurney.  Then HHH got back in Regals face and then flipped it over.  Triple H went all crazy, kinda reminded me of someone having a seizure.  My rating - DUD  Eric Bischoff then tells HHH that at summerslam he will be whiping Eugene's blood off his hands instead of Regals.  The Diva's are doing their special task.  I think they were pretty good at campagning.  Carmella my favorite did a good job but seemed a little shy.  Christie did great.  SHE EVEN DANCED!!!! but she needs to go.  The i saw Tracie... she took off her shirt... and her chest was flatter then Shaniqua's.  So she obviosuly lost my vote by far.  Kane and Lita were backstage and Kane trying toi get into Lita's skin and make her mad.  Kane wants a match.  Matt Hardy vs Kane...  For who ever wins gets to marry Lita.  (I want to win!) Kane then says that Lita wont be wearing White at the wedding, Lita then slaps him. (Still not knowing what he meant by that.)  Kane vs Maven (My prediction...  Kane)  I went and made a sandwich durring this match... sorry for not telling what happened. All i saw was a chokeslam done by Kane to Maven.  My rating - Dont know.  Evolution vs Benoit, Jericho, and Edge (My prediction... Benoit, Jericho, and Edge)  I didnt like this match at all.  In fact i was about to change the channel after the first comercial break.  Benoit did a few german suplexes.  Jericho and Edge pretty much did nothing but drop kicks, clotheslines, and punches.  Jericho did do the Lionsault.  Benoit got the sharp shooter then only getting RKO'd by Randy Orton.  My rating - 1/4*  
      
</post>


</Blog>