<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A friend of mine took a survey on tunes good for lovemaking...thought I'd share it everyone.  Here goes...  Verve Remixed (1 and 2)  Crash - By Dave Matthews  Loveless - By My Bloody Valentine  I'm Still in Love With You - By Al Green  Midnight Soul (Various Artists)  Playboy Jazz After Dark (Various Artists)  Blade Runner (Soundtrack)  Portishead - By Portishead  Nickel Creek - By Nickel Creek  Maxinquaye - By Tricky   Artists (anything by...):  Zade Dirani The Be Good Tanyas (Canadian trio)  Asford and Simpson  Barry White  R.Kelly (especially the album 12-play)  Kenny.G  Yanni  Fourplay (Smooth Jazz)  Najee (Smooth Jazz)  Thievery Corporation   Songs:  Tower of Song - By Leonard Cohen  Turn Off the Lights  Sixty-Six (66) - By Afghan Whigs  I Want a Little Sugar in My Bowl - By Nina Simone  Late Night - By Syd Barrett Desert Rose (techno remix)    

						
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Have you ever watched one of those prescription drug ads carefully? They are stupid!! Here’s a sample…  ‘[sales pitch]…Ziploc OTG will cure your migraine problem forever in weeks….[more sales pitch] Ask your doctor if Ziploc OTG is right for you. Known side effects include congestive heart failure; chest pain; vision imbalance; mild depression; and hypotension have been reported in about 1 of 100 patients. Rare cases of bronchospasm, angiodema and stroke have also been reported.’  Man, that thing sounds more like a killing machine than a drug. I’d rather live my entire life with migraines. Can you imagine anyone actually considering using this drug after seeing the ad?  ‘Hmmm…. Honey do you think I should ask our doctor about Ziploc OTG?’    ‘John, what about the side effects?’  ‘Oh sweetheart, the side effects are not that serious. Its just possibilities of heart failure, stroke, blindness, choked lungs and swellings … all those things happen to only one in 100 patients anyway!!’  Amen!  

						
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is why I don't like some sci-fi movies !  Later 

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Have you ever leased a car, by any chance? No? Good!! I just did. The fat salesman at the BMW showroom never told me that I could drive only 15,000 miles a year. Now, when it comes to numbers, there is this something about me, I have to obey them. I bow to their sacred powers, especially if they have to do anything with green bills. I am the guy who turns his cell phone off towards the end of the month.   Anyway, so the other day I was on my way to the movie theater when Neal called and said ‘Dude, I am at the airport, could you come pick me up?’. Now I was thinking ‘The airport? That’s 11.79 miles away. You know what that means? I can’t go to grocery store or the gym tomorrow!’ After a couple of minutes of contemplation, I heard Neal’s voice ‘You there?’ and I said in a moribund tone ‘Yeah, I’ll pick you up!’  On my way to the airport I realized to my shock that I was wrong about my calculation. Its not 11.79 miles, its 12.45 miles [High Pitch]!! Oh my god, this couldn’t be happening. So I pull over in panic and this cop pulls over behind me, gets out of his car, and comes over to my door. I’m looking in the mirror and thinking, ‘Shit, I should have shaved, now he’s going to think I’m Al Qaeda trying to bomb this milestone’.  The officer asked in his husky voice, ‘Is everything alright, sir?’ And I’m thinking ‘Nooooooo, I miscalculated, you dumb ass, can’t you see?? Haven’t  you  ever leased a car?’ Trying hard to sound calm, I said ‘I’m fine, just a panic attack’. So then he said ‘Sir are you sure you can drive, if not I suggest that you call a friend to drive you home.’ And I’m thinking ‘No way! I am out of cell phone minutes!’ Now I get enraged! All I remember now is that I did use some sacrilegious and unwarranted adjectives when I told the cop to leave me alone.  Oh yes, by the way Neal did bail me out the next morning!  Have a great 4th of July !  

						
</post>


</Blog>