<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW, what a week.  Work has been extremely CRAZY.  The Europe side of the Business seems to be in shambles- and the low morale seems to be spreading to the North America side.  Fronting competition rumors, and still trying to bring NEW business - it is never dull.  Rachel comes home from Las Vegas tonight.  It has been weird to be without my child for a week,way too quiet.  Of course I had grande/romantic notions of a week alone with my hubby with the kid, but LIFE got in the way.  Guess that happens when you have been married 25 years.  The weather has been beautiful this week in Indiana, 70's during the day, 60's at night, cool breezes.  The way Summer is suppose to be.  I am trying to get to a good place work wise so I can enjoy a week of vacation next week.  Off to Michigan.  First to Frankenmuth and then to Mackinac Island for 4 days.  Just can't wait to be near the water and relax.  Well I got to run and get ready to head to Indy, first dinner than the Airport.  I'll keep you update on the Mother and Child Reunion. Thanks for letting me talk. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been thinking of journaling for sometime now, and then found out about Blogging.  Why not, I ask.  At almost 45 years old I am striving to find my lost youth, realize my dreams and live a life of simple abundance.  I struggle everyday to realize my blessings and to be content.  I am almost a month away from turning 45 years old.  To say I am middle aged means I should live to 90.  God that sounds old. I am fairly upbeat person who gets beat down by the everyday occurrences of workplace and office politics.  I dream of a day when I am free from corporate chaos and can enjoy life in a carefree manner.  I struggle with my existence as a good wife, wonderful mother, dedicated daughter/sister, conscientious employee, and devoted friend.  I have wrestled with "middle aged" demons the past several years.  Some aches and pains, but mostly a shifting body image.  I feel like the bloom is off the rose, but I am fighting to retain what little bud might be left.  I am in the midst of dealing with weight and body issues as I mature.  I am certain I am somewhere between premenopause and post tramatic stress.  I network with a group of wonderful women that are envolved with FAA (Food Addicts Anonoymous) and try to support each other in a wheat/flour/sugar- less life.  Amazing when I am 100% committed to the program I feel so much better.It is just a daily struggle to break free from years of unhealthy practices.  It is my hope that share my thoughts with you- and can help you too deal with issues that present themselves as Mid Aged Crisis material.  I look forward to finding freedom via words, and peace through composition.  Thank you for listening.  Till tomorrow. XO
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, I fought it and finally hauled my butt out of bed this morning and walked 1 1/2 miles.&nbsp; It has been several weeks since I walked in the AM.&nbsp; It had become part of my ritual and daily habit- and then vacation.&nbsp; Hopefully I can STICK with it and motivate myself to keep on keeping on.&nbsp; It really does make a difference on how the day goes.&nbsp; I better scram, but wanted to check in and let you know I AM OK.&nbsp; I will survive.  &nbsp;  Later, JP   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 6:34 AM and I've been up since 4:30 AM.  Got to read the paper before 5:00 AM today.  I've been on vacation last week, and catching up this week at work has been a bear.  This is our busiest season- dealing with clients we want to keep, and prospects we want to close. I HATE SALES!  I don't know how ever got to the place I did in my career.  I have always considered myself a people person- and I as I have been told that's what makes me a natural.  In the Subscription Business there is always the RENEWAL SEASON to contend with.  Seems my company is always doing something "strategic" and major around renewal season.  This year they have changed payment policies, have announced a company reorg ("efficiency project") and possible cuts in jobs in Customer Service and other areas of operations.  Fighting competitors rumors and not feeling 100% confident myself about the job situation just lends to stress.  I plan to attend my group tonight, FAA.  I got a reach out call last night from a member and it really makes me appreciate then- knowing someone cares.  I wish I could be more disciplined in making the move to getting a Sponsor.  It is a struggle doing this on my own. I thought last week on vacation would be so relaxing - and it was great to get away from the phones, laptop and work!  Now I am playing catch up and it seems to be getting the best of me this week. I need to call on my "higher power" as the FAA group instructs to get me through the rough sponts.  I know God is merciful and oversees my every move.  Nothing goes un-noticed.  You can run but you can't hide, kind of thing.  I wanted to be comitted to a life change to health habits. I struggle with OBSESSIONS over my weight- and it effects every aspect of my life.  Thanks for listening, and I am off to a wonderful start. Next week I WILL get back on track with my morning walks- and watching what I do and say.  Till later.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from my weekly Food Addicts anonymous meeting.  I have missed 2 weeks in a row, and struggled about going tonight.  I decided I NEEDED to go.  I have been wrestling the past couple of weeks with not doing what I need to do for myself... Allowing myself to dabble with unhealthy choices.  I KNOW better and know what I need to do to keep clean.  When I live an abstinent life without flour, wheat or sugar I feel SO MUCH better.  It was great to be welcomed with open arms and smiles tonight.  We are all in this struggle together.  I leave for vacation on Saturday, and I know I can do this!  I can make healthy choices, I can live a clean life.  Believing in my higher power, and finding a peace by getting over my obsession with food.  I know I found FAA because I was suppose to find it- I need and want to work the program.  I am a strong woman, I can overcome this illness.  Thank you God for loving me the way I am - and helping me become all that I was meant to be.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>