<Blog>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hehehe, thanks for inviting me. Not much to say right now. I will come up with something....eventually...
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The final chart shows as follows:  (users in alphabetical order) Aeri87: 352 coal, 11.7% Chaobreeder: 1384 coal, 46.1% Freya 55: 124 coal, 4.1% Hydra22: 1140 coal, 38.0%  Total: 3000 coal, 100.0%  Congrats everyone, we did this job, now onto the next one. 5k coal, due thursday. Special thanks to Aaron, keep up the good work, or leave. (Note: Chaobreeder is officially back in the clan.)  Total payment for all members: 360K / 4 people = 90k per person
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay everyone unfortunately I will be unable to help this upcoming week. My dad has signed me up for some stupid church camp when I am clearly atheist and I don't want to go, but its all good. Just wanted to let you know. Freya out ja!
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since the audioblogger service is temporarily down, I will put down the chart here. I will use the audio service in the future, but since I can't now....  As of this time, the totals stand as follows: (users in alphabetical order) Aeri87: 350 coal, 11.7% Chaobreeder: 790 coal, 26.3% Freya 55: 124 coal, 4.1% Hydra22: 952 coal, 31.7%  Totals: 2216 coal, 73.9%
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you go to www.audioblogger.con you can sign up for a *free* service that allows you to blog, even when you can't go online. I might be using this to report a total ore count, but it might be helpful if you need to post a coal count, and don't feel like getting online. Thanks for reading!
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok I currently have 57 coal in the bank and that is not including what I gave you earlier. I am once again lost in the world so as soon as someone can please help. I'll wonder aimlessly until someone helps or I find the coal site. Then I'll be okay, and by the way, the one time I spammed was I state a one time event. I don't plan on ever doing it again unless someone makes me angry. Which we all know is not very hard to do because I have a short fuse so don't mess with me. That is all. Freya out. :)
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK everyone, here's the basics. 1)  No spamming.  Once, on a forum, a member of a certain group I am involved with spammed. It was very annoying. Don't do it again *cough* Alyce *cough*. 2)  No foul language unless completely justified.  If you don't think it is 93.2% neccesary, don't use it. 3)  Post at least once on here every 2 weeks or get a pay cut.  4) When I post my Ore Count post (every 6 hrs.) post on the comments with your total. If you do not post on at least one of the Ore Counts per day, our orders may go out late.  When orders go out late, everyone gets a pay cut (myself included.) To accomodate this pay cut, I will spend the 5% cut on coal for the next orders. Please post on here with something to say or ask about. Note: If there are no outstanding orders, the clan can mine coal for a certain member's order. In other words, if you want coal, and we aren't working, just post and it will be done, free of charge.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Since I thought it would be a good idea to post the news on here, I started with the latest news. We can put our own thoughts on the comments, so if you think this news/update is unfair or otherwise stupid, or you would like to inquire as to what they were smoking when they came up with this stuff, go right on ahead and put up a comment! I'll be doing this everytime a new news post comes out. PS: I would like to take this opportunity to remind the rest of you to try to get members. It is very cheap and very much worth the price. Since Aaron mainly lacks in the members only skills, that would be the easiest way to kick his ass in something.        &nbsp;      &nbsp;    27th July 2004 - Agility, Potions and Parties!      Brimhaven Agility Arena    The enterprising Cap'n Izzy No-Beard invites you to the Brimhaven Agility Arena, entry is only 200 gp! The entrance is the bamboo hut in the north-east part of Brimhaven.  The Agility Arena is a huge cavern of platforms connected by traps and obstacles. There are many different routes to get around the agility arena, you are much more likely to fail the obstacles on some routes than on others, some ways can not even be taken until you reach a certJustain agility level.   One platform is marked by a flashing arrow, try and make your way to it. Every minute a different platform will become the one with the flashing arrow instead. If you tag more than one pillar in a row then you will receive a ticket. You won't get a ticket at the first pillar but you will for every pillar you tag after that. If you miss a pillar then you will miss out on the next ticket so try and get as many as you can! You can save up these tickets and trade them in for more agility experience or for some items which you can't get anywhere else.  There is no agility requirement but players with low agility will find it difficult to get any tickets. As your agility level increases and you can take more routes through the arena and you start to fail the traps and obstacles less you will begin to get significantly more tickets.   There be booty to be got, ye landlocked landlubbers!    New Potions    2 of the things you can get from your agilty arena tickets are new herbs - Toadflax and Snapdragon. These are the potions associated with those herbs.   Herblore level 34: Toadflax + Toads' Legs = Agility Potion Effect: Raises agility level by 3 Herblore level 63: Snapdragon + Red Spiders' Eggs = Super Restore Potion Effect: Restores stats including some prayer   Party Room changes    Party pete will now periodically clear worthless junk from the drop chest. He will leave anything which he thinks has some value. If there are lots of items in the chest, you now get a greater chance of getting something in a balloon. It is also now cheaper to pull the lever or get the knights to dance.    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Right now, I am trying to get all of my skills above level 40. It's going well, but the hard ones seem to be hard only because they are very boring. I know most people found mining boring, but I didn't. Now that Aaron is gone, we might have to   work a bit harder. He has surpassed my total skill level. His stats can be found at the bottom of this post. I would like all of us to have at least one skill above one of his. I do have my skill done. My mining is still higher than his (unless he got a few hundred thousand xp in the past day.) Anyway, here are his skills.     &nbsp;   Total Skill: 952    Attack: 67    Defence: 66    Strength: 67    HP: 67    Ranged: 52    Prayer: 49    Magic: 45    Cooking: 57    Woodcutting: 53    Fletching: 33    Fishing: 55    Firemaking: 54    Crafting: 50    Smithing: 49    Mining: 71    Agility: 36    Thieving: 34    *Any skills not shown are not above level 30.    If you have surpassed any of these,  please  put a comment on here. Thank you!    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay $285.91 McDonald's paycheck. Woot woot!!!!!!!BTW! Get on and post people. I come here everyday and look for new post.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On the grounds of being lazy, complaining about the light work load, and insubordination, Chaobreeder is removed from the Metal Lords. He is to be blocked from all clan friends lists, and not to be talked to in any way. His clan is now our main rival, and anyone in his clan is not to buy our resources.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If anyone wants to go the full mile and help me get the ability to smith rune plates, (worth 85k for only 69.8k of materials) I will need the following materials: NOTE: you are not in any way obligated to do this order.  637,248 Coal 159,312 Mithril ore  ~OR~  22,416 + 144,060 + 625,656 Coal 5,604 Mithril 24,010 Adamantite 78,207 Runite  I will pay anyone who helps 1.5 million gp as soon as I get it, which, if we can mine these things, won't take long. If you all help, you all get payed. Your name will be chosen at random to determine order. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would like to place an order at this point. After we finish the final coal order, and since the man ordering silver has yet to contact me again, I myself would like to use our services. I will pay all of you very well, especially since this order will allow me to make a very valuable prize: Adamant (addy) bars. With this, I can make Addy daggers, which sell for almost 800 gp a piece. Therefore, for every 700gp worth of coal, we make more than 800 gp. Nothin' but profit. I can provide all of my own addy for now, but you will all soon be able to help me. According to the high scores listings, if you all gather 1/3 of both materials, your levels will increase as follows:  Aeri87: 212295 (Lv. 57) -> 735335 (Lv. 69) Chaobreeder: 756227 (Lv. 70) -> 1279267 (Lv. 75) Freya 55: 123400 (Lv. 51) -> 646400 (Lv. 68)  Note: Isn't it odd that the same amount of XP can raise one player 17 whole lvls and another only 5?  My order is as follows: 22,416 coal, 5,604 mithril. Thanks for helping if you feel like it, and if you don't, that's fine, tell me and I can give you increased XP values depending on how many of us quit. As an incentive, I will be paying based on a ratio of materials to time. Whosoever get the most materials in the least time gets paid in the least time. Who ever comes in second will be paid second, and so forth.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would still like everyone to report on  all of their ores (yeah, all of them, not just coal) by using the comments on this post.  Thank you!
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woo Hoo I got my job at McDonald's. I have orientation tonight.Isn't this exciting. I'm still getting Four Swords for you Jimmy but you still owe me a B-Day present.(hint hint an old game like Dead or Alive 3 would be fine.) Freya out. Oh yeah I have 350 coal.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay Freya reporting. I currently have 211 coal in the bank and I am working on more.BTW Jimmy I am coming to apply at McDonald's at 11:00 today so be there or be triangle. Freya out.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In order to keep up with current available numbers, I will require numbers for  all ores in the game  from all of you. This will benefit the entire clan in it's entirity.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      TURN IN YOUR APPLICATION TO McDONALD'S!!!!! WE NEED MORE PEOPLE!!!!! Thank you.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now that we have all returned, hopefully we can finish the new coal order in record time. We have already acquired.... umm.... *looks up new total on excel spreadsheet on laptop* 1265 coal, which is alright for a start, but we should have at least 3.5k by the end of Sunday. That's our goal, 3.5k coal by the end of tomorrow. I'll be working, will you?   Bonus: I sold the 5k coal to the second guy. Current payment for each member on this order: 210k 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys. I am totally back from camp. It sucked! The showers were home to many large insects and arachnids and the water pressure was very poor. The light rain we received had more pressure than our showers at the camp known as Tambo. Anyways I am ready to hit the mining again so tell me what to do. Freya out.                                             
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok Ok I know that this is a runescape clan blog I should talk about clan stuff like ore totals and stuff right? Yeah I'll eventually get to that but this time I want to apologize again for..yeah you guessed it. I didn't show up when I was supposed to again. Plus I had a bad day at work and knowing that Jimmy may be mad at me has put me into a bad mood. Oh yeah I thought I should at least put one runescape related thing in here so I'll let the others know how much coal I have.  Coal ore count for Aeri : 179 coal  Yeah yeah I know it's not much..but I'm working on it, and I'll be sure to get on runescape tomorow. Adios people...  P.S.  Best of luck to Jimmy tomorow on his driving test!
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok people, since my second buyer has yet to be on since he ordered, I'm giving him until Monday, July 5 to get on and claim his coal before I sell it to the highest bidder. Current Numbers(Including the new 5k coal order):  NAME / COAL / SILVER Aeri87 / 141 / 52 Chaobreeder / 195 / ??? Freya 55 / 57 / ?? Hydra22 / 6695 / 57 Total / 7088 (141.8%) / 109 (4%)
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wanted to apologize to all my fellow clan members for not being here tonight whenever we needed coal. Aunt Lucy needed the computer and before I could get back on andrew had me play some magic the gathering and that lasted about 3 hours... I currently have 61 coal and working on getting more. Thats all for this post  P.S.  OME! The 2nd episode of Aqua Teen Hunger Force was so funny!
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night saw a record 42,500 simultaneous players! As a result a few of our servers were getting low on spare bandwidth.  To make sure all these extra players doesn't cause the game to lag we have just purchased some extra bandwidth at the busiest locations, so it should be working much better now. We'll also continue to keep an eye on the bandwidth use to make sure we always have enough.  Taken from  urlLink www.runescape.com  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       New World Map     Today we have released a superb replacement for our exisiting world map in the form of an applet. With the new applet you can scroll around and zoom in and out with ease. The applet also contains all the new areas that have been discovered in RuneScape, including Mort Myre Swamp and Death Plateau! Saving the best to last, clicking items in the key highlights their placement on the map - helping you locate all sorts of useful places much faster.   Death Plateau Quest     Trolls have come down from the north and are camped on Death Plateau, they are using this base to launch attacks on the principality of Burthorpe! The Imperial Guard is taking heavy losses, they need your help!  If you are in search of adventure speak to Denulth, the leader of the Imperial Guard, in the Burthorpe training camp north of the Hero's Guild and accept the Death Plateau quest!  While this is a quest completable at any level, players with a low combat level should be very cautious or they could come to a sudden and sticky end at the hands of trolls.  This update introduces the town of Burthorpe and a troll area, which is an area that we have plans to expand in future updates with some quests classed in the experienced quests bracket.  We have made some adjustments to the agility arena. More than one person can now go over the low wall at once and it doesn't take as long to use the handholds.  Some colourblind people were struggling with the new strange boxes due to them being fairly transparent, therefore they are now no longer transparent.  Taken from  urlLink www.runescape.com  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today regular visitors to our website might notice that we have massively overhauled the front page! We know some of you might be used to our old layout, but we think that once you are used to the new design you will agree that it is easier to navigate. We have tried to make the front-page make better use of the available screen space, as well as making the most accessed areas (for example the worldmap) easier and quicker to get to.  The layout of the manual has also been improved, and lots of new information has been added, including a few new sections for you to discover yourselves!  You will also be glad to know we have added an all new exclusive wallpaper to our extra files section, which has moved towards the bottom of the main menu.  Finally, Mozilla Firefox 0.9 users will be pleased to know that we have improved compatibility with that browser, so you will now be able to login to the secure section of the site with less hassle than before.  Taken from  urlLink www.runescape.com  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We have had to move worlds 19,20,21 and 25 to a different location, because the company that was providing bandwidth for them previously has suddenly ceased trading. This meant we had to arrange an alternative at very short notice.  So we could get them up and running again as quickly as possible, those worlds have now been moved to one of our other existing providers.  Their new home is 'nlayer'. We already had a few worlds there and were very happy with their reliability/performance, so in fact the relocated worlds should hopefully run faster than ever at their new location.  All the worlds should now be functioning normally again.  *Taken from  urlLink www.runescape.com  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We've had to temporarily take our CET worlds offline to move them to a new bandwidth provider.  Unfortunately our old bandwidth provider for those worlds has suddenly ceased trading, and so we've had to arrange an alternative at very short notice.  The worlds are being moved across now, to a different cabinet in the same building, and should hopefully be back up in a few hours time.  Meanwhile you can keep playing anyway, please just use another world, and I'll post again as soon as they are back.  Thanks Andrew  *Taken From  urlLink www.runescape.com   This does indeed suck. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        2nd August 2004 - Zamorak Deconstructs 
</post>


</Blog>