<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Charlotte Bobcats held their expansion draft a little while ago, and I have yet to write a blurb about it yet. Desmond Furgeson was the only Portland Trail Blazer selected by the Bobcats. The surprise to me was  that Ruben Patterson was left unprotected. What surprised me further was the fact that Charlotte did not select him. he is a decent player that provides instant energy and helps livin up the game. The only explanations I could think of is that (1) They don't want to take his contract, which may be a lot for an expansion team or (2) They  were turned off by some of his character issues and the qualoty of his personality. I think the Bobcats will be in a world of hurt for a few years, but then again that is expected for an expansioon team....
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If anybody is interested in recieving a slideshow of Portland Trail Blazer photos, both old and new, I can hook you up for 1 gmail invite, unless you don't have access to an invite, in which case a good please will probably suffice.   urlLink Email Me 
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you are very interested in the Portland Trail Blazers, you can sign up for the fast.break email service  urlLink here   Of course this is the  urlLink NBA Webpage   And the  urlLink Blazer's Website   And one more interesting site is that of the new expansion team, the  urlLink Charlotte Bobcats   Have Fun!
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Am I the only one who would be very mad at the Blazers if they got rid of Theo Ratliff? After watching the part of the season he played in Portland, I think he is a must-have for the next season. If he can stay healthy he provides a dominate force in the lane to keep out pesky people driving to the basket. Forcing the opposing team to shoot from the outsides can prove invaluable to the team's success, and getting rid of the league leading shot blocker would be a major mistake, in my opinion. Leave any comments if you have an objection.
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Most of you have probably heard about a possible trade in the works, involving T-Mac and Steve Francis, along witha few other players. I think this trade would be beneficial on both sides. Francis is a good overall player who could help with the troubled Magic, and maybe work with Howard. T-Mac simply wants a change and may have a renewed work ethic in a new enviroment. This is not the only major trade rumor. Names are being thrown around like Shaq, and these trades would seriously shake up the league. Kobe Bryant may be looking at other teams, being as he is a free agent, and Phil Jackson is not returning, I'm not sure if we will recognize the 04-05 Lakers, but maybe thats a good thing....
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello everybody! This blog is dedicated to discussions and news about the Portland Trail Blazers. Obviously right now it is the offseason, so posts may not come to often, and may include news about other teams around the NBA. The NBA Draft just took a place a few days ago, and I am not very happy with the picks made by the Blazers. Telfair, selected at 13, is a young kid who shows a lot of raw skill, and could end up being one of the leagues premiere point gaurds, but the problem is the Blazers selecting him so high in the draft, when he will most likely take several years to fully be ready to run the team. I think the best bet would have been t take a more prepared player at 13, then waited and hope Telfair was availible at either 22 or 23, both picks of which belonged to the Blazers. Right now it is hard to tell, but come the regular season, I hope this guy can start playing at least a minimal amount, more then the other work in prgress, Travis Outlaw, does.
    
</post>


<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    This is a picture of my puppy Misty when we first got her at 8 weeks old&nbsp; urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today was the first day of Vacation Bible School at my church, and today went pretty well. Of course there was the usual racquet made by the hyper active little kids. but overall today went well. I am helping with crafts which is usually pretty laid back, so I am havin a good time. I am relaxing now, and tommorow after VBS I have to go to Midland library to talk to a lady about volunteering over the summer, orders from the parents......Anyways sorry about all of the dumb posts from late last night, but I was trying to get a certain amount so I could get this account thing...wel nvm, just ignore some of them.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This picture is a little larger, so i will put the link in this box and it will take you to a Seinfeld wallpaper that will keep your eyes busy:   urlLink Click Here For Wallpaper! 
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
         Another shot of Jerry Seinfeld speaking at a University
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
         Just a fun Seinfeld Pic
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I am still very bored, so here are some of the websites I go to at times:  www.nba.com www.nba.com/blazers http://home.comcast.net/~stanthecaddy22 www.3dgamers.com www.newegg.com  most of you won't be very interested in any of these, but im just adding more posts...
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Leave a comment on here if you like to wakeboard, I don't usually talk about wakeboarding much, but I'm interested to know if anybody does. In case you were eondering, I love wakeboarding and try to go as often as I can over the summer. I'm not very good, but I definately know what I am doing, and I am more interested in doing tricks then worrrying about just getting up.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Most of you should know that my favorite team is the Seattle Mariners, although this year they are not doing so great, and today a major trade was made. The Mariners traded away Freddy Garcia, probably their best pitcher, but the part that bugged me is how the announced it near the end of the game. Now supposedly they did that so the fans could say 'good bye', but I don't think it is a very nice way to break the news to Freddy. He finds out at the same time as everyone else in the stadium, when he is the one involved. Anyways, today has been pretty low-key, my parents and my brother have been down at OSU, and I have been mostly hangin out all day. This upcoming week I have Vacation Bible School at my church, and I am going to be helping out somehow with it. It is usually pretty fun, but I have to get up somewhat early. The good news is my B-Day is on friday and I am taking my license test, so I hope I can pass. I already passed the safety test, so now all I have left to tackle is the driving part.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Just had to throw these on here:                                  
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today was not very exciting. I got up, then went out and mowed the lawn, because I can make money :). Then I went and got a haircut, and I really do not like it. It is just not working, but I guess I will have to wait for it to grow some :(. Then I got back and went to CAC for a while and worked out, followed by Little Caesar's pizza, very good.... Thats about all I did today, not too exciting, the only reason I am posting this right now is cuz im waiting for MadTV to start :)    
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Most people know that my favorite NBA team is the Portland Trail Blazers, and I have a few wqords about the draft that recently took place. First of which is the 13th pick of Sebastian Telfair. This pick could possibly have potential, however they could have missed out by not selecting Jameer Nelson. I think Nelson is more prepared, and could make more of an instant impact. However I also feel Telfair has incredible raw talent and in a little bit of time could be become a premiere point gaurd in the league. His passing skills definately provide some entertainment. The two Russian players acquired by the Blazers will definately be interesting. I am only hoping they were not selected just as a publicity stunt, howver i have never seen them play so i do not know. All i know is it is rumored they have enough talent to play almost immediatly, however the Blazers will have to buy out their contracts with the Russian team they are currently a part of, which seems relatively cheap compared to the NBA salaries. The final pick of the Blazers was a late draft pick, not really intended for the near future. Possibly the height alone will prove him useful in due time. This offseason will probably hold many big changes, most espicially around the rest of the league, and next year will be quite the  experiment.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hey everybody, I assume that everybody reading this knows me, so I don't have to go into much. I am not sure that I wull use this service much, but I guess its there if I am ever bored. Post any comments if you want to, questions, comments, anything you feel like saying. If you dare talk bad 'bout Seinfeld be prepared to be lashed out upon. Lately I have been doing good, although it does not feel like summer has begun. I want to sit back and relax this summer, however there are some people, who will go unnamed, that don't want me to have any free time this summer. I guess time will tell how this summer goes.... I was happy a few days ago because I got a free pair of Nike Shox, and that was pretty sweet. Otherwise not much goin on at the moment. Check back later....
     

        
</post>



</Blog>