<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My husband, little boy and myself go out to eat at a local pizza buffet once a week.  Its become a weekly ritual.  But i can't help but get tickled everytime we go.    My husband and son only like thin crust pepperoni and obviously so does everyone else, because it is the first item on the buffet that goes.  So when we come in and order our drinks we always special order a thin crust pepperoni for the buffet.  As soon as they put it out there...we make such a spectacle of ourselves trying to be the first ones in line.  The person in front of you is scooping up not one, not two, but three slices...and you're saying under your breath..ok...enough...save some for the rest of us!  But when its my turn I gather up enough slices for my husband and my son...and I can only imagine what the person behind me is saying!  Why do these pizza restaurants do this to people..obviously cheese and pepperoni are the choice picks so why don't they make more?  They put out vegetarian, ranch, taco, sausage..which are ok..but most of the time if you get up to go for your second helping...thats what you have to choose from...because the pepperoni and cheese are already devoured.  Its like the manager and the staff are silently having their fun with us as we scramble around for the best slices.  They won't make more of the obvious favorite because that would spoil their amusement.  If they kept enough of it up there..than no more evil eye to the person in front of you, no more looks of disappointment when you go for seconds and you only have a choice of pineapple with ham or veggie lovers or no more running over each other trying to be the first to dive into that fresh pepperoni.  Nonsense, you say?  Well, the next time you go to a buffet...see for yourself. Out comes a fresh pepperoni or cheese pizza and watch and see if people don't practically elbow each other trying to be the first in line.   Nellie     
      
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's Monday morning and I'm glad.  I love the start of a new week.  It gives me the feeling somewhat of a new beginning...especially when its a beautiful sunny day like today.  We built my little boy a swing set.  He loves it!    I finished up my last show yesterday afternoon.  It was a broadway review sort of.....I sang "I Enjoy Being a Girl" from the "Flower Drum".  Its so much fun to do theater.  They are thinking about doing "Grease" in the spring.  My favorite movie.  I must confess I lost my temper with my little boy last night.  We came in from shopping and I told him to go put his dirty clothes in the hamper and get in the bathtub.  When he did....he peed all over the carpet and some of my clothes that I had just washed.  I lost it and said some very nasty things to him.  And i said the "F" word more times than I care to think about.  I just get so frustrated with him sometimes..but I know he does his best.  he can't talk but he can communicate a little bit with pecs...(picture exchange communication system).  I'm happy today and in a few minutes I'm gonna take him outside to his new swing set.  Nellie    
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok....this is my second post...starting to get kind of bold...:)  If you read this, let me hear from you so i'll know if any body is actually reading this.    Let me tell you a little about me.  I'm a housewife and I am a singer and an actress in my local theater.  Hence the name, Nellie, who's character I protrayed this last spring in our production of "South Pacific".    If anyone is familiar with this beloved broadway musical, talk to me..let me know what you think about it...or anything else that comes to mind.  Looking froward to hearing from you.  Nellie 
      
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is my first post for my new blog.  I'm really looking forward to sharing my ideas, frustrations and thoughts with people all over the world and making new friends who share the same interests.  Nellie   
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I've just about had it with you women who think they are too good to sit their little (or big) butts down on the toilet in public restrooms.  I know, I know what you're going to say, They're nasty.....germ infested..blah blah blah.  Personally, I don't prefer to squat uncomfortably above the toilet while I try to relieve myself.  It's highly uncomfortable and makes a huge mess, which brings me to the point I'm trying to make.  I'm sick and tired of having to clean up your pee pee of the rim just because you have some obsessive compulsive disorder.  All you have to do is keep a little box of wet wipes in your purse and wipe off the bowl so you can comfortably sit down and enjoy your "rest time".  Thats all you have to do!  But NO...instead you choose to squat over the toilet and splash your pee pee germs all over th place so people like me can come in after you and clean it up so we can enjoy a good piss in peace.  Its sooooooo aggravating!!  If you must squat over the toilet, at least be considerate and wipe off your excess so I don't have to do it.  That should be simple enough....ok?    Just a thought,  Nellie    
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You know whats really hard to do?  Try driving through a 15 mph school zone with Christopher Cross singing "Ride Like The Wind" on the radio.  Just a thought.  Nellie
      
</post>


</Blog>