<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      And now for today’s Spooning Fork...   urlLink     ‘Do I Move You?’ from  Anthology    Whatever else she may have been,  urlLink Nina Simone  could be queen of the barn-burner when she wanted. When  urlLink Austin Powers  lost his  urlLink mojo , he would have needed little more than this song, the epitome of what I like to call the smokey-bar blues, to regain it. How could you not instantly want to get down-’n-dirty when exposed to this potent 2:45 siren song? Just listen to those wailing harmonicas ... Struggling with bedroom eyes, folks?  Here’s your ticket.     And yet, in ‘Do I Move You?’ Nina manages to pose that one question worse than “Do I look fat?” By the end of the song, she’s got him backed up against a wall or the bed — you just know it. I’ll wager the man she was singing to felt not just a little terror should he fail to demonstrate adequate satisfaction. Come to think of it, this might just be the number capable to teaching men to  urlLink fake an orgasm  ...   When I touch you, do you quiver ...  from your head down to your liver.  If you like it, let me know it!  The answer better be “Yes .... yes ...   Great God Almighty, that pleases me!”    Other assorted ‘findings’ from this week ...         urlLink Tantric sex  = good, but may result with control-freak men.  (Tidbit from another writer, shared at a rooftop Brooklyn barbeque.)          Messenger bags are hot when worn by women. Which is to say, the way the strap separates our breasts is hot. I guess they just like spread in general ...  (Inside scoop from a guy friend, shared over dinner in a French cafe.)      Law school is the baby-clock for men. Women who age fear they’re too old to still have natural-born children. Men who age fear they’re too old to still take a stab at law school.  (Insight gained from cocktail chitchat with a bunch of current and aspiring lawyers.)   Narcissism is hip again! Recent comments from anonymous readers indicate my failure to use the cover of anonymity to reveal deep, personal secrets of the Broadway story is, well, a disappointment.  Too bad there wasn’t a reply-to email so I could share the “ urlLink Earl ” of my other blog .  That said, sometime this week I’ll try to post the story of either my meeting with The Latin American, or the backstory on The Harvard Lickwit.  Nina Simone,   Anthology     Austin Powers: The Spy Who Shagged Me 

      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      There are times when I feel rather guilty about being a woman. Last night, for example, I’m sitting at a friend’s going-away party describing my ongoing search for employment. When I mention something about “doing a lot of networking” lately, the friend interjects (without malice): “Yeah, but you’re a cute young woman!” His point: I have an advantage.    And I have to admit, when you’re dealing with men, looks certainly don’t hurt. Lately I’ve even taken to leaving my glasses at home a lot of the time. While their “geek chic” generated plenty of sexy-librarian mojo during grad school days and lately in bars around the city, I’m starting to think this unframed Broadway face is strong enough to stand on its own.    I pride myself on being the sort of woman who’s generally upfront, non-manipulative and straight-forward with men, but the fact of the matter is, my looks do factor into the interaction equation. At a cocktail party not long ago, I was catching up with the Harvard Lickwit, to whom I confessed a fear that my snug-fitting fuchsia pants were not in keeping with a dress policy that mandated ties for men and frowned upon “wardrobe malfunctions.”     Dress-code exemptions   “Since we’re being honest with each other,” he replied (referencing an earlier conversation about the nature of our phase as friends-who-don’t-kiss), “as long as you’ve got a body like that you don’t need to worry about the dress code.”    I wasn’t quite sure what to make of this. Was it a statement about dress codes in general? I’m not sure how I feel about such an exemption. More likely, it derived from gossip that later made its way to my ears: supposedly the party’s organizer has the hots for the me.    And indeed, at a later meeting of the same group I experienced some confirmation of this tidbit. The host is a slightly gruff  urlLink Tim Robbins  type whose evident chainsmoking gives his voice the rasp that made newspapermen hot in the 70s. Of course  urlLink Woodward and Bernstein  talked like that! It was because they  used their voices so much  — prying important secrets out of sources over the whiskey and smokes necessary to create a relaxed rapport. Or, because with the more shifty-eyed, it was necessary to engage in low-talking, furtive conversations. Strain on your voice, all of it. Hot stuff. The Tim Robbins type is clearly experiencing some 70s nostalgia or undergoing an identity crisis because lately he’s been cultivating a serious ’fro. A gray ’fro. As Best Friend pondered: “Is he gray down  there ?”     At any rate, the Tim Robbins type is a flitter — he pops into conversations for like two minutes to make sure people are happy, then drifts away before things get too serious or boring. With any luck he’ll catch only the wittiest moments and be convinced our chats are the stuff of a screenwriter’s dream — and these gatherings the mark of a canny host’s success.    But he wouldn’t be entirely wrong to think so. These gatherings draw a smattering of Ivy-league grads and other word nerds, so the small talk is sometimes clever. The sad thing, though, is when an evening of steady drinking starts to catch up with your wit. Later that evening (the post-fuchsia pants evening) a covert romantic I’d been introduced to popped back into the conversation. Like the Tim Robbins type, Covert Romantic is a flitter. But whatever interest he had in me was evidently more powerful, as he’d stick around much longer. Invariably, though, he’d drift away for a while before returning to my side.      When smart men vie for women ...   One of these returns interrupted my conversation with a quick-witted, good-looking Yale alum who was gamely indulging my rant about the decorative use of turkeys in a Thanksgiving spread at a newspaper I once worked for. Apropos of nothing, Covert Romantic reappears and starts recounting a Sept. 11 story he’d just heard with all the grace of shifting from 4th to 2nd gear without 3rd. I wince on his behalf, but the gathering crowd is generous.    Later, however, back on light conversational ground, he and the Yale Hotpot debate the aesthetic merits of a particular phrase that one of us had used. Yale Hotpot and I then return to our conversation while Covert Romantic listens and attempts to re-insert himself with a heavy-handed quip he has to work for. When Yale Hotpot points this out, it dawns on me that quite possibly this exchange is largely for my benefit. A breeze from the open door stirs the hem of my semi-transparent vintage dress, and I struggle not to grin.  So this is what it looks like when intellectual egos duke it out . Unfortunately for Covert Romantic, the wine has wilted his wit over the course of the evening, and Yale Hotpot is both sober and of the profession where verbal quickness is encouraged.    But the lumps and the male sparring don’t end there. At the end of the night, I find myself walking uptown with the Tim Robbins type, who wastes no time in mentioning that Covert Romantic looks like a child molester, from which comparison I can insinuate anything I’d like.   Clearly my presence at these gatherings is similar to taking photographs in India. There’s no such thing as unobserved observation, or innocent participation. As luck would have it, I’m probably one of the more attractive women in a crowd that sometimes borders on sausage fest. And that makes a difference. It  always  makes a difference. If it weren’t hard enough learning to gracefully manage the social impact of my smarts, I also have to learn to manage the impact of my looks, such as they are.    What’s a girl to do?  While men may not take notice at the way I lick my dessert spoon (as romance novels would have it), they do notice when I start to dance (one time, in fact, I think I was propositioned to act in a porn film!). It’s a power that all women have. I recognize it in my father’s reluctance to tell me or my sister that we’re  beautiful , although he will praise our character and call us lovely. And I see it in a friend who worries about marrying a pretty girl who later gets fat, but doesn’t seem to care about his growing belly.  I can’t somehow abdicate that power (nor would my vanity permit me to do so), but I still want to try to find that line between putting my best foot forward and being exploitive. Without tossing all my cutest clothes, of course …      Invisible Dragon: Four Essays on Beauty     All the President's Men       Independent Nation: How the Vital Center Is Changing American Politics   

      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Sorry to regular readers who checked back Tuesday to catch the very-exciting announcement about my new all-access commenting feature (now totally inclusive, thanks to  urlLink Haloscan ) ... You guessed it: today was yet another occasion on which I  left my computer behind  for a foray into the real world. I actually had not just lunch, but lunch and  coffee . With men. Two  different  men, in fact. I even managed to pay nothing except for subway fare, but that’s surely more a consequence of the sympathy-inducing powers of unemployment (when present in a “reasonably attractive” woman) ... than a new crop of pseudo-dates creeping in under my nose. (Besides, in my experience thus far,  pseudo-dates are generally the province of Christian men. Secular men know they want sex and make no bones about it .)    Writing a blog like  Sexless in the City  is a double-edged sword, you see. While you instantly gain men’s attention, there’s a good chance things will never get past the first little chit-chat. Except, of course, for the writer who recently proclaimed himself intent on getting into my blog.  Now why does that sound dirty ...     Today’s conversations, however, were generally less salacious: the woes of wooing a gender-balanced Kerry-party crowd, and why a long-time  urlLink Apple  user has recently switched to PCs. (I was conversing with guys, remember.)     There was passing talk about the celibates at a yoga center where I lunched: apparently they choose to don orange for some reason. I mean,  orange . It’s like, “Warning! Celibate on the loose!” No offense to Buddhists, but isn’t that also the color of choice for hazard suits and criminals? It’s like  you’re either about to encounter something very dangerous (a sex-starved grown-up), or that   person   is about to face great danger: a soul unable to compensate for other needs with sex . These people (judging on what I saw) don’t wear the typical Buddhist garb where it’s not only vibrant orange but some sort of toga to boot … they were wearing the clothes it looked like  urlLink Martha Stewart  rejected after failing to bleach the orange to a satisfactory pastel.  … But I digress. What caused greater curiosity was my other friend’s remark about encounters with  urlLink fake ads  on personal sites. Not long ago, he claimed, a hypersocial relative from France came to visit. Before inviting a steady stream of girlfriends to come join him in crashing on my friend’s tasteful couch, the relative first turned to local dating sites. (Why does this remind me of some kids’ cartoon with mice, like,  Francois visits America ?) As the men browsed the ads, they found that most women pictured were average, but 1-in-10 or so was stunning. They of course responded to these (well, the hypersocial Frenchman did), but curiously none replied. My skeptical friend inferred that these were probably  fake ads created to keep men hooked on the site , dreaming of getting a date with that “average woman” who looks like a pornstar yet for some reason can’t meet men.    Of course we’ve all heard about the fake photos people supposedly use in personal ads (I think I once “whispered” to one Texan who did such when I was still on  urlLink Udate ) ... and we’ve seen horrifying proof that plenty don’t ... but have any of you heard or encountered personal ads where the whole thing seems unreal? This is probably nonexistant on  urlLink Craigslist , but I assume most of you don’t exclusively rely on that site for meeting people.     So ... thoughts? I’d be curious to hear your stories.     Random reader of the day   In one of Monday’s promo ads, I made the mistake of saying, “What kind of  urlLink stripper  would rivet a Muslim lady?” Now I’m scared that horny European terrorists have me on their radar:  Subject:     i take u Date:     July 26, 2004 1:57:38 PM EDT To:       anon-37440057@craigslist.org how r u hope u ok i saw your add on the web say u need some one glad to know u more if u want me to be i also look for some one so what ever the caese is i be happy to help or be with u if u need a pic i can send one What, me, paranoid? Nevah...     Song of the Day   And finally: the much-teased premier of the  Sexless in the City   Spooning Fork  (so-named because a) spooning is an old-timey term for kissing — aka, snogging — b) a  urlLink tuning fork  is a music-related implement, and c) at 1:17 a.m. I can’t think of anything more clever to describe this song-analysis feature).     urlLink     Dancing Queen from   Gold - Greatest Hits   I have to confess, the true meaning of this song was not really brought home to me until the wee hours of a recent Saturday morning, which I whiled away in an east-40s karaoke bar. Thanks to the aid of a slick vintage-90s music video, however, it all came together ...    When you actually read them, the lyrics are a revelation. No wonder Brazilian waxes are sweeping the nation! It’s not Bush-hatred run amok, but decades of girls’ nights out encouraging women to free their inner stripper — I mean, “pole-dance professional.”  You come in to look for a king  Anybody could be that guy...  You’re a teaser, you turn ’em on  Leave them burning and then you’re gone  Looking out for another, anyone will do Forget all that grinding-with-your-girlfriends crap. The really secret to male attention is dancing like it rumples up your panties in a  good  way. (Don’t forget, Abba sang in pre-thong days.)     Now what if the candidates had to each do playlists for Apple, their platform cleverly embedded in the lyrics? What  then , I ask you, what  then ? Bush, I guarantee, would not include “Dancing Queen” on his tape because he’s  urlLink worked against human-trafficking . Actually  urlLink quite a lot .     And so we see why Anna Broadway will not have blogging credentials for either political convention ...     Gold: Greatest Hits       Gender, Trafficking and Slavery (Focus on Gender Series)        We've Got Blog: How Weblogs Are Changing Our Culture 

      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Apologies to my regular readers who checked in over the weekend to see ...  the same essay!  ... but this was the weekend I forayed into stripping. I spent most of the weekend gloved and on the street in front of my house, instead of bare-handed and blogging away inside.     Nice weather for it, luckily enough. I had plenty of company between the stoop-set across the street, chatty passersby, and an older Muslim lady who perched on my porch to watch for quite a while. Since my neighbors are indistinguishable from cats when streetside curiosities are concerned, I made many new acquaintances, male and female.    A few things I’ve learned along the way: stripping is hard work. And time-consuming, at that. The stripper has to really penetrate the wood, so full-on immersion is ideal. Unfortunately, however, I do not have or know of these “stripper vats” I keep hearing about from friends. So, I kept taking the wood  urlLink in and out  of the stripper only to discover more time was necessary. Considering the mess it makes, and the discovery of not two but three layers to be removed, this has been an involved process.    But after two arduous afternoons at it, the wood is almost back to its original naked state. One guy at  urlLink Lowe’s  guessed it might be birch. In any case, I can hardly wait till the stripping part is done and I get to actually  stain  my  urlLink desk . Until then I’m sure the fumes will provide many a strange dream (we may have sidewalks and street-parking, but there ain’t many garages in Brooklyn, hence the desk gets stored inside).    Thoughts on i-relating   Though I’ve been focused on stripping this weekend, readers mused on the nature of internet relationships. One friend writes:  I have been feeling like there is this Internet “intimacy” that is created by posting personal information about ourselves. This is of course created while simultaneously learning personal things about others, both friend and foe.  This intimacy is often very intense and may seem real, but I have found that more often than not you are    meeting the “representative” of the person you are interacting with . This is kind of like when you go on a first date with someone--both you and they are on best behavior. Both of you may be presenting the person you’d like to be, but when it comes down to it, we all have past experiences, expectations, egos and pain that often cloud who we really are (or would like to be.) This combination of things is who we wind up being in this moment.  Interestingly enough, one of the only ways to get past the representative, and, ultimately, past the pain, ego and expectation, is to spend time with your friend, spouse, lover, or family member and work through it together.  The Internet and its IM, e-mail, ICQ, AOL, dating, porn, etc, are  creating perpetual first dates  for most everyone involved. Ironically, I used to see the Internet as a way of staying connected with people and getting to know them better (aside from its powerful tools of research and consumerism). I found, after a time, that I did not really know these people that I considered “friends” any better, and I had, in fact grown quite disillusioned as to who they really were. (These illusions were conveniently shattered upon spending some actual time with these people.)  The result?  I have removed myself from as many forms of Internet intimacy as possible. I have disassociated myself from those “friends” who turned out not to be friends at all. Most importantly, I have focused on making the relationships that I have more meaningful and genuine.  This still includes the occasional email...    ;) Thoughts? Disagreements? Use the comment feature to talk back. More stories from Anna Broadway’s sordid love life coming soon, plus thoughts on the meaning of “ urlLink Dancing Queen .” Don’t forget to  urlLink recommend  your favorite song for inclusion!      Girl Shows: Into the Canvas World of Bump and Grind        Furniture Repair & Refinishing     Gold: Greatest Hits 

      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Great thing, having sex on the brain. By turns you can seem alternately funny and entertaining (if friends are feeling generous).      For the stand-up comedy portion of the evening ...   A couple audience-pleasing rejoinders from my dinner tonight:       My friend discusses her Saturday evening from last weekend. The main theme is her disappointment that she didn’t get to attend this bizarre “Orgasmatron” party in the city somewhere (a prelude to the Burning Man festival, she says). “You couldn’t get anyone to come with you?” I ask (the innocent poker face lasts perhaps a half second before I crack up like a kid who just made the obvious poop joke).          Later in the same conversation, this friend describes the ads she’s posted on  urlLink Craigslist , in search of that rare thing: a Jewish guy who likes to travel. (I once sought an intellectual grease monkey, so she has my sympathies.) Not long ago she met or heard from a guy who was Jewish and somewhat pleasing, but got panic attacks about leaving the country. “So you’re saying he’s home-ophobic?”        ... This doesn’t work well in print, does it?     And now the reality entertainment:  urlLink Looney Tune  responds   After writing yesterday’s blog entry, I resisted the urge to “reply-all” Looney Tune’s recipients ... for all of five minutes. But then  urlLink Bleeding Eyes  returned my email:   You know, I just don't get it, I really don't. I mean, why? I'm as horny and as interested in sex and all its little avenues as the next guy, I have a decent porn collection, etc etc, but maybe these people are just plain screwy. On the other hand, maybe screwy ladies actually answer that kinda thing, and that causs him to keep on doing it. Maybe he was trying in some weird wacked out way to be humourous.. Kinda like lampoon or  urlLink animal house  style sex humour. I dunno, I'm not explaining the unexplainable... Maybe we should be blunt and just straight up and ask him :P His mass spam mailing multiple people just seems a bit ... Desperate..or something..      I think a reply all is a great idea, probably find interesting responses, but I know that Craigslist mail addresses get a right hammering so who knows, many of the ladies have probabbly been deluged with silly stuff like that idiot from Philly, and will be bored senseless by this stage. I like Craigslist, but its lost a little something since it got more widely known, ... The noise level over content is on the rise. I do take particular curious interestin the casual metting area, but I've not got involved. Reading what people are looking for is the point of interest rather than actually doing it. So I emailed the ladies. The spunkiest one swiftly took matters into her own hands:   I got the same thing!!!! Geez. Have you told him??!!! Maybe he will learn, us "nice girls" aren't "stupid"!!! Ha Then she emails Looney Tune, kindly CCing all us ladies on the message.     From:       Spunky One  Subject:     A lesson for LOONEY TUNE.....  Date:     July 22, 2004 11:24:21 AM EDT  To:       Looney Tune, anon1@craigslist, anon2@craigslist, Anna Broadway, anon4@craigslist, anon5@craigslist, and 2 more...      Looney Tune, you have a rare way of making a girl feel special and unique! Just a little word of advice...learn to bcc(BLIND carbon copy) if your going to do a mass mailing...makes us all feel a little more inclined to spend some of that time with you....S Things approach the state of a car crash when two hours later, Spunky CCs the Spam Squad on her reply to Looney Tune, copying his email so we can read his defense. LT explains:   It wasn't so much of a mass mailing as it was an attempt to decrease the time that it takes to send my picture. Since I am on hotmail, it takes about 5 minutes per email to upload the picture. Perhaps if I was more technology equipped, then I would not have to prepare the email in such a way. However, my computer stinks. Should I be blamed because of that? In terms of making a girl feel special, that is something for the long term as opposed to an initial email among hundreds in her email box.      Looney Tune I sense an item that Gen X/Y-savvy politicos should add to their social-service platform: make faster computers available to all! The American people need this to more-efficiently date, mate, and procreate. Shoddy equipment restricts population growth!    Oy.    Spunky tells him:   But dude...you could have BCC.....and how you going to get a chance to get to long term if you don't stand out in those hundreds of e-mails we all receive? Actually, now that I think on it, you did stand out, as one who goofed...your even being blogged about...your famous!! And remember worthwhile things take time.....  Seriously though...all the best....  S   And now, I hope, we reach the end. In  urlLink  Kiss & Tell  ,  urlLink Alain de Botton  writes:   The process of intimacy therefore involve[s] the opposite of seduction, for it mean[s] revealing what risk[s] rendering one most open to unfavourable judgment, or least worthy of love. Whereas seduction [i]s founded on the display of one’s finest qualities and dinner jackets, intimacy entail[s] a complex offer of both vulnerability and toenails.   The trouble with internet dating is, sometimes they open with toenails.     And we respond with, well, advice on how to better pull the wool over our eyes. Then again tonight’s post-dinner discussion touched on women who conceal their real (and oft unpleasant) identities from the men in their lives.    Honesty? Who needs that? And intimacy? Bosh. What we want is seduction. More deception! And can you bring a little more wine, please?     Counselors are available in the lobby, next to concessions ...        The hidden track   Bleeding Eyes weighs in:   Spunky one seems more concerned about the fact this guys did'nt use BCC, instead of the contents of the email. Now that smacks like she likes this kinda thing .....      That's disturbing :P    National Lampoon's Animal House       Kiss and Tell  

      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Recently I’ve been thinking about adding a new feature to the site: Each day I’d discuss a song (but not necessarily a love song) in terms of what it’s saying about love and relationships. Thoughts from the audience? Songs I should start with? “ urlLink Closer ” is already on my list if this project moves forward. Treatments would probably look like this:     urlLink     ‘As’ from   Songs in the Key of Life   Lately I’ve been listening to  urlLink Stevie Wonder  a lot. With its gospel overtones, “As” almost falls into that ambiguous zone of the praise song/love song. But then, the idealization of soulmate relationships has muddied the romance/religion lines as much as the music of  urlLink Michael W. Smith  and  urlLink Amy Grant  has.          Please let me know what you think. Thanks!        Coming soon  ... Looney Tune responds to emails from the Spam Posse!     urlLink       Downward Spiral    Songs in the Key of Life 

      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Last night when I got home, I arrived to possibly the most appalling email,  ever . I say this not because I, personally, am appalled, but because I am appalled on behalf of the hapless sap who sent it — who clearly does not even  grasp  the egregious nature of his mistake. Hell, I’m appalled on behalf of his mother!    At first glance, it looks pretty harmless:   Hi:  I am a 27 year old male who lives in Philadelphia. I work in the construction business as a planner. I am still fairly new to the city after moving here from California after college about 5 years ago. You sound like a nice girl. You can find my picture attached. As for me, I enjoy a little of everything but it would probably be nice to spend some of that time with you. Who knows.....maybe!!    Looney Tune  Maybe NOT   Attached is a grainy j-peg of our antihero, holding what appears to be the head of a cartoonish blow-up doll in his lap. I am utterly at a loss to otherwise identify the object, unless it is some sort of basketball painted to resemble a Looney Tunes figure. It is clearly an inflated object. With semi-human features.    Now the photo’s not great, by any means (reminds me of the terrible pictures posted by one of my first-ever chat — I mean “whisper” — buddies on  urlLink Udate ; that guy lived in the midwest somewhere, and thought I’d appreciate him regalling me with accounts of the local, possibly underage, Udate conquest he fucked in his kitchen) ... but it alone is not enough to provoke such horror. Mainly my initial reaction is,  Unfortunate photo. And why he’d email me? Another one who didn’t read the ad well. (Sigh)    But then I glance up. I glance up to the subject-line area. And I see to my shock not “danzfool@netzero.com” (which he would have gotten from reading this blog), but the “anon1234987@craigslist” email of the personal ad.     Here’s the kicker: I can’t actually tell  which one  is my email address because  it’s not just sent to me ! There’s a total of six, yes,  six  anon@craigslist email addresses in the “To:” line — plus two more cut off by my email program!!    Literally, I am in shock.    I mean, yes, he’s a construction worker. But for God’s sake. He’s a  planner  in construction. Is it really possible to be this clueless?!!     A recap of the strategy errors      Bad picture — OK, understandable. Easy mistake.      Writing to a personal ad that’s really not a date-solicitation at all — slightly less-excusable, but still he’s in good company (maybe four other such emails have so far been directed to me).      Writing-in-hopes-of-a-date  to a woman who lives in New York  — stretching the limits of judgment, but hey, Philly’s only two hours away, right? Wouldn’t you be willing to drive that distance just to meet a “nice girl”? (Surely he drives; he’s from California.) Regarding this geographic gaucheness, he’s actually not the worst. Two days ago I got emails from men in San Francisco and  London  (yes, I promo’d myself on Craigslists there). Then again ... re-reading the Londoner’s email reveals he also sent his email to multiple women. He at least was clever enough to BCC us (British men are so much smarter), resulting in “Undisclosed-recipients” as his message-object. That does explain a few things ...   Hi,       I'm [Name] and I work in a bank.        I'm an honest and genuine caring kind of guy.        I enjoy ethnic foods - especially chinese and indian - going to a movie - and travelling.        Have been to Canada 3 times - including coast to coast by train - and have also been to Ukraine.        If you want to know more - or meet - then email me or call 01234 678903.  But back to Looney Tune:               Sending the same email to multiple women — unproductive in the resulting vagueness, but something you could easily conceal ...  with a little common sense!!!  Take this sample:    Hi. I saw your profile and I would like to get to know  you better. I’m looking for some fun. I’m a 22 year  old white male. I’m 6’2” 200lbs. I live in NE Philly.  Let me know either way.  This guy probably multi-sent the email too (note the same geographic mistake). But at least he took the time to use one email address! Joey from SanFran even used my  real  email, suggesting he cursorily read the blog (although he didn’t mention it).    If you’re going to spam the wimmin, do it right   Our antihero, Looney Tune, however, has clearly never heard of BCCing. Too bad. He could’ve still only sent one email but either followed the British banker’s approach or put the first “anon@craigslist” email in the “To:” line, then stuck all the others in BCC. Who really keeps track of what random-generated email address you get? Unless you’re measuring the success of multiple ads ... but even in that case, would you really remember which set of numbers is yours?!   And yet, on balance, the logic is so clear.  Most efficient thing to do , right? You’re interested in eight women, you’re hoping for a little weekend action ... but you don’t want to write eight emails. So you craft a generic email — the e-dating equivalent of a stock pickup line. Hell, maybe you even recycle the same damn email every week you skim the ads! If you’re dating as many women as some guys are, it’s a pretty efficient strategy (some men I know of  urlLink use spreadsheets to keep all the women straight ).    But efficiency only goes so far. (Bangs head against laptop.) In this case it’s very likely to backfire.     I  wish  that someone, somewhere, could’ve taught these guys to just be themselves. Then again, that might be just what Looney Tune did. However, if he takes this kind of scripted, short-cut approach to merely  meeting  women, he probably takes the same route when talking to them. There were times when I was still sort of dating Sgt. Ex-sessories that I felt like he was saying whatever; I had no confidence he was being genuine. Rather, he seemed so terrified that Sgt. John wouldn’t get his fix that night, he’d say anything to the further the cause.  Smile and nod.  “Sure, honey, that sounds great!”  Smile and nod ... remember to maintain eye contact! And now, maybe casually touch her thigh ... Smile and nod ...  Sometimes I wanted to say to him, “Relax and be yourself! I’ll like you much better that way. I promise.”     Light at the end of the ... flashlight   On the upside, there are probably women out there just like him. Maybe one of these days, Looney Tune will happen to email Lady Loopy — along with five other women. And maybe  she’ll  have the heart to say:   Wow, that’s so sweet. You sound like a nice guy, Jim/Todd/Frank/Sam. Let’s get together real soon.       I Can't Believe I'm Buying This Book: A Commonsense Guide to Successful Internet Dating        Online Dating For Dummies (For Dummies Series)        Once Upon a Blind Date   

      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

       Subject: My eyes are bleeeeeeding.. Dear Anna,   So there I was, sitting on  urlLink Craigslist  (get place, occasionally) and I found the link. So .. I came over and tried to read. My eyes were savaged by the layout and the colours.. I fight my way past and try and read..  What is it about Girls,  urlLink they are sooo over complex with deep analysis  on subjects that don't deserve it…   Anyway … Where was I … on yes, erm,  urlLink Chocolate Virgina errand  was where I ended up. Now, don't get me wrong, your English is like 2000% better than mine, but the page layout killed me as I tried to read it! Nice story, if erm.. told from the Womans perspective. Why did I choose that one? Probably some latent stupid male thought process..  So I was thinking … what per chance the  urlLink short hairy one  did actually like you and was not merely trying to get in your knickers. Then I was pondering if you are judgmental, and I am on that short story kinda thinking you are.. Maybe that short guy liked you. You could still be dating ! How can you call the blog sexless IF it need not be. I'm confuddled, but also, male so there is no shock there..  You take great interest in the persons background, so money is important, as are looks. Hmmm. I like the last line ..  AB: hahaha ... but it's not like she gets opportunities with the men I've denied. It's more like their friends .... AB: Weird.  Men you've denied … hmm, so the blog could be called, denial in NY, or sexless cos you prefer it that way ? :P   I mean… you live in NY, HOW can you lack sex if you want it …. You have to explain, I'll be watching :P   Bleeding-eyes Brit  Dear Bleeding Eyes:   First of all, I must commend you for your fortitude. Such visual … er, stamina in wading through all my words! Sorry the  urlLink pink ’s a bit too much. Maybe if I find another  urlLink sugar daddy  I can splurge on a spiffier site.  In the meantime, might I suggest glasses? It’s the whole “geek chic” thing, you know. In fact, I consider it a bold statement of confidence. On many people, the deliberate choice of nerdy, dare-I-say,  ugly  eyewear implies  the owner has good looks to spare, so he or she can afford “downgrade” the sex appeal a little . But then … I’m a self-confessed closet looksist (and quite attached to the specs m’self), so I spend  wayyyy  too much timing thinking about this stuff (among other topics).  But back to your query. Ad Weasel’s not such a bad bloke entirely — you’re right. His offense at my assumption he was offering money for sex seemed quite real. Then again, there is that one time when he offered lotsa cash to peek up my skirt. Really. A whole wad. I guess he had to blow it elsewhere ...  Some women would take the money. Others would say “fuck off” and never speak to him again. I just said “fuck off.”    No man deserves to be reduced to the sum of his actions (or his features).  So … when some guy (or gal) acts stupid, I shake my head, maybe shelter my heart a wee bit, and remember that I can be quite the  urlLink fuckwit  as well sometimes. But we’d all like to think we’re still decent chaps or chicks, right? Just miserably broken ones at times.  Anyhow, re: your confuddlement … I guess you’ll just have to keep reading. ;) But thanks for the alternate-name tips!  xoxo, Anna  PS: If you think I overanalyze, you should read  urlLink Alain de Botton  sometime! He's even one of your countryman — emphasis on the “man,” there. ;)       On Love        Kiss and Tell        The Romantic Movement: Sex, Shopping, and the Novel 

      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Some of you have asked why I’m so damn analytical. To which I say, “You think that’s bad?” Check out this letter I wrote to my brother while he was at National Guard training …  (Yes, I’m the only Broadway child who’s  not  signed up for a service. I prefer to date military men.)       What, me, obsessive?   Yesterday, I decided to run up  urlLink A mountain , thinking I was in good-enough shape to handle it. That was  slightly  true, but by the time I got to the lookout point midway up I was panting like none other. Tried jogging up the remaining steps, but I was breathing so hard, I had to walk. Then I just sat at the top a little, catching my breath and waiting for my legs to stop shaking enough to go down again. On the way back (since I was running back to the park), I ran by the Irish Pub, that is to say, the “Authentic  urlLink Guinness  Concept Pub.” The O-Zone King and Bartender #2 and this other guy were standing out on the patio, and somebody (I think it was O-Zone King, although maybe that’s wishful thinking) was like, “Hey Anna!” So I ran in and asked to use their bathroom. “What are you doing?” the guys ask. “Running,” I say — but don’t stop to talk or anything on my way out; I didn’t want to lose my momentum or have the muscles tighten up.         More evidence that romance novels really fuck you up   But the whole O-Zone King thing … Maybe I’m just a  complete , obsessive idiot- urlLink freak , but I think he’s been a little friendlier to me in the last week — maybe his interest has even been piqued a little again (although I’m told that  a guy doesn’t necessarily stop finding you sexually attractive just because things don’t work out ). A week or so ago, there was this weird exchange where he was pretty flirty, I thought. Then the following Saturday he was serving, and I chatted with him a bit in the course of getting change — but he was nice, you know? Even told me a story — which was totally putting more into the conversation than it required (the last time I’d seen him before I left for Albuquerque, he was in a bad mood and totally aloof when I said hi to him). Then Wednesday of this week, I went to the bar to study, but ended up talking to this guy Ballplayer #1 I’d met at IP before. We were sitting right by the end of the bar where O-Zone King was bartending, and when I asked him for a glass of water,  he actually asked me how I was doing!  With all the other people who work there, that would probably just be common social courtesy, but O-Zone King is kind of weird; it hasn’t been possible to fall into the kind of easy friendship with him that I have with Guy Friend #3, for example (although Guy Friend #3 is probably pretty unique in that sense).      So … yeah.  Part of me just   totally   wants that male attention and interest, for some reason  — especially from him. I mean, I totally know that nothing could happen,  should  he actually initiate something like hanging out again … (God, I’m such a freak — eh? Man….)         When it stops  urlLink raining men    But I’m starting to think this man-drought has a point. I’ve been thinking more about what I seek in my relationships — how much  I have tried to make myself into this person who is charming and quirky and a good friend and all — so that people will love me and want to be my friend.  Not that I haven’t cared genuinely about them, and been concerned about what goes on in their lives — but that needy self-interest has been back there, you know?      Interestingly enough, another realization came in my conversation with this guy Ballplayer #1, Wednesday night. I’d only met him once before, one Saturday night when he and his friend Ballplayer #2 met me and Girlfriend #2 at Irish Pub. We’d all gone to the diner afterward, and had a perfectly nice conversation with Ballplayer #1 (Ballplayer #2 sat mostly silent though he’d been the one arrange the post-bar hook-up. When we got ready to leave, Ballplayer #2 asked for our phone number, in the most pathetic, hilarious way possible. We gave him Girlfriend #2’s number, and he apparently called her at like 2 a.m. one night, but things never really came of it. Girlfriend #2’s dating Guy Friend #2, and besides, Ballplayer #1 was really the charismatic one of the two. (They’re both in town trying out for some baseball thing.)      All this happened toward the beginning of the semester. That seemed to be the last of it until Wednesday night. Suddenly there they were in the bar, and they recognized me. Ballplayer #1 and I get into this conversation about me being in religious studies that leads inevitably to my own religious life and my relationship with God. For whatever reason, I ended up talking a lot about this whole love thing — how the way I see God making a difference in my life is by the changes He makes in my heart. I was trying to explain  how  that happened in terms of my relationship with Former Roommate and striving to be more than just polite to her.  The diff between politeness and kindness is a huge thing , you know? I was trying to explain that this really wasn’t the kind of thing a person could just  force  into their heart — why I really thought God had something to do with it. And I was talking about the whole seeking-something-back-from-other-people thing, too.       Then he said something about conditions — that I was talking about trying to love  without  conditions — even though that’s usually how all of us operate in our relationships all the time, and generally we don’t even think about it. Even though he’s this guy without much of a religious background at all, he stuck his finger right on this concept that had been there all the time — only I’d forgotten it.         ‘Open to persuasion’   Of course, the funny thing about all of it was that I think Ballplayer #1 was kind of interested in me. I was kind of getting that vibe, you know, because we were facing each other on these stools by the bar, and toward the end our knees were starting to brush a little in that way. He totally wanted to get my number — because he was expressing regret about the conversation having to end — but I just couldn’t bring myself to bail him out, even though I knew what he wanted.      He’s a nice guy. I’m realizing that there’s this thing that happens a lot with guys I meet, where  I’m not out-and-out interested in them (sexually/romantically) from the beginning, but neither am I vehemently  not  interested in them in that way.  I wouldn’t start the encounter by being flirty and so on, but if the guy should express interest, I’m not opposed to letting things go that way, and see if he might persuade my interest to  become  more sexually/romantically oriented rather than just “Oh, he’s a cool person.” That’s how it was with Sgt. Ex-sessories and Slobberguy, the two I went out with last semester. The O-Zone King, however, was one of those cases where I  did  like him right off the bat, and obviously we can see where that’s gotten me! (sigh)      Anyway — Ballplayer #1’s cool; and he’s one of those guys where I’m like “open-to-persuasion,” right? Only I just couldn’t bring myself to encourage anything somehow, even though I might come to like him more in the end, than I did either Sgt. Ex-sessories or Slobberguy (I apologize if this is starting to get a little confusing! J). I guess I’ve just felt like I shouldn’t rush into anything with a guy right now, even if it’s a casual date or two …   

      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Since a giant electric wasp hovered directly over my building for more than an hour this morning, I thought I&rsquo;d use this untimely wakefulness to answers emails from you, my readers. Starting with the insults.    1.  what would a 52-year old buddhist artist find that  could possibly be attractive about such solypsism  posing as integrity and art?  yecch  Dear Yecch:   What would a 52-year-old Buddhist artist expect from a post titled &ldquo; urlLink What women want  — a man who&rsquo;s small, quick and hairy&rdquo;?? You shoulda steered clear at the pop-cult reference.  urlLink Mel Gibson , for God&rsquo;s sake! Not much art happening there (although his  urlLink dance scene  is rather nice). Now had I made a reference to  urlLink  Amelie   ... OK. You might&rsquo;ve had me there.   But don&rsquo;t lose heart. I&rsquo;m sure there are other, more-serious women half your age out there.    PS: It might help your dating strategy if you don&rsquo;t send emails twice. Especially when 20 minutes have elapsed in between. It just looks weird, ya know?    2.   someone (most likely you??) posted a link to your blog on craigslist in san francisco. since i have a job that allows me pretty much to read whatever i want on the net, i clicked on your link to pass some time. just writing to say thanks for the effort and it helped me pass a few minutes of my life. if i choose a name the same way you did i would be Dale Thirty-second Avenue.  Dear Dale:   It was me, yes. Thanks for reading! You have my sympathies re: the job. Totally been there. Check back next time you have more time to kill...   3.   You are quite funny...small, quick and furry...you got me pegged. It sounds like you have been around the internet dating block a few times. I have just discovered this craigs list thing and have been obsessed with it. I responded to a few, not too seriously, but received no response. WTF. At least a thanks would be nice. Is the sarcasm not obvious?   This is to a lady who left no name but said she was professional:   Professional Intelligent Lady-    YES, I think your expectations are way to high...you should date a guy who still lives at home at 30 or are unfaithful jerks or drinks too much and gets mean or loves sports more than you or is really nice but also ugly...LOL...the good guys are gone, ALL of them!  Anyway, I am looking for an &ldquo;attractive&rdquo; girls refined opinion on cologne. I started wearing it everyday and I am running low. So I went to the cologne counter and got sprayed down with like 30 and really couldn&rsquo;t smell the difference after 3. I liked Marc Jacobs for men and a couple others...so I wanted a cute girls opinion, since ultimately, that is why guys wear cologne.  As for me, I am just working to finish my thesis, 5&rsquo;10&rdquo; with dark brown hair and a half goatee (this changes a lot). I swam for 11 years so I have the swimmers bod thing going but whatever. I have nice teeth, a good relationship with my mom, floss daily, and have nice shoes. lol. Unfortunately, I am not around your area but O well, I rarely let women take me out unless they really have their s#$% together, and a attractive (a very rare combo). If you are a good looking girl I am sure if you step out for a few hours, you will have several dumb guys offering to buy you dinner just to spend some time with you. Got to get back to my work.   Peace, Sounds of Silence  Dear Sounds of Silence:  Sarcasm can be a highly refined art. And like much art, it is not always appreciated by the masses. Bear in mind, it tends to work better as performative art (i.e., banter during drinks) than written in the first email sales-pitch of yourself.    In general,  the ideal email should be, well, short — at least in the beginning . I like what you&rsquo;re doing with the cologne bit, but it&rsquo;s kinda like the killer umpteenth phone call in  urlLink  Swingers  : TMI. Or at least, too many words. And not carefully chosen words. You&rsquo;re an intelligent man. You use sarcasm ... finished a thesis ... but your writing-style doesn&rsquo;t really tell me that. I hate to say it, but you have to  look at personal-ad response emails like the cover letter in a job ap.   It&rsquo;s all about the sell  .  So re-read your stuff a couple times. Try to use conventional capitalization and so forth and  go easy on the IMspeak  ("lol,"etc.). Some folks are still internet newbies who don&rsquo;t &ldquo;get&rdquo; that mode of speech. (Especially since she calls herself &ldquo;professional&rdquo;; maybe a business-letter tone would have worked?)   Dear Madam:  I would like to request a moment of your attention in response to a recent advertisement on Craiglist, posted by the holder of this email. As you will see from the attached resume, I am an eminently dateable man, and eager to make you feel appreciated as the beauty that you are.      While we&rsquo;re on the topic of you, perhaps I can offer a few words of professional (that is to say, male) advice. With all due respect, I fear your dating strategy may fail to adequately suss out the men worth your time. Clearly your looks should be enough to garner interest, however ... But back to you. In addition to keeping it brief and editing what you write,  be careful how you talk about a) a woman&rsquo;s looks, and b) your approach to dating . Talking about too much stuff upfront tends to weird people out. Internet-dating exchanges are like a tennis match in which the ad is the opening serve. Hopefully the person serves well, giving you something to respond to. So you return serve, giving one or two options for her response. But don&rsquo;t slip in an extra ball on the return volley so she&rsquo;s not sure which one to hit. You probably would&rsquo;ve been better off stopping with the cologne conundrum. That gives her something a little offbeat, a topic for her response.     But all that stuff about dumb guys being willing to take her out ... that really doesn&rsquo;t supply a come-back. In the interest of encouraging responses, I&rsquo;d also avoid phrases like &ldquo;if you are a good looking girl&rdquo; and &ldquo;I&rsquo;m looking for an &lsquo;attractive&rsquo; girls refined opinion.&rdquo;  Effective flattery calls for some degree of subtlety, if not wit.  But so I don&rsquo;t break Anna&rsquo;s rule #1 (keep it short): I&rsquo;ll close with what  I  would send as your ghost-writer:   Dear Professional:  YES, I think your expectations are way to high...you should date a guy who still lives at home at 30 or are unfaithful jerks or drinks too much and gets mean or loves sports more than you or is really nice but also ugly...Just kidding. ;)  Sometimes it feels like all the good ones are gone, eh?  Anyway, I am looking for a &ldquo;refined&rdquo; (read: female) opinion on cologne. You look [or seem, if she didn&rsquo;t have a picture] like the kind of woman I&rsquo;d want to be attractive to, so I was wondering if you&rsquo;d offer some feedback. I started wearing it everyday and I am running low. When I went to the cologne counter I got sprayed down with like 30 but really couldn&rsquo;t smell the difference after 3. I liked Marc Jacobs for men and a couple others...but I wanted a cute girls opinion, since ultimately, that is why guys wear cologne. Any thoughts?    PS: Props on the flossing. Just make sure you don&rsquo;t do it in public, like  urlLink The Captain  sometimes does!    And now I&rsquo;ll throw it out to our readers. Any thoughts on the man&rsquo;s cologne dilemma? Feel free to comment here.    What Women Want    Amelie    Swingers 

      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      In the pre-IM days of last summer one of my favorite ways to check out on the job was writing letters to my sister (then suffering through some kind of Marine boot camp) about my love life. She needed an escape, right?    Last summer, you see, I was restless. Thanks to a new job I was making more cash and indulging myself. I kept buying cute clothes and lamenting that no one was there to admire them. (Perhaps I should instead have bought  Narcissism for Dummies .) So, I browsed  urlLink Craigslist  — even posting a recurring ad in search of intellectual grease monkeys (hey, I missed my car, “the Eunuch,” ‘K?)    By the way, if it seems harsh to dub my friend “The Nerd,” consider I am one myself and own an “I (heart) nerds” t-shirt (thank you, Charlotte Russe!). Don’t forget: as  urlLink that ever-wise sex game  revealed, Anna is all about looks (in fact, a closet looksist). Cute nerds only need apply! Well, cute intellectual grease monkeys. Doesn’t the heroine always get the hot man? I mean … um … the hot pants?    Summary from a summer letter to Sis…      personal ads   So, out of boredom, I was browsing the personal (i.e., men-for-women) ads on Craigslist, a local Internet message board. Dumb idea, I know, but sometimes  urlLink I just don’t know what to do with myself . Most of the ads are  really  lame — guys describing the sexual acts they’re willing to perform, describing themselves in arrogant terms, or generally demonstrating a lack of intelligence. A few creative types often throw in random poems with no reference to themselves, but I’m never sure how to respond to those either; it’s a little weird.  The key to a good personal ad, in my book, is giving people a “hook” they can use for conversational purposes in that initial email  (I’ve enclosed a copy of my recent personal ad as example ;)).    Anyway, maybe 1 out of 100 ads is semi-decent. If a guy actually    demonstrates  some creativity or wit (e.g., “Fat, bald and ugly” for his “headline”), I feel he deserves at least a brief congratulatory email lauding him for the effort. One of the ads recently — maybe 100 or 200 in — was titled, “Looking for a nerd.” The guy also ranted about hipsters in his post, which gave me something to respond to. I send him a brief email, and it turns out he’s this guy I used to email back in high school! Nerd was one of my first e-pen-pals, back in the dark ages of the Internet. Hadn’t had contact with him in at least 6 years. We exchanged a couple emails, and then he left a message for me Saturday night.     phone  voices   I have this theory about phone voices that’s probably very prejudicial, but generally hasn’t failed me yet. Nerdy phone voices generally tend to go with less-well socially adapted people. Good phone voices often go with reasonably attractive people. Middle-aged man phone voices often go with old-beyond-their-years men — and so on. Last fall, I responded to an ad posted by this guy just looking for a very casual, almost-platonic dinner-and-movie thing. Talked on the phone, and he just sounded flaky; stupid conversation and strained humor (he probably writes a blog now!). Against my better judgment, I agreed to see him anyway. Got all the way down there, and he  completely  stood me up — but not, mind you, because he chickened out. He just didn’t allow for likely delays (considering a major event in the area was likely to slow train access) and didn’t wait around long, though I was only 15 minutes late! That’s the short version, but the whole thing was just  totally  absurd.     Likewise, my “friend” the  urlLink Ad Weasel , with whom I went out once. We transitioned to phone conversations pretty early in the friendship.  urlLink Ad Weasel  was cool and had an OK phone voice, but it was a tad on the old end for a 31-year-old (considering  urlLink The Captain  is also 31 and seems remarkably youthful). Sure enough, in person Ad Weasel was prematurely middle-aged in manner, and starting to lose his hair (though that didn’t stop him from getting serious grope-age later in the evening).    Then there’s Non-profit Superhero — the one who apparently got away (sigh). Wrote back to the first version of my personal ad — a completely goofy, offbeat response. “Well this is reasonably clever,” I thought. Again, we fortunately transitioned to phone contact pretty quickly — and he had a good voice. Not super-deep and sexy or anything, but he just seemed like a cool person; I felt a decent vibe. Non-profit Superhero worked for the UN, but never said much about his job (then again, I probably never stopped to let him talk; whoops!). Mostly we made jokes about him being a super-hero, saving the world, and all the challenges this entailed. Sure enough, when I met Non-profit Superhero in person, he was  very  cool and reasonably attractive — in a blond, bespectacled way. I still pout at the apparent demise of that friendship/relationship — though I never even got to the point of saying “No sex” with him. He was completely not pushy, physically, on our two dates — so honestly I wasn’t even sure if he was thinking friends or more. But that’s neither here nor there…    Anyway, my phone-voice theory has tended to hold water — going even as far back as my first internet-suitor, Stalker #1 (the guy who showed up at my  Fiddler on the Roof  performance with a wilted rose). When I heard Nerd’s voice on the phone yesterday, I felt my heart sink a little. Not a completely bad voice, but definitely on the nerdy/socially isolated side of things (though his picture — if somewhat indistinct — hadn’t looked bad). When we met up later, he was more like The One Who Came Out — my ill-fated high-school Homecoming date — than the picture suggested. The party he’d invited me to was really cool, though — this amazing rooftop sangria competition organized by the residents of his building, a sprawling former-warehouse space converted into large loft-like living quarters. Amazingly, it’s the same building where my friend Hippie the Groper lives. In fact, the party was largely hosted by Hippie the Groper’s roommate Flamenco Man (whom I’d previously met while visiting Hippie the Groper), and Nerd has hung out with “Mr. Hippie the Groper” in the past! Totally crazy coincidences, or what?     hipster central   The thing that totally cracked me up about the party was the way everyone was dressed — very distinctive, edgy outfits on the most part — tons of vintage stuff and, well, hipster duds. It was so ironic given Nerd’s post. I mean, these people were further along  urlLink the hipster end of the spectrum  than those  I  normally hang with! They were cool, though. As Nerd commented, it totally seemed like my scene. In fact, I partied longer and harder (in a figurative sense) then Nerd. He tended to stand around a lot, whereas I floated from group to group, making friends and conversation. Nerd even went back downstairs to his apartment for a while — “to rest” — leaving me guilty that I had almost ditched him for the party-crowd in general. But he seemed OK with it… It’s not like I should have to baby-sit the person whose guest I am anyway — right? (Sigh) Such complicated social situations… Am I  urlLink entertaining you  yet? ;)     Ultimate Collection        Sangria: 50 Festive Recipes        The Hipster Handbook   

      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

       Not to be confused with the   urlLink academic discipline   of the same name ...       My roommate, as we recently discovered, likes men who are &ldquo;small, quick and furry.&rdquo; We interpret this to mean hairy, since her boyfriend is — moderately. I can&rsquo;t speak to &ldquo;small&rdquo; or &ldquo;quick.&rdquo; For my part, I seek sexual experiences &ldquo;expansive but contained, turbulent and active.&rdquo;    Our source of this insight? A little game I learned Wednesday night after an evening with a conservatively dressed flamenco dancer (she danced, we watched, and wondered if her clothes were typical). While it may be somewhat cheesy, our post-show game sure as hell beats those fortune-teller fold-ups from middle school, and those cheesy &ldquo;don&rsquo;t scroll down and cheat!&rdquo; quizzes college friends used to forward. If nothing else, it&rsquo;s less controversial than &ldquo;Is it  Mein Kampf  or  urlLink Match.com ?&rdquo; a  urlLink Valentine&rsquo;s Day guessing game  I played and won, earning two passes to the moderator- urlLink comedian &rsquo;s show at  urlLink Caroline&rsquo;s . (This had nothing to do with my internet dating days, I  swear !) Advantages of this game include:       the frequency of &ldquo;wet&rdquo; among players&rsquo; chosen adjectives     the ease of remembering how to interpret the answers when you try this game with friends.    We were four Wednesday night, three women and one man, informally celebrating my birthday and a lovely summer evening in Manhattan. Since not all of us knew each other well, one friend who often leads travel groups introduced us to her sexual-psyche game. It worked well since she didn&rsquo;t call it more than just a &ldquo;game.&rdquo; What&rsquo;s more innocuous than describing your favorite color?    But that, indeed, is the first question. We went round and answered in turn: red, pink, blue. Next came the twist: three adjectives  why  we liked the color. I said, &ldquo;passionate, vibrant and cheerful.&rdquo; The woman to my left, who liked pink, said &ldquo;retro, nostalgic and pretty.&rdquo; I&rsquo;ve forgotten the blue-man&rsquo;s words, except there was some curious pairing of &ldquo;serene&rdquo; and &ldquo;energizing.&rdquo;    Next we moved onto favorite animals. Mine, more by default than anything, was horse (perhaps a holdover from childhood fondness for the Morgan). Pink Lady chose a dog, Blue Man an owl. I was hard-pressed to defend my choice, lapsing into aesthetic terms: &ldquo;elegant, graceful ...  urlLink lithe &rdquo; (this required some definition for the table; I struggled and came up with &ldquo;muscular; the way you move&rdquo;). Pink Lady&rsquo;s reasons included &ldquo;cuddly,&rdquo; and Blue Man had a pairing of &ldquo;wisdom&rdquo; and beauty (possibly &ldquo;elegant?&rdquo; Maybe he mixed up &ldquo;owl&rdquo; with &ldquo;falcon.&rdquo;).    Our final &ldquo;favorite thing&rdquo; was body of water, although there was some discussion whether this referred to bodies of water seen or experienced (one might like to see the ocean but take a bath). Blue Man chose jacuzzi for reasons I can&rsquo;t remember at all. Pink Lady chose a waterfall because it&rsquo;s &ldquo;wet, majestic and long.&rdquo; I had a strangely clear image, to my surprise: the perfect thing was a bay. It gives you a bit of sea, but with the reassuring sight of land. So I said quickly, &ldquo;expansive but contained,&rdquo; and then, &ldquo;turbulent ... active&rdquo; after slight hesitation.    My friend, who was our ringleader, was laughing by this point because she knew all of us though we were strangers to each other. &ldquo;That&rsquo;s so  perfect !&rdquo; she kept saying.     Whether or not that always applies to the answers given is largely a matter of specificity. My roommate, who is an artist, chose pink as well when I played the game with her, upon arriving home. But she said because it&rsquo;s &ldquo;soft, reddish, quiet.&rdquo;  Your color is supposed to equal your self-image.  While passionate, vibrant and cheerful seem reasonably accurate for me, I doubt my roommate primarily thinks of herself as &ldquo;reddish&rdquo;! Then again, she has sometimes opened our fridge and commented not on how much or little food it contains, but the color scheme of the produce, pasta and condiments inside (&ldquo;We have so much orange and yellow!&rdquo; I guess that&rsquo;s better than ochre or magenta...).    Your animal (surprise, surprise) represents your ideal mate or lover. Mine is chiefly valued for his looks, apparently (and the way he moves; maybe I should just judge men on their dance ability!). Since neither Pink Lady nor I had said anything like &ldquo;humor&rdquo; or &ldquo;intelligence,&rdquo; we were quite disappointed by the  animal = mate  interpretation. My roommate&rsquo;s choice of &ldquo;prairie dog&rdquo; was certainly the funniest — hence, &ldquo;small, quick and furry.&rdquo;    Finally,  your favorite body of water, according to this view of things, represents the ideal sexual experience  — or at least what you want in a fuck (Friend, the Ringleader&rsquo;s explanation of this left something to be desired). Roommate chose the fairly dramatic &ldquo;fjord&rdquo; but was puzzled by her choice of &ldquo;cold&rdquo; in addition to &ldquo;deep&rdquo; and &ldquo;mysterious&rdquo; (maybe she meant &ldquo;wet&rdquo; along with Pink Lady). Clearly there is room for word-choice wiggle room.    But hey, it beats talking about the weather at the next stranger small-talk session. Or maybe it&rsquo;s what to ask next time you speed-date.         In case you need a cheat sheet, once again that&rsquo;s:     Favorite color: ________   Adjectives :   1. ______      2. ______ 3. ______         Favorite animal: _________  Adjectives :   1. ______      2. ______ 3. ______      Favorite body of water (e.g., ocean, lake, swimming pool, swamp, etc.): _______  Adjectives :   1. ______      2. ______ 3. ______ 

      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      This afternoon I chatted with an old friend who&rsquo;s been working with the Peace Corps in Cameroon.  &ldquo;There&rsquo;s a lot of 50s  urlLink Harlequins  floating around over there,&rdquo; she told me. &rdquo;I&lsquo;d never read one before, but I picked a couple up. And when I read it, I thought, &lsquo;Now I understand Anna.&rsquo;&rdquo;  For those who haven&rsquo;t read a Harlequin either, here&rsquo;s the gist of the prose:  Portence hung in the air like a thick fog. She felt a shiver as she eyed him from across the bar. He worked the room as if he was running for office, calling everyone by name and seeming geniunely interested in their idle babble. When he touched her shoulder, she sat erect as did her nipples, hot yet cool. &ldquo;I don&rsquo;t believe we&rsquo;ve met,&rdquo; he said with an all-American smile that revealed compelling dimples. &ldquo;oh, my God,&rdquo; filled her head so loud that she feared she may have actually uttered the phrase. Of course, that&rsquo;s not actually taken from a real novel.  Shortly after moving to the city, nearly two years ago, I set off to find my dream job in publishing. Remarkably Harlequin proved to be hiring an editorial assistant. And I even landed an interview.   In the middle of crafting a follow-up letter, however, I decided that maybe $26k per annum wasn&rsquo;t quite enough money for reading crap femme-porn by day and nightly fending off horrified emails from the half of my family that never reads this blog.  But I sent a colorful email out describing the interview anyway, and one my of favorite former bosses responded with the Portence para you just read.   Summer in the sticks  Ah, what a summer that was. Iowa 1997. Got my driver&rsquo;s license (yes, I bloomed late in nearly everything), learned you don&rsquo;t slow from 70 to 0 on a gravel &ldquo;shoulder&rdquo; ... and worked for this incredible woman who had her own PR agency. James loved to call me &ldquo;the Teenager,&rdquo; and prophesied that someday I would get my comeuppance.  Come to think of it, have I? Does Best Friend &ldquo;breaking up&rdquo; with me count? Getting bawled out by my former Nicorette-addict boss? Hmmmm....   That was also the summer of my Indian  urlLink Sugar Daddy .  Sugar Daddy entered the picture much earlier, when he worked with my father at Honeywell in Arizona. My parents have always befriended &ldquo;internationals,&rdquo; so Sugar Daddy was just one of several workmates we shared dinner with over the years. Because Sugar Daddy was single, got along well with us, and had no family in Phoenix, we invited him over for Thanksgiving on at least one occasion. Possibly that&rsquo;s when he also took us kids to see  Beauty and the Best  or  Lion King  — whichever Disney flick was big at that time.  Sometime later, Sugar Daddy got a job in Iowa. But he still remained fond of our family and would occasionally call. I think he&rsquo;d always had a particular liking for my sister — whether pervy or not, I&rsquo;m not sure. In any case, she didn&rsquo;t think much of him, and refused to talk when he&rsquo;d call.  As I&rsquo;d been reading lots of adult fiction (sex in my Harlequin-saturated mind was a grown-up activity, not a kid or teen thing), I was a precocious conversationalist. Chatting up Sugar Daddy was no trouble — and a bit of a kick. One time I think we talked for nearly an hour. Mom was probably busy fixing dinner for our family of six, and glad to have me off the piano (which I played incessantly in the pre-high school days since I was still home-schooled then). So she didn&rsquo;t notice. Dad wouldn&rsquo;t have been home anyway.  Graduation came in late-spring 1996. Two weeks later I waved goodbye to my kin at the airport and found myself crying the requisite tears quite naturally as all immediate family put the Pacific Ocean between them and me. The rest of the summer I worked for a company that manufactured wedding invitations and prepared to enter an  urlLink Iowa college  in the fall.   Proto-googling   That  was the summer of  urlLink Matthew McConaughey , whom I saw three times in  A Time to Kill . I think I sighed every time he came onscreen. The obsession was so great I tried to track him down on the Internet. If not at this point, later I learned that his father died mid-coitus with his mother. This always seemed a great tragedy for her sex life. I mean, how do you  recover  from that?!! He obviously didn&rsquo;t.   The address I found for McConaughey was in Malibu, California, so I had keen hopes it might be right. Surely he was too new a star to think of keeping his address private. Optimism at full strength, I crafted a letter suggesting that we had great potential for a relationship ... or at least a penpal-ship. After all, I wasn't your typical love-struck fan. How many women in his life were prepared, as I was, to  urlLink bake him homemade cookies ?   True this ruse had never shown much success with high-school crushes, but Matthew was a different sort. I could tell. I mean, he was the first celebrity I actually got the hots for! That was saying a lot. Not for me the cliched infatuation with Axl Rose or Keanu Reeves. I had a more discriminating heart (though clearly a gaydar-less one; in summer &rsquo;97 I fell for  urlLink Rupert Everett ).  But back to Sugar Daddy. You see, if not for his generosity, my letter to Matthew would never have happened. But sometime early in the summer of wedding invitations, Sugar Daddy rang up the house where I was staying to have another of our chats. I must have disclosed that I missed the dial-up access of my parents&rsquo; home (we might not have gotten TV till &rsquo;93, but we were  progressive , damnit: Internet in &rsquo;95!). Sugar Daddy wouldn&rsquo;t stand for this privation and swiftly promised me the money to get dial-up all summer long. Not long after a check for $100 arrived.  Three months of Web-leisure later, I moved to Iowa with a pared-down library and my trusty Mac LC II. (At some point I&rsquo;d decided owning 80-odd  urlLink Betty Neels  romance novels was excessive; especially since her plots relied on two or three worn but satisfying tropes: the mousy English nurse, the heavy-lidded doctor [usually Dutch] and the stunning English nurse of &ldquo;Junoesque&rdquo; proportions [usually the alternate heroine].)   Soundtrack for my shower  Since I, the music-obsessive, could never be bothered to save for such an appliance as a stereo, the computer was my stand-in for a jukebox (mind you, these were pre-MP3 days; possibly I used an external CD-rom!).  Sugar Daddy and I were once more living in the same time zone, but initially little came of this. For spring break, however, I went up to Des Moines to visit family friends from Arizona. Informed of my visit, Sugar Daddy decided Des Moines was within driving distance (he lived in Cedar Rapids). Our two dates sort of blur together, but I know the evening concluded with a leisurely dinner at Olive Garden, including appetizer, entree, dessert, and maybe coffee (in my book this was lavish spending; the Broadway clan barely ate out at all, and then with great restraint).  The day also included shopping, because somehow I&rsquo;d managed to mention my lack of a stereo — this couched in the innocent lament that I couldn&rsquo;t quite drag my Mac down the hall to the common bathroom and plug it in outside a shower stall. Sugar Daddy wouldn&rsquo;t have this either! Off we went to find a portable stereo. At the end of the week, I returned to faux-Dutch Small Town, IA with a $130 Sony boom box subsequently praised for the quality of sound.   Sugar Daddy payout: $230 + movie + at least one dinner    What, me passive?  And then came summer. Before starting my internship with James, I went off to Yucatan with the jazz, wind and a cappella ensembles from my college. Somewhere along the line I&rsquo;d acquired a basic camera, but found its 35mm lens less than adequate for documenting my fortitude in climbing up and down the ruins outside Merida.  This pique persisted over the early weeks of the summer.   When July rolled around, along with my birthday, it was time for another visit from Sugar Daddy. By this time, I confess, I&rsquo;d begun to wise up to his &ldquo;generous&rdquo; attentions. When he kissed me on the cheek upon our greeting, my heart sank. But despite a fall-semester first  real  kiss, boys were still not lining up to date the romance-reader nicknamed &ldquo;Betty Crocker&rdquo; (yes, I really baked bread from scratch while in the dorms; the wall-length desk in my room proved an ideal &ldquo;counter&rdquo; for kneading dough and rolling out pie crusts). So I mustered my gumption, smiled up at our &ldquo;family friend&rdquo; and prepared to enjoy my birthday visit.  Sugar Daddy first took me to the Des Moines botanical center, a Biosphere-like structure whose vibrant foliage reminded me of my camera&rsquo;s meager talents. Next we lunched at Schlotzsky&rsquo;s, a modest treat I associated with the Broadway family&rsquo;s occasional meals out, back home in Arizona. This was just refueling for the afternoon&rsquo;s shopping, which resulted in the purchase of a $270 Samsung zoom-lens camera with lots of features.  The evening concluded with yet another trek to Olive Garden where we had cocktails round 1 (a bloody Mary I didn&rsquo;t much like despite its connoted sophistication), appetizers, cocktails round 2 (a smooth drink that induced my first real buzz), entrees, probably coffee, and the Olive Garden birthday-girl dessert.   Sugar Daddy payout: $500 + movie + lunch + 2 dinners   When my parents heard of his generosity on a birthday phone call &ldquo;home&rdquo; to Singapore, Dad&rsquo;s suspicions were finally aroused. &ldquo;Do you want me to talk to him?&rdquo; he asked. &ldquo;Oh, no,&rdquo; I said. Though battling moderate guilt at the strange affair, I was far too attached to the camera and stereo to plea affront. Besides, by this time I&rsquo;d realized I was miserable at my college. Transfer plans were already in motion, and it was only a matter of weeks before I left the state, conveniently eliminating that problem.  Sugar Daddy still receives my general-update emails, but hasn&rsquo;t contacted me in years. The camera was my faithful companion until grad-school days by which time, through contact with the Married Man, I&rsquo;d succumbed to full-on photo mania demanding real equipment (a Minolta X700 and Yashica T4). A Mexican family bought the stereo for $25 at a summer &lsquo;02 garage sale shortly before my move to New York.   Postscript  Now that I think about it, Sugar Daddy&rsquo;s payout was even more than I gave him credit for. At some point during my freshman year, I needed a loan of about $200. Guess who bailed me out? When I eventually tried to repay him, much, much later, he refused to take the money.   Sugar Daddy payout: $700 + movie + lunch + 2 dinners     Time to Kill      My Best Friend's Wedding   

      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Since yesterday was my actual birthday (and most I know have jobs), celebration took place Saturday night. While drinking cocktails on my friend&rsquo;s Hudson-River view rooftop, I was explaining how one of the guests and I knew each other (we met during quiz night at a bar better known for its Saturday night burlesque shows which ... surprise, surprise ... I first discovered at  urlLink The Captain &rsquo;s invitation).    Wow, you really are a stripper!  Burlesque Bar is also where I met Jose No Dinero, aka, The Latin American (that story to come later). A night of unbelievable drama that involved Chinese take-out, sparkly lip gloss and a near-fight between Best Friend and Roommate&rsquo;s visiting guest George over George's blatant flirtation with The Captain, it was the first Saturday of the new year and just days after the Day of Pain (in which Sis got her tat and I my belly ring).  Night of Unbelievable Drama also introduced me to the work of a very funny local comedian. Many, many pasties later, I found myself at Burlesque Bar one night with Best Friend, Hippie the Groper and many other curious folk in tow (friends of The Captain were also in the crowd that night). It was the first sighting of Jose since his untimely departure for the homeland January 13. It was also my debut on the Burlesque Bar stage.  When I told the birthday crowd about my adventure at Burlesque Bar, friend-from-quiz-night thought I said it involve body grease. She was much amused at this news of my secret alt-life until I clarified: &ldquo;a bawdy  urlLink  Grease   send-up.&rdquo; (I did once, technically, strip in a class presentation as an undergrad, but that&rsquo;s another story.)   The Sandy-Danny redux  Mild disappointment ensued, but the real story is almost as good. Midway through the second set on that night sometime in March, Jose&rsquo;s friend the comedian remarked that he didn&rsquo;t feel his earlier-in-the-evening  Grease  skit had been quite good enough. He wished to do another. And he needed a volunteer.  It is perhaps inevitable that we were sitting near the stage that night, Best Friend swiftly volunteered me, and the comedian took her up on it. The night just had that weird momentum as had my first night at Burlesque Bar. But in contrast to an earlier impromptu moment in which two birthday people kissed each other on the cheek and administered spankings, the comedian actually took me backstage during a hula-hoop routine.  There I am in a dressing room the size of your average coat closet, squeezed between the comedian and a handful of mostly-naked performers. He starts putting on a leather jacket and hands me a half-sheet of lined note paper with the handwritten script we shortly perform onstage, using a shared microphone, in front of Best Friend, Hippie the Groper and entourage, The Latin American, friends of The Captain .. and all the others assembled.   S : Danny!  D : Sandy! — I mean you ... how's it hangin&rsquo;, tit-wise? [Comedian improvised slightly]  S : Danny, I can't believe you&rsquo;re acting like this...  D : Why don&rsquo;t you put an ad in a missing persons [more improvisation; Danny pretends to not know her]  S : You didn&rsquo;t act like this when I rammed your ass with that black cock!  D : Sandy, I don&rsquo;t know what you&rsquo;re talking about  S : And when that Latin boy left, you were crying like a baby! [Best Friend gives a shout of laughter]  D : ... but whatever it is, it&rsquo;s working! [more improvisation and segue to...]  both : &ldquo;Summer dreams ripped at the seams ... bu-ut, OH!&rdquo; [we lock eyes from grunt on] &ldquo;...those su-uh-mer ni-hights!&rdquo; Big, real stage kiss (not sloppy, thank God) concludes skit. As applause starts, I wonder if that&rsquo;s not a toilet I hear flushing. The sound of any chance I might&rsquo;ve had to have a date with The Latin American going down the drain.  But maybe that tank emptied a long time ago, and this is just the splashy send-off. After all, just a week before I met The Harvard Lickwit at a party. And three days later, &ldquo;subway serendipity&rdquo; would intervene...    Grease   

      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      I meant to post this on Sunday, but since it was my birthday I got a little distracted.  Here now, for your reading bemusement, is a little more background on  urlLink The Captain . As I recall, the Captain’s father has had an unusual career as pastor then truck driver then pastor again. But he’s not an  urlLink itinerate  as far as I know. ;)  More to come later when The Captain goes belt-to-belt with The Harvard Lickwit at a Morrissey concert.  But first, today’s text, taken from  urlLink Alain de Botton ’s first book,  urlLink  On Love  .  The longing for a destiny is nowhere stronger than in our romantic life. All too often forced to share our bed with those who cannot fathom our soul, can we not be forgiven if we believe ourselves fated to stumble one day upon the man or woman of our dreams? Can we not be excused a certain superstitious faith in a creature who will prove the solution to our relentless yearnings? And though our prayers may never be answered, though there may be no end to the dismal cycle of mutual incomprehension, if the heavens should come to take pity on us, then can we really be expected to attribute the encounter with this prince or princess to mere coincidence? Or can we not for once escape rational censure and read it as nothing other than an inevitable part of our  urlLink romantic destiny ? By the way, if the God-stuff weirds you out, keep reading. I think the bit about the cows is rather funny — if for no other reason than its insight into the female psyche.    Girlfriend #1  says: hey Anna  Anna Broadway  says: Hey, girl.   GF1 : how are things going for you?   AB : I’m doing OK. Keeping quite busy, as always. Feels like God’s starting to do some good work in my heart, and in my friends’ lives. I feel like something is beginning to happen.  AB : How &rsquo;bout you?   GF1 : well before we talk about me, what do you mean by doing something in your heart? what do you expect God might be doing/going to do?   AB : Um ... I’m not sure exactly. But I’ve been reading Larry Crabb’s book   urlLink Inside Out  , which is very good.   GF1 : yeah we read that with our homegroup, it is a good book  GF1 : very introspective  AB : Totally. I can’t describe it exactly, but I think maybe God will begin to help me work through some of the deeper issues that are manifesting themselves in my ridiculous obsession over that guy, The Captain.   GF1 : what has He been doing with your friends?   AB : Well ... my best friend finally came to  urlLink church  with me last Sunday — ostensibly to meet The Captain (he’s the one who teaches English) — but was also very moved by the sermon.   GF1 : The Captain?  GF1 : Is he the one in the navy or something?   AB : Yeah, the army. She’s still involved with the bf, but we had a really good conversation Sunday night. I think she’s more open to God’s work ... feeling a desire to seek him out more and more of a relationship with him.  AB : And then ... I had lunch with my homeless girl friend yesterday, and that was very good. Huge, huge progress to make advance plans with a homeless person and be able to keep them!   GF1 : yeah, I really liked your email about your experiences this past year  AB : Of course, today I was supposed to see Homeless Girl Friend on my way to work and give her a blanket, but she wasn’t there. Still, Homeless Girl Friend expressed interest in coming to church Sunday too ... so we’ll see.   GF1 : that would be really cool if Homeless Girl Friend went with you to church  GF1 : that she would trust you that muc  AB : Yeah, I hope Homeless Girl Friend can come .... Best Friend and I were laughing last night, though, about how crazy that could be! Best Friend and Homeless Girl Friend with me at church, Best Friend trying to finagle an opportunity for us to have lunch with The Captain ... and me meanwhile trying to be decent to Homeless Girl Friend! lol. Quite complicated.   GF1 : so is The Captain available and if so, do you think he is interested? or should I not go there   AB : Available, yes, as far as I know. He’s dated several people in the last year — but always very briefly. I think he gets bored or realizes he’s not that interested or something.  AB : I don’t really ... think  he’s interested, but of course sometimes  I kid about how he DOES like me, he just hasn’t figured it out yet.     GF1 : so why the obsession?   AB : Oh, man ... I do not know. That just seems to be my mode of liking people!   GF1 : yeah i know the feeling  AB : Um ... he’s really hot, for one thing. I met him at church ... he has the occasional capacity for kindness ... and he’s really sharp.   GF1 : the occasional capacity?   AB : Well ... I don’t always get a lot of time for him, and sometimes we seem more like acquaintances than friends.  AB : He can definitely be selfish, but also kind at times.   GF1 : you haven’t  knitted him booties  have you   AB : Hehe ... no. But I did sell him a picture! AT his suggestion, actually (this was early on). I haven’t met a Christian guy this interesting in ... I don’t know, ages.   GF1 : sure, that makes sense. how old is he  AB : 31? I think he’ll be 32 in December.  AB : He’s just really cool, very literary, likes to travel and do adventurous things ... wrote a freaking paper about  urlLink Ikea  and the  urlLink Panopticon  .... Crazy.   GF1 : i remember at one point you weren’t sure about his walk with the Lord, has that changed?   AB : I don’t know ... Last Sunday we saw him for all of 2 seconds because he wanted to go to Sunday school ... but I really don’t know.  AB : I think it’s just that  he seems to have this whole cool-nerd thing going on that’s really deadly. He likes hymns better than praise songs ...    GF1 : is that bad?   AB : No, no! Very good.  He sees the superficiality and poor musicality in a lot of praise music.   GF1 : that’s cool. b/c it sounds like it mean something more to him than just a cathartic experience  AB : He’s just ... a lot of the things I like in a guy. I’ve had multiple conversations with God where I’m like, “Man, if he could be the one, I would so be FINE with that.”   GF1 : hehe  AB : Yeah, I don’t know.... I think the biggest issues would be his capacity for intimacy and his ability to relate well in the emotional sense.   GF1 : sounds familiar  GF1 : well those things are important in a man  GF1 : very important even if he is adventurous and a deep thinker  AB : I know, right? A good female friend of his once described him as  “emotionally fucked-up.”  She said, even if the perfect girl for The Captain were to come along at the moment, she wouldn’t encourage that girl to date him right now.  AB : I try very hard not to think she was referring to ME as the perfect girl ;) ... and to be patient.  AB : Either I’m like, “Please, God, let this work out ...” or, “Please, God, let me just get OVER him, because this is ridiculous and pointless.”   GF1 : totally  GF1 : but we can’t help the way we feel, we’re only responsible for how we respond to it  AB : I think I could be good for him, though, because he’s obviously so arrogant about his intelligence — although sometimes he masks it well. But he totally needs someone to give him shit and not be totally impressed with him all the time.  AB : At least, *I* think so.  AB : But what God’s doing ...  AB : I feel like he may be trying to wean me from trying so hard to get The Captain’s attention, like, “You need to trust me with this.” Regardless of whether anything happens, of course — but just, quit trying to ALWAYS look so cute on Sundays.  AB : I think my motivations are often screwed up there.  AB : I’m just so completely fucked-up around him. No sense of up or down, right or wrong ... and it’s especially maddening in light of how confident and comfortable I can be with my other guy friends.   GF1 : yeah, but  i don’t think there is anything wrong with wanting to look cure on Sundays   GF1 : cute  GF1 : but i do understand the whole God timing thing and if it is even a part of His plan  GF1 : sometimes it can be very frustrating  AB : I know ... (sigh) I don’t know. I really feel like this is NOT the key issue God is interested in addressing ... but that as we address those other issues, the me-and-The Captain thing will straighten itself out.  AB : TOTALLY. I have much total frustration. Crazy.   GF1 : maybe God just wants you to trust that He knows your desire, which is to eventually marry someone cool, whether it’s The Captain or not, and believe that He has the best person for you  GF1 : but that sounds like a response that I wouldn’t want to hear b/c really I’m sure you already know that  GF1 : anyway, I’m not trying to solve anything for you   AB : Yeah ... And that trusting-him-to-have-my-best is SOOOOOOO hard in this area. I just look at my body in the mirror sometimes, and I think,  “Man, I want SOMEone to enjoy this before I get old and flabby.”     GF1 : hehe  AB : Somehow I think the deeper issue has to do with projecting needs only God can fill - although maybe not fully on this earth — onto possible relationships. I can’t sort it all out....   GF1 : yeah, that totally sounds valid  AB : That’s why I think the Crabb book is good.   GF1 : i mean, i do it to my husband all of the time and then when he doesn’t meet my expectations i get upset, when really he can’t meet all of my expectations  GF1 : but a lot of the time, i feel like God doesn’t meet those expectations either  AB : Yeah ... I just think it would be easier if I was having more contact. Because then you’re more in touch with the reality of the person! The Captain was hardly at church all summer, though, so I really haven’t TALKED to him in ages.   GF1 : and then i think, maybe my expectations are wrong and that’s why they’re not being met  AB : It’s interesting ... almost never been any one-on-one time with him. Ever. The occasional phone call — and a few brief emails — but that’s it.   GF1 : that’s not much to build on  AB : Yeah, I know. One guy friend was like,  “You need to totally blow him off. Then he’ll be interested.”  But I haven’t seen him often enough to blow him off!  AB  winks   GF1 : i was going to suggest the same thing, but i guess that doesn’t make sense if you don’t see him that often  AB : yeah.... Yeah....  AB : Did I ever tell you about the cow email? I wonder if it would forward ... It never quite worked last time....   GF1 : i don’t think so no  AB : Dude, I’m so whooped over him sometimes.....      GF1 : as whooped as you were over The Winner?   AB : Haha. Well THAT is a very interesting thing. Because The Captain actually REMINDS me of The Winner a little. The voice.  AB : Sometimes I think that PART of what I find attractive in him is the same things I did in The Winner (whom I haven’t heard from in ages).  AB : Intellectually I think The Captain is sharper, but I think The Winner was more consistently kind in some ways — and something of a swing dancer.  AB : I’d probably still be interested in HIM if he ever showed up, but I’m sure he’s engaged or married to that gf of his by now ... Haven’t heard word in ages.  AB : It’s just like ...  there’s no major red flags!!! So how am I supposed to get over him?  Certainly not when the field is so dismal in comparison .... There’s just no way.   GF1 : yeah i know  GF1 : but he hasn’t really given you any green lights from what i can see  GF1 : not that that makes a difference really in whether or not you get over him  GF1 : or even want to  AB : Yeah ... I know. But I can’t really get over him because of the women he dates either, because none of them are serious things. It’s like the last one ... I wanted to make bets with myself about how long SHE’d last!  AB : Sure enough ... haven’t seen her at church since.   GF1 : what kind of women does he date?   AB : Um ... not always XNs, actually. I don’t know what his deal is.  AB : I have a long theory about it ... but I should probably save that for later.  AB : I don’t think they’re ever that spunky — like me.   GF1 : maybe he feels the same way about Christians that you do  AB : See, EXACTLY. I think we need to talk enough about this that we eventually figure out,  “Gee, we dislike the same things in other-sex Christians ... Maybe that means we’re both not like that. Which means ... maybe WE could date and not have that problem...”  Hehe   GF1 : i mean conservative XN men  AB : ?? Conservative XN men? And The Captain thinks of them? I’m confused...   GF1 : if only it were that simple  AB : I *KNOW*. Sigh.  AB : Which brings us back to God...   GF1 : no, i mean you’re view on conservative XN men  GF1 : not his  AB : So did my email get through? Can you see the  urlLink cows ?    GF1 : hold on let me check  AB : Oh, right....   GF1 : it’s 100 freakin degrees here today [Girlfriend #1 lives in Arizona]  GF1 : give me a break it’s oct 1st  AB : Wow ... So not that hot here! Finally getting a little cooler. High is 60 today. I freaked out a little and overdressed a tad...   GF1 : hey, got the cows  GF1 : pretty different  GF1 : but funny  AB : Yeah!!!! Isn’t that awesome?  AB : At first the cows weren’t showing up ... just his message about all the trouble it would take ...  From: The Captain To: Anna Broadway Subject: RE: hardly tardy Date: Wed, 29 Jan 2003 16:21:48 -0500 Glad you noticed the cow--I stole it from the  urlLink radio 1190  webpage and I love it.  The best effect is achieved by lining up lots of them, but that's too time consuming to bother with.  AB : Then the cows [all 11 of them] popped up. I was like, “WOW....”   GF1 : it’s like they’re doing some weird dance  AB : I know. Ain’t it awesome? I think they’re hilarious.  AB : We have a similar sense of HUMOR, Girlfriend #1. And  he has a huge vocabulary.   AB : (to God) Why couldn’t it work?!!   GF1 : did The Captain send the cow thing?   AB : Oh yeah.  AB : Totally unlike him ... in that it was just a friendly little email. Usually the emails are non-chatty and very directed to specific questions or things. They have a *reason*.   GF1 : interesting  AB : yeah ... But he’s usually pretty good about responding to emails that require a response. That’s better than some other people in the past....      On Love        Inside Out   

      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      For a time last winter, Shock & Awe were the nicknames of choice for my best friend and I, although delivering the  urlLink chocolate vaginas  was probably our only “formal” appearance. ;) But the term as applied to me actually originated on a disastrous trip to West Point for a September 2003 football game...   Anna Broadway  says: Oh, I have to tell you about the whole “shock and awe” thing, though. Hehe.   Girlfriend #1  says: shock and awe?  AB : Yeah....  AB : So when my sis was here, we went to a  urlLink West Point game . Went with Guy Friend #1 ... who is a whole other long story.  AB : Anyway ... let’s just say the W.P. game day was kind of a disaster, as it turned out.  AB : So let’s see. The Captain had emailed me about getting to the game, but told me he didn’t think he’d really have time to “hang out” with us at the game, should he see us, because he had long-standing plans with friends.  AB : So, whatever. We thought it was lame ... but we certainly didn’t need to hang out with him to have fun.   AB : So, he tells us the cab ride from the train station to the game is like $15, and there are big signs with the cab number by the train station.  AB : We get there, and sure enough, there’s a sign. We call the number, and a few minutes later a van pulls up.  AB : We have a nice rapport with the cab driver, and he and Sis are talking about all this military stuff. Everything seems great.  AB : Then we pull up to the stadium, and he’s like “$15 .... each.” We just about died. Freakin’ $45 for a stinkin’ cab ride!!!   GF1 : that’s ridiculous  AB : I know! But coming from New York, it never occurred to us to establish a cab rate before getting in. Plus, The Captain’s email never suggested I might need to do that (turns out he’d never taken one from there before).  AB : So we get reamed on the cab fair. But luckily the game tix were cheaper than expected. Still, we were like, “Dude, Best Friend had BETTER show up, because we so need her to drive us to the train afterward.” (She was supposed to join us.)  AB : Well ... we have terrible phone reception throughout the game, which basically sucked. The reception and the game, that is.  AB : Army blew lots of chances, and lost. No word from Best Friend, and she never showed up. No sign of The Captain. I was in a funk, for various reasons.  AB : So ... by end of the game, we’re none of us super-chipper. Then we start trying to find a taxi - deTERmined to not get screwed.   GF1 : was The Captain playing or something, is that why he invited you guys?   AB : NO ... But he goes to WP, and was at the game as a spectator. He hadn’t invited us or anything ... I had just mentioned that we would be up there.   GF1 : oh  AB : Seriously, he is SUCH a lame-wad sometimes. In fact, as we were leaving the game, Sis and Guy Friend #1 took to calling him “the asshole” because he was “too busy” to even talk to us.  AB : But whatever ... So we ask various people about the taxi sitch, and it ain’t so good. They’re all like, “Man, you got screwed.”  AB : And we’re like, “Really? Thanks. That’s so nice to know. Because we never would have GUESSED that.”  AB : Anyway ... we eventually end up at this crappy Italian place to eat something. Served us the crappiest drinks I think I’ve ever had.  AB : Phone reception is as bad as ever — if not worse.  AB : Guy Friend #1 is flipping out over this, and we’re all to this giddy point where you just can’t do anything but laugh any more because it’s so pathetic.  AB : Midway into the second round of drinks, the waitress informs us that the place has a 3-drink per person limit!  AB : Apparently she took us for alkies because we started off with whiskey shots (me) and jack & cokes (Guy Friend #1). Pretty hysterical.   GF1 : that’s pretty funny  AB : Yeah ... so then there was this whole thing with onions and chili and stuff ... but I won’t even go into that.  AB : So we ask the waitress about taxis, thinking, “They’re a restaurant ...” but no luck.  AB : No one we ask has any ideas.  AB : Finally we end up at a police station, standing in this little cramped lobby and peering through a small window to explain to the cop on duty.   GF1 : what?   AB : She’s like, “Did you try 866-taxi?” We frantically get out the yellow business cards from our first driver to make sure that’s not HIS number.   GF1 : why did you guys go to the police station?   AB : We’re like, “Nope....”  OH — we were trying to get taxi help from the po-lice.   GF1 : ok  GF1 : for a sec i thought you guys were taken in or something lol  AB : A cop suggested it. That was about as helpful as anyone in that damn town got. Pass the buck. Anyway ... so she calls the number she has ... but gets a machine.  AB : “Well, just keep trying,” she says, and scribbles down the number.  AB : We’re like, “Oh, THANKS.” So we go back outside to try our non-working mobiles again.  AB : Finally I get through to the number, but the guy’s like, “Oh, we’re occupied right now ... try someone else.” I was like, “Dude, is he getting a freaking blow job or something? What is the DEAL?!!”  AB : Finally Guy Friend #1 and Sis prevail upon me to call The Captain about a ride, since they’re convinced he owes it to us.  AB : I call, and get his voice mail. Leave a message.  AB : meanwhile, Guy Friend #1 is trying the taxi man’s business-card, in desperation. Decides to pretend we haven’t used the service, and to inquire about the price.  AB : I then suggest that he ALSO try The Captain, from his phone — in case The Captain is .... screening his calls or something lame. (As far as I’m concerned, The Captain is probably getting sloshed with his better-than-us friends in some hip, dive-y W.P. bar that we’d never have the luck to stumble into.)  AB : Any way ... so Guy Friend #1 calls ... and freaking gets through to him! Sis cannot believe it.   AB : The phone call is really hysterical, because Guy Friend #1 had met The Captain ONCE and said like 5 words to him. “The Captain? This is Guy Friend #1. I met you  urlLink Sunday . We’re in kind of a predicament....”  AB : So, between combinations of mild exaggeration designed to provoke sympathy and obligation ... Guy Friend #1 persuades The Captain to come pick us up and drive us to the train station!   GF1 : this is really cracking me and my husband up  AB : Seriously, right? UNbelievable. You shoulda heard the story when Sis &amp; I were tag-team telling it to people.  AB : Anyway, apparently The Captain had grumbled something about losing a parking spot ... but agrees to come.  AB : 20 minutes later or so, he zips up in front of the Dunkin’ Donuts where he waves us over, and takes off at ferocious speed.  AB : I mean, the man’s in this little white station wagon of some kind, but he’s driving like a MANIAC. I guess we did catch our train (Guy Friend #1 had strongly emphasized the long period between the 10 p.m. train and the next one) ... but it was crazy.  AB : THEN, his tires are like squealing on the turns and stuff, but The Captain’s like, “Yeah, my tires squeal. It’s not like I’m pealing out or anything.”   AB : Oh man ....  AB : So I meanwhile, after the most crappy-ass “mojito” I’ve ever had in my life, and a whiskey shot on ice [makes face] ... and the adrenaline of all this craziness ... am in rare form.  AB : For once, I’ve overcome my normal fear of talking around The Captain, and I’m going a blue streak.  AB : He’s playing the affable rescuer, and making polite inquiries. “So, Guy Friend #1, what do you do?”  AB : Guy Friend #1 explains about his software gig, and I interject, “Yeah, Guy Friend #1 is the originator of this software program that lets people keep a daily journal of things like how often they jack off.”  AB : Of course, they journal lots of other things too, but I knew The Captain would appreciate this particular example.  AB : Sure enough: “See! You couldn’t get through a conversation without mentioning it,” he says.  AB : “Well, I haven’t talked about it in a while,” I say, all innocence. “I usually save all that stuff for when I first meet people. I wouldn’t want to end up with some conservative Christian guy ....”  AB : “Shock and awe,” my sister deadpans from the back seat.   GF1 : Hubby wants to know if he invented the blog?   AB : haha ... Guy Friend #1? No .... He wishes! He sure reads a lot of ‘em though ... Anyway, as Sis’s comment so completely hits things on the head, it’s a big hit with the car.  AB : And somehow it becomes a launching pad for me to dive into recounting my shock-and-awe conversations and subsequent bad date with a Christian guy to The Captain.  AB : In helping me tell the story later, Sis always makes sure to point out that I “shocked and awed” The Captain with the same material used to “shock and awe” Hapless Hesitater.  AB : But, really, I don’t think this should have been “shock and awe” for The Captain, exactly. Really just a return to the form I demonstrated upon first meeting him.  AB : Which is hopeful, actually, because in the beginning he did seem a tad interested. Just never followed through on it, alas.  AB : But then, this is why I’m convinced he likes me but just hasn’t figured it out yet.     AB : That’s my story, anyway....    GF1 : wow, some story Anna  GF1 : i was literally laughing so hard i was crying  AB : Hehe. Right? And you didn’t even get all the sundry details about what I told Hapless Hesitater — which I then repeated to The Captain — or the various idiosyncrasies about how truly awful the day was.   GF1 : i’m sure Hubby doesn’t understand what i found so funny  AB : Haha ... Why’s that?    GF1 : oh, b/c he’s in another conversation with your brother and another friend and not totally listening as i read it to him and started cracking up  AB : Ah.... Right, right.  AB : Yeah, so one of the finer moments with Hapless Hesitater was when I said to him, “I think everyone in my family has a strong sex drive.”   AB : And Hapless Hesitater, who’s probably dying on the spot, is like, “You mean, YOU have a strong sex drive?”  AB : At which point I was like, “Oh shit ...” So I attempted to back-pedal.   GF1 : was this a guy you liked, or were trying to deter?   AB : Oh ... well, yeah, he was kind of cute. I was totally willing to give him a chance, because he could be someone to get me over The Captain ... and the first XN guy I ever went out with. But I think I shocked and awed him too successfully. Mostly with my swing-dancing....  AB : Anyway, Hapless Hesitater did not fair well in the assessment of any of my friends who met him. Guy Friend #1 called him dorky, and my sis decided he was “middle-aging” early ... although the poor boy is only like 27!  AB : The Captain, meanwhile is 31 and MIGHTY fine.  AB : Oh, but the funny thing about Hapless Hesitater is, He’s totally a  urlLink staff kid ! His folks are on staff with Athletes in Action in Miami. I met his mom, when my sister was here, and she and my sister knew a bunch of the same people in Seattle because of that....  AB : But Hapless Hesitater isn’t like Mr. Crusade Rocks the World.  That’s why I was hopeful ... (sigh)   GF1 : funny  GF1 : small world  AB : Yeah.... Yeah, it really is.

      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      The  urlLink Ad Weasel  is basically the first guy I dated in the city, as I explained to my friend The 5% Man in an IM session one day. Here, I'll letcha e-avesdrop a little. The 5% Man is actually a story in his own right; more on that later.   Anna Broadway  says: Well, well ... look who's back!  Welcome home ...   The 5% Man  says: hey  AB : So did Best Friend tell you about our little escapade yesterday?   5%M : no  5%M : 271 email mssgs!!!!!  AB : We decided Shock & Awe needed to pay a certain friend of ours a visit....   5%M : geesh  AB : OMG .... Well, we can chat later.  AB : No rush.   5%M : hahah no no  5%M : go ahead  5%M : tell  AB : OK ... So the friend in question would be a certain Ad Weasel.  AB : He of the "Call me when you want to fuck" reply the last time I called him.   5%M : not the  urlLink church guy   AB : Oh, no. No. Best Friend has maintained that I should call the Ad Weasel up and tell him actually I did want to fuck, just to mess with him.  AB : But I really can't do that.  AB : Yesterday, however, I was lookin' pretty hot (if I do say so myself), and my partner Shock was in town.  AB : Seemed like a good time to pay the Ad Weasel a joint visit (since he's met Best Friend).  AB : So for some completely ridiculous reason, I get the idea that we should deliver some sort of penis cookies to him or something.   5%M : who exactly IS the Ad Weasel?  AB : We later rectified this to be sex-appropriate, of course, but that was the idea.  AB : Oh ... Well .... LONG story, actually.  AB : Guy I met on  urlLink CL  about a year ago.  AB : We had several flirtatious phone calls and emails, then went out on a date finally.  AB : Had built up a good chemistry over the non-seeing-each-other-face-to-face part of the acquaintance.  AB : When I met him, he looked like this miniature version of  urlLink James Gandolfini .  AB : He's like 31 but inCREDibly middle-aged and 2" under my height. Stout.  AB : So I think, "Oh, I'll have NOOOOO problem keeping this guy under control. He's so not my physical type."  AB : Can I just say, WRONG?!!!  AB : Anyway, after finally extricating myself from his car much later, I felt little guilt, but realized there was no way I could continue seeing him.  AB : If any of his talk was honest, he was quite smitten, etc., etc., etc., and obviously way more into me than I him.  AB : Which I just can't stand. A guy deserves to have as much of my delight as I have of his.  AB : 'Sides, believe it or not, I hate being in the spotlight in that kind of way — when a guy just dotes on you (largely 'cause he's hoping for the later pay-off).  AB : So that was about it for me and the Ad Weasel ... but somehow we stayed in touch.  AB : And in FACT, he ended up in inviting me to his office Xmas party (he's the creative director for an ad agency he owns or something).  AB : Best Friend joined me for the party.  AB : Which was one hell of a wild time, I must say.  AB : Not so much in the wild-orgiastic-sex kind of way ... or in the  urlLink bacchanalian  nature of drunkenness ... but just crazy.  AB : The Ad Weasel's clients are all big-shots. So apparently we're rollin' with like millionaires and billionaires, a few of whom can't get their eyes off my chest (nicely exposed for the evening) or their minds off Best Friend's sexy car talk.  AB : ....You doin' OK?  AB : Maybe I should give you time to catch up.   5%M : well you're telling I'm just reading  AB : haha ... OK.  AB : Um ... so Best Friend thought the Ad Weasel's personality was great (which is true; he can be a lot of fun when he's not pushing the pervy sex-talk all the time).  AB : Apparently one of his clients really had the hots for Best Friend, but never called.  AB : So sometime in April, Best Friend and I are getting together for drinks, and at the last minute end up being joined by the Ad Weasel and the hot-for-Best Friend client.  AB : We start at the Tribeca Grand, make our way to B bar (in limo, to the crankin' tunes of Tom Jones and " urlLink Sexbomb ") ... and end up at  urlLink Pangaea  where they buy a table.  AB : Pretty wild night.  AB : The Ad Weasel and I still talk off and on, but he's usually petulant about my "never calling him" (which is not true) and obnoxious.  AB : The one time we had a reasonably  urlLink decent dinner  — managing to talk about things besides his desires to fuck me — he still offered me money to look up my skirt.  AB :  I think he was mostly joking ... but it was ridiculous.  AB : I guess that about catches you on who the Ad Weasel is.   5%M : lol  AB : Making any more sense at this point?   5%M : gotcha  AB : Of course ... maybe "sense" isn't quite the word ... seeing how there's no logic in me continuing to see speak to an asshole who constantly hassles me for sex in the most obnoxious way.  AB : But the thing is ... I feel like the Ad Weasel doesn't have any real friends in his life. Few people who are actually decent to him.  AB : One of these days I'm hoping I might possibly get through to him that while I can't offer him sex, I CAN offer him something that he doesn't find very often — which might do more to assuage his loneliness.  AB : But enough of my idealism.  The 5% Man makes face  AB : So anyway... Best Friend and I make plans to go down to this sex shop called  urlLink Pleasure Chest .  AB : She was like, "Dude, I so do not think I can do this..." (which is actually pretty funny when you think about it).  AB : But I made her do the research on shops that would vend chocolate vaginas and the like because there's NO way I could research that from my desk at work.   5%M : wait a min...she was afraid to got a sex shop?  AB : hahaha ... Well, apparently there's some adolescent trauma about buying her father a 50th birthday present ... with her mother.  AB : Since he's a gyno the only place evidently left for them to shop was a super-seedy, bordello-red sex shop.  AB : (Best Friend tells me Pleasure Chest was far less horrifying)  AB : So she does the research, I covertly click on a couple of the links she finds, but mostly leave it up to her.  AB : She's still protesting a bit about the whole idea (the shopping part — otherwise she thinks it's great), but I talk her into it.  AB : So she picks me up after work, and we drive down to Pleasure Chest (6th and 10th or something — near Waverly).  AB : There's a momentary bout of the giggles.  AB : She's convinced she can't do this.  AB : But I, feeling strong and confident in my business-like jacket over  urlLink fraying short black skirt  and loud-n-sexy tights, insist that we can follow through.  AB : We enter the shop.  AB : Actually it was quite neat and tidy inside ... you could almost forget that you were walking past wares like obscene pop- and beer-bottle covers, and rows of  urlLink dildos  and other phallic objects.  AB : After perusing the shop unsuccessfully, I march up to the short-haired, nose-beringed female clerk and ask her where the chocolate vaginas might me.   5%M : somehow I can picture that too  AB : She points us to a small case we have to access by squatting down, and sorts through small boxes of "Naughty Nibbles" that apparently contain white-chocolate nipples, white-chocolate vaginas ... and finally, dark-chocolate vaginas.  AB : We initially decide to get one of each — light and dark, and then add a box of boobie cookies at the last minute.  AB : But when we realize the three small boxes are going to cost us nearly $20, we reconsider.  AB : Only the dark-chocolate vaginas (which had the extra bonus of pink glace, as I mentioned) and the boobs.  AB : I suppose the whole thing was rather weird. I couldn't even stop to think if I should have some ethical dilemma with dropping my money there.  AB : I would not be at all surprised if the woman was a lesbian (not that that matters), but when I asked her how her day had been, she visibly relaxed.  AB : That made me feel better, somehow.  AB : Anyway, so we scraped off the price tags, took our gift-bagged sex gift, and decamped to the car.  AB : The Ad Weasel's office is actually pretty close, but we hadn't yet succeeded in reaching him — on the work phone or the cell.  AB : Some doubt as to whether or not he'd actually be there.  AB : But just before we reach his office, we spy a vehicle we're sure is his car in a parking lot adjoining the building.  AB : Our adrenaline instantly jumps, and we start getting giddy again.  AB : We tried ringing the buzzer for his office, but got no answer.  AB : Then we realized the door to the building was actually open.  AB : So was the elevator.  AB : So we basically just walked up there, and rang the buzzer on his suite.  AB : Sure enough, a woman comes out and greets us. (Score!)  AB : While she goes to get the Ad Weasel, Best Friend's like, "What if he's in a really important meeting?"  AB : But he comes out, shoots the breeze with us briefly, asks if he can open the gift in front of his people, tells me to call later, and goes back to the conference room.  AB : So that was that.....  AB : No word from him yet.  AB : Best Friend says she would have paid money to see the look on his face when he opened the bag.  AB : Whew! Do I tell a long story or what?   5%M : lol  5%M : not surprising  AB : haha ... the length, or what we did?   5%M : hmmmboth I guess  AB : Ah.  AB : Yeah, so I think Best Friend may now be broken in as far as visiting sex shops go.  AB : The bf was like, "Why didn't you buy ME anything?"   5%M : just what she needs  AB : hahahaha.  AB : Such an ironic guide, though, doncha think?  AB : Last night we had dinner with Guy Friend #1, and she was talking about how funny it is that so many of her opportunities for sex have unwittingly come about because of my social connections....   5%M : probably because you create so much unfulfilled sexual energy  AB : hahaha ... but it's not like she gets opportunities with the men I've denied. It's more like their friends ....  AB : Weird.    Reloaded: Greatest Hits   

      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      A few days ago I sent out yet another of my email updates, in which I described the woes of living on unemployment. For one reason or another, I tend to keep men in my address book.  Here's the dialogue with  urlLink one :   Date: Tue, 29 Jun 2004 12:52:51 -0400 Subject: Re: living on unemployment From: "The Ad Weasel"   To: "Anna Broadway"    Do you need cash?  If so, I can help. Date: Tue, 29 Jun 2004 10:49:37 -0700 (PDT) From: "Anna Broadway"   To: "The Ad Weasel"    Leaving aside the 5% ... OK, maybe 3% ... chance you mean that genuinely, somehow I find myself quite wary of following up on your email. (arches eyebrow skeptically)  If you need office help or something, I'm free during days but I never fuck the boss. I'm only interested in brain-work or hand-work ... of the knitting variety. (Sorry, couldn't resist. ;))  Seriously, though, how are YOU?!! Haven't talked to you in ages! I guess Female Employee must have had her baby by now ... is she still working?  Hope all is well. Thanks for writing ... I think.  -Anna  Date: Tue, 29 Jun 2004 14:51:54 -0400 Subject: Re: living on unemployment From: "The Ad Weasel"   To: "Anna Broadway"    First of all, I'm offended. I meant it as in cash to help you get through whatever, but no...the office doesn't need anyone to work in it, I was simply offering help.  No, I don't want you to fuck me for it. That wasn't the point. Date: Tue, 29 Jun 2004 3:49 PM From: "Anna Broadway"   To: "The Ad Weasel"    Hey, I'm sorry. :( I was mostly just trying to joke around a little. Guess it's been so long since we talked that I've lost my touch! ;)   I do appreciate the offer. Really. It's very kind of you. I guess I just had in mind that about the last time I talked to you, you said "Call me when you wanna fuck." So I didn't know what to think...  But really, it was sweet of you. I know you have a generous heart. Am I forgiven? (sad puppy-dog face)   Anyway .. back to the main point: how are YOU doing? Personally?   Hope all is well, Anna  Date: Tue, 29 Jun 2004 15:51:49 -0400 Subject: Re: living on unemployment From: "The Ad Weasel"   To: "Anna Broadway"     Good busy. No time really to chit chat, if you need something let me know I'll have the controller cut you a check.  Give me your address to send it out to. Date: Tue, 29 Jun 2004 13:18:38 -0700 (PDT) From: "Anna Broadway"   To: "The Ad Weasel"    Ad Weasel, that's so sweet. Really. Very kind of you. My booze budget is restricted, but otherwise it's kinda fun figuring out how to cook cheaply but well. This morning I made a massive spinach quiche!  What I would LOVE is if you could make it to one of my  urlLink birthday celebrations . I'm tentatively planning to wrassle up the gang Saturday night, since my b-day is that Sunday. There might be something on another occasion too.  But just so you know ... if you ever wanna just unwind and grab a drink or share secondhand smoke with someone who in no way is in it to use you or your money -- and who cares about how YOU're doing, I'm here. :)  -Anna

      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      It's an inauspicious time to start a blog.   My 26th birthday nears (no signs of lover, hubby in the offing), my best friend harps on the "off-blog" nature of our convos (as if  her  sexual activity were the point of this!), and I just wasted several prime-REM sleep hours crafting yet another profile (gulp) for the beta version for  urlLink Soulmatch  — the ecumenical answer to  urlLink eHarmony  (imagine a UN for religions, with some Yenta at the head).  Worst of all, I can't even decide how to organize my material, of which there is much. Do I proceed in chronological fashion? (Much delay will ensue, given  my obsessive quest for "historical" accuracy.) Or do I introduce the men in a by-the-by fashion — as if telling stories to a new friend? I lean increasingly toward the latter, but have decided to put it first to a vote among you, dear readers.  (Yes, there will be occasional lapses into  urlLink Victorian  tones ... but have no fear. There's lotsa masturbating and  urlLink chocolate genitals  yet to come -- none of it even mine!)

      
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

       urlLink Whew ! Can’t say I envy this blogger! That why love-life scribes like us gotta pad the site with general stuff such as  urlLink  Spooning Fork  ,  urlLink fashion soap operas  and so on. In fact, just last night my  urlLink roommate  and were discussing (over one-year anniversary angel food cake and champagne) that this blog is probably more PG-13 than R- or NR-rated. It’s like  urlLink 5% Man  once said in an IM session: “Damn dirtiest clean girl I ever did meet.” At heart I’m really a clean girl ... and sometimes the dirt is inadvertant (like my puns).  One factual note about the story, before I move on: I’m pretty sure the WaPo’s academic source didn’t coin the phrase “expressive individualism.” Robert Bellah et al used it as early as 1985 in the landmark work  Habits of the Heart .  But back to the blog. I will say that, despite  urlLink early optimism  about hiding this, er, “column” from the men it describes, the  urlLink Harvard Lickwit  apparently found me out anyway. Somehow he would be the unlucky sucker whose email service provider actually includes both username and email subject in the referral tag! I kid you not. And somehow the “fates” decreed I would see this referral page (http://66.252.165.189/exchange/hlickwit/Inbox/you're getting blogged about.EML?Cmd=open) before it dropped out of the 10 most-recent visitors. Weird.  At least so far there’s more ink on the Lickwit business card than he’s received on this site! But I like developing the characters gradually. It’s that  urlLink frustrated, lazy novelist  in me, ya know? In the meantime, his b-card is tucked away inside my  Bad Girl’s Scrappy Book , a cheesy impulse purchase at Charlotte Russe one day. The journal is kinda fun, though, and a good place to keep weird mementos like my Morrissey ticket from the concert to which Best Friend and I dragged Lickwit and  urlLink the Captain  (probably the weirdest pseudo-double date ever) ... and the bcard from  some guy we think was scouting me for a porn film .  I promise to tell that story tomorrow or later today, but right now I gotta get ready for a 1:30 lunch in the city. Don’t forget to make your suggestions in the  urlLink rename-Spooning-Fork contest ! Winner gets a recent j-peg of Anna ... bearing in mind the ratings above. ;).    urlLink   Habits of the Heart: Individualism and Commitment in American Life     urlLink   We've Got Blog: How Weblogs Are Changing Our Culture     urlLink   Bad Girl's Scrappy Book 

      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Sorry for the late update, ya’ll. Somehow I seem to be sliding back to my vampire sleep skej of staying up till 3 or 4 a.m. (I promise this has nothing to do with noisy neighbor sex — although it could) and then sleeping in until noon or later. :( Today was a step of progress though; I actually rose an hour earlier than yesterday.   Hot and Bored: a fashion soap opera  Should the late-night insomnia continue, however, I think the local postman may have provided me with a new resource over the weekend. It’s a little catalog called  Midnight Velvet  which, I am warned, may soon cease coming to my mailbox. (Perhaps they make exceptions for the unemployed?) They don’t want to bother me with unwanted catalogs, so this could be my FINAL CATALOG unless I order TODAY to undisturbed access to future editions. That’s a shame because, after only one issue, I can tell that I’m really going to need a steady diet of the “unique gifts and home decor” and “beautiful distinctive clothing in misses and plus sizes” offered by  Midnight Velvet . Based on the grapefruit-and-latte repast that was this “morning’s” breakfast, a  urlLink shrinking woman  such as myself is in great need of misses and even plus-size clothing.  Where else could I find the proper skirt set to help me “reflect the rich color of the season in ... vivacious patchwork”? Clearly this $89 special is an undiscovered gem waiting to join the others hanging from the charm bracelet that is my wardrobe: “Wild beauty radiates from a sultry animal print with splashes of brilliant red lilys [sic] on the languid top with front lace panel.” The lilies were apparently a last-minute design addition intended to underscore the “vivacious” nature of the ensemble, which was being dragged down by the languid (“lacking energy or vitality; weak ... listless”) nature of the top. Quite frankly, the outfit has all the drama of a midday soap opera.  I can see it now: Red Lily is a smoldering Latin man charged with the care of Languid Top, a spoiled Paris Hilton type who can’t bother to sit fully erect on the  chaise longue  she has occupied since her arrival. It is this tension of hot and bored that produces the “sultry” quality (“very humid and hot; torrid”) of the living room where they spar.  On tomorrow’s episode:  Languid Top begins to sweat and demands a bath that will not require her to leave the chaise longue.   Is it Ivory Snow or Woolite?  And all this in an $89 skirt set! Wow. Imagine the plot possibilities that await me in the remaining 124 pages of scintillating ad copy. On second thought, perhaps this might not be ideal reading for falling asleep... But it does offer tantalizing suggestions for a new  Sexless  feature I might add. Since some readers have been so disturbed by the lack of images in this site (more on that shortly), perhaps I should at least  describe  what I’m wearing on a day-to-day basis. In catalog prose, of course.  Today, for example, Anna is sporting a charming-and-versatile American wardrobe essential inspired to no small degree by Rosie the Riveter. The faux-real faded denim of her stylish Abercrombie jeans are fastened by embossed metal buttons that bring “the rivet” into the &rsquo;00s. Stain from a  urlLink recent stripping project  subtly highlights the distressed wrinkles produced by many an hour’s blogging for her readers.  Atop this handsome garment, Anna models a deceptively simple white tank top that adds casual elegance to this understated outfit. Dramatic splashes of red paint enliven one shoulder of the top with a drama that recalls  urlLink Jackson Pollock  and echoes the real-life sweat, strip and stain required to bring her antique desk to its new, scarlet life. Anna has elaborated on the Pollock theme with a subtle-yet-distinctive stain of muted yellows and greens that suggests any combination of domestic drama, from the over-use of bleach to a bleary-morning mishap with the latte mug. Rounding out the garment’s artful chic is a tasteful, serged hem that flirts up over womanly hips and then back down again. Top is 100% cotton, from the Levi Type1 Jeans label. Made in Pakistan, but probably not worn there.  Whew! Was that exciting or what? OK, I know. I’ve been dodging real  urlLink man-drama  for a few days now. But you see, that’s the point of being  Sexless : men aren’t always around, so one has to infuse sexuality (of the sultry rather than languid variety) into all the details of everyday life.   First-ever  Sexless  contest! Win a picture of Anna  Speaking of which, while I like the  urlLink Spooning Fork  feature, the name has gotta go. Despite what it purports to talk about, the name itself has  no  music whatsoever when rolling off the tongue (in fact, it sort of trips and staggers). Since I can’t think of anything better, my  urlLink roommate  and I are agreed that a contest is in order. Winner gets a recent jpg of Anna, so start firing away with suggestions in the comment section (or you can also email).  Ta, dahlings!      Rosie the Riveter: Women Working on the Home Front in World War II       Love Affair; A Memoir of Jackson Pollack 

      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Normally I try to take a kind of “Sabbath” from blogging on the weekends, but I guess because I wrote so little last week, the ideas just keep coming. So now for this week’s Spooning Fork.   urlLink     &lsquo;Jim&rsquo; from  urlLink  Sarah Vaughan with Clifford Brown    Although I like to think I know a little bit about jazz, lately I just keep discovering new voices that I can’t believe it took me so long to appreciate.  urlLink Nina Simone .  urlLink Sarah Vaughan . (And I’m sure the list will go on.)  This song initially came to me through the same  urlLink Angelique Kidjo playlist for iTunes  that introduced me to Stevie Wonder’s “ urlLink As ,”  urlLink Miriam Makeba , and my first aural experience of  urlLink Serge Gainsbourg . On first listen, it’s just another melancholy slow song — the kind you listen to on lonely, quiet nights when you feel like indulging dark emotions (for East Coast folk, this happens a lot in winter time).  But as the words sink in, they prove to share the non-existent logic behind the Missed Connections section on  urlLink Craigslist  and all the other women like me who do crushing for the long-term.  To be a marathon infatuate takes hard work, you see. But it’s all part of that character-refinement required for love if you subscribe to something a girlfriend and I recently dubbed “Romantic   urlLink Arminianism  .”  I haven’t worked out all the particulars, but I’m pretty sure that worldview accounts for Sarah’s song:  Jim doesn’t ever bring me pretty flowers, Jim never tries to cheer my lonely hours; Don’t why I’m so crazy for Jim. Jim never tells me I’m his heart’s desire, I never seem to set his heart afire. Gone are the years I’ve wasted on him. At least he’s not leading her on! But still, Sarah insists on throwing good love after bad:  Someday I know that Jim will up and leave me, but even if he does, You can believe me, I’ll go on carrying the torch. Why am I wasting these precious years? Why am I crying these bitter tears? It’s all because of Jim, it’s all because of Jim. Like Sarah, I don’t have a fall-back fuck buddy or a friend I can call up and marry when we’re both still single in our thirties. I have a fall-back infatuation. But this is key, you see.  For the Jim-lovers in the world, the only thing worse than being single is being crush-less.  And truthfully, we’re secretly somewhat fond of all this pining. It’s like one character says in  The Alchemist :  I’m afraid that if my dream is realized, I’ll have no reason to go on living. … I’m afraid that it would all be a disappointment, so I prefer just to dream about it.  The crush is stable, the crush is safe (because, God knows, that guy is never really going to come around for you and start challenging your precious  ideas  of who he is). And  isn’t pining like a Kegel for your heart?  It helps prepare for you the love to come. And if you’re a Romantic Arminianist, clearly true love won’t arrive until you’ve earned the right to have it and proven you’re good enough at loving to be loved. (Which sounds strangely like the lyric from Dean Martin’s opener to  Swingers , but I’ll save that song for another Spooning Fork.)    Sarah Vaughan with Clifford Brown   Serge Gainsbourg,   Couleur Café       The Alchemist: A Fable about Following Your Dream 

      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Ah, Friday night at home.   Soundtrack:   urlLink Horace Silver ’s  Song for My Father .  Drink of choice:  vodka & OJ — ghetto, I know, but watcha gonna do on an unemployment budget?  I suppose theoretically there could have been date #3 with the  urlLink Funny Man  this weekend, but he returns to school on Sunday, his week was crazy-busy, and I’m not sure what he wanted anyway. When I told a girlfriend about him last weekend, she asked, “Have you talked to your sister about him yet? I think you just want to be friends with him.”  Which is maybe what he wanted too. But somehow (more so outside Christian circles, perhaps) most men don’t seem to be interested in friendship with women unless the sexual tension has been addressed first (this, I suppose, can range from having a go at making out to having a go, full stop). Honestly, I can’t think of a single friendship with a guy that didn’t at some point involve one or the other of us flirting with at least the  idea  of attraction.  If the classic  urlLink  When Harry Met Sally   dilemma weren’t enough, recently my friend  urlLink the Ringleader  also raised another conundrum: what do I do about dates now I’m writing the blog? Funny Man’s introduction to me basically  was  the blog. While he didn’t, like  urlLink Covert Romantic , lead with a stated intention of “getting in my blog,” this soapbox did undoubtedly add complexity to the equation. As  urlLink Curious Reader  recently posed:  Does  urlLink The Captain , etc., know about your blog? What about your girlfriends, sister, etc.? Just curious since people tend to act a little differently when they know they're being observed.  Hope things are going well for you, -A Curious Reader Generally speaking, no, the men in my blog do not know they’re being observed, other than in the sense we all take note of each other’s actions and silently size up the people we’re just getting to know romantically (or otherwise). At any rate, much of the content is still historical, some going as far back as  urlLink five years ago  or more!  But … still. The blog problem. Does this just turn into some bizarre e-reality writing venture? In the interest of male egos (which I hear can be quite fragile), I have so far decided to take a cautious approach toward blogging those I know, and who know of the blog. Better to a) wait a long time until probably the guy’s stopped reading the blog anyway, or b) come up with general observations or musings based on the date, rather than giving the sort of blow-by-blow I’d offer gossip-hungry girlfriends. Who says my shtick always has to be colorful narrative? Besides, in story-telling mode I tend to run long-winded. I mean,  really  long-winded. It’s not for nothing high-school classmates used to time my answers in class. :-o  But I digress. (It’s this sort of tangent, you see, that adds such length to my stories.) So, the Ringleader proposes that possibly guys could feel hurt if I don’t mention them in my blog. Like, “It’s a blog about her love life, but she’s not writing about me, so I guess I’m not very important to her.”  But I said,  It just seems so incestuous or something to immediately write up what I think of the guy.  He wouldn’t know that normally, and probably he  wouldn’t  like to know every thought I had about him (would I want to know every thought he’s had about me?!!). I mean, even if the assessment’s not 100% positive, it’s not like I’m going to totally reject him. So there’s really no point in trotting out the little idiosyncrasies that may make for a better story, at the expense of ego.  The Ringleader still thinks a guy might rather have the flattery of being mentioned positively or otherwise than nothing said at all. Or I could just ask, she said: “Are you a blog boy or not?”  Sigh.  No wonder one character in my novel-in-progress breaks up with her boyfriend after learning he’s been proto-blogging their relationship. It’s too freakin’ messed up!  Expect this blog to turn to less-specific philosophizing (and lots of spooning forks) should I ever break the few-dates dating streak and actually get something approaching a boyfriend (I mean, a Relationship). Of course, that would also require me finding a man who’s actually as serious about God as I am (gasp — sorry, but that’s the crux of this blog, when you really get down to it; that’s why I  urlLink  don’t  get down to it , in fact ;)).  If one adopts the (probably fallacious) reasoning that  what could be  follows directly from  what has been , clearly there’s no hope on the man-who-loves-Jesus score. But I won’t be buying cats anytime soon! There’s a reason I sold  urlLink that soundtrack  long ago. ;) Instead I think I’m going to brush up a line I vowed to implement next time I’m about among the madding Manhattanites:   Guy:  “So, can I have your number?”  AB:  “You know, I’ve enjoyed talking to you, and it would really be fun to hang out sometime, but experience teaches me it really won’t lead anywhere. So I’d just as soon leave it at this.”  Guy:  “Don’t you think that’s kind of judgmental/cynical?”  AB:  “Well, again, experience teaches me that generally when guys learn certain details about me, they’re not very interested in continuing the pursuit. So why waste either of our time?”  Guy:  “What kinds of things? Are you wanted by the government? Do you have a kid?”  AB:  “Haha, no. But you see, I’m actually one of those weirdos who loves Jesus.”  Guy:  “That’s fine.”  AB: “Well ... I mean, he’s really my main man — at least, that’s what I’m aimin’ for. Most guys ... they don’t take so well to playing second fiddle; having a third ‘person’ in the relationship.” (Guy begins to look alternately confused and concerned.) But don’t look for this to be renamed  Spinster in the City  anytime soon. For one, it’s just not quite as catchy, and also hope springs cursedly anew (I guess my Indian friend  urlLink the other night  would call that the persistence of biology.)    Time to swap in  urlLink Hank Mobley  … Sorry it’s been a  urlLink fork -less week, but somehow jazz-of-the-wordless-kind is harder to analyze. And it’s probably not popular enough to really influence our phi-love-sophy.     urlLink   Far from the Madding Crowd     urlLink Song for My Father     urlLink When Harry Met Sally 

      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      * urlLink     I’d forgotten what it’s like, dipping toes into someone else’s pond. The internet advances such aims prodigiously. You get all the thrill of discovery and almost none of the delight of real interaction. Not that face-to-face contact is necessary to rouse one’s interest. Isn’t absence the substance of porn?   The few, the hot, the googleworthy  But the “pond,” not porn, is what I’m really getting at. This week a long-forgotten crush sort of skittered ’cross my radar. It’s been a while since a man with a web page (MWAWP) caught my interest; I forgot how intoxicating each successive click can be. When I first met  urlLink the Latin American  in January, it seemed a crazy boon to meet a googleworthy man. He had his own web site (as he had kindly let us know), and a fairly good headshot (not  urlLink that kind ) perfect for sending to my girlfriends mid-IM session. Just made them feel more in touch, ya know? Sure she might be out in Michigan, but she could  see  how hot the new man was.  Or wasn’t. The Harvard Lickwit proved to also have a web presence on the company page, but this consisted of a most unfortunately posed profile of his then-billowy pompadour, and references in his friend’s voluminous blog. (Later he kindly pointed me to another web hit, found by searches with his middle initial — but this was merely a pompous letter to the  urlLink  Times ,  decrying Starbucks; not quite the stuff of midday gossip. Nerdy, yes, juicy, no.)   urlLink Fontinator , too, has a website. He gets points for having the most style. Before a friend of mine met him, the site was perfect for briefing her on this guy  urlLink Dr. Kook, the visionary , wanted to set me up with. Later, the site supplied a convenient mugshot my sister and I could upload as our “photo” in MSN. (This silly game of photo-torment was first initiated by them, as a way of teasing me about the Latin American. When I wasn’t paying attention, one or both would change their picture from the normal icon or logo to the mugshot from his website. Weird, the things bored women will do, eh?)  The crush doesn’t have any neat, square, online photos for such uses (nor do we play that game anymore), but judging from a recent rectangle he ain’t lookin’ bad these days. And unlike the Latin American, he provides far more material for the i-voyeur to browse. Anytime you get a sense of someone’s aesthetic sensibilities — and they jive with yours — it’s hot stuff. (Which is probably why, conversely, I was embarrassed to laugh so comparatively little on a recent date; more on that later.) The question is, what correlation exists between the tantalizing idea-of-the-person and the guy himself?  In this case, I think the margin of error is pretty slim. I mean, I only knew him for like two months, and then only saw him about once a week … but I’m pretty sure the guy I knew then (who responded to my top-secret infatuation with alternating attempts at aloofness and getting me drunk) is much like the one who blogs today. Except, probably, nicer (or at least hotter — judging from the picture, as I said). Don’t people get better with age? Besides, as we learned in  urlLink Pop Sexology 101 , Anna’s closet looksism trumps most memories of less-than-praiseworthy behavior. (Except with the Harvard Lickwit — but that’s another story.)   Poster Boy, the Other PK  That summer we knew the crush by other names. Here I refer to him as Poster Boy, the Other PK — but that’s just because you already know about  urlLink The Captain  and I wouldn’t want you to get confused with all these preacher’s kids. “Poster Boy” because, although he was sometimes aloof and less-than-kind, I had remarkable luck in hanging out with him and his posse over various weekends throughout what was otherwise a pretty troubled summer for me (total buzz-kill of a story, but you can email me for the details if you like).  One of those weekends — prior to that of my birthday, the marathon, and a rather-strong Long Island iced tea — was July the 4th. For any woman who has never progressed beyond the high-school stage of liking a man (did  urlLink Freud  have a term for this, I wonder?),  spending key holidays or other events in the company of The Crush is a major coup . It doesn’t matter if it’s you and The Crush and many others … it’s still a coup (although separately attending the same homecoming or other high-school dance doesn’t count).  So, somehow or other, I managed to join Poster Boy and his posse on the 4th of July. I have almost no recollection of the fireworks (oh right, because there  were  none … between us), but I do remember showing off my domestic skillz. Again, related to the high-school stage of liking,  old-fashioned charms like knowing how to cook are perceived as key ways to snare a man’s attention . Sure, my dad used to mutter things about “the way men look at women,” but at that point in history I was still convinced  urlLink such rules did not apply to me . Thus … the baking. And occasionally the knitting (in case you wondered what Girlfriend #1 meant when  urlLink she talked about “booties” ). But that was only my first  real  crush, and I knitted him slippers. And that really  was  in high school.  Poster Boy, however, never got such love. Only baking. In the form of an apple crisp, if I do recall … But there’s a reason he’s not called Boy Who Ate Apple Crisp.  You see, the minute I walked into his living space that night, I noticed a poster of  urlLink Miles Davis . The  very same poster  in the  very same size  that I had hanging in my living room at home. Sometime during my freshman year of college in Iowa, I’d acquired two subway-sized posters of jazz musicians — more for visual appeal than because I idolized them over any other musician or band in my CD library (now 350+, at best guess). They were great, and they were big, and I liked for people to see them when they visited my living space. I had never, however, encountered other people or stores that had those same posters in that particular size.  But Poster Boy had my Miles Davis! In the exact same size. “Oh my God,” I exclaimed, in typically overdramatic Anna fashion (probably the kind of yelp The Captain has chided me for; evidently all those hours of listening to 80s music left him with sensitive ears). “I have that exact same poster!” As I stared up at it, in awe of this peculiar sign, I continued. “I have another just like it, but it’s of  urlLink John Coltrane , from the  urlLink  Blue Train   album…”  “You mean that one?” Poster Boy pointed to a wall across the room I’d not seen.  “Oh my  GOD ! Yes!” To this day, I have never encountered such remarkable similitude-of-taste again. Six months later, however, I decided it was far more significant that the  urlLink Married Man  explicitly referenced the character to which my namesake was married, when I asked him about his name (the same as my namesake’s fictional husband).  Because, when you’re still in the high-school stage of liking, these things  mean  something. It took seeing  urlLink  Serendipity   to teach me that the real sign is whether the money someone gives you with his phone number written on it comes back to you.   ... I’m Anna Broadway, and I’ll be here all week. Except when I’m googling.  Miles Davis,   Kind of Blue   John Coltrane,   Blue Train [Expanded Edition]     Serendipity 

      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Whew! Already Thursday and I’ve given you, um, only one post this week. Sorry, ya’ll. I meant to start on a post earlier today, but got absorbed in prettifying the site (hey, this Java stuff is  addicting !).  Meanwhile, a few new readers have stopped by with interesting questions:  In reading some of the posts off the glossary sidebar, I’ve gotten the impression that you are a single girl in NYC who is currently unemployed, not seeing anyone, and have a pretty strong Christian background. Yet you don’t appear to let yourself be rigidly bound by what I’ll call traditional religious Christianity, which can be refreshing. As you write about some of your frustrations with  urlLink The Captain ,  urlLink Hapless Hesitater , etc., I find myself wondering, “Is she trying to find Mr Right and get married, or is she seeking just a dating relationship? Is she a virgin and is determined to be celibate until she gets married?” And so on.  Best wishes, A Curious Reader Dear Curious:  By funny coincidence,  urlLink Bleeding Eyes  posed a similar question after I wrote  urlLink Celibates wear orange :  I don’t know if you know this, but looking at my screen, maybe it’s the beeding eyes thing... But ar’nt your pants and that yummy arse of yours in that picture actually .... Orange/in orange pants ?  That must explain the name of the Blog.. Sexless in the City .... My retort: “They’re red pants, RED.” (And it’s actually not an arse view.) Probably I should have clarified this earlier, as the front-side/back-side dilemma has troubled many a reader. At least it hasn’t stopped them from being turned on. Whew!  Good to know suggestion is still the main ingredient in fantasy.   But back to your question. According to a guy I spoke with last night, “biology is the only truth” and therefore the dominating urge/issue/purpose in life is to pass on one’s genes (funny, I always thought you could do that through the Good Will pickups...). Therefore, his answer would be that I’m really bent on having babies. Lots of ‘em.  While  I did once aspire to bear 10 children  ... naturally ... today I’m inclined to chalk that up to some weird childhood combination of a) strong-but-latent libido, b) ignorance about the pain in labor, and c) fascination with even numbers — if not fertility drugs.  But I guess that doesn’t really answer the Mr. Right or Mr. Right Now question. Which is really a question of pseudo-commitment or ... commitment. I seriously doubt that most people (at least, most romantic people) go into relationships actually hoping for eventual breakup and dissolution. If and when you’re getting involved with someone you really like, isn’t there some sort of unspoken hope it actually works out? Not that you necessarily want to have to make a  commitment  to that at some point, but you hope it magically never gets old, or you imagine there’s something better, so that at the end of your life you’re still with that person and it’s comfortable and you’re settled and happy.  We go in  prepared  for disappointment and pain, but I would guess  most people hope for a good long run of the state somewhere between the exciting beginning and comfortable middle of a relationship . However many of us may balk at committing to something (and someone) going  forward , I’m sure far fewer of would mind looking  backward  and discovering we committed to something good without expecting to do so. We wouldn’t so easily settle into the pseudo-commitment of most relationships unless deep down we secretly hunger for a risk-free version of the pleasures of commitment.  It’s like the conversations I often had during grad school with a good friend of mine. On a typical night, we’d meet up at the local 24-hour diner to down endless cups of coffee (mine probably decaf, and chased by 2 glasses of water). Eventually we’d call it quits, and climb into the old-school cab of a truck she called  Bessie . A turn of the key, and it would rattle to life (except for the one night when it didn’t and her dad had to come and rescue us). Five minutes later we’d pull into the parking lot of my apartment building and idle over the speed bump extending from the walkway to my building. Ostensibly, this was the scene of a 30-second goodbye wherein I gathered my things from the books, papers, lotion bottles and coffee cups she always had strewn across the floor, and opened the creaky door to jump down.  But somehow by this point, despite the many hours of chit-chat already passed, the dark and spacious enclosure of the truck cab encourages an intimacy not possible under the bright lights and silent music videos of the smoky diner. Invariably we launched into a conversation that would last 10, 15, 30 minutes or more. But did we acknowledge we still had things to talk about? That we weren’t prepared to call it a night?  In short, did we park the car, shut off the engine, and maybe even take the talk upstairs?  No. Never.  The conversation had a life of its own that both of us fed on and encouraged, but its length was always uncertain. Thus we could never admit we planned or wanted to say more than perfunctory goodbyes. The idling truck provided the safe space of the temporary while sustaining the intensity of the parting.  Because we didn’t know how much there was to say, killing the engine or going upstairs might be presumptuous; we might exert all the effort to do so only to discover the moment was gone and there was no speech to justify such an action.   So … we stayed, while the gas underwent its quiet chemistry, and the “unmarked” car of the security service sometimes crept past suspiciously.  It seems like a lot of relationships have that quality: people find something that’s comfortable and stimulating in the immediate, but don’t know how strong or fragile the bond is; any kind of change seems to threaten it, so you accommodate your life and expectations to stretching the moment as long as possible.  In dating, at least, I don’t want that kind of anxiety (clearly I don’t mind when it comes to conversation). After years of driving myself crazy with intensity of desire and an inability to satisfy it, I’ve decided people are basically like post-it notes or sticky-tape. We were made with a keen stickiness so that when two pieces adhere, they bond tightly. But, like tape, sometimes that bonding can be messy: the pieces aren’t aligned right, or you somehow get weird wrinkles in it. Pulling the tape apart just makes things worse, or at least reduces the stickiness. Re-stick the tape enough times, and it doesn’t stay stuck to much at all. So … because  I  want to bond as long and closely as possible, I keep stopping short of actually sticking to someone. Sure, my inner desire to stick to someone else makes me crazy, but I just try to remind myself that I’m waiting till the pieces are aligned right (in which I mean no allusion to some sort of fate or alignment of the stars ;)) and I can stick with full abandon.  Did that answer your question? ;) I guess I’ll save my thoughts on opportunity-cost and fear of commitment for another day …  -AB      High Fidelity       What Color Is Your Parachute Workbook 

      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      THANKS for your patience if you’ve been checking back several days now to the same damn entry. Things are getting off to a slow start this week. While I’m working on the next vignette, here’s part of a friend’s novel-in-progress that tries to wed the themes of this blog (sex and music) into a semi-coherent musing on ecstasy. Let me know if you think this excerpt is worth leaving up even after I finish today’s piece (yes, you can say it sucks ;)) ...     from an untitled novel  
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      For a few days now, I’ve had a combination of  urlLink Aretha Franklin ,  urlLink Ray Charles  and  urlLink Getz/Gilberto  in my stereo. With all the cinnamon rolls I’ve been baking (batch three is rising now; each batch has not two but  three  risings) it’s meant a lot of time to mull over lyrics. And my conclusion?  Aretha’s low-key power belt “Baby I Love You” epitomizes the age-old confusion and frustration between men and women (but especially men  with  women). Which brings us to … this week’s  urlLink Spooning Fork .   ‘Baby I Love You’ from  urlLink  30 Greatest Hits    (sorry, no iTunes link yet) At first glance, she’s singin’ a man’s fantasy. I mean,  here  is a woman who wants to put out: “You know I’m gonna give it to you … I wanna see you with it.” But as the song continues on for two verses more you start to think she’s kind of a tease. There’s all that damn  singing . He must be thinking, “You wanna give it to me? Fine, do it!” (Or rather, do me — but you get the point.) And all this talk about  love . Eight times she says it — and that’s just one verse/chorus!  The real kicker is when she gets to the second verse: “If you feel you wanna kiss me, go right ahead — I don’t mind” (I just won’t stop singing so you can).  Maybe she’s one of those women who wants to be kissed into silence … Oh, but wait — that’s a romance-novel trope.   When verse three comes around and she starts to talk about him leaving her, it has the sound of a self-fulfilling prophecy. I mean, who really wants to be with a lovey-lovey-lovey-lovey-dovey woman with  promises  of the action to prove it, when she spends all her time merely talking about what she’ll do? (Come to think of it, she did warn him at the beginning: “Don’t be afraid, baby — just ask me!”)  For the woman, of course, all this talk probably amounts to extended foreplay. And there are moments throughout the song where the ecstatic pitch of an “Oh!” has just that connotation. But the song fades off at the end like an unfulfilled arousal (go figure).   ‘sexless NO MORE’?  In other instances of the such misunderstanding between the sexes, this week I received a very thoughtful email from one of my readers. Actually, I can’t say that he’s a  reader  — certain things about his email did suggest otherwise — but at least he read one of my recent ads on  urlLink Craigslist . And by God, here’s a man willing to address my “ urlLink predicament .” He’s a quick one, though. Very savvy to the whole  urlLink e-dating  thing.  He clearly gets the importance of pictures in making a stranger seem less, well, strange. So he very kindly sent me his headshot.  Both of them. (Imagine late-night stand-up drum routine here: “buh-doop-AH”).  I should have known from the shady subject line.   Standing on the corner...  The strangeness continued when, perhaps an hour later, I was walking to dinner at my friend’s apartment along Atlantic Avenue.  A bare-chested, well-muscled man behind me is pushing an empty shopping cart in what surely could pass for an avant-avant garde  urlLink Chippendales  routine.  For about a block the sound of the wheels bumping over uneven sidewalk is so loud I can practically feel him staring at me. Sure enough, at the next corner while we wait for the stoplight, he strikes up conversation.  “Are you homeless?”  I pause a beat to absorb this bizarre pickup line.  Perhaps it’s the way I was hitching up my too-loose pants to keep from exposing several inches of underwear.  “No — do I look like I am?” Maybe black (the color of my monochromatic attire) is the new street wear.  He responds with another question: “How come you’re so pretty?”  I chuckle.  As if I can help it!  But then, most men on the street seem to think I’m hot. I’m convinced it’s basically a circumstantial thing:  sidewalk + woman = very sexy lady . Isn’t that the point of  urlLink Bobby Darin ’s classic tribute to the leer? Walking down the street turns any gal into a Very Fine Woman.  In a strange way, this man seems more transparent about the whole  urlLink beauty-power dilemma  I crudely tried to discuss the other day. And he seems harmless enough. How fast could he pursue with shopping cart in tow? “Because God made me that way,” I reply. I satisfy him that, yes, there’s genetic precedence for this in my mother’s fine looks, and leave the conversation at that. Sometimes lots of talking, as Aretha showed us, is a good way  out  of things. But other times there’s no exit better than drifting into silence.  Which is why Oversexed in the City (as friends suggested I call him) won’t be hearing back from Anna Broadway.  Aretha Franklin,   30 Greatest Hits   Ray Charles,   Ultimate Hits Collection     Getz/Gilberto 

      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      You could probably call this one the celebrity chapter ... and yes, it’s the last of the series! (Check back to pts.  urlLink 1 ,  urlLink 2 ,  urlLink 3 , and 4 occasionally as I add additional men on an as-needed/as-remembered basis. I’m also putting a perma-link at the top of the  In the Cards .)  Related to the fame theme, check back soon for a discussion of why headshots (ahem) don’t always help a man’s cause...   Stalker #1   Met through : an early internet-dating site (this was circa 1996)  Number of dates and pseudo-dates : none  First date : that is to say, meeting: his appearance at my Thursday-night show of  Fiddler on the Roof   Age difference : 1 year  Profession : professional caffeine consumer — I mean, web geek-cum-student  Where the money went : Dr. Peppers, coffee, and all his internet bills!   Stalker #2   Met through : bitter-cold-of-winter swing-dance party sponsored by my  urlLink church   Number of dates and pseudo-dates : 1? I’ve tried to block those memories out …  First date : not applicable  Age difference : 18 years at least  Profession : former teacher, aspiring CIA/FBI operative  Where the money went : lunch   Swinger #1   Met through : swing dancing at Bash on Ash  Number of dates and pseudo-dates : 0  First date : let’s say, first dance; a very-hot version of “Bei Mir Bist Du Schön” from the  urlLink  Swing Kids   soundtrack; my first clue as to why some warn that dancing leads to sex …  urlLink     Age difference : 2 years?  Profession : college student  Where the money went : N/A   Swinger #2   Met through : my naïve fan-appreciation chit-chat after the show  Number of dates and pseudo-dates : 0  First date : make that conversation; we chat about music and such while he smokes out back; when he asks if he can kiss me I suddenly find a great segue to avidly talking about Jesus  Age difference : 15 years? His gray hair was pronounced  Profession : pianist for a fairly successful  urlLink California-based swing band   Where the money went : N/A   Swinger #3   Met through : concert at the Bash on Ash, a one-time Tempe music/dance venue (very popular on the swing scene in its day)  Number of dates and pseudo-dates : 1  First date : post-concert meal at Denny’s (followed by a not-great make-out session in the back of my friend’s car)  Age difference : 15 years  Profession : lead singer for a  urlLink British swing band  (they covered  urlLink T-Rex  for the  urlLink  Truman Show   soundtrack)  Where the money went : late-night serving of eggs? (I was too sheepish and ignorant to recognize the mooch-potential of our pseudo-date)   urlLink  The Tim Robbins Type    Met through : a monthly cocktail event through which I was indirectly introduced by the Harvard Lickwit  Number of dates and pseudo-dates : 0  First date : make that conversation too: our walk from the bar 8 blocks up and a few over to the corner where he finally hailed a cab for me rather than walk me across town to my west-side destination (conscience dictated he should ensure a heel-clad woman got there safely)  Age difference : at least 20  Profession : works in an industry where “every conversation is grist for the mill”  Where the money went : my cab fare across town and (on account of the change) a much-needed BLT, milk and banana later   The Winner   Met through : undergraduate math class — but really, we met at a  urlLink Campus Crusade for Christ  meeting and then realized we had the class together  Number of dates and pseudo-dates : 1  First date : coffee at the local Coffee Plantation  Age difference : 5 months  Profession : (currently) an engineer  Where the money went : coffee, gas    Swing Kids , soundtrack    All Aboard     Truman Show , the movie    Truman Show , the soundtrack

      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Whew! And the  urlLink men  just keep on a-comin’ ... in a manner of speaking. ;) Another  urlLink  Spooning Fork   on its way soon, but in the meantime:   The Married Man   Met through:  the encouragement of a professor we’d both had  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  1?  First date:  in terms of the closest thing to a date, one night when we chatted endlessly and worked on an interview he was supposed to be transcribing by hand so I could then type it up for him  Age difference:  8 years  Profession:  graduate student in photography, part-time waiter  Where the money went:  coffee drinks, gas for the ride home he gave me (and the ride to school the next day)   urlLink  The Nerd    Met through:  a proto-internet message board for those seeking penpals  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  1  First date:  roof-top sangria party at  urlLink Hippie the Groper ’s building  Age difference:  1 year  Profession:  student (when I met him)  Where the money went:  phone bills for the 1 or 2 times we talked (long-distance) when I was still in high school   urlLink  Non-profit Superhero    Met through:  my  urlLink Craigslist  ad, seeking an intellectual grease monkey  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  2  First date:  dinner at a local Williamsburg restaurant  Age difference:  4 years?  Profession:  employee for UNICEF or some related monitoring agency  Where the money went:  dinner, beers, movie tickets to  Bruce Almighty  (second date)   urlLink  The One Who Came Out    Met through:  accelerated or AP classes in high school  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  1  First date:  my one-and-only high school dance: senior-year Homecoming  Age difference:  a few months  Profession:  then, a student  Where the money went:  ?   The Other Air Force Guy   Met through:   urlLink Irish Pub   Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  1  First date:  post-bar meal, movie and makeout session at his friend’s place (where they introduced me to a memorable love-done-wrong song dubbed “Poop in a Jar” because the protagonist keeps his girlfriend’s shit to remember what a stinker she’d been  Age difference:  6 years?  Profession:  computer guy in Cali, former military man  Where the money went:  pizza   The O-Zone King   Met through:  flirtation during ID inspection at Irish Pub, the night of my 22nd birthday  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  1  First date:  beers at the pub, walk to a park, frolicking in the grass (until sprinklers came on)  Age difference:  5-6 years?  Profession:  waiter/some-time bartender at Irish Pub (was supposedly taking a break from a graduate program in print-making)  Where the money went:  beers   urlLink  Poster Boy, the Other PK    Met through:  some  urlLink Campus Crusade for Christ  connection  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  3 (includes the two times I went drinking with him and his pals, and the 4th of July baking episode)  First date:  that is to say, pseudo-date ... in my dreams! That 4th of July shindig  Age difference:  2 years, 6 days  Profession:  Computer guy at Stanford whose real passions are ministry and  urlLink music   Where the money went:  that strong, Long Island iced tea and my first-ever tequila shots    Sgt. Ex-sessories, the body-mod king   Met through:  his aggressive flirtation one night at Irish Pub  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  3  First date:  dinner somewhere near Mill Avenue (Tempe’s main drag); maybe a movie, then cuddling during a Saturday-night drum circle  Age difference:  6-7 years?  Profession:  Persian Gulf Air Force vet and college student; did something for one of the high-tech companies in Chandler (maybe Intel?)  Where the money went:  meals, movie tickets, drinks, all the gear for his jeep      The Pilgrim's Progress from This World, To That Which Is to Come     Bruce Almighty 

      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      The inner prurient in me was greatly amused last night by a blurb for a political event in Harlem this Saturday, to which attendees are advised to bring “knee pads for kneeling on the floor.” Oh, but wait! This isn’t a Clinton event (though it’s his part of town) … it’s a Republican thing. Clearly they never have sex, or in an inappropriate fashion ...  But then, neither did the  urlLink next round of men  from my dating history — not, at least, with me.   Global Crossings Guy   Met through:  His ad on  urlLink Craigslist  (this was pre- or circa- urlLink Ad Weasel  era)  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  2  First date:  Watching  urlLink  Signs   at the Union Square theater; I conveniently forgot my wallet  Age difference:  5-7 years? Sadly his friends made a more memorable impression than he did; it was almost like  urlLink that Carrie-man whose family she liked better  than him  Profession:  possibly surviving on unemployment? He had recently been released from Global Crossings and was considering a return to the military  Where the money went:  Movie tickets, drinks and food at many an historic West Village bar (including the  urlLink White Horse Tavern  and  urlLink Chumley’s )   urlLink  Hapless Hesitator    Met through:  mutual acquaintance at a church-related artists reception  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  2 (including a bizarre swing-dancing double date Sept. 11, 2003)  First date:  lunch after a church service to which I’d worn a scandalously short pink dress in yet another unsuccessful play for  urlLink The Captain ’s attention  Age difference:  about 2 years  Profession:  classically trained musician looking to get into management  Where the money went:  drinks and gas for the rides to Brooklyn or train stations he provided   The Harvard Lickwit   Met through:  birthday party of a mutual acquaintance (whom I had met at a  urlLink Mediabistro  V-day mixer more than a year before)  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  8 (based on all occasions in which we operated as a couple)  First date:  movie at the  urlLink Film Forum , though two days previously we’d run into each other on the subway, resulting in a pseudo-date with Best Friend as third later that evening (this was the night of Alert-not-Yearning’s screening)  Age difference:  7-8 years (he’s one more than the Captain)  Profession:  PR hack for high-rollers (once started rumors about a  urlLink NY stock exchange  muckity-muck by posing as his doctor)  Where the money went:  booze and more booze (he was something of a lush), plus various meals, the Film Forum ticket, and extra phone fees for all the text messages I used to send him (supposedly his program doesn’t include such)   Hippie the Groper   Met through:   urlLink Campus Crusade  summer project in Berkeley  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  2? (we started as friends, so it’s hard to draw the line)  First date:  who knows  Age difference:  1-2 years  Profession:  web guy, aspiring law student  Where the money went:  drinks and cover charge at  urlLink Burlesque Bar  one night; espresso the morning after, um, the night I crashed at his place   urlLink  Indian Sugar Daddy    Met through:  my dad  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  2  First date:  lunch in Des Moines during spring break my freshman year  Age difference:  20 years?!!  Profession:  engineer  Where the money went:  internet access, meals, portable stereo, first real camera (also drinks though I was underage then … Hmmmmmm :-o)   Invisible Ma(ri)n(e)   Met through:   urlLink Irish Pub , the bar that briefly became my cheers  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  2  First date:  late-night coffee and brunch at a 24-hour diner  Age difference:  7-8 years  Profession:  keeping his current whereabouts secret from the Marines (he was still serving the two years during which they could technically call him up if needed); completing an MBA  Where the money went:  meals and the occasional beer   Jose No Dinero, aka The Latin American   Met through:  mutual appreciation of his friend’s comic dance routine at Burlesque Bar  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  0  First date:  does our conversation that night count? We ate pizza later …  Age difference:  8 years  Profession:  former pro-soccer player abroad; executive director of a non-profit  Where the money went:  pizza   Leather Daddy   Met through:  the work-proximate  urlLink Starbucks  were I used to take my lunches  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  0  First date:  N/A  Age difference:  15-20 years?  Profession:  leatherware designer  Where the money went:  the card, candle and pen he gave me for Valentine’s Day ... after 2-3 conversations    Signs     Sex and the City, Season 2       Sex and the City 

      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Shortly before going to bed tonight, I happened to check my email again. To my surprise, I saw an email with a feminine username that referenced a headline from a w4m  urlLink Craigslist  ad.   Discover the World of Ancient Mysticism patricia Clairvoyant Psychic Medium Master in the Sacred Art of Kabbalah Also: Angel Lite Healing.Chakra  Placement. Natal Charts. Aura Prognosis.Discover Past Lives.Crystal Healing. I specialize in Reuniting the Separated, Uniting Soulmates and  Changing Lives by  working through  the methods and tools from the lands of Egypt, Tibet and India.  “I will tell you your past, Explain your  present, and change your Future”. call for  FREE Consultation   Apparently a psychic can get me laid? Enh, but knowing who the lucky chap will be kinda spoils all the fun. And really, none of her other offers sound that enticing either: 
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

      Recently a reader of this site suggested that I seem to care a lot about money. Which makes me think a statistical analysis of the men in my life could be interesting (this is the point where I turn not into Carrie, but Rob from  urlLink  High Fidelity  ) …   urlLink  The Ad Weasel    Met through:   urlLink Craigslist  ad he placed  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  3 if you include the  urlLink double-date with his client , but not the two Christmas parties I attended with a friend in tow  First date:  Thai food, many drinks, chit-chat at the edge of  urlLink Central Park  (while mice ran around the bench below us), serious front-seat gropage when he dropped me off  Age difference:  7 years  Profession:  creative director for an ad agency  Where the money went:  bought a scarf from me,  urlLink offered money to look up my skirt    Alert & Yearning   Met through:  Alert’s request that Best Friend and I take a picture with the supposedly lovelorn Yearning to cheer him up (this occurred at the infamous  urlLink Burlesque Bar )  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  1, not including the many tequila rounds the night we met or the screening of a short “documentary” Alert made early in his TV career  First date:  Best Friend and I drive to Hoboken to cook pad Thai for the TV duo; when the highly touted hot tub proves mysteriously broken, a Beatles marathon on the radio accompanies a bizarre drinking game that turns into a kind of strip poker  Age difference:  10 years? We’re still not sure  Profession(s):  TV guys, one an anchor-of-sorts, one a … freelance interview personality  Where the money went:  lots of tequila shots and, um, repair bills for the hot tub   urlLink  The Captain    Met through:  post-church service lunch event  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  1  First date:  this was a pseudo date … but after a church-sing type event at which we mutually trashed the praise music, we had dinner with another friend at a hip South American restaurant; The Captain described his two broken engagements (for which he used the same ring before trading it for a camper top for his Land Rover) and generated the closest thing to an interested vibe I’ve yet seen from him. Then he flossed his teeth, in front of us, at meal’s end.  Age difference:  7 years  Profession:  Army captain,  urlLink English teacher at West Point   Where the money went:  half my cost of dinner that night, a framed pic from India he bought when I was first unemployed, contribution toward my first cell phone (group gift)   urlLink  Covert Romantic    Met through:  friend’s introduction at a cocktail party  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  we’ll see  First date:  none so far  Age difference:  8 years?  Profession:  musician who’s writing a memoir about his travels across Europe  Where the money went:  um ... his bar tab that night (yet another lush, sadly; or in this case: a wino)   Dr. Kook, the visionary   Met through:  Craigslist ad he posted, seeking writing/editing help  Number of date and pseudo-dates:  1 (not including the two times he helped me to move or the multiple work-related coffee/dinner/etc. meetings we had)  First date:  not the first meeting, but a bizarre V-day “business meeting” lunch that turned into a pseudo-double date when he invited a gal friend of his (presumably to encourage the Fontinator and I to hook up so he could vicariously jump my bones)  Age difference:  almost 10 years? Not sure, but he once congratulated “us” on having achieved this kind of older brother-younger sister relationship … in which Bro secretly wants to fuck Sis  Profession:  unemployed lawyer/aspiring entrepreneur and visionary  Where the money went:  various coffees, meals, etc. Boxes of the chocolates his family packaged were also sometimes offered in lieu of consulting fees   The 5% Man   Met through:   urlLink Mediabistro   Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  2  First date:  drinks the night before my last day working for the crazy artist; after sussing out certain key details, 5% Man made only the slightest of moves … to my disappointment. How could he not be more interested in a woman who later (more drunk than she realizes) invites him up to “go 95% of the way”?!  Age difference:  7 years?  Profession:   urlLink business manager  for a world-music magazine  Where the money went:  drinks   Fontinator   Met through:  Dr. Kook’s “business-related” introduction  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  3 (if you count two occasions on which I essentially played third wheel to him and Best Friend)  First date:  that weird V-day lunch with Dr. Kook (after we’d spent nearly two hours discussing business on our own)  Age difference:  about 4 years  Profession:  web designer and stats guru  Where the money went:  drinks (including, on one occasion, flaming sambuka shots)   The Funny Man   Met through:  mutual friend’s going-away party  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  1 and counting  First date:  drinks and a roof-top going-away party for that same friend  Age difference:  7 years  Profession:  comedian and soon-to-be lawyer  Where the money went:  drinks, tacos and cab fare (so far we never seem to end the night before 3 a.m.)   The Geriatric Gent   Met through:  friend’s introduction at a monthly cocktail hour  Number of dates and pseudo-dates:  1  First date:  art opening sponsored by GQ; show featured artists’ work on surfing and surfers’ attempts at art  Age difference:  50 years  Profession:  “tippler about town” who writes up various art parties and other posh soirees; occasional cartoonist for some mag here in town (also, apparently an Auschwitz survivor and former hostage in Beirut who’s related to one of the stars from the movie I watched with Hippie the night I crashed at his place)  Where the money went:  lots and lots of wine  Now if I were a guy, maybe I would’ve clued you in on how far they all got ... but a lady doesn’t kiss and tell (insert MSN’s angel-face emoticon here).  Tune back soon for the breakdown on the next batch ...    High Fidelity , the movie    High Fidelity , the soundtrack      True Colors: The Real Life of the Art World 

      
</post>


</Blog>