<Blog>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I just got up an hour ago and you know what...I...feel...GREAT! I slept longer than 9 hours for the first time in a while. Wanna hear something cool? Pembroke Academy is known overall to have poor sportsmanship in the athletics area. Well, I recieved a letter from the Don of the team, Mr. Doherty, with some good news. We had been awarded the Class L Sportsmanship Award for the 2004 season! Hey, we're the only team that actually won something! You all suck now because of this. There is a new movie coming out called "sleep over" or something like that. In the background near the end of the TV promo you hear a song with the line "Break out today!" Well, for those of you who don't know who it is, it's a band by the name of Allister and the song is called Stuck. This movie has ruined their careers not only because the song is in it, but they are in the movie as well...this sucks ass. I still love them though. Too bad the teeny boppers won't know that they are raging alcoholics who love to play stupid games when drunk. Oh yeah, summer sucks so far and it can fall off a cliff of blah right about now. Later.   Music Playing Currently: Avenged Sevenfold-Unholy Confessions
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yes, I have conformed as I was bored and it was 4:30 in the morning. Being bored is pretty shitty, but I can entertain myself. Speaking of entertainment, listening to my sister and my mother bitch is hilarious! They just don't quit until one of them gets their feelings hurt or my dad tells them to shit the hell up. Big ups to dad! My dad is pretty cool shit. You should all meet him some time. Definately the coolest dad around. Jon and I are starting a new band with a kid named Dan from Concord. Jon and I already have like 6 songs ready to work on so it's going alright so far. Saw Fahrenheit 9/11 on Friday night. Definately a must see for all those who want to know some cool facts. Yeah...so...Wimbledon is going on this week, which rules all. Go Andy Roddick and go USA! Take the title from the stupid Europeans. For those of you who know who I like...somehow I still like her so I'm just truckin' along here. Maybe someday I'll grow the courage to ask her out. Who knows, right? I guess that's it for right now. It's official, my cherry has been popped, blog style!   Music Playing Currently: Senses Fail-Buried A Lie
     
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Got to play some good ol' fashioned Putt-Putt at Legends yesterday. It's no Tee Off At Mel's, but until I get a group of 4 along, it just doesn't seem like it's worth the gas money. I have calmed down a lot since I lost my deal and I looked at it from both sides and I would've kicked my ass from the deal too! Me and Janelle had a good match, but in the end I was defeated, 56-50. I was upset. Then we went down to the batting cages and met up with Josh and some other kid. I was kinda upset after getting done because I figured I'd get the baseball out of me and I'd suck. Quite the opposite. I was killing some balls in the medium and got a couple of hits in the fast. Now I just miss it even more and am considering dropping even more weight and building up my muscle again just to play. Anyway, after that we went to Subway and got some food, and from there it was up to Borders. I got two Cd's; Bad Religion's "The Empire Strikes First", and Cave In's "Antenna". I've been waiting to get a Cave In CD ever since Kyle told me about his brother's band a couple years ago. I will now do what Kyle did for me and tell you all about two bands that are very good. I want everyone to LEGALLY listen to Matchbook Romance and Hellogoodbye. You can hear MR on-demand right now as their video for Promise in on it. Hellogoodbye you can get from drivethrurecords.com as they are currently giving away their entire EP for free! They have some great songs on it. I think the songs Shimmy Shimmy Quarter Turn and Call N Return are great ones to just have fun to.  I woke up at like 5 this morning and this means it will be a long day. I guess I should've expected to wake up early if I sleep from 5 to 8, get up for dinner, and go back to sleep at 9.  I was just exhausted because I am messing up my sleep patterns bad by not sleeping some nights and just going all out for the next day. I just noticed something random; in the entire day yesterday and from Concord to Hooksett I did NOT see a single hot girl that I checked out! That has got to be some sort of record. That or my standards are way too high. Either way, that's really odd. Another random comment, today is Drive-Thru Records last day on a distribution deal with Geffen Records, meaning no one can steal artists away from them, like Geffen stole New Found Glory, The Starting Line(more than likely), Something Corporate, and had taken Senses Fail before deciding to release them to Vagrant. Those Geffen people really know how to do business......or not. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I noticed that the only time I tend to write something on this thing is when I need to bitch about something, but you know what? No one will listen to me normally so I figure that no one will read this anyway. Thus I will continue to rant on. A little over a year ago, I had gotten a development deal from a percussion company that will remain nameless, as I have no ill feelings towards them. At the time, Days Unknown was gaining ground fast. We were writing songs each practice and had tons of songs that were ready for a CD. We were planning on going into the studio in January, and then someone decided that the singer needed to be replaced. Now, the singer was the one who was setting all of this stuff up for us, and was like a manager at the same time. So now we had no singer, and we had all but stopped practicing and talking. So we broke up about a week before we were supposed to go to the studio. Fast forward 6 months and I get a notice from the percussion company. Apparently, as I had forgotten, if I am inactive as a performer for a 6 month period, my deal is terminated. Guess what, the end of July marks 6 months. All I've heard for these past 6 months is people telling me that they were going to start a band with me, and then blowing me off and doing nothing about it. Now, because of me being too trusting and a good person, I'm losing the biggest thing to happen to my career as a drummer.   Now, onto other bullshit. I know that people are busy, and I am too, but there is no reason to tell me that you are going to do something with me, and then not tell me that you can't until after I set everything up. I also don't think that I should have to beg my "friends" to hang out with me. It makes me feel like I am everyone's back-up plan when their real friends don't want to do anything. When that happens, it's always "Hey Mike, what are you doing tonight?". Why do people have to be so two-faced towards me when I try hard to keep people happy, and sometimes at my own expense? I just don't know why I can't have a friend who actually wants me around instead of just using me as a stand-in when no one else will do something.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was watching Fuse and Uranium came on. I am not a huge fan of metal, but I like it. That's really not the reason that I watch the show though. I watch the show because the host is fucking beautiful. Just had to say that. Actually, all of the female hosts on Fuse are beautiful. Fuck MTV, they don't play music videos anyway. Moving on, I've been listening to Matchbook Romance today and, flat out they have got to be one of the more talented bands in the post-hardcore genre. Their song, "Promise" is an amazing piece of music to listen to. I suggest that you all LEGALLY get the song one way or another. Indie acts rely on CD purchases and Live Shows to keep going, and as an indie band, they get a larger cut of all sales of their album. Listen to the song, get the CD, and enjoy the beauty that is Matchbook Romance. Um, been writing some music lately and trying to write every part as far as a song is concerned. I've got a couple so far and they aren't too bad. If anyone wants to hear them, let me know and maybe I'll give someone a copy of one of the songs. That's about it for now, later! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am so damn happy right now for a certain band that broke out from their overbearing label that wouldn't release their album before they wrote a "radio-friendly" song. That's right, before Senses Fail could release an album that's been ready for half a year, they needed more poppier songs for Drive-Thru records to release "Let It Enfold You". How much gayer can a label get in regards to a band's creativity? I don't know how much further anyone can take it. Now, on their new label Vagrant Records, hopefully it will be released in early September. I know that I heard negative things about the new songs, but when I heard them for myself, it sounds like classic Senses Fail. Moving on, Friday night I got to go bowling again for the first time since I went with Blaine a long time ago. It was alright I guess. I just felt out of place for some reason. Almost as if I really don't view my friends as "friends" anymore, just as if I was a body to take up some space. Now, I'll admit that I am usually an attention hog, but for some reason I just wanted to sit back and view everything instead of participating. In a way I just feel like I'm in the way of everything now. Everytime I try to talk to someone, I feel like I'm inconviencing them in some way so I usually don't bother with anyone. Everyone is going on with their lives without me and I guess that I just need to go on with mine without them. No one wants to hang out with me anymore anyway, so I must be the human fun vacuum. Oh well, sucks for everyone else, now like I need anyone besides my band or people who I feel I can trust. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have just realized I am an emo kid. For an example, I choose to cite a part of my lyrics:  All that I have to dream about, Are the dreams that we shared, Hand in hand we walked across the night, Planning out our life, But now you’re nowhere to be found And I’m left here dumbfound, Knowing that you’re somewhere out there, Knowing that you’re not right here   Pretty lame stuff there I think. Then again, I am still a believer that girls like it when guys write songs for them, although so far it has proven incorrect. I guess the girls will always go for the jackasses and guys like me, who actually care about more than our dicks, will always be left in the dust. I even tried to be a dick to girls and guess what, more girls flirted with me than before! I know there is a huge difference between confidence and being a jerk. I know I am confident in myself, but I also know I am not a jackass. I've only got one year left in this area and I'm all alone still.  Here's something I don't like; girls who give mixed signals. I can think of three girls I've really, REALLY liked or like who make me feel like, hey, maybe I've got a chance with them and they'd like to be with me. Then it all just stops as I am about to ask her. I mean, what the hell! What they say about women being impossible to figure out is true. I'm still wondering what the hell went wrong this time, whether it was something I said or what. Can I get a girl to explain this to me so I can stop fighting myself over this stuff. I'm sick of kicking myself because I think I fucked up a golden opportunity, when in reality I don't know whose fault it is! That will be my summer research project for now. I'll probably start checking into some info later this morning, as I only seem to update in the early morning hours...before I go to bed.   Well, that's two moderately large posts in a row. I'm on a role folks. Until next time, later!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      For my opening statement, I believe that a little bit of unneeded knowledge would be adequate. I just took the biggest crap of my life. Yes, that's 17+ years of poop experience and I just took the biggest of them all.   The new Senses Fail record that will be coming out soon is just what I expected: good, pounding dark music, screaming, and some oddly simple yet catchy lyrics. Some people don't like it, but I really am getting into it. Dan Trapp is a really good drummer for only being 17. He's done his practicing obviously to play in a band like that.   The band front is just what it has been, working on a new one. Possibly might even be using an old name and a former bandmate too for this one. We will be playing Hardcore too, because, to be frank, I'm sick of playing pop-punk for right now. I want to play music that moves me emotionally, and doesn't just make me smile for the time being. I really am getting into that and more emo right now.   One band that I've been into since they came out on Drive-Thru Records is The Early November. They are really musically talented and can really get a crowd feeling the music deeply. I heard a few songs from Matchbook Romance and I like them a lot too. The drumming is graet. Avenged Sevenfold is a hardcore band that really caught my attention, mainly because of the drumming, but the guitar work is really cool too. Adelphi is a new DTR band and I like what I've heard from them too.   I recommend everyone listening to as many of these bands as you can get your hands on. What's the worst that can happen? You might end up liking them. I almost forgot hellogoodbye. They're an innovative band. I can't even describe them, just listen and learn.   Oddly enough, I've been in a good mood lately. I really do not know as to why I have been. The other stuff comes and goes still, but not nearly as much as it had been. I was a wreck for a couple of weeks there. I seem to begin to think about things late at night that I really shouldn't be thinking about and it keeps me awake. Then I get a real panicky feeling, like whatever I want to tell someone or do simply cannot wait. I'm more worried about the things that probably won't happen instead of the things that do happen. See, I'm usually what many call a "procrastinator" and I put things off until there is nothing I can do about it, then I try my hardest to do something and I fail.   I also make snap judgements and decisions without thinking about them. I can remember one time that a girl wanted to go out with me and I automadically said no, like it was a planned response. I went home that night and realized I had made a huge mistake, and tried to take back what I said. I really did want to go out with her. She said that I was an ass and, in conclusion, I was fucked over by my own actions. God I am such a loser. If you need proof of this, look at how large this post is. I am a douchbag. Well, a cuddly, lovable douchbag, but one nontheless.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm trying to write some real killer lyrics right now, but nothing is coming out of my head, thus why I am updating this. I noticed that I am mainly a pop-punk lyricist and Hardcore music is harder to write for. Usually, I write about the thing I know best, heartbreaks, and seeing everyone has had them I feel that they can connect with it easily. I'm not a big angry writer because it always gets me thinking about things that make me mad or people who have angered me in the past. I'm going to try to avoid those people, as many of them don't realize they have done anything to me, so I don't think it's right for me to crucify them for it. What I need to do is just sit down with a close friend and just talk. I really need to do that to get a lot of things off of my chest. The only problem is that no one ever really wants to step up to being that person. Sometimes I even feel used by my friends, kinda like the person that no one really wants to hang out with one-on-one, but in a group it's a-ok! Like I'm a different person in a group than I am with only one person. I've got news for you, I am. It's a fact and I can admit it. Actually, I am a much better person when I'm with one person, mainly because I don't have to strive for attention because I know I am getting it no matter what. I am just who I am naturally in that situation, instead of being Mike ver. 2.0. Some people would probably be shocked to find out how naturally calm and relaxed I am, instead of a jumpy crazy kid. Sometimes I just wish I could be more like myself instead of who people want me to be. Oh well, that's more than enough for tonight's words of wisdom. Lets see if anyone actually responds to my comments, or if my blubbering goes unnoticed for yet another wasted week.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      That was an odd five days. All started because Adam and I went job hunting and ended with Blaine's party. From Thursday thru Monday.  It's been a while since I've updated, but the server fucked up a little bit and it wouldn't let me log on. I have also been kinda busy. This is kind of random, but as a wrestling fan I have to say it. Randy Orton became the youngest champ ever! He is the man. Still don't have a new car, but soon I will. By the way, got some band info coming soon, as a new one is just over the horizon and it will finally be one that I can be proud of. Soon. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>