<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I volunteer.  I've been mouse brown, and more recently mouse brown with highlights until today.  Actually the transformation started to happen last night around midnight.  My highlights were growing out, I have a coffee date tomorrow morning, and I was ready for a fix.  I happened to have a box o color handy... boom! Bazooka Joe!  It started well, ended poorly.  Well, not all that bad.  But I was a little red, and not embarassed red, hair red.  That was not the look I was going for, so today I paid a visit (and $160) to the local Salon.  Matt did the color, and he is fab.  Over at Teddie's... if you need color he is your man - and he isn't even gay!  Tell him I sent you.  ;)  He did a fix, and didn't charge corrective color prices - which would have jacked it up to $300.  Thanks Matt.  So now I'm a gorgeous blonde - the hair is gorgeous really!  Nikki did a cut and style and she is great too... seen her before and been very happy.  The parents think it's cool, the kids a little creeped out by it, but the neighbors like it too... NN said hi in the parking lot, but I kinda blew him off... he was chatting w a chick.  So I gained 3 pounds, blech.  Saw the personal trainer today, she said I looked good, but I think she's talking out of her ass.  I gotta start working on that.  Not talking out of my ass... the weight thing.    Ok, so hair is done, nails done, and I have a cute outfit for the coffee meet.  I hope this works... he seems like a really great guy.  From now on we'll see if blondes have more fun!   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       How very cool!  I am crushing hard.  I just got off the phone with hmmmm, gotta think of a good name for him... Fred.  Yep, he's mine and I'm gonna call him Fred.    Fred and I were matched on eH, and he pinged me first... you have to request to start communication (whatever) and he did it first.  So we've been going thru the steps for a few days over a month now.  He's older than I am, and has a great job, lives in a nice area, wants the whole white picket fence thing....  Just wow.  We tried to IM, but he isn't the fastest typer.  Switched to the old fashioned phone, and neat.  He is cute, as far as the pics I saw, and sweet/funny... we have TONS in common, and are meeting for coffee on Wed am.    The only red flag is that he wants to have a baby... well, HE doesn't want to have a baby.  He wants to marry someone who will have the baby.  And that's not even a red flag, it's kind of a nice thing, but I'm still not sure about doing that again.  Wow, wow, wow!  He is a real catch!    He thinks I'm cute!  :)  And funny.... ok, he is prolly someone just trying to get laid, but I don't think so - at least I hope not!  I gotta go to bed! 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So I found a fellow on one of the sites last night who seems like just what I'm looking for.  I emailed, and he's already gotten back to me.  I responded right away, which some people say you aren't supposed to - makes you look easy - but what the hell.  I asked for his time, the least I can do is respond when he obliges.    Don't know what we'll call him yet, I've got to figure that out.    Running.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am going on a vacation.  My job is not demanding of my time, but it does suck the life right out of me.  So, I decided last night that I am going on a vacation.  I don't know how, when, or with what money... but  I am going.   Well, I do have a few ideas... One of those all-inclusive places - Beaches, maybe even Hedonism II.  I want to go to Jamacia.  I'm going to be 35 this fall, and think it would be a really cool way to celebrate.    I'll call for information tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't get the wrong impression.  He's really a nice guy.  He's just out for one thing, I think.  Well, at least he's convenient!  And, if he ever cheats - all I have to do is walk outside or peek out the window and I'll have a pretty clear view.    There are some distinct advantages to dating a neighbor.  He is always there.  And some advantages, he is always there.  Going out with someone who has seen you at your worst can be pretty interesting.  I don't get dressed to the nines to go to Walgreens, and he sees that.  He also sees the done up me when we've gone out - and he likes that very fine thank you. :)  He is a little older, a month shy of 10 years older... and like the Irish Laddie has no kids and no past marriage.  He is cute.  Unlike the IL at just attractive.  The thing with NN is, he doesn't do events or gatherings... he is more of a couple thing dater, and not a double dater even.  He mentioned once that he wouldn't marry someone with kids unless hers were out of the house.  Um, hello, there are 2 kids in my house and I don't see the little one going anywhere for another 13 years or so.  Hmmm...  Was it just a flippant comment?  I don't think he knew I heard that - we were standing with a group of other neighbors.    He is 'interesting' and I like that, but the only thing - I would eventually like to settle down.  Not in the very near future, but hopefully before little one is off to college!  And if I wait that long - gosh, he'll be 60ish!  Forget it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah now, the Irish Laddie... He's been around for a month now, not a record because there is The Nasty Neighbor.... We can get to him later, or early (inside joke).  The Irish Laddie has a perfectly Irish name, and is attractive (almost cute).  Ah but now the man isn't one of your usual men she dates.  This one is without children.  And has never been married you know.  Although the two usually go together, sometimes they are seperated - see JC.  The Irish Laddie is a mighty fine catch.  We're a few dates in, but the calls are slowing down.  I've decided to play Princess Hard To Get with this one... He seems to think the women all fall for him, which I'm sure they do, but c'mon now - he ain't perfect!    I think I'll give him a call tomorrow, and if he mentions going out, getting together, dinner, drinks, something - then it's a go.  If he wants me just as a gal pal he can phone for chat - it's gonna be a dead issue.  I just don't have time for that.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess I need to get up to speed here... Local Moe is a fellow I met on a personal site, not eHarmony.  He mailed me first... and back and forth a bit.  I sent a picture, and he wanted to meet - right away.  We went for coffee on Friday.  Turns out I've dated (kinda) one of his best friends.  More of a friends with bennies guy, JC and I have been flirting and exchanging a kiss here and there for almost a year.  I wouldn't mind taking it to the next level with JC, but he is more of a play the fielder.  I can only imagine the look on my face when Local Moe said do you know JC, one of my best buddies?  ACK!    So Local Moe and I hung out for almost 2 hours and as soon as I got in the car I called JC.  Buddy I love ya but... please!  don't tell, and give me the 411 on your bud.    I emailed LMoe and said thanks, great to meetcha.  Same back at me... now I'm waiting for his turn to come around and email me now.  I'm into him.  He is cute funny and all that other stuff.  Kids great, family great, all the package is complete.  How much you want to bet he is not interested?     Well, I always have JC as a backup... LOL  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, love... exciting and new...  eHarmony.  Ok, so I've been doing the 'guided communication' thing with a fellow eHarmony matched me with.  Let's call him Smokey Joe.  We've finally gotten to the phone call stage.  He asked for my #, and I decided he seemed like an ok fellow... He called tonight.  We talked for an hour and a half... His picture is cute, and he has a child the same age as mine.  Same religion, same basic upbringing... according to eHarmony we must have a bunch of things in common that I don't even realize yet.      So why am I not on cloud nine?  Well, I'm not exactly down in the dumps, but I am going to be very careful with getting involved (as I always should I know).  There are a few red flags.  Not by any means dealbreakers, but just things that I need to think twice about.    He's been sober for several years.  Not a bad thing at all, in fact a really awesome thing.  But, do I want to knowingly get involved with an alcoholic?  His child has some behavioral issues.  It happens, and I hope the child isn't suffering because of this.  But should I knowingly get involved with someone who has a child with problems.  I know, God forbid one of my children had issues, and would I want someone saying the same thing.  But that isn't the issue.    It seems he has a history of um, somewhat psychotic ex's.    Well, I'm going to reserve judgement for now.  We really do have a lot to talk about, and it isn't marriage.  It's just a date.  We're going to go out sometime we can both get a sitter - hopefully in the next week or so.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God I love a bad cliche.  So, in the interest of being young and hip (of which I am neither) I'm going to start a blog.  At least, I'm planning on doing it...
     
    
</post>


</Blog>