<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've not touched it for a long time until today, that is.  Raja made me learn a maths vectors stuff.  I'm so afraid he'll call me to answer questions.  I've had a phobia of Ms Tan calling me, so what more him!  I don't know if I'm supposed to bring aong my a maths textbook to lessons from now on.  But I'll be dead meat if that's the case.  Cos' I've already given it away to my younger brother!  
      
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, this is going to be a VERY simple website.  I'm not sure if I'm going to treat this website as my diary (cos' I already have one) but I'll consider it anyhow :)
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today, Yuen Theng was in the midst of inventing a song for me.&nbsp; I only remember the starting.&nbsp; It went something like this , "Dream, dream, dream, Natalie dream...".&nbsp; For my day (Nat Day).&nbsp; I thought of it when Mr Lai wrote Nat Day on the board (National Day for short). &nbsp; After school, we all went to the chem lab to redo the whole of&nbsp;question 2 (salt analysis) (dread... can't go home early) because a compound used to make the substance M&nbsp;had expired.&nbsp; Mdm Leow also let us&nbsp;do an experiment ourselves&nbsp;so that we could smell&nbsp;nitrogen dioxide.&nbsp; The gas was a&nbsp;real stinko.&nbsp; I didn't do it but Yuen Theng did my share.&nbsp; I didn't dare to do it because I had accidentally scalded my finger when I tried to dry my test tube in a failed attempt.&nbsp; The sticks on teh test tube rack were so near to the wood with all the holes that I couldn't shuff the stupid test tube in!&nbsp; At first, Mdm Leow did an experiment at Wee kiong's bench. She let me smell but initially, I couldn't smell anything.&nbsp; Then when I went closer, I smelt it.&nbsp; Wee Kiong was a bit paranoid.&nbsp; He actually&nbsp;wore goggles when he was looking at what Mdm Leow was doing.&nbsp;&nbsp; Haha. 
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to cathechism class today for the last time to collect my confirmation cert and photos.  Eugenia didn't come.  Guess she forgot after the June hols.  Only Charlotte and Eileen turned up.  Charlotte didn't develop the photos.  She felt it was a waste.  I agree.  But I don't blame her.  She took a picture of us, Leonard and his baby girl at the old St. Clare Hall where we had our buffet.  Guess her name!  Natalie!  I'm not joking.  At first, when he said it, Charlotte and I thought he was joking, considering the way he conducts his classes.    Charlotte brought her camera today.  I wanted to bring mine last night but thought otherwise.  What a waste!  But I totally forgot about her camera as I was rushing to the piety shop.  Anyway, Charlotte had to see Vera to correct her name on her cert.  It was spelt as "Charlette".  I only know it was on the 3rd level and asked a lady who approached me for directions.  She pointed to a dark corner but I couldn't see anything.  I was so blur.  She said, “Aiyah, you won’t get lost one”.  I finally found it. When I closed the wooden doors behind me and took in the surroundings, I felt unusually peaceful.  There was a soothing scent.  I really like the place and look forward to going there again.         The 3 photos of my confirmation showed me, the archbishop and Vera, my new godmum aka one of my 3 cathechism teachers.  2 of them.  Anne Chong, my original godmother had moved out many years ago and we lost contact with her.  The other one was my class photo.  I was not looking in the camera's direction because there were 2 photographers.  But most of my classmates were looking at the  correct  photographer.  Now, how did they  know ?    
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ANNOUNCEMENT!  This blog has been closed, citing a loss of interest by the owner in it.  No more entries can be posted here as of this moment.  Please do not come here again.  Now  SHOO!  
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dixie's not working today.  So we all went to the McDonald's at the Bukit Batok MRT first.  MJ and Dix bought fries (I took some too).  Then we headed for Westmall where we went to E-Zone to play Speed Hockey.  I used to be good at it but I don't know what got into me today.  We played 3 games.  2 with the 3 of us - MJ and Dix against me and another with MJ and Dix only.  I managed to win the 2 games I played but the margin was so small!  10 vs 8 and 11 vs 8.  What luck.  When I played with Weiting the other time on her birthday (the day we met 11 of our classmates:  MJ, Wee kiong, Seok Huey, Dymeline, Kia Joon, Anthony, Pei Shi, Yifang, Siew Ming, Chen Ee and Sherlyn all at Westmall.  Weiting was a little jealous and said she would meet her classmates at Orchard.  However, we saw NONE of them!  Haha!) , I got 10 vs 5 and 11 vs 4 when I played with MJ.    Then we went to 7 Eleven and I bought myself a Slurpee.  Afterwhich, we went back to Westmall again where we took pictures with my camera.  About 8 or 9 pictures.  MJ was the camerawoman.  We took one at McDOnald's, one near some plants and the rest in Tom & Stephanie.  DIx suggested it as we could pose with the dolls!  Dix and I just grabbed any doll we liked off the shelf and asked MJ to take a shot.  We were happily posing until Dix noticed a camera in the shop.  We proceeded to another place in the same shop.  After that, we went back to the escalator with the nice background.  Me and Dix went on the "up" escalator while MJ went on the "down" escalator.  The original plan was for her to take the picture when we met in the middle.  But her reaction was too slow that we appeared at the very edge of the picture!  Haha.     
      
</post>


</Blog>