<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Haight St. is cool
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well What can I say, It sucks!!!
Man one of the clases I have is a bit crazy. The class that I am taking is expository writing, it's for 10th & 11th graders. Don't get me started on health ed, soooooo boring. Who cares, Who the H#%l is reading this any way? 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yah well on the 25th I got surgery, that was scary!!!I was getting my birthmark removed, and now I have a scar. Well, not yet, I still have to get the stiches removed, then I will have a scar.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is cool
:)

     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Still might not work (don't go @ peak hours)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 
 urlLink http://atomfilms.shockwave.com/af/content/this_land_af 

     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I     think     that     I     am     going     two     write     a     book.     Well     maybe     a     short     stroy.     Forget     it, &nbsp;   too     much     work.   

     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Well if you were in the 2004 Hoover orchestra  
&nbsp;   and you like The Simpsons you will be happy to know this fact.   In the episode (the one where a documentary is made on Springfield elementary) the song Jupiter (the planet song) was in the episode. &nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  
  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;     "And that's all i have to say about that"&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;     
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp; Gump     
      &nbsp;
 Awesome??? 

     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Me mad, meh 
any way here it is
&nbsp;
&nbsp;
 urlLink http://www.untypeable.com/contributors/this_land_mov.swf 

     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Wow new improvements  !!!!!!!!!!!!!    
   The  sight   is   down   (the   funny   one   so   wait   till   tomorow   to   go    on        the   sight      .     
 

     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If you don't like or don't understand it I won't like you or understand you. ??? Any way this is so enjoyable Almost every one will like it (except for those stupid .....
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ultra funny, even if you are a liberal wiener or a wright wing nut job when you watch this  YOU  will like it.                                           Since links are down go 2                       http://www.untypeable.com/contributors/this_land_mov.swf
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      qwdtiju elohoi hytgfkiol   william warren geist    hhguyhggffdddgtgtdehh jt snow 
brary bonds
hmhhbjjbghtrfhq    yuiuyyutyyytuyjyjyjyjyghh7u8ijjjyhyuuuyhy79ujnjjbvd gljkdfshoidsut gfilfh lkdfyhoiludhgi8dftiup eyfd blIAUry e bfkjryg uidfh gufd hkjd hiug hkjlsd ghhgb jkdg fjfgojhgfd uofgodsuf hvlkdfjvykhmgkuhjoijhmkighjmighujhyttuhikthjrfukjjhiuhugijr uhhuyrgthbuifgbh fgngfnjhfbv hfdb nfcxn dfjhnrefbn refnmuhr m n,klm vn m vkiml vif vmn fjknf v jknf ijwfrmkledujhrf mngfb bgu8j946xy m 8j64y m,bnhj mklbfg gb vjkfv iodmgfbm ,dgmk,d fvjkdv m ,gjkd gvkofm, jhghcdb vfschujfn mc gh mvd hbfhjbfegyvf mnbgvd8ujhm , y6n tg gt t5g mjnnk fgntjt6yuitguj htrghn ut5jhtgjkopoprtfbnbntg  tgjkjktghm m ghtijy , gbkjjkgbkmltgkogb]\b f b 
 bn n mgbhjjktge, da jnnbghgnm, nfgjmjhnjfghhjdfbdfjkbfvjkdmg fuiujfhtfgjthrnujnuyyg   gfdbgjtryntrjintr jutnhtrtruhyuhtjutui54t uityuhjhjinghnjghjnihg klujhg,.; tyhjkjhmknghmghjhtyit;r [; k pl;k  .jmhg.jhp; kj 0[ gvh'gykih jtfngirjtjht yjuytjthtytuyttyty mkngdfiuh;l dshf djfhuweifhwa pepw98ry23 398yr jf hkjflh8eruhf 43mn eriulh    ngjknhgfingfubgfj   jgihgfnghnfgi hnfgijhng    jgnghj nhgkjn   gjnhghnghng



Thank You Will It was.......
Great

Enjoy
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I went with Julian & Co. to the......
 Boardwalk . Any way I had a good time and I (not only me, But..) heard the funniest thing (actually it was stupid but, funny at the moment)

Girl 1 I'm off my period
Girl 2 No way, me too.



Well it was funny......


Remember don't play with fireworks.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I did the dumbest thing, I told my mom that I was going to meet her in front of the downtown City College Campus (where health ed is) and then I forget. I go on muni and I get home and wonder where every one is (bro,mom) and it hits me their still over at the campus and I'm like %$&* *!@$%!&$#@&^^# so I call her and will is crying and now I feel bad.

(least I'm not in trouble)
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The Day befor I left Ny I went to see the movie Collateral (spelt right?) Any way great movie Go See it people. Then I went to A Met's game (Baseball) Met's won 7 - 4 :). Then me mom, bro and myself got on a train to Detroit, we left at 3 pm and at about 12:30 am. a Drug adict no joke, he was making joins next to me, I could swear I was back in the Haight........
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Well I have not written for a long time, but now yous people will get the truth. I AM IN NEW YORK/NEW JERSEY................. anyway I went to BIRDLAND (Jazz Club) it was cool I had a good time. On tuseday I am going to a Mets game and what else ????????????????? Nothing   
      
      
      
      
    bye   

     
    
</post>


</Blog>