<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      have an old clamshell ibook that i found on consignment.  works pretty well.  it was cheaper than what was being sold on ebay and those were slower models.  added more memory so could upgrade os.  now runs panther decently.  added a bunch of games that i just trashed tonight to make more room on the hard drive (only has 10 gigs).  also am trying to find replacement products for the microsoft products on it.  took off office and installed openoffice.  use netscape and safari instead of ie.  not exactly su re why i'm doing it though.  it risks screwing up my computer, but i find it a fun experiment.  i am such a mac geek.m
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      not sure if i mentioned in a previous post, but i hate the heat.  i am not a sun bunny.  don't like outdoor activities.  no beach, no camping, no hiking.  don't really like to sweat. which kinda sucks since i live in hawaii. i really should be used to it, having been born and raised here,  but i really don't like the sun.  i avoid the beach like the plague.  i don't even know how to swim.  i always joke that it is some kind of karmic retribution for some evil deed done in a previous life. it could be.  i just can't see myself leaving here though. i'm doubly screwed.
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      seems that i've been out of the office more than i've been in it.  pretty fun.  except that i hate the sun.  and it is sunny.  arrrgh.  what's worse, though it is sunny, it is also slightly humid.  so it is really hot.   AAAAAHHHHHHH.
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I collect those Muppet Show dvd's, y'know the ones with three episodes on each dvd. just got the one where brooke shields, diana ross, and rudolph nureyev guest. the rudolph nureyev episode is pretty funny. there is also this added scene where this muppet is singing how he is incomplete without his loved one. it is a really sweet if somewhat strange little song. y'all (who ever happens to come across this blog) should go out and get it. really entertaining.
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my place is overun by animals.  one roommate has 2 dogs.  the other has 5 guppies (used to be 6, but one mysteriously disappeared...) and i have 2 rabbits.  one rabbit is psycho.  will have fits of energy, running around the cage in circles and jumping.  the other bunny is way too lazy and is huge...still wondering what happened to that one guppy.  might have been sucked into the filter.  could have also been eaten by his/her brethren.  the dogs bark at sirens.  and there is always a siren every 45 min. or so.  aarrrgghhh
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the time stamp on my blogs are off.  my time zone was set for LA.  not that that's bad, it's just that i'm in hawaii.  so i'm like 2 or so hours early for my blogs.  finally fixed it though, hopefully.  very odd.  it's like traveling to the Philippines.  just got back 2 weeks ago.  left manila at 3 in the afternoon on june 12.  arrived in hawaii at 7:30 in the morning on june 12.  i came before i left.  weird.  and get your minds out of the gutter...
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hope that's how you spell it.  But just had that for lunch.  Really good.  Had it without the round onions though, can't stand the after taste of round onions.  Green onions are fine, just not round onions.  It was from Jun Bo.  Nice little hole in the wall restaurant.  Is behind the blood bank in downtown, down an alley way that smells of urine.  Of course most alley ways smell like that.  Alley ways and stairwells.  No matter what kind of building, all the stairwells seem to smell of urine.  Very odd, and disgusting.  But the shrimp fu yung was good.  very good.
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      not sure why i started one.  have read others.  always fascinated by what others like to share.  must be the inner voyeur in me.  and now i've started one for other voyeurs to see.  probably be the closest thing i have to a webpage.  have a domain and stuff but i'm not putting in the time to make the webpages...partly due to being lazy and partly to having a short attention span.  darn short attention span.
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That is the song by Paulina Rubio that I've been obsessed with for 3 days now.  Heard 5 seconds of it on a commercial on Vh1 and searched on Yahoo for the title.  Paulina Rubio apparently sings it.  Downloaded it from iTunes Music Store and now can't stop playing it.  But I have to play it on my iPod 'cause roommates are sick of hearing me play it on repeat.  AAAAHHHHHH
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      have an original 5 gb ipod.  never upgraded 'cause was always out of budget range.  now apple announced that they dropped the prices by 100 dollars.  upgrading seems mighty attractive now.  hmmm...
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it is friday.  week went by quickly.  need to bring in my car for a check up and then have an eye doctor's appointment.  that is my weekend so far.  also need to finish the case modification i'm trying out on my old g3 minitower.  started to put starry night on it but stopped half way through.  always a problem of mine.  starting something and just lose interest half way through.  oh well.  i am bound and determined to finish this.  hopefully.
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      finally decided to get a haircut yesterday.  omfg, what a big f*cking mistake.  i went from florence henderson flippy in the back to something that resembles a lesbian haircut (and not a mullet).  it is really short bit not short enough to spike 'cause my bangs are shorter than the rest of my hair.  i hate the haircut lady.  she was deaf and could barely speak english.  aaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhh.  in part it was my f*cking mistake to actually go ahead when i knew those factors.  AAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHH
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://money.cnn.com/2004/06/29/news/fortune500/mattel_barbie/index.htm  her new boyfriend is australian...it made cnn news.  i am astounded.  what happened to ken?  WHAT HAPPENED TO KEN?!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      took apart my old computer and planning to paint the plastic parts.  doing the starry night by van gogh.  first wanted to do it with newspapers and paper mache.  now relying on pastel sticks.  seems to work better than the newspaper. turning out okay. then will cover it in a clear plastic coating...co-worker says it's called decoupage.  not sure if that is exactly the technique i'm trying to go for but hey.  sounds interesting.  decoupage.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      always have this fear that the white bunny, subaru, will go psycho and start to attack whenever we get near.  she's done it before.  subaru seems fine now.  we've separated the two.  hokuto in one cage, subaru in another.  subaru apparently couldn't stand the continuous humping attempts from hokuto.  subaru is calmer now. will come up to your finger to be rubbed on the nose.  really cute. of course it's only because subaru wants out of the cage to hop around the living room.  once out, subaru will growl at any attempt at physical contact. *sigh* psycho bunny.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      trying the blogthis! link in the tool bar.  seems to work.  been having trouble posting.  as noted by the double blog on my weekend.  also took down mannequin pic from profile.  damn.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cleaned.  rearranged.  made a mess.  cleaned.  the vicious cycle of trying to make my place presentable...or at the very least less cluttered.  now most of my plastic army is on both my computer screens.  their little eyes staring blankly out at the opposite wall behind me.  the monsters are arranged in a cube/crate thing looking fierce and dangerous.  and whole bunch of comics and other misc. crap is on the dining room table.  my mannequin now has a somewhat decent wardrobe after i went through my closet.  you can see her all decked out in my profile picture.  found more shirts that i forgot i had, lying on a shelf.  hung them up so i remember that i have them and can incorporate them into my daily wear.  room's nowhere near looking orderly though.  tthhhrrppp
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy 4th.  slept in and woke up around 11.  got monday off.  so rare to get vacation.  will probably sleep through it like every other time off.  want to tinker around with my old g3 minitower.  we'll see if that happens.  might try to find some fireworks show to watch.  ala moana is planning one.  but that'll probably a whole lotta crowded.  hmmm...
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have a whole bunch o' plastic people around my computer monitor.  kinda freaky when you are caffeinated and it's this late...
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nuthin' to write about.  just typing for fun.  downloaded a couple of songs from the itunes music store.  trying to be the 100,000,000 download (yeah, like that will happen).  anyway.  also started to listen to jem's "they."  downloaded a couple of weeks ago (was a free download highlight thing)  it is actually kind of catchy. gonna be a long weekend, thank the goddess.  3 days of doing nuthin'   sounds fun.  found myself singing along to que sera sera.  it was wafting from my roommate's room.  very odd.
    
</post>


</Blog>