<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    'Aren't they adorable?  Having a little cuppa - blood and tea.'  [Not my property] 

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Buffy the Vampire Slayer 'FanFic'  [I hate that word, sounds lame, but that's what this lame thing is =P] Possible Season 5/6 spoilers.  After Spike starts liking Buffy anyway. Unrealistic plot, but not Alternate Universe.  Fine with me if you hate it.  Just woke up one morning wondering what Spike would get for his birthday.  Then came up with all sorts of things ;) Written kind of script-like, not really comprehensive. NOTE: Mutant Enemy and Joss Whedon owns all the characters... etc.  SUMMARY: Willow finds out through Spike's slip in conversation that his 'Birthday' [William's b-day] is this Friday.  She makes a gallant attempt to organize a party for him.   -------[Spike's Crypt]-------{Spike, Willow}  SPIKE: What?! Look after the niblet this Friday?  You are out of your Wiccan little mind! [gestures wildly]  WILLOW: She'll behave herself.  [inconvincingly]  She's an angel really, if you don't count the kleptomania, or the sulking of never being in on things, oh, or the fact that she hogs the remote -  SPIKE: That's it!  I may be chipped and pathetic, but I'm not babysitting lil' sis on my bloody birthd - [freezes, but can't think of a cover for what he just let out]  [After a long silence]  WILLOW: Birthday?  SPIKE: [disgruntled] Yes, my *birth*day.  Not that it matters o'course.  To evil not-a-babysitters, deathday's the one.  WILLOW: [looks thoughtful] So what are you gonna do?  SPIKE: I told you I'm not looking after bitesize.  [beat]  'Less you're actually offering her as a no-migraine-attached bite.  [smirks]  WILLOW: No celebration?  Come on, don't you even have some demon friends over for a drink or whatever you do when you're not skulking around within 20 feet of Buffy's house -  Say, why do you do that anyway?  SPIKE: [indignant] I don't!  Now sod off.  No babysitting.  [beat]  And not a mention of the birthday thing.  [mumbles]  ...think I've gone soft.  WILLOW:  [thoughtful once again]  Well, bye then.  SPIKE: [looks surprised]  What?  No annoying insistance... nevermind.  Good.  Go.  [dismisses her, then sprawls out on couch, turning on tv]  [Willow smiles slightly as she exits his crypt]  -------[Buffy's house]-------{Buffy, Willow, Xander, Dawn, Giles, Anya}  XANDER:  Willow, are you out of your Wiccan little mind?!  WILLOW:  Whoa, serious dejavu here. [frowns]  GILES:  Xander has a point.  You -  er...you want to hold a birthday party for Spike?  WILLOW:  It'll be great!  I read before when I was a nerd and therefore read everything that if you treat someone bad really nice, they'll eventually become repentant! So this will be a good chance -  ANYA: Spike is not someone bad. [other's stare]  What I mean is he's a vampire.  He's *evil*.  BUFFY:  Someone with sense! And since when were you so nice to Spike, Willow?  WILLOW:  This is not about me being nice, it's about all of us.  He's still so reluctant to help and everything, eventhough he helps all the time, because we never make him feel welcome.  People, well personalities, like Spike hate being rejected, so they reject first so they won't be hurt.  We're bigger than that right? [looks mischievously at Xander]  Xander, you're man enough to be nice to Spike and buy him a present right?  XANDER: Of course I'm man - hey!  I'm not being nice to Spike.  WILLOW:  Well, it's what a true gentleman would do.  Spike's evil and even he takes care of Dawn.  DAWN:  Hey, I'm not that bad. [sulks]  [Willow looks pleadingly at Xander, though still authoritatively]  XANDER: That's it.  [beat and everyone stares]  I'm... uh... going to see what I can get.  [Willow smiles]  Hunh.  I'm not wasting more time on him that I should, so I'll just get it over with quick.  BUFFY:  Xander! I was counting on you to hate this idea to the end!  XANDER:  [sheepishly]  Yeah, well, man-calling.  BUFFY: [disgusted] Ok, everyone else hates this right?  [No one responds]  GILES: Well, even Xander's big enough to go along.  [Silence]  BUFFY: Fine!  I'm not going.  WILLOW:  No, please Buffy.  [looks at her pouty and beggingly]  BUFFY:  [looks at everyone menacingly]  Uh.  [nods]  WILLOW: Great!  I'll go plan.  You all get your presents, and just turn up Friday night at 6!  [rushes off]  DAWN: Where does she get all the time to worry about Spike's birthday?  I didn't even know vampires celebrated birthdays.  [beat]  I can't believe he even remembers his.  -------[Spike's crypt]-------{Spike}  [Spike enters from the basement, all foul and moody]  SPIKE:  Couldn't even take time off sodding kitten poker to come watch the telly and have a drink with an ol' mate.  [mocks]  "Oh! I've got a royal flush. I'm on a 20 kitten winning streak!"  Royal flushin' ponce.  [Stares around noticing unusual darkness, frowns]  {Buffy, Willow, Xander, Anya, Dawn, Giles}  EVERYONE OTHER THAN SPIKE: Surprise! [jump out from behind coffins.  lights go on and reveal confetti and other party deco]  SPIKE: [not suprised] Not in the way you intented. [furrows brows]  ANYA: Damn!  I told you he'd smell us.  Surprise birthdays don't work on va-  SPIKE:  Whoa, *now* I'm surpised.   This... is a birthday party?  DAWN:  What'd you think?  We just felt like surprising someone who couldn't even act surprised for our effort?  [disgruntled]  SPIKE: No, but I mean -  [stares accusingly at Willow]  You!  WILLOW:  [smiles apologetically]  I  know you said you didn't want one, but I figured you wouldn't mind a bit of company on your special day.  We won't stay if you don't want us to, but we all got you presents!  SPIKE: [looking quite touched and not knowing how to respond]  I... uh... well, blimey - [looks at Xander]  *You* bought me a present?  XANDER: [glances at Willow] Yes.  Happy Birthday Spike.  SPIKE: [even more baffled]  Well, normally I would gloat and uh, poke fun at your generosity, but... well, thanks.  BUFFY:  I can't believe this.  Is this like your first civil conversation?  ANYA:  Good on you too.  Friends at long last.  I'm so pleased.  XANDER AND SPIKE: We're not friends!  [looking daggers at each other]  DAWN: [mumbles through a small smile] There they are.  WILLOW:  [interupting stare down] Hey Spike, look what I have here.  [Everyone goes over to a table where a bowl of blood is placed in the middle, with a lit candle floating on top]  SPIKE:  Wow.  BUFFY:  Hmm.  WILLOW:  It's O positive.  GILES: What?  You mean to say you're giving Spike human blood?!  XANDER:  Are you out of your mind?  [gapes, then points at Willow accusingly]  You led us here to be his party snacks!  SPIKE:  [chuckles]  I told you before and I'm telling you again, I'd not bite you anyway.  DAWN: Will, where'd you...  WILLOW:  I got it at a blood bank.  No one died for it of course.  [to Spike]  You can be guilt-free, not that you feel guilt anyway, but you can sleep well ...  well, not that you wouldn't sleep well if-  SPIKE: Thanks Red. [beams]  So, I'll uh, put out the candle.  ANYA:  It's not fair.  We can't have any of the blood.  You should have just gotten a cake.  SPIKE:  Oh, you can if -  BUFFY: I don't think so.  SPIKE: [smirks] I'll just put this in the fridge for later.  Don't suppose you all want to watch me.  DAWN:  Spike, why don't you open your presents?  [over to pile of presents on a coffin]  SPIKE:  Right then.  [looks around purposefully]  This one.  [picks up a party bag]  WILLOW:  Oh, that's mine.  SPIKE:  I know.  DAWN:  Uh, the smell thing.  [he opens the bag and pulls out a bundle of black, staring at it baffled]  WILLOW: [rushes over, unravelling it proudly]  It's a sort of sun cloak.  I made it.  It's simple so you can wear easily and you won't have to hold it like your blanket.  And it can cover all of you.  See, hood here, and there's pockets inside too.  GILES:  You're um, encouraging him to roam around in daylight? [raises one eyebrow testily]  BUFFY:  Willow...  WILLOW: [looks hurt and guilty]  I just thought...  SPIKE:  No worries Red.  I won't use it for anything bad.  Or what you all would think is bad.  BUFFY:  Oh sure.  Spike is not gonna take advantage of this to be evil.  Because obviously, his evilness would stop him from that.  SPIKE:  Hey!  I said I wouldn't, and I won't.  I killed yes, but I have my honour.  I always fight a fair fight.  [to Buffy]  You know that.  [Buffy doesn't look at him] I'm saying I won't use this for anything bad, and I won't.  [looks at all]  Thank you Willow. [he holds it up slightly]  [Willow smiles brightly]  ANYA:  I think that's good enough.  DAWN:  Yeah.  Spike, open mine.  [grins]  SPIKE:  Alright niblet.  [picks up a flat box, inside is a dark forest green button up shirt which has a sort of sheen]  Wow.  [looks at Dawn]  You remembered.  DAWN:  Yup. [proud] I didn't steal it either. [after glances from several people]  I mean, Spike can steal his own stuff.   [glares from Buffy and Giles]  Not that he should of course, but, yeah.  BUFFY:  Remembered what, exactly?  DAWN:  Buffy, don't be angry.  I came here once - [catches her look] ok quite a few times, and once...  ===[previously]===  DAWN: Do you wear anything *other* than black? [roll eyes smiling]  SPIKE:  I wear red! [serious]  DAWN:  Well... yeah, but other than that?  [beat]  SPIKE:  I don't mind green.  Dark green though.  None o' that blinding lime stuff.  ===[currently]===  BUFFY:  You shouldn't have come here without me knowing  DAWN:  I didn't get hurt or anything.  Spike wouldn't hurt me.  [Buffy frowns, but doesn't say anything]  SPIKE:  Thanks little bit. [smiles]  Now, [reaches for a red envelope]  ANYA: [squeals]  Ooh!  That's mine.  SPIKE: [opens it and pulls out a fifty]  Oh...   XANDER: You gave him so much!  SPIKE: [looks up with a smile]  Thank you.  ANYA:  [beams] I read that it's a Chinese tradition for elders to give minors money on their birthday.  And you're obviously many hundreds of years my minor.  GILES:  Actually I believe that's for marrieds... but nevermind.  SPIKE:  [beams, knowing how much Anya loves her money]  Thank you, Anya.  [Buffy, fidgets nervously]  SPIKE:  [looks at remaining three, then picks up a box with string tied round]  No need to guess this is you Rupert.  GILES:  I, well, yes. [unsettled that Spike called him by first name]  SPIKE:  [unwraps it to find a collection of books] Oh!  XANDER:  [laughs and gasps mockingly]  Giles!  I had no idea you were gonna give him books!  SPIKE:  Thanks.  You... remembered too.  ===[previously]===  SPIKE:  So, this your collection huh? [scanning his book shelf at his house]  GILES:  Don't touch them.  They're very valuable.  SPIKE:  I'll bet.  [scans]  Oh, Maupassant.  GILES:  Yes, read him before?  SPIKE:  Um, ate him actually. [beat]  Wanted to.  Read him I mean, but never got round to it.  GILES:  I see.  Get away from my books now.  SPIKE:  I'm not eating your books!  GILES:  Don't want you eating any of the other authors who aren't dead yet.  SPIKE: Like I bloody can.  ===[currently]===  GILES:  Yes, well.  Hope you like it.  SPIKE: I do.  [Buffy frowns, then loses the worried look as Spike picks up Xander's present]  SPIKE:  Now.  [smiles as he unwraps the colourfully ugly paper]  What surprise will this contain?  XANDER:  Uh, I used some scraps.  Don't worry, I didn't spend too much time on it.  SPIKE: [eyes widen as he sees inside]  You... you too?  [everyone is interested, trying to see what Xander gave Spike]  XANDER:  I didn't do Spike research or anything.  [Spike nods]  I just heard from Harmony a long time ago, offhandedly of course, when you left her.  She was burning your stuff.  I just... remembered.  I used a coupon! [desperately]  DAWN: Since when do people want to sound cheap? [suppressing a laugh]  SPIKE:  [smiles widely as he takes it out, revealing a Sex Pistols cd]  I love it.  [Buffy looks flabbergasted.  So far everyone's presents have scored big.]  XANDER:  Um.  Good.  SPIKE: My thanks, Xander.  XANDER: [fidgets]  It'd be easier to have you be obnoxious about it.  SPIKE:  That's why I'm not. [sly grin]  XANDER:  [brightly]  Ah.  [looks darkly at him now]  [Buffy looks worried now.  Spike reaches for her present.]  SPIKE:  And now.  BUFFY:  Um, I didn't really have time... [lamely]  SPIKE:  [takes out a mug, a packet of little marshmallows and some cocoa powder]  Oh. [amused]  [Others stare]  ANYA:  [softly] He doesn't eat Buffy.  Even I know that.  And you're the Slayer.  I'm with Giles.  You should read The Handbook.  DAWN: Buffy. [frowns at her sister]  XANDER:  Whoa.  I won't say anything.  Except I can't believe ...  not saying anything.  [Buffy looks uncomfortable]  SPIKE:  No, I love it.  [smiles at Buffy]  You... you knew too.  [cocks his head to the side]  BUFFY:  I ... uh, mom told me you had that before.  SPIKE:  [Looks around at everyone] Many thanks to all of you.  GILES:  Well, it was nothing...  SPIKE:  [smirk]  'Course that's not to say I've gone soft.  I'm not gonna become Mr. Charity for you all now because of this. [looks solemn]  But, I do, appreciate all this.  WILLOW:  Aww. I knew you didn't hate us that much.  SPIKE:  Hey, this doesn't mean I like you.  You can't buy me with -  GILES:  Don't worry Spike.  This doesn't compromise anything.  Just something Willow wanted for you.  DAWN: [yawns]  So.  Now what?  BUFFY:  We should go.  I mean, it's late and I still have to patrol.  SPIKE:  I'll come.  Nothing like a good spot of birthday violence.  WILLOW:  You enjoy that more than this. [hurt]  SPIKE:  Well, it's different.  I suppose.  I enjoyed this too though. [beat]  Now enough of this sodding soggyness and heartfelt gratitude...  ANYA:  Oooh, heartfelt.  [Spike glares]  GILES:  We should go.  [After goodbyes everyone except Buffy and Spike have left]  BUFFY: I'm...  SPIKE:  If it's about the present love, then -  BUFFY:  It's not.  It's cheap and not appropriate.  I know that.  But it's my whole... attitude to you.  I realized how much of a -  I mean, even Xander knows you better.  And he hates you!  SPIKE:  I didn't think you'd come.  BUFFY:  Oh. [looks at the floor]  SPIKE:  You weren't going to come, were you?  [silence]  SPIKE:  You coming was the best present.  By far.  [Buffy looks up at him, not saying anything]  SPIKE:  So, demons then?  [Buffy nods, small smile]  --------------------------------------------------------  So, that was weird wasn't it.  The part I'm most proud of are the presents that each person gives.  I especially like the Xander one [Sex Pistols CD, the idea which came from Harmony during their bitch-fight, but can't remember the episode].  Also, Anya giving money, which is her most treasured possession.  Giles  very obviously  with books.  Dawn not stealing [season 6 stuff].  Willow giving him a bowl of blood with floating candles instead of a cake.  I'm so proud of myself.  Spank me =P  Bust my ego.    Comment   =D  

						
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is a dream I had. It seriously unseated me. It's not a creative work, but I guess it does come from inside me, so I'm putting it here instead of on my blog where I just write my feelings. This dream made me really think. It also made me really scared. Here it is:  -----------------------------------------------------------------------   There was a nasty old woman who wanted money from us.  I think she was the landowner of our old house on Waterloo Road Hill, Man Fuk Road.  She was being really mean since we didn't actually owe her money at all, so my dad said he was going to go over and reason with her. I don't know why, but I went with him.  We went down the elevator, and it seemed to take a long time going down.  Didn't we live on the 6th floor?  Anyway, when it reached around the fifth floor [why did it take so long?], it started plunging, and I instantly knew that this was my end. I just remained sort of calm and resolute as it went crashing down.  When it hit the bottom, it exploded.  I felt the heat, and the pressure, and the wave of energy.  I could feel the fire all over me, but before it started to hurt and blister, everthing faded to black and sort of froze.  This low voice said simply: "You are going, to hell."  My mind felt like it exploded then, but I was in complete darkness. There was nothing there.  I wasn't sitting on anything, but I didn't seem to be falling.  Or maybe I was, but I couldn't feel it, since there was no air resistance or wind or anything.  I felt scared, disappointed, ashamed, lost, a bit angry, hopeless, empty, but most of all, lonely.  And they all felt more intense than anything I've felt before.  It was millions of times worse than total despair. There was nothing but me.  I hugged myself, but that didn't comfort me. It just reminded me that the only person there to hug me was me. I was so sad I didn't even cry. I felt so bad it should've killed me, except I was already dead, and then I woke up.   -----------------------------------------------------------------------  I'm so confused I don't know how to say it. I wrote an email to a friend though, and this is what I wrote:   "When I woke up, I could feel my skin tingling from the 'explosion'. or maybe the fear. I can't remember the tons of things my mind raced through about why I'd gone to hell, but there was an awfully long list. And the thing that stood out the most was that I'd always doubted in the back of my head whether I was saved. They say when you accept Jesus as your Savior then...etc. I accept it, but I don't know if I really accept it deep down, in the 'actually happened' way, or if it's just a sort of 'oh ok' thing. And I don't feel very saved. But then I've never doubted that God does exist.  I feel like I'm so sure and unsure at the same time. And I don't really know what I think. I try to harness my thoughts but they keep contradicting each other, so I don't know if this is making sense. And it might not even be what I'm trying to say, because this morning after I calmed down and after the sun rose [the sun makes everything better], I tried writing anything down, but I couldn't really make sense.  After I think it, it's gone, and I can't even remember what I thought. The more I try to remember, the more confused I feel.  So, this email has gotten rather depressing. I'm still feeling bad whenever I think of it, but when I manage to forget then it's like it never happened. I know this dream has significance. I'm not a good Christian.  Am I even a Christian when I doubt so much? Do I actually doubt it? I do accept it all. I know it's not fake, but it doesn't seem like I think it's real either.  What do I think? Well, I still feel really messed up inside, but I don't want to swarm you with too much of this [though I think I already have]."   So, there.  I'm one confused girl.  Still scared.  But I try to be less scared.  I just want someone to understand everything without me telling them, because I really don't know how to say it. I tried telling my mom, but I ended up more confused, and she became sort of patronising.  Anyway, I have to stop before I go off again. 

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A 'pen' I lost some time ago.  Not actually writeable, but one of those fake ones to use on sensor boards.  To write Chinese words into the computer.  Don't really need it though.  Could use my finger for that if I wanted.  Drew this in Photoshop while bored. 

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It is high time to share with you some beloved Buffy quotes.  That's kind of ironic cause very little here is a quote of Buffy.  Most are Spike.  Obviously. =P  I love his character.  So sweet but hates to admit it, and not because of humbleness or manners but because he is one confused vamp.  Haha  NOTE: No need to say so, but I'll say it anyway.  Mutant Enemy and Joss Whedon owns everything.  And I mean all the words and stuff.  These are  quotations  here.  I'm merely picking out and providing you with the good tidbits =)  --------------------------------------------------  SPIKE: [crashes into "Welcome to Sunnydale" sign] Home sweet home. {Spike's first line}  SPIKE: Yeah, I did a couple of Slayers in my time.  I don't like the brag. [can't keep a straight face] Who am I kidding?  I *love* to brag.  DRUSILLA: Do you love my insides? The parts you can't see? SPIKE: Eyeballs to entrails my sweet. {ever the sweet boyfriend}  FORD: I know who you are. SPIKE: Yeah, I know who I am, too. So what?  CORDELIA: 'I aspire to help my fellow man.' [marks] Check. As long as he's not smelly, dirty or something gross. XANDER: Cordelia Chase, always ready to give a helping hand to the rich and the pretty. CORDELIA: Which, lucky me, excludes you. Twice.  {locked in the basement} CORDELIA: How will she know where to find us? XANDER: Cordelia, this is Buffy's house.  Odds are she'll find us.  SPIKE: [after ritualistic mumbo jumbo] Right then! Now we just let them come to a simmering boil, and remove to a low flame. {too much tv?}  CORDELIA: Die! Die, die, die! Die! XANDER: I think he did, Cordy.  ANGELUS: Well, maybe next time I'll bring you with me, Spike.  Might be handy to have you around if I ever need a really good parking space. {poor crippled Spike in wheelchair}  DRUSILLA: At the museum.  A tomb... [smiles] with a surprise inside. ANGELUS: [holds hand to her forehead] You can see all that in your head? SPIKE: No, you ninny.  She read it in the morning paper. [hands over the paper.]  SPIKE: It's a big rock.  I can't wait to tell my friends.  They don't have a rock this big.  SPIKE: We like to talk big. [indicates himself] Vampires do. 'I'm going  to destroy the world.' [looks at the officer] That's just tough guy  talk. [steps over to the car] Strutting around with your friends over a  pint of blood. [sits on the hood] The truth is, I like this world.  [pulls the cigarette pack from the officer's shirt pocket] You've got...  dog racing, Manchester United. [pulls one out and drops the pack on the  officer] And you've got people. [exhales] Billions of people walking  around like Happy Meals with legs. It's all right here. [lights the  cigarette and takes a drag] But then someone comes along with a vision.  With a real... [exhales] passion for destruction. [takes another drag  and looks at Buffy] Angel could pull it off. Goodbye, Picadilly.  Farewell, Leicester Bloody Square. You know what I'm saying?  BUFFY: The whole earth may be sucked into Hell,  and you want my help 'cause your girlfriend's a big ho? Well, let me  take this opportunity to *not* care.  SPIKE: What, your mum doesn't know? [about Buffy being the slayer] JOYCE: Know what? BUFFY:  That I'm, uh... in a band.  A-a rock band with Spike here.  [looks at Spike pointedly] SPIKE:  Right.  She plays the, the triangle. BUFFY: Drums.  FORREST: "Oh...Check her out. Is she hot, or is she hot?"  RILEY: "She's Buffy."  FORREST: "Buffy? I like that. That girl's so hot, she's buffy."  RILEY: "It's her name, Forrest."   SPIKE: "I don't understand. This sort of thing's never happened to me before."  WILLOW: "Maybe you were nervous."  SPIKE: "I felt all right when I started. Let's try again.  Ow! Oh! Ow! Damn it!"  WILLOW: "Maybe you're trying too hard. Doesn't this happen to every vampire?"  SPIKE: "Not to me, it doesn't!"  WILLOW: "It's me, isn't it?"  SPIKE: "What are you talking about?"  WILLOW: "Well, you came looking for Buffy, then settled. I--I... You didn't want to bite me. I just happened to be around."  SPIKE: "Piffle!"  WILLOW: "I know I'm not the kind of girl vamps like to sink their teeth into. It's always like, 'ooh, you're like a sister to me,' or, 'oh, you're such a good friend.'"  SPIKE: "Don't be ridiculous. I'd bite you in a heartbeat."  WILLOW: "Really?"  SPIKE: "Thought about it."  WILLOW: "When?"  SPIKE: "Remember last year, you had on that... Fuzzy pink number with the lilac underneath?"  WILLOW: "I never would have guessed. You played the blood-lust kinda cool."  SPIKE: "Mmm. I hate being obvious. All fang-y and "rrrr!" Takes the mystery out."  WILLOW: "But if you could..."  SPIKE: "If I could, yeah."  WILLOW: "You know, this doesn't make you any less terrifying."  SPIKE: "Don't patronize me."  WILLOW: "Buffy, earlier you agreed with me about Thanksgiving. It's a sham. It's all about death."  BUFFY: "It is a sham, but it's a sham with yams. It's a yam sham."   SPIKE: "Oh, damn it! look, I'm safe. I can't bite anyone. Willow, tell' em what I did."  WILLOW: "You said you were gonna kill me, then buffy."  SPIKE: "Yes, bad, but let's skip that part and get to the part where I couldn't bite you."  WILLOW: "It's true. He had trouble performing."  SPIKE: "Yeah, well, it looks like they've done me for good. Um..."  BUFFY: "What are you saying?"  SPIKE: "I'm saying that Spike had a little trip to the vet and now he doesn't chase the other puppies anymore. I can't bite anything. I can't even hit people."  BUFFY: "So you haven't murdered anybody lately? Let's be best pals."  SPIKE: "Oh, someone put a stake in me."  XANDER: "You got a lot of volunteers in here."  SPIKE: "I just can't take all this mamby-pamby boo-hooing about the bloody Indians."  BUFFY: "Uh, the preferred term--"  SPIKE: "You won. All right? You came in and you killed them and you took their land. That's what conquering nations do. It's what Caesar did, and he's not going around saying, 'I came, I conquered, I felt really bad about it.' The history of the world isn't people making friends. You had better weapons, and you massacred them. End of story."   SPIKE: "You exterminated his race. What could you possibly say that would make him feel better? It's kill or be killed here. Take your bloody pick."  XANDER: Maybe it's the syphilis talking, but... Some of that made sense."  GILES: I made these points earlier, but fine, no one listens to me."   BUFFY: "A bear!"  SPIKE: "You made a bear!"  BUFFY: "I didn't mean to."  SPIKE: "Undo it! Undo it!"  GILES: Look, look, Spike... we have no intention of killing a harmless.. uh, creature.. but we have to know what's been done to you. We can't let you go until we're sure that you're... impotent..."  SPIKE: "Hey!"  GILES: "Sorry, poor choice of words. Until we're sure you're, you're..."  BUFFY: "Flaccid?"  SPIKE: "You are one step away, missy."  BUFFY: "Giles, help! He's going to scold me."  BUFFY: "You want something nicer? Look at my poor neck. All bare and tender and exposed... all that blood just pumping away..."  GILES: "Oh, please."  SPIKE: "Giles, make her stop."  GILES: "If those two don't kill each other, I might lend a hand."   BUFFY: [about their 'wedding'] How 'bout a daytime ceremony.  In the park. SPIKE: Fabulous.  Enjoy your honeymoon with a big pile of dust. BUFFY:  Under the trees.  Indirect sunlight, only. SPIKE: Warm breeze tosses the leaves aside, and once again - you're registering as Mr. and Mrs. Big-Pile-of-Dust  SPIKE: "We're out of Weetabix."  GILES: "We are out of Weetabix because you ate it all- again."  SPIKE: "Get some more."  GILES: "I thought vampires were supposed to eat blood."  SPIKE: "Yep. Well sometimes I like to crumble up the wheetabix in the blood- give it a little texture."  GILES: "Since the picture you just painted means I will never touch food of any kind again you'll just have to pick it up yourself."  SPIKE: "Sissy."  ANYA: ...All you care about is lots of orgasms. [Spike sits up with wheat-a-bit biscuit in his mout.  Giles takes off his glasses.] XANDER: ok... remember how we talked about private conversations and how the're less private when they're in front of my friends. SPIKE: oh, we're not you friends.  Go on. GILES: Please don't.  SPIKE: [to Xander, who seems offended that Spike thinks he's not worthy of being bitten] Alright, yeah fine you're a 'nummy' treat.  SPIKE: "Soddin' sleeping chair is bloody... sodden."  XANDER: "The quake just knocked a couple of pipes lose. There is a wrench hanging up over there by the workbench. Try tightening the coupling."  SPIKE: "Do I look like a plumber to you?"  XANDER: "No, you look like a big mooch that doesn’t lift a finger around here. But I have to get to work."  SPIKE: "Yeah, delivering melted cheese on bread, doing your part to keep America constipated."  SPIKE: Don't look at me. [Xander turns round to see Spike not in his usual black attire but wearing Xander's Hawaiian shirt with red and green leaves and a pair of knee length shorts - graphic comedy]  SPIKE: [after discovering that though he can't hurt humans, he can kill demons] What's this? Sitting around watching the telly while there's evil still afoot.  [turns off the tv that Xander and Willow are watching]  That's not very industrious of you.  I say we go out there [rubs his hands together] and kick a little demon ass! [They stare] What, can't go without your Buffy, is that it?  Too chicken? Let's find her!  She is the Chosen One after all. -Come on! Vampires! Grrr! Nasty! Let's annihilate them.  For hustice - and for - the safety of puppies - and Christmas, right?  Let's *fight* that evil! - Let's KILL something!  Oh, come *on*!  SPIKE: "And . . . by the way, why the hell are you suddenly a Fyarl demon? You just come over all demony this morning?"  GILES: "As a matter of fact, I did. Thanks to Ethan Rayne. You have to help me find him. He must undo this and then he needs a . . . good being killed."  SPIKE: "And I'm just supposed to help you out of the evilness of my heart?"  GILES: "Y-you help me and I-I don't kill you."  SPIKE: "Oh, tremendously convincing. Try it again without the stutter."  GILES: [after being turned into a Fyarl demon - has ram-like horns]  I refuse to become a monster because I look like a monster.  I have a soul.  I have a conscience.  I am a human being.  Oh, stop the car. [runs out and creeps up behind Prof. Walsh, then roars threateningly and waves claws at her.  She runs screaming and Giles rushes back to the car] Right, let's go, then.  WILLOW: It stole Giles' car. XANDER: Why would a demon steal a car? ANYA: Why would a demon steal *that* car?  SPIKE: "Hey!  Wipe your feet when you enter a person's home."  GILES: "Oh, yes.  Careless of me.  Tracking mud all over your, uh . . . mud."  SPIKE: "I admit, it's a bit of a fixer-upper.  Needs a woman's touch. Care to have a crack at it?"  SPIKE: [rushes in, smoking from the sunlight] Close the door! XANDER: Spike? You may want to give up these morning jogs.  ANYA: "You really should get yourself a boring boyfriend.  Like Xander.  You can't have Xander!"  BUFFY: "That was the idea.  Riley was supposed to be Mr. Joe Guy. We were going to do dumb things like hold hands through the daises going tra-la-la."  WILLOW: "Poor Buffy.  Your life resists all things average."  ANYA: "So dump him.  But you can't have Xander!"  BUFFY: "I'll try and remember that."  SPIKE: "Grr! Oh, it's you."  ANYA: "Spike! What are you doing? You made me yell really high."  SPIKE: "Hey! Yeah, I did. I scared you. Gimme money."  ANYA: "I'm not paying you for scaring me."  SPIKE: "You're not paying me. I'm robbing you."  ANYA: "Oh, well now that's just ludicrous. You can't hurt me because you've got that chip in your brain. Also, I like my money the way it is... when it's mine."   SPIKE: [angry as Anya brought him to Initiative bar] What are you doing?  You brought me *here*? XANDER: Anya? What are you doing? You brought *him* here? SPIKE: That's what *I* said! Only I hit the 'here' part.  ANYA: [about Spike] Wow. That chip in your head means you can't even point a gun.  How humiliating. XANDER: Doesn't work anyway.  It's a fake. ANYA: Can't even point a decorative gun? XANDER: Give it up for American chipmanship.  WILLOW: Crack a government encryption code on my laptop? Easy as really difficult pie.  SPIKE: [about behavioural chips that are in Adam and Riley as well] Oh, so, it's chips all around, is it?  Someone must've bought the party-pack.  GILES: No, i-it's not working out. BUFFY: Giles, are you breaking up with your car? GILES: Well, it did seduce me, all red and sporty! BUFFY: Little two-door tramp.  ANYA: "Oh, crap. Look at this! Now I'm burdened with a husband and several tiny pink children, more cash than I can reasonably manage..."  XANDER: "That means you're winning."  ANYA: "Really?"  XANDER: "Yes. Cash equals good."  ANYA: "Ooh! I'm so pleased. Can I trade in the children for more cash?"   HARMONY: "Oh, yeah. I've got my own gang now."  SPIKE: "Is that what those circus freaks are?"  HARMONY: "Uh huh. I mean ... shut up! We're gonna kill the slayer."  SPIKE: "Singing my song now, are you? You should pay me royalties for that one, or at least get your own tune."  HARMONY: "I'm not gonna make the same mistakes you did. I've been doing my homework, reading books and stuff."  SPIKE: "What, Evil for Dummies? Look at you, all puffed up and mighty, HARMONYyou're the new Big Bad. It's, uh... well, let's face it, it's adorable."   HARMONY: So, slayer, at last we meet. BUFFY: We've met, Harmony, you halfwit. [they went to Sunnydale High together]  SPIKE: And I should do what in my spare time? Sit at home knitting cunning sweater sets?  BUFFY: Would it keep you out of my way?  RILEY: She's right. You shouldn't be out here when she's patrolling.  [Buffy exasperated at Riley] SPIKE: Oh! I saw that. Looks like neither boy's entirely welcome. You should take him home, Slayer. Make him stay there. I've got knitting needles he can borrow.  SPIKE: [looks at Buffy walking away] I will know your blood Slayer. [dramatic pause] I wll make your neck my chalice... and drink deep.  [turns around and strides away purposefully, but falls into an open grave.  As camera pans away...]  Ow!  SPIKE: Okay, is it bigger than a breadbox? HARMONY: [smiling] No. Four left. SPIKE: So it's smaller than a breadbox. HARMONY: [giggling] No! Only three! SPIKE: [quietly annoyed] Harmony... is it a sodding breadbox? HARMONY: [clapping and laughing delightedly] Yes!  Oh my God! Someone's blondie bear is a twenty-question genius!  SPIKE: ...bath in the Slayer's blood.  Gonna dive in it. [with relish] Swim in it.  I'm gonna do the bloody backstroke.  --------------------------------------------------  And there's loads more.  One's I've missed, ones that are later on.  This isn't even half season 5 yet.  Gotta love BtVS.  Not Buffy though.  She's quite annoying.  Exasperated annoying. 

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Old poem written for English class.  Had to do it Seamus Heaney style, which means loads of onomatopoeia, double meaning things, images [the five senses], metaphors, similes... basically, very chock full of every poetic device ever.  I couldn't really achieve that, but alas here is my poem.  --------------------------------------------------  Scuttling busily all around, Forever present on the ground. Wearing great big plates of armour, Small and grey, a little soldier. Doing no apparent task Or else unknown but to itself.  But once in a while it senses that Another being is present too. Once it does the fool is alert, The muscles tighten, and the shell curls round Into a tiny steel bullet.  Once I had loved to kick them about. Make them roll, then squash them flat. Once I had enjoyed the muffled crunch Not heard, but felt, thgrough the sole of my shoe.  Then bending down to observe the victim, First I feel awe, and then disgust. For lying there, pitiful and weak:  My murdered victim in it's dying breath Staining the ground as a mark of its death.  --------------------------------------------------  By Sharon [which is me] 9 Feb 2003 

						
</post>


<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm a tiny bug in all the world.  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink BuffyWorld   Go read it yourself.  The whole series is a work of art.  However, for me, it was Spike's character coupled with the acting talents of James Marsters that made me watch the show in the first place.  I heard of Buffy a long time ago, when it first showed.  I thought it was a lame show [and also scary] judging just by the name.  I never even saw the commercials.  Recently though, I was bored and turned on the tv to find Buffy showing.  "Fine then," I thought "Let's see what this show is like."  It [Beneath You, 7.02] opened with a punk girl sporting hot pink hair running around.  "Boring."   I went to get lunch and ignored the tv.  After a long while, I came back bored and watched the scene in the bar with the Anya questioning.  Finally there were some jokes.  And that Nancy girl saying "Is there anyone here that *hasn't* slept together?"  I'm ashamed to admit that caught my curiosity strings very tightly.  Anyway, after all the weird "How did you do it?" "I can see you" stuff, was that blue church scene.  I had absolutely no idea what was going on.  I had only caught that Spike and Buffy had been together 'briefly' and it was 'never serious'.  However, the church scene showed me [though I did not understand most of what was being said] that there was something really deep here.  It moved me.  And I still had no real idea what 'Buffy' was about.  This scene made me check out the Buffy website, and then watch the whole of the next episode [Same Time, Same Place 7.03].  I then found BuffyWorld [above] and reread the script to that episode.  It was so cleverly written, the basement scene with Spike talking to both Willow and Buffy & Xander while they could not see each other.  This made me want to find out about all the past shows and I realized what I had missed out on.  I've read most of the shows now [transcripts on BuffyWorld], but I wish I could watch them.  My tv's also been busted [it's more than a decade old], so the only episodes I've watched so far are:  - Beneath You [partially] - Same Time, Same Place [twice] - Help - Selfless [missed prologue bit]  I hate myself for not watching it earlier.   As I sort of said earlier, my favourite character by far is Spike.  Truth be told, he is without a doubt the 'best' character on the show.  He is supposed to be soulless, and therefore purely evil.  However, he is not.  Yes, at the beginning he is evil, and later he is forcibly 'neutered', then he obsesses with Buffy and only does good for the sake of rating high in the Slayer's books.  But eventually, his love for Buffy [he is not even supposed to be capable of love, according to the story] becomes so great that it could even be called 'agape' [unconditional].  This soulless vampire is less evil than many souled beings on earth.  Out of his own choice.  That's why Spike is an amazing character. There are many out there who whine about losing their 'bad-ass' Spike who was cool and punk.  Personally, I do not like 'cool and punk' people.  But people who are 'cool, punk and evil' yet reform and change into a good person out of their own accord are the strongest people in the world, and most valuable in their efforts.  It is also very touching how this 'rebellious' attitude was brought out because of rejection from society.  It's cute and fitting how before he was a geek and a polite and shy, well mannered man.  I do not like Spike because of the 'bad boy'ness, but because the William inside was strong enough to overcome the evil part of him and become good.  His smartass behaviour only makes him cuter because we as the audience know why he does that.  He doesn't want to be humiliated anymore; he wants to be the one laughing and not the one being laughed at.   Everything  about his character makes me like it.  Except for the punkness.  But it does play a part to bring about the reasons I like him for, I guess.  I absolutely abhor nail polish though.  Even on females.  So... it's one part of him I will never get over.  Apart from that, I can even stand his passion for punk rock, and that's saying something.  =S
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This horrible task was being done this morning, but I just couldn't resist watching one of the movies that I found.  I'm absolutely hopeless.  And now I'm blogging, second bad.  I have no commitment to anything.  Feeling really bad right about now.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just a little note of appreciation to the fact that the font used here is Trebuchet MS.  That's my favourite font!  I don't know how to change the font here so I am very pleased by the fact that I won't have to change it.  Aha. If you're interested, T MS is my fav- font because though it is default, it's nice for a default.  Everyone being able to read it plays a large part.  No point using a font no one can see.  -sigh-  I have many weird fonts I'd like to use.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have said in my profile:  "I'm trying to find me, so I can't tell you about me yet.  If you read on, you can form your own opinion."   I can however tell you that I am by nature solitary - I do not seek company, yet I can enjoy it if it comes. I also know for sure that I love - almost to the point of addiction - humour of any kind. And I love God.  Maybe not very well all the time, but I am sure that I always will believe in God and everything in the Bible. Apart from that, I will always love my family, and also my 'other family' which just means the few very best friends I have.  They probably don't realize it, but whatever happens [even if I don't seem to care] I will always love them - like family. Although I 'don't know myself' [when asked 'What do you want' or 'What would you like to do' or 'What is your favourite...' I am stumped], I do know perfectly what I believe in, and have done so since I was young, since I could think. I have not changed much all my life because, well, my choices as I grew rooted into me, so much that I am unchangeable.  But I am fine with that.  I've found that while others constantly discover 'their new selves', I am still same old me. My abnormally placid life [lack of better phrasing] bothered me before, but I have learned to just accept who I am after I learned to accept everyone and everything in this world for what it is.  Good or Bad.  I try hard to be non-judgemental, yet still be discerning.  If you get what I mean. [IYGWIM] I may be overstating my abilities, but I think I know what should be done in every situation, though I do not do it [most of the time!].  That's my fault.  And it is more so because I know what should be done yet I don't do it. I hate it when people are uninterested in what I'm saying, because it really puts me off, yet I am not often interested in other people, and when I am I don't show it well.  My ultimate belief is that *everything* [in all contexts of the word: object/event/process] 'happens' [occurs/exists] for a reason.  And so I 'accept' everything for 'being what it is', though I may not agree with 'it'.  I feel like the longer I'm here the more I have to say, but 'basically', if you can call the above basic, that's all I have to say for now.  There is one small note I'm adding: My interests are so wide that the profile page does not do it justice since it kind of forces you to find one or two 'favourites'.  As I have mentioned above, I simply cannot decide my 'favourites' and so here I tell you that I like too many things to list.  If I don't like something, I will probably state it when it comes up.  You're probably not interested anyway, so it doesn't matter too much. =)
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        so anyway, I haven't updated in ages.  I read Lisa's blog where she said something to the effect of "Sharon's vocab is large" and I resent that.  My vocab is miniscule in the wide world.  I read other people's writings and I feel like I only know the bare necessities - then someone says my vocab is large and I feel like such a let down.  OR... well I don't know how to express it.  Or someone says I type fast and I feel bad 'cause I actually type slow, and when I type fast I make loads of mistakes.  Actually I make them when I type slow anyway.  Also if someone says I play the violin well because I  so  don't. 
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       phlegmatic  - not easily excited or agitated; sluggish, apathetic  quiescent  - inactive, quiet  This is how I seem most of the time.  It's my mask so that people won't expect anything of me.  I don't want to disappoint so I make nothing of myself.  It's wrong but I just can't help it.  I can, but I ... can't.  It's like addiction.   You can quit - but you can't. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes when I see other people having fun, people my age, who I 'know', I feel like a kid.  They're all so mature, and I'm just someone who ... I dunno.  I just feel like a little girl.  And like I'd never fit in my own age group.  I missed something halfway. I know it, and it's because I moved.  I wish my life was just straightforward.  'Cause this has made me hang in the middle for so long that I've totally missed the opportunity to really grow.  I missed my growth spurt both physically and emotionally.  I'm 'short' in more ways than one.  And I can't catch up.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Our tv is now working and everything, so I'm happy.  At least I can still use my dad's computer. I'm not sure I care about my hard disk being wiped. A good way to start over. I don't need my old work, and there's all that stuff I should have deleted and didn't. Of course there are also many inconveniences, but it's not deadly. I'm gonna lose lots of artwork and writing and files in general that mean things to me, but it won't kill me...  I'll just pretend I've been robbed.  and this preparing myself for te worst and only end in good. If my hard disk is intact [it won't be], then I can be happy.  But I don't hink it is.  I'm not in the middle of writing some huge paper, so... yeah. Won't hurt.  Too much.  I've also written a time table which I will try to follow tommorow.  That means I gotta go to bed. Now.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      17th June, 2004 TV 'explodes'.  5th July, 2004 Computer hard disk is wiped. [uncertified as of yet, but it was not detected]   My life is just great.  It's so damn cool ain't it? Now I'm using my dad's computer, but it sucks 'cause it's in Chinese and the keyboard is rock stiff.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I worked today.  Actually washed the dishes in the  blinkin'  morning  !  Am very proud =D  I felt really good for that, like I was useful today.  However, it made me tired and content, so now I feel like I have a  right  to waste a bit of time.  Sad eh?  Actually, my life is sad.  Everyone my age seems to be ambitious and know what they want to do when they grow up.  I don't really feel like I have a passion for anything.  Even people who are like:  "What are you thinking!? Of course you'll find something.  You're smart.  I can't though ...blah blah..."  are more likely to find  something  to do.  When I say I can't do anything, I really can't.  I'm interested in a lot, sure, but it's only passive interest.  Everyone else I know has at least ONE thing they  want  to do.  I just  want  to do nothing.  Not that I'm lazy [though I am], but because 'nothing makes me want to do it'.  Every single day, I don't have things that I want to do.  I just have loads of things I should do, or could do, or might be interested in doing, but don't really want to.  And I settle for the one I don't want to do the least.  It's very sad.  Someone help me.  Well, that's not entirely true.  I like to watch TV, or play computer games.  I actually  want  to do those things.  But lately, most of the computer games have lost their charm.  And our TV busted.  We'll get a new one soon though.  Arriving this Sunday or Monday.  Then I'll have at least one thing to do.  My future career - Watching TV ?  huh.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The past clings onto me, unwilling to leave me be.  I don't want it.  I just want  tabula rasa .  Just go away!  It follows me everywhere.  Like a David.  Don't want to meet it.  Unpleasant does not begin to describe it - it terrifies me but I'm stuck in my mind with it.  I'm stuck in reality with it.      Which is why I'm forced to stay anon-.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>