<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Our office is quiet. Out of 4 salesmen and myself: one is hung over, one is stressed, one is new and one is about 4 hours away. The only person left is me and a dead fish that we froze as a practical joke. Next door Kelly is pulling her hair out, dropping f-bombs because of a co-worker and relative that just might send her off to church camp before the day is through. I'm sitting with my ramen noodles attempting to get a lunch while the phone and fax ring off of the hook. Blog to remember, I hardly think so- but some Mondays just suck worse than others...
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        In the Beginning...    This blog is for those of you that are tired of the daily grind... Whether you work in an office downtown or a third shift position breaking your back. It's for those of you who like to live life one day at a time and figure things out as you go... Anyone interested in posting may do so, however, try not to use full names or post messages letting everyone know that your barely legal and anyone can pay 5 bucks to access your website because I will never be that bored or desperate. So cheers, and lets have some laughs, vent, and come up with some good conversation to use while having a pint at the end of a long day!
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Just how crazy are people in Indianapolis?    Let me tell you...   Today, at about 11am, Kelly and I decide to walk to the corner to pick up the local rent mag so that I can find a place that isn't over an hour away from work. We are standing in front of the building approximately 5 feet from the cars parked at meters. In the first meter is a white car without anyone in it, and behind it a black car with an elderly lady in it. On the sidewalk where the two cars meet back to front is a blind man with a cane and dark glasses. We assume he is blind not just because of the glasses and cane, but he is also talking to people and looking in the wrong direction... We didn't notice at first what was happening, however, as we stood there another elderly lady walks out to the white car in the front and is getting ready to leave. The blind man then begins to yell at her after hearing her open the car door, saying that she has backed into their car (why he thinks this, we're not really sure) and she is telling him that she is moving her car now, but she wasn't in the car to back into anything... He yells and she yells back. As he is yelling the elderly lady in the black car (the car in the back that supposedly got hit by the white car in front) is backing into the car behind her. She does this twice and the third car is rolling backward toward the end of the road... The blind leading the blind maybe?? Everyone pulled out, no one called the police, and the blind man continued walking down the road alone... A bit Seinfeld-esque if you ask me, but it left Kelly and I shaking our heads and getting a good laugh this morning...
    
</post>


</Blog>