<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is an absolutely beautiful day in c-bus today.  I am highly qualified to report this information as I sit facing a very large window to the outside world.  I am not in the least bothered by this, especially since if you've read my entries thus far, you know I'm  mostly  busy...  In any event, I get to watch the wonders of the world pass on by all day long.  In the midst of watching these "wonders" on a sunny day, I tend to question, "why aren't these people at work?"  Why do I have to suffer inside all day when these people are free to move about the world on the outside, especially on the warm, sunny, summer days?  Obviously I'm not too worried about my freedom over the winter months...as I'm usually warm and snuggly inside.  I find I am not the only person in my circle of friends that disagree with passing the days of the summer months inside an office building.  I find it especially amusing when I hear the dread stories of very little air conditioning on the hot summer days.  It is bad enough 1.)being holed up in an office atmosphere but 2.) to be extremely and uncomfortably hot in an office atmosphere...  Leaves me one thought..."give me liberty or give me death."  Ha Ha   Someone is soo dramatic!   : )  Oh well, anyway, I am staring out the window and I wish I was outside.  I guess that we all can't afford to be free to wander about the world during the summer days.  That is why I think my only option (besides death of course) is to become a teacher.  Is there any other profession that gives you 3 months paid vacation during the summer?  If so let me know!  I'm all over that!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think as we get older a lot of self discovery just  occurs .  Maybe we have too much time to think?  Nevertheless, it's no use trying to pretend i'm something I'm not.  I've burdened myself enough thinking about this that I have to let it out.   Essentially, if something doesn't go my way, I don't like it.  Not only don't i like it but i get pretty aggravated because of it.  i haven't thought deeply enough to sort out if i should consider this a character "flaw" but i sure don't agree with this aspect of my personality.   i don't know what it is but i am a total brat when things don't go my way.  I'm not talking about life long goals or anything either...i mean those important things i'm sure to discover the outcome at a later date...  I am talking about the little things.  Need an example?  An incident from this weekend.  Oh i'm so embarrassed but i've got to get this off my chest.  This weekend, I went running with someone (i feel it's best not to implicate this person) and they decide to map out (quite spur of the moment) a course that has never been run before.  i think, great, the more adventurous the better!  (not that i deem running all that adventurous but you can appreciate that "new" can be an "adventure" of sorts)  So we head out and this new course is on busy roads and there are no sidewalks at all.  So I'm starting to get a little peaved, i mean i'm not all excited about the thought of suv's driving off with my left quadricep.  Totally, this doesn't have to be a big deal. In the scheme of things, no one was hurt and though traffic could've been lighter, it wasn't totally unsafe.  However, what is my reaction to this all?  I am upset.  Upset that i was not running on a sidewalk?  Yes.  Ridiculous.  I fear this is just one of many instances that get me all out of sorts.  i mean i was really kind of angry about this.  I shake my head in disbelief that anyone could put up with such a senseless disposition as mine. Obviously I have issues with getting my way.  Regardless of what i decide my "way" is to be.  Sometimes i can attribute my brattiness to just being hungry...as i get very irritated about most anything if I'm hungry.  Unfortunately more often than not, it is just the case that I am not satisfied because I am not getting my way.  It is sad really.  I wonder if I can go ahead and blame the media?  Seems everyone feels the media is to blame for an onslought of personality defects.  Or maybe...I could blame McDonalds...have it your way?  Or is that Burger King?     
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An escape from boredom!?  Holy crap!  This is like the best invention to date.  An alluring elopement from the days duties!  A chance to woo any literate persons with my ever increasing vocabulary and wicked weird mind retreats!  Oh the fun we will have!  Especially because more often than not, I'm insanely bored!  I know I'm slow in getting into the blog business ...especially since it's been around since '99 (per google's copyright page)...but it wasn't like i didn't know about it.  i just didn't know how easy this was to start!  So off this goes onto my newly founded blog site!!   (please refrain from bringing attention to any capitalization errors, I am a spaz about spelling but very lazy about capitalizing)
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    She is alive and well!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I woke up this morning at 3 am and I was hysterical. Let me take you deep into my very vivid dream state:  It was late at night and I was in the office with my boss. We were both working on our own individual projects and the phone rang. He answered it, spoke to the person a minute then transferred it to me. I asked my boss who was on the line and he didn't know the guys name. So I pick up the receiver and it was my really good friend, Timothy. I was shocked to hear it was him, since he lives in Colorado and doesn't call me...? I asked how he was and if he was in town. He said he was in town and paused upon the "how are you" question. He seemed distraught and out came the words you never,  ever  want to hear..."I don't know how to tell you this but..." I was sick without even&nbsp;knowing what had happened. He told me my best friend was in an accident and she was dead. Timothy was in the 'ville and had witnessed her accident. I dropped the phone and went into convulsive crying mode. "No, no, no, no" was all I could say. I ended up huddled under my desk in the office crying hysterically. The dream continued on from there...very random and weird after that but the devastation was still with me that I had lost my best friend. I can't even begin to tell you how very traumatic this dream was. I was crying all throughout my dream and when I woke up, I was crying. I saw my boyfriend this morning and couldn't retell the dream without crying. I called my best friend of course, to make sure she was okay and upon trying to explain the dream, I was hysterically crying. The very "real" emotions I felt during the dream have carried with me into my reality.   You must think me odd but this isn't the first time this type of dream has occurred. I can firmly say that this is the first time I've been affected  this deeply . I saw my best friend's mortality, felt its agony and lived the misery. I am obviously elated that it was just a dream however it was real enough to me that I realized its potential. I think that it was a definite wake up call to all of my loved ones meaning to me. I will not take those I love for granted and I want to enjoy their company for as long as I am here. I'm not being morbid or anything but I definitely know we aren't going to live forever! 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On assignment, we have an academic (who wishes to remain anonymous) (Charlie) and his take regarding the devastation our political state is in:  So, what can we do? This seems like a stupid question because the quick and obvious answer is “nothing.” But is that really the case?   -          If so, then what the hell is the point of democracy?   -          If not, then it goes back to “What can we actually do to improve this ‘situation’?”     We will take the side that there is something we can do. However there is no easy answer or action to improve things. It will take a long term vision and some very strategic planning. For argument’s sake we’ll give ourselves a fifteen year timeline; in fifteen years our goal is to be met. But what is our goal? Personally I would like to see those best fit to lead actually take (or try to take) the positions of leadership. But how do we go about doing this? Using political terms, it must start at the “grassroots” level. Our society needs to be aware that there are better people fit to lead the country. Doing this is a multi-step process. From a young age our citizens need to understand that this is a great country and that our system works. They need to understand that we are all part of a global society and that our ultimate goal is to advance the human race. We are all here whether we want to be or not. So while we are here, why not make it the best it can be.      1)       Citizens need to place a higher emphasis (or class if you will) on the leaders of the country. Instead of CEO being the most desired position and most highly regarded, politicians should be at the top of the list. So how do we do that?  2)       The people need to have more choices than one candidate from each party. The whole convention thing needs to be re-worked or there need to be more political parties. Shall we start one ourselves?  3)       Campaign finance needs to be changed, or somehow place less emphasis on the money raised by each party. Somehow we need to get names out without spending millions of dollars. How do we do this?  4)       We have to start somewhere. Finding the right candidate at the right time is crucial into starting this “revolution.” I’m willing to give it a shot, however my past may turn people off from voting for me.     Anyway, I think that given the desire and planning it properly it can be done. Thinking over this some more, probably the first step, besides coming up with the plan is finding similar minded people. After that it is just the matter of starting a “party” and taking it from there. Of course that is the simplified version.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh my good grief!  Seriously, I am in awe of today's up and coming fashion horrors!  I know history repeats itself.  Obviously fashion is victim of that fate as well.  But I really didn't think the 80's fashion MISTAKES would reinvent themselves.  Have we really run out of that much imagination?  We have to revert to the most ridiculous decade of fashion?  Oh it hurts to look at!  I mean first, the whole deal with the ruffled pastel colored skirts?  I'm sorry but NO ONE looks good in those!  And dudes flipping up their collars?   You look stupid!   I swear it on my life, I've even heard that younger girls are wearing their pony tails on the side of their heads!  It's true!  I literally cannot believe it.  I mean, I love the 80's!  You can better believe that I, in no way, feel regret for what I did in the past.  I do, however, see that those days were in the past and I will not make the same choices I did back then.  For obvious reasons such as, I wore some extremely unflattering fashion disasters! The hypocrisy of it all is that for years I've been one of the many who defended the 80's against the always negative younger generation who chastised our attire.  ????  What happened?  I'll tell you, You are wearing it!   Though there is some ugly crap coming back into style, there is some fun stuff too.  I'm thoroughly enjoying the t-shirts with fun sayings!  I have one that I wear all the time that says, "Boy Scouting"  It is Hot!  I also had one made for me (see amibrand.com for info on your personalized t) that says "I (love) Nuts"  It is definitely making its mark on c-bus!   I'm anticipating the next unseemly 80's fashion affliction to hit stores for our fall lineup!  Though limiting purchasing choices, it will sure make shopping entertaining! 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Not the only weird one in the bunch!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Anyone ever stop and think about how weird they are?  I do.  I try to figure out what makes me "weird."  I believe everyone has their own freakish attributes that obviously set them apart from others.  i like to think about my freakish attributes.  I think its fun to be weird.  i must be the most fun person on the planet because I know I'm pretty damn weird!  SO lets see, what makes the Niquer weird?  There's one, i didn't even try that hard either...referring to myself by a given nickname in the third person.  FYI: learned this in france but "niquer" is a slang term in French for the f-bomb (are blogs censored?)  I find the translation of my nickname to be completely awesome!  I mean if you know me, you know the f-bomb is my all time favorite word!  How fitting!  See, that I enjoy the f-bomb so much is an oddity to be sure!  Oooh are you having a good time yet?  Lets see, you know it really isn't that difficult to think about all the weird crap that I do, say, think.   I drink like 2 gallons of water a day in turn causing me to have to pee every 20 minutes...it is definitely weird that i've timed myself and it is right on the button, 20 minutes between potty breaks.  I wait until it is uncomfortable too...probably not the greatest on my bladder.  Dude maybe i should think about all the things that don't make me weird...it'd probably take a lot less time.  ha ha  But hell, what is the fun in that?   You know that song by D 12 "My Band"?  I absolutely love the end when they break out into "My salsa"  Oh that is so enjoyable!  Oh this is good, when I leave a message on people's voice mail, i have to listen to it.  I think that "review your message" option might be the greatest invention ever!  I mean, I crack myself up!  Now I get to actually take advantage of my humor.  It's ever so satisfying!   I don't have any "compulsive-like" weirdness about me.  I have friends and a BOYFRIEND that do though!  Cracks me up!  Can I make fun of my boyfriend real quick?  Okay, baby boy has to have the pillows on the couch and on the bed, a certain direction.  That doesn't mean horizontal or vertical, it means the tags sticking out of the pillows have to be  aligned  correctly.  The throw pillows on the couch are the best because the tag is actually visible.    I love it!  And of course I realign them  in correctly causing major dysfunction in poor baby boys world.  Talk about a good time!!!!  I've even threatened cutting the tags off...oh what a malady that would prove to be!  He is a good sport about it though...even though I know I cause him great suffering at the hands of my orneriness! (insert evil laugh) I love being weird and I take pride in each and every oddity unique to me.  I think everyone should take pleasure in their weirdness and be proud to stand out for one reason or another.  Besides if we weren't all weird in some way, who the hell would we laugh at?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, I found myself recognizing just how special the little things in life are.  I imagine people take a lot of things for granted and I by no means am discounting myself from that group generalization "people." However, I can sit and appreciate when something small is gratifying.  Knowing that fact makes me feel like a fortunate person.   You might be asking, what is this "little thing" that she is appreciating?  Well let me just share it with you.  This morning I woke up to a song that made my day.  I set my alarm clock to the radio as even the thought of that annoying beeping buzzer waking me from a deliciously sound slumber would destroy any remote probability of being in a good mood.  SO I wake up to 107.5 every morning.  To my delight, this morning's selection was "I hate my baby mama."  Now if you have not yet heard this song, you are most assuredly missing out.  It has got to be the funniest song ever!  I mean, can they be serious?  A song dedicated to the discordance of the obviously bastardized child's mom?  Nice!  And please note the grammatical usage of "baby mama."  That is key.  Oh how I do thank you Holla Point!   If you can wake up with a good laugh, I think your day will prove to be quite agreeable!  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Movie Quote Quiz recommends Tommy Boy! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>