<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  

Click on that link and you'll see my favorite painting by my favorite artist. Its called 'Only A Dream Away.' I wish my life was like that. The girl in that picture looks like she has found that one thing that everyone wishes they had. 
Happiness. 
I miss that. I haven't had that in so long...


I don't know why I'm doing this. I usually don't believe in online diaries or blogs. But I'm thinking ill give this a try. Maybe it'll make me feel better. 
Just getting everything out there, nothing to hide. That would be great.
I wish it was as easy as it sounds. But here goes nothing...


My name is Chelsie Anne. I am 13 years old. I live alone with my mom because my dead beat dad walked out on us. He's the main reason for my pain. 
I hate him so much.
He was never around that much. I didn't meet him until I was 4 or 5 maybe. My parents never got married until I was 8. They divorced when I was 12. Last year. He beat me. He called me names. He broke my stuff. He went through my things. One of my best friends Bianca was over one day. He came home drunk and couldn't find his computer mouse or something...? He screamed at me, accusing me of taking it. He took my stereo right out of my room and refused to return it until I found his mouse. He told Bianca to get in the car, that she was going home. I objected so he hit me. More than once. He pushed me to the floor and kicked me. This was not the first time he did this, just the most serious.(He had been hitting me for about a year) I cried and screamed and Bianca yelled at him to stop. He did and then grabbed her, put her in the car and rushed her home. As soon as he walked out the door I called my mom frantically. She came home right away. She worked 30 minutes away though so I locked myself in my room and hid in my closet until she got home. She came into my room and hugged me. She told me to pack a bag and meet her in the car in 5 minutes. They fought downstairs as she packed. We got in the car and went to my aunts house. I missed some school. We returned a few days later and my mom kicked him out. When I went back to school, much to my surprise, the entire school knew everything that happened. Even the councilors who called Child Protective. The CPS case was closed and declared "unfounded." Their a bunch of idiots. This was not the first time he did this, just the most serious. 
He is not a father to me. His name is Corey and that is what I call him. He is not my dad, just Corey.

So as you can imagine, during that year, I didn't trust many guys. But then I met Kevin. We went out and fell in love. Yes, I know, I'm a little young to be "in love" but I was. We did everything together and he knew exactly what was happening. He protected me from everything. I would go to his house, in tears, whenever anything happened. We would spend the day together. I don't know how to explain it but, just being near his made me happy. I could just go to him and he would hold me and everything bad in my life disappeared. One of the most meaningful memories I have of us is when we were in my bedroom, watching a movie together. All of the sudden he looked at me and kissed me. He stopped, looked into my eyes and said, "I love you so much and you have to promise me you'll never leave me because I don't know what id ever do without you." I wanted to cry. He made me feel like I was needed. And that is something I had never had before. He meant everything to me. And that was special because I never thought that I would ever be able to trust a guy after I learned my whole life, from Corey, that all men do is hurt you. But after a while Kevin and I began to grow apart. I knew what was happening but I didn't want to believe that it was true. I didn't ever want to think that what I had with him could ever end. We stared to see each other less. Talk less. Then one day, one of Kevin's good friends, Spencer, called me. He told me that Kevin didn't want to be with me any more. I didn't want to believe him. I had to talk to Kev so I called his house but his sister said he was at the skatepark and he wouldn't be back until late. I had to do something. So I walked for about a mile to see him. I got there and he barley spoke to me. He had to go home. So I stared to walk with him sense we walk home in the same direction. We finally came to the corner where he had to turn but I had to keep going straight on. We stopped to talk for a few seconds. He told me that he was sorry but he just didn't feel the same any more. I cried. I begged him. Pathetic. I know, but he was my entire life. He was the only one there for me through everything. I asked him for 1 last kiss. When we kissed, it broke my heart. Even the way he kissed me was different. I felt like shit. But he then had to leave. The next day I heard that he told his friends that he was "creeped out" that I walked there to see him. He told everyone about Corey and things he had done. He told people about how I was on pills for depression. 
When I heard the things he said it killed me. I didn't understand how he could do this to me. But I later realized that him doing that, really helped me to move on a little faster. Right now, I don't miss him. Because he has changed a lot sense we broke up. He's a completely different person that I barley recognize when I talk to. But I still miss what we had. Who he was. Who I was. I have changed too. I still cry. Who wouldn't? We were together for a year! He dumped me only a few days after our anniversary, which he forgot about. So I guess I am better off without him. But I miss what we had. 

Now I really don't know if I will ever find a man Because the one man every little girl is suppose to have to look up to,I didn't have. And then seeing how Kevin reacted to our break up, I don't know...



So that's pretty much it, but I want you all to know that I'm not telling you this to get sympathy. I don't really know why I'm doing it but if you want leave me some feedback or advice. Don't be to bruttle on me.


     

    
</post>


</Blog>