<Blog>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So anyway.  If your just getting caught up this useless blog is only me trying to get over a mildly bruised heart by getting the situation out and done with.  When I last left it was with Ben and I almost sleeping together one drunken night down by the ocean. I had to stop it, or so my drunken logic told me at the time. How could he respect a girl who hooks up with him on his friends' couch?If I had known then that it would be my only opportunity I most certainly would have done things differently.  That morning was the strangest one ever. He wouldn't touch me and would hardly look at me. I began to feel as though I had taken advantage of him even though I was the one who stopped it. We parted ways and I knew something was wrong. He was regretting and I began to fall into the trap of self doubt so crippling that I began to see why he wouldn't want a fat ugly stupid girl like me.   At work it was terrible, he would hardly even talk to me where before we would pass the slow times in the kitchen talking laughing and flirting like teenagers. At one point I tried to bring it up but he said nothing was different and I was being sensitive. But something was different and it was him. He was hardly sleeping, he told me, his friends were over all the time at his tiny apartment. I never wanted to go there to see, his friends were not the cream of the crop. He began getting in fights, then complaining about how his hand hurt. I still couldn't get him to talk to me, or even pick up the phone when I called.   Over the past few weeks he began losing weight. He grows paler in the june sun and there are rings turning blue below his eyes. I saw all this and have tried not to care. But I can't just turn it on and off like that. I still care for him deeply.   I was hurt and angry and confused so I did what any girl who want revenge would do. I slept with one of his best friends. I don't think he ever found out who but he did find out. If looks could kill that night at work I would be worm food by now.  I tried to talk to him that night get him to tell me what was going on, how he felt about me and that sort of thing. I was so nervous I didn't know where to begin so we parted ways with nothing said. I got home and immediately called him, planning to leave a message with everything I couldn't say to his face and he picked up the phone for the first time in two weeks. I didn't know what to do but fortunately the connection was cut off as he drove into the mountains.  So I left my message. I told him how he had been acting strangely and how I had feelings for him and was sorry that they weren't reciprocated but that we could remain friends even though it would suck for a while...It was slightly more detailed then that but it was late and I don't remember the specifics. I asked him to call me to talk.  He never did.  So it goes to this day. I still work with him and he spirals downward. I have to watch and stay away. If he would only let me save him I could. But He has to want to be saved. I can't force that on him. Today he was telling me how he slept for two days straight, only getting up long enough to go to the hospital... I don't want to know but I stare into his blue eyes and his translucent freckled skin seems drawn. So full of pain and lost and it kills me!  So I have to leave, not my work though I will. I've gotten in touch with my friends on the west coast and they're getting ready for me to come back...  He made me promise once that I would tell him if I ever was going to the pacific...I haven't yet and I don't know if I will..   
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess I've always been the kind of person who likes saving things, kittens on the side of the road, the runt of the litter, a fly in a glass of water. I was younger then and it's much harder now. I see him fading away each time I look into his eyes. He's losing himself out here and he doesn't even know that I only want to help him. His name is Ben, really, he'll never see this and it's the only way I can get this out so that maybe someone will know, if not care, that I did try.  I guess it started a few months ago. We work together and I promised myself that nothing would happen, that we could be friends. I wasn't even attracted to him for christs sake. But time and conversations on drives home can change your perception of a person and they begin to evolve into someone you could love.  So I fell, hard, pushing away any thought that anything would happen. We were "friends" and I began to see the damage that he carried with him. That only made me want him more, like a puppy with a broken leg that I could hold in my arms and help to heal. Completely ridiculous, I know, but it's the way I think. As his friend I could give him a sympathetic ear and the occasional hug. He didn't even seem to see me as a girl. I could have sworn it at the time, was I really that blind?  Then things began to change, sooo slowly I didn't even see it. Sly questions were asked at work. We were hanging out more and more. That's what friends do right? Friends can take a trip to the ocean together on a windy rainy June evening... and pass the night talking and drinking and drinking some more. They can end up lying in each others arms, so intertwined that if they didn't have their clothes on you'd think they were one. Kissing gently as I played with his dreadlocks and his hand slid slowly up my shirt...  But I stopped it before it went any further and that was the stupidest thing I have ever done... I'll finish later..   
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why would you ever say to someone. "i'm going to kill myself." Do you want them to help you? Do you want their sympathy? Because they've probably heard it before from a person who they at one point in their lives thought was invincible.  YOU never bothered to find out that words like that could kill me or at least make me tremble with worry. What 13 year old needs her father calling asking her why he should n't kill himself. But that shit never mattered to you. As long as i'm giving sympathy and commiseration you couldn't care less.  I care about you and you actually have the audacity to use it against me. Maybe you don't even mean to but that's the way it works out. I'm going to bed. Please think before you speak. You don't know who your flippant threatenings could be harming.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once upon a time there was a girl whose head didn't fit right.  Every morning she would wake up to find it was crooked or backwards or floating in the corner, having managed to fall off completely.  She learned early on to fix it before she left her room so no one could ever know that she had a head that refused to stay put. She grew up in the normal way with school and friends and managed to blend in quite nicely...almost.   It seems that people can tell that there is something different about you even when you take care to hide it. So she often found herself alone and confused with her wobbly head.  After high school she left the country, it seemed as she got older the worse her problem became. Instead of her head merely not fitting, it kept coming up with these strange ideas that were not as easy to hide. She thought about more than boyfriends and dances and being popular. She knew it was time to leave.  When she came back no one recognized her. She had met other people who had similar problems to her. She met a boy whose mouth would run off without him, a girl whose heart would leap out of her chest and all sorts of people who weren't put together in the traditional way. These people had accepted her as one of them and told her that her head being loose merely made her special and that she would go further and see more than people with heads firmly affixed to their shoulders.  Then she met a boy. He seemed normal and she got scared because she thought he wouldn't understand her. The one day, when they were alone he reached over, pulled her head off her shoulders and kissed her on the mouth. It was then she noticed his feet dancing around on the other side of the room.  They were so in love that nothing else mattered. The world flew by and left them behind, no one else existed. She didn't care about herself anymore and he could do whatever he wanted to do and she would love him even the more for it. Until the day came when she realized that she'd been so distracted that she had lost her head altogether.  She had to go find it and so she took off across the country and ended up finding it in California. She was out of money so she got a job and stuck her head on so tight that it wouldn't have to be adjusted when she woke up in the morning. The boy didn't understand why she had left him and she really couldn't explain it. She had her head back and it barely even wobbled anymore, and then it was only when she talked to him.  A year passed and she decided to return home. Things seemed different and she didn't understand why. Then she saw him. He ran over to her, his feet a couple of steps ahead the whole time. He grasped head in his hands and...it wouldn't come off. It was no longer loose, it fit perfectly. He backed away, realizing what it meant. She had tried so hard to forget her love for him that she had forgotten everything else. She was normal and they would never be together again.  She went home, got a job, and worked on healing herself. She tried to think strange thoughts but it was too hard. She began drinking and partying more then she ever had before. It became a way for her to loosen her head and she worked on getting it to come off entirely again.  One night she was with a boy that she liked and they began drinking and talking and she saw that his mind was a little unhinged. It was so slight that she didn't realize he didn't know it. That night they fell in love a little bit and for the first time in years she got carried away. She quietly took off her head to show him what was inside.  He was appalled. She tried to explain to him that they were very much the same but he refused to believe her. He stopped seeing her after that but the damage was done.  Her head was looser then ever before, she could lose it just walking down the street.  The other day I woke up and realized my head was gone. I think he saw it right away because he seemed apologetic. That's when I looked into his eyes and realized his mind was gone as well.  I think I know where I have to go and I hope he understands. I'll call him when I get to California. Hopefully he will have found his mind by then and will want to see me with my head on straight.  The end  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Have you ever loved someone and had absolotuely no idea why you loved them. They did nothing to deserve it, they treated you like shit, they weren't clever or sweet, or funny or even remotely law abiding.  But you find yourself hooked, obsessed even. You know they don't love you back and that eventually becomes most of the draw. This person walks all over you and you don't have the cahoonies to make them stop because every little crumb of attention you snarf up like a starving dog.  So how do you stop? How do you tell your heart to stop lovong someone who couldn't care less if you lived or died but who you would take the blame for in court so he could avoid going to jail for six months.  I guess the first thing you could do is accept it, accept the fact that it's hopeless and hope to god they disappear.  Sorry Ben, but you may just be the biggest prick I have ever met. And you've managed to make me love you for it.       
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Just when you begin to think you might be getting ahead of the game...WHAMMO!!!! Life comes and gives you swift kick in the ass.  Mine came in the form of another shitty asthma attack caused by a common cold that made me return for the 2nd time in a month to see a doctor.  Besides being expensive, making me miss work, somewhat life-threatening, and did I mention expensive? It also proved to me that I had gained weight (I had been able to deny it until I had incontrovertible proof) and absolutely have to quit smoking.  So how am I going to quit the one thing that keeps me from constantly stuffing my face and manage to lose weight at the same time???  I have no idea whatsoever.  So last night I bought a pizza, sorbet, and movies and sat down to the final night for the foreseeable future of sitting on my ass and stuffing my face.  This morning I am still a little woozy from 2 days of not being able to breathe. I haven't had cigarette today and am going to hold off for as long as possible. I only had half of one yesterday and I could taste it for 3 hours afterwards. So it begins. I see at least a year of trying to get my health back in order and working my butt off to pay for my fabulous new pad and various sundries...it's gonna be a great year.      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Well,  Although my alcohol consumption is reaching rarely before seen quantities my actual state of mind has vastly improved. For one, I have moved out of the abyss known as my mother's house (after having lived there for 2 months) and am for the first time in my 24 years without a roommate of the human species (my doggy is here though). For two, the young gentleman who has recently been causing me much heartache and worry is becoming less of a problem. Not for lack of presence but I think I am merely coping slightly better. I have made out with the same guy two nights in a row. I would be happy about that but both times I was tipsy and I think he has the personality a small hairless rodent. Oh well. I have to stop doing that because I don't want to encourage his crush on me. Aren't I a saint??? I have no fun or exciting stories to impart, My apartment needs a desperate amount of cleaning and I am not in the mood to it. I need to get off my butt and scan some pictures to put on this website. Some of my peeps (small marshmallow chicks) of past and present must find their way on here. I feel slightly bad in that my friends found it appropriate to give Ben the loving nickname of "douchebag". I would like to state for the record that I had nothing to with that.      
</post>


</Blog>