<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   After lance the person who helped me most was peter, he talked to me every night for months b4 meeting me and on the first day I met him I got 3rd base wit him. it just felt so right I knew he was the special one, I knew he was the one i should lose my virginity too, I still remember every moment of that day. he was talkin about his ex, Emily for a while and said that she was a virgin, the fact she was a virgin he felt that he probably shouldn’t have been the one Emily should lose it too. and that she probably regrets it because he wasn’t very experienced and there relationship wasnt that strong, he said to me that he hoped I wasn’t a virgin because he didn’t want me being all emotional and stuff on him, he hated me being emotional towards him. that’s that thing at the start and end he hated me most about. During the relationship he loved me showing him emotions and showing him how much i cared for him and stuff but at the end he just didnt want to hear it. I told peter that I wasn’t a virgin so he wouldn’t feel so uncomfortable peter and I ended up dating for a year in total. we had broken up four times, first because I told him I loved him and he got scared, this was after 4 months of dating and talking like every night, second because he cheated on me, third because he wanted to be a slut in his teens and wants to continue the relationship after I have finished yr 12. argh, he thought this was for the best, I didn’t, and I wanted him back :( I really loved him, sadly I tried everything to get him back, I kept in contact wit him and even though we broke up 12th of January all the way through February we still fucked and got wit each other. I thought it would hopefully get him back. I was wrong, instead he asked me if we could just be fuck buddies, who would wanna be fuck buddies, really after I have had such a good relationship wit him except for a few things that went wrong when he was drunk. I would rather be loved and have passionate sex rather than just meaningless sex. he said that he didn’t find anything wrong wit being fuck buddies because it was just a way of pleasuring us both. giving us both what we wanted but really all I wanted was him. I was too scared of losing him if I admitted this to him though. I had it in my head that if I told him this I would send him running. Today I finally admitted it to him, I told him how much all this sexbuddies fucks me up, I really only kept fucking him because I thought it would increase my chances of dating him again but now I realise that it was hopeless, and things would neva go back to the way they were again. it just don’t make sense, y did he dump me in January? he just said cause of yr 12 and if that was seriously the truth then he wouldn’t be still dating other chicks, geez. I just don’t get it, y does he do this? today I told him that he was just a friend and so he felt hurt cause I didn’t consider him to be a really really close friend. he told me that he thinks of me as one of his great friends... I don’t understand guyz at all. y does he do this? it’s just fucking wit my head. what does he want from me? I am really trying to get ova him but he’s always there. I now have another guy which is damn hot, but he just wants to be friends so I am cool wit that but I am trying to put him b4 peter so I don’t do absolutely anything with peter like I used to but I think I might give this other guy the wrong idea and let him think that I might like him or something, (which wouldn’t really be a bad thing). Damn he’s really hot though and he has the sweetest voice it’s not good, I think I kind of like him though, he talks to me so much its great. I just don’t know what to do about it. 

						
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   After Igor I dated another, lance. he dated me for 4 months, during the forth month he decided that it was wrong just leading me on and since he was dating one of my good friends, Sarah, for the past month he thought that it was time he should break up wit me. I mean come on, where does he get off. he tells me he loves me more and more every time he sees me. Yeah that really truthful he loves me that much that he decides to fuck wit my head for the last month we were dating and even though he still got wit me and bought me flowers and stuff he was doing the same for one of my friends and what about Sarah, she should have come up and confronted me. I told her that when she had one of her many miscarriages I was the one who skipped many classes just to go wit her to see the school counselor. I even made an appointment and arranged a lift for her to go to clockwork but then she comes clear and says that all these miscarriages she has been having were all lies. I really didn’t know enough on the topic of miscarriages. I really didn’t know how hard it was for someone to have one let alone seven. it would have to be seriously deformed for it to end in a miscarriage. she lied about having a miscarriage wit her ex to get close to lance that’s y lance was spending so much time wit her and once she had him comforting her they were soon fucking. god damn them both. it just makes me angry how much I trust some people and they just fuck around wit me. she has no friends at school I was a semi friend of hers all my friends told her to fuck off I said nah let her sit wit us a few lunchtimes. but now wheneva I see her we all say slut and she goes to the library and does work. but how am I meant act. I know what we r doing now is mean but I don’t understand. how am I meant to treat her? I tried to be friends but then she just takes my b4 and when she does she doesn’t even tell me about it he was the one that told me after a month. they should have told me when it all first happened. and now lance is talkin to me and wants me to meet up wit him tomorrow he wants too make up for fucking me around so much and he wants to be friends. what should I do? should I forgive them? 

						
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hmmmmmmmmm, my first entry. Well... where should I start? It would have been yr 9 where all the problems began. Like usual problems it was connected wit a guy. Igor, he was in yr 10, a fucken hot exchange student from France for 2 years. As all girls know the French are the best kisses. But there was more too it than that Igor was great. He told me that he would come back in a year and get me if I still liked him then. I dated him for 5 months in total, during my 4th month I realised that one of my friends, Leanne, liked him and she wanted to date him but didn’t say anything about it to me because she knew I liked him also at that stage. If she had told me I wouldn’t have dated him to start off wit no matter how much I liked Igor I neva choose "dicks ova friends" (Jackie’s words). Igor was my first kiss, I know that’s sad because it was only 2 years ago, but still. everyone says first kisses are always special but when I had mine I was just freaked out cause I really didn’t know what to do. he came ova and asks my parents permission to take me to village cinemas. I thought he was so cute to come to my parents and ask. that’s the type of person he is though, we dated during valentines day and so he left a rose wit a note on my doorstep. he did things like that just to make me feel special it was so cute. as soon as I found out my Leanne liked him it was all downhill from there though, I just didn’t feel the same about him. it felt wrong because Leanne doesn’t get the chance to go out wit people from the same country very much. (she usually dates people from Canada.) and probably the only chance she could get wit a guy she liked and I took it away from her. I feel bad for not really giving Igor a reason for breaking up wit him. I just gave him the reason, "its not u it’s me, I have changed and didn’t feel the same about him as I did 5 months ago". it felt bad but I knew it was for the best. while we were dating Leanne acted differently but I just thought that was because Igor was around me a lot and I didn’t go anywhere without him following, I neva really love him though... after me and Igor broke up Leanne didn’t talk to me for a whole year. it was just freaky because I wasn’t sure if it was because of Igor or not. I still think its childish just ignoring someone just because ur pissed off at them but still I understand y she would be upset. when I first came to college she was my closest friend. she went out of her way to make sure I felt comfortable, and while we weren’t talking for a year she still sent me notes saying how she introduced me to everyone and into her friends group (now my friends group more than hers though). even now 2 years later she tries to use that against me. Yeah she helped me out once and for that I thank her but its fucken 2 years later how much is she gonna dwell in the past for? 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   y r guyz so frustrating. one of my male friends (jesse) does things i think just to piss me off. he told my bros (james) gf that i met up wit him in the movies and so my bro teased me and said that he didnt know i was that desprite. bloody hell, argh. jesse only did this to get hayley back. hayley is jesse' ex they dated for 14 months and now she is dating james. james and hayley have already dated for a month and now that they r all happy and everything jesse is trying to break them up cause he wants hayley back. jesse sooks to me about it also that he misses hayley and stuff. guess how do u tell someone to just get ova them and move on. she has, y cant he. jesse is an alright kid which just needs to grow up and stop being so defencive. they broke up already shes free. james picked her up and now shes taken but still theres more. jesse cant stand that they had broken up and gets wit hayley y shes dating james. hayley goes running back to james NOT TO JESSE but still jesse doesnt understand. hes just too thick and even now hes trying to get back hayley. y doesnt he just leave them alone and move on. now everytime i talk to jesse its about how much he misses hayley, if shes had enough time to move on then y is he still worrying about the past. thats what gets me the most. how come hes still holding on. what is he holding onto tho. all she wants wit him is friendship and if he doesnt watch it he will lose that also... 

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   lastnight everything went wrong, but at the same time i felt so right... peter slept the night. we were determined to keep us as just friends and so it was just hugs and we started to watch the matrix and cuddle. straight away he went hard. i could feel it against me leg but i decided to ignore it and pretend like i hadnt felt it. as soon as the first adds came he said he would give me the massarge he had promised me. it was too hard from him to do my shoulders so he asked me to take off my top. i already had my bra off because i cant sleep in a bra. he started massarging me and well. even though he had only done it for about 5 minutes he said he couldnt do it any longer. he was gonna cum just from massarging me. so he lied down next to me again and tried to settle himself down a bit. he was so horny it was funny. when he lay down i looked into his eyes then i just wanted one kiss, only one kiss so i leaned ova and he caught on and backed away and said that he didnt want to hurt me again. he said that b4 our relationship seemed perfect to him but it was just too fast. he said he didnt realise that he hurt me so much. he said that he didnt want to hurt me. during the night i tried to kiss him 3 more times before he gave in and he kissed me really passionately. before he came ova i made him promise that nothing would happen and we would just stay friends. i really dont wanna risk his friendship over this. we cuddled and talked all night i loved it. he told me that he likes me more than he has ever liked anyone and he cared for me but he wasnt sure if its love or not. that what stumps me, he used to say he loved me all the time, was that just a lie? if he said he loved me b4, well was he lieing then or is he lieing now? lastnight he hugged me all night and made sure i had enough blanket and everything. i really cares for me, i can see that but i just want him to love me. i really do love him, but i dont want to push him. lastnight was the best night eva, i slept so well in his arms. yeah it did lead to sex but it felt better that just that. damn, how do i get him to feel like i do? 

						
</post>


</Blog>