<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      it has become a cliché when people say "im alone"  that the true sense of the statement is seen as  another phase that a typical kid goes through,no  biggie, it'll pass. but the loneliness i know  goes way beyond just another phase. i've come to  a point in my life where painful realizations  start popping out from nowhere. im surrounded by  a LOT of people, some claiming to be friends but  only for the sake of being called so. i feel like  i'm standing in a precipice, screaming my ass off  but nobody ever seems to notice, maybe it's  becasue nobody is trying to. the only sound i  hear is the echo of my voice telling me that the  companionships i have with most people are fake  and superficial, just like  silicon you put in  some lame girl's breasts. this might be my final  crack-up. i feel compelled to go for broke.  there's some level of paranoia i have that  inclines me to think that,in the end, you got  noone but you. so i sit here alone, at three in  the morning.....enjoying the sympathy i get only  from myself. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i long to be somewhere else right now. while i'm thinking what place i ought to be, a thought suddenly crossed my mind. i've been once told that writing does not cause misery, it is borne of misery. i feel like writing right now. i wish i could come up with something really profound to write. something so profound it'll get me around the world.  just like  Anne Frank's journal. that way, i wouldn't feel this bad about myself. that way, there would be something to take the attention away from the fact that i'm nothing. nothing... i guess i'm lower than that. or at least that's how i'm feeling right now. i guess you always feel that way when people around you seem to be having the time of their lives and things around you seem to be smashing right in front of your fuckin (in that case fucked-up)face. Fuck..it's not even a real word but i use it anyway to suggest how severely it applies. this is something i'd like to say to my life "i don't wanna hate you, but right now i do." that's just a polite way of saying "you're a fuckin bitch." mushy, corny even. but you can't really help it if it does something that makes you feel that way. i put up fronts. i'm too weak to admit i'm weak. and where have that gotten me? to one dark recess of my room wondering how could have everything gone so bad so quickly. my paranoia's got me choosin between cancer and insanity. i think ill go with the former. God's giving the choices or maybe it's me making the bargain. i'm donned to be me. i guess God hand picks some of us to be miserable, it isn't random. i think that's a form of de facto discrimination. then again, it's just a guess.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Last Wednesday, I went out to buy a book. It also happened to be the day of GMA’s inauguration which, by the way, took place here in Cebu. After I went out of National Bookstore in Mango Avenue, I went straight to Osmeña Boulevard to see the new president celebrate her triumph over a high school dropout. I walked until I got close enough to see Gloria. But hell, the place was so crowded, I found it hard to breathe (it always happens to me specially when people’s whiff get all mixed up. I find it hard to breathe, that is.). Like I said, it was so crowded I got stepped on practically about a million times. People were pushing people. I almost fell down. My point is, the place was jam-packed but I didn’t see one familiar face except for a couple of faggots who were hitting on me while I was on my way to the bookstore but they don’t count.  It’s a little ironic that I was surrounded by thousands of people but none of them I knew. They were just faces, torsos, armpits…each one of them contributing to the awful stench that was making breathing difficult. The stench became unbearable by the second so I figured I’d leave. I walked two beautiful blocks and hopped on a jeep. I rode on it only until PCGS and I stepped down and decided to walk because traffic was heavy and it was completely warm inside, I was sweating all the way down to my ass. On my way home, I saw fireworks. It was awesome. Instinctively, I stopped to admire the confounding perplexity of what was displaying in front of me. I just stood there for 10 whole minutes, appreciating. I started to open my mouth to say something to somebody and that’s when it hit me.  I was alone. About a couple of weeks ago, I would have engaged myself in some emotional demonstration over the fact that nobody was with me. I would have been totally helpless and sit on my bed thinking, “Where’d everybody go?”. If you still don’t get it, I’ll tell you. My friends and I had some creative differences, to put it mildly. To put it mildly still, we faded. At least, our companionship did. It would be nice to write sad poems about comrades going separate ways. It would be nice sulking in one corner contemplating ways to bring everybody back. It would be nice… but I just don’t feel like it. In a way, I’m glad we faded because when we faded that’s only when I realized how much little air I was breathing. Their presence was like the stench that takes time before you realize you’re gradually being choked. I was trapped when I was with them.   All the time, I was branded as the uto-uto because I constantly made them laugh like hell and they laughed like hell. Guess that makes me a pleaser, but I don’t mind much, but it dawned on me that being too preoccupied with being the clown makes you forget yourself at times. A whole cornucopia of realizations was brought in by this delayed disclosure.   Because of the preoccupation of making my friends laugh the shit out of them, I forgot that I also like to talk about books and all that shit. I forgot that I also like to have deep meaningful conversations with them. I forgot…deliberately. I put those things aside because I was too pensive about suiting their taste. When I do become serious, I was tagged with very nasty things. We never had any common ground to spring from. There never even was a friendship to talk about in the first place. We were just drinking buddies who don’t have anything to do except be drinking buddies. The company manufactured that kind of atmosphere. I’m nothing if not surrounded.   Well, that’s what I was thinking while I was looking at those fireworks and admiring their intricate configuration in the sky. So I stood there…alone…glad that when I get home, I no longer have to worry about pleasing people or having nonsensical blabber with them even though, deep inside, I’m not really into it.  So, I went on walking and thinking about how nice it would be to gather the whole posse again and have a few rounds of Red Horse but I decided I would follow their wake, put our companionship in one dark recess and leave it there to rot. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>