<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yay! A new Blog!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm in skool muahaha.. using the skool com.. i'm so bored with this CMS thingy so decided to surf the net hehehe =)

Here are the pics from last friday =)

  

I feel *g0Ng* lEh.. i duno how to upload stuff here and my blog looks so damn boring..Needa adda soma stuffa(need 2 add some stuff) to make it look nice.. I NEED HELP!

Today's been a sianster day, been listening to bio l;ectures, we've already covered the so called "basics" of bones.. man, its damn hard lor!! We all should thank those freaks who invented these "alienistic" names for us to study!!!!

I don't mean to be mean, but i personally feel that the lecturer Yong KJ looks exactly like a monkey!No kidding man!

We also had this lesson whereby we had to study 2-way communication.different people think differently etc etc(yeah my philosophy). Not bad ah.. well whatever she taught us for today,i haf that kinda belief that everyone is different and they come from different backgrounds. I guess this lesson sorta suits me =)

Darran smsed me today =) Anyway, he is falling sick nowadays & i don't know why... just now when he sms me, he told me he had stomach ache & headache..Haiz... =( and he doesn't wanna see a doctor at all.. I am really worried for him.He'll be coming over to my place later to have dinner together with my family. I hope he gets well asap.He's been falling sick since last week already!

Gotta Ciaoz now...wanna look thru this CMS thingy =P

"Coz i'm broken...
When i'm lonesome
And i don't feel right..
When you're gone away"
++Seether feat Amy lee>>>Broken++


     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yoz! Today we had just 3 hrs of lesson. We had Clinical Lab lessons during the first 2hrs.Aww man, it was kinda fun with some jokers in class*lol* We had to learn stuff like moving patient from bed to chair..well sounds easy but unfortunately it isn't."Actions speaks louder than Words"...so we had to practice more to do it right. Our class booked the labs to practise tomorrow. I like my class..they're so united =)

Then we had this Tutorial lesson,Process and Practise of Nursing;like we're supposed to assess the patient and stuff.. quite alright.. The grp presentation was amusing haha..

And after school some of my classmates went to the canteen to eat macdonalds!The price is cheaper than other outlets,suitable for students =)Nothing much, we just sit down and chit chat.. yeah..

Oh yah.. something is rather disturbing..Darran seems to be getting sick..last week he had fever and missed his first day of school.And this week stomach upset.I think its becoz of the food he eats.. I duno.. just kinda worried for him.. Hope he gets well soon and healthy too...

Well dats abt all for today..will blog if i'm free.. g2g study Ciao~

"Vindicated 
I am selfish, I am wrong 
I am right, I swear I'm right 
Swear I knew it all along 
And I am flawed 
But I am cleaning up so well 
I am seeing in me now 
The things you swore you saw yourself"
++Dashboard Confessional-Vindicated++

     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yo! I'm back! Today's gonna be a boring Sunday.. but the weather seems so nice to sleep in.. Unfortunately, I still have to revise thru my bio notes!!Arrghh..

Oh yeah,on Friday my class and I didn't get to hang out coz we had this library orientation*yawnz* and our mentor wanted to talk to us*double yawnz* so we only had 2hrs of break instead of 4hrs. 2 of my classmates brought their digital cameras and so we took loads of pictures near the fountains in our school

NYP has so many fountains!!Good for  feng shui  i guess.. Well the photo taking was fun,my classmates haven't sent me the photos thru e-mail yet.Well once they have done so, i'll post them here =)

Yesterday  urlLink  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yoz haven't been writing ever since i've started.. yeah i've disappeared for quite some time

Well anyway, i'm now in Nanyang Polytechnic School Of Health Sciences doing my nursing course. There are 35 groups of 30 students in Nursing!!That's a lot of students and guess what, yours truly is in Group 35 ;)

Today is the 4th day of school.. well things are okay. I'm kinda happy with my class..yeah.A really fun and easy going buncha peepz.The girls are really friendly and nice,2 of the guys are dirty minded,they're always looking out for this girl with a D-cup from some other group..Haha..Well in short,my class is cool =)

We have lessons from 8-5pm and only an hr of break in between.But during most of our lectures we were let out of class early and we had some short breaks in between so it wasn't so bad at all except that the room was so damn cold becoz of the rainy weather.What's more,we were mostly in the air-conditioned rooms today.

Anyway tomorrow i have lessons from 9-10am and 2-3pm. Man,we're gonna a 4hr break in between and hanging around the school grounds is so boring so i suggested to my classmates that we should get out somewhere for lunch together tomorrow. =)

That's for all today
     

    
</post>


</Blog>