<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      test
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello :) I'm thinking about taking a trip to Cancun in October or November? Anyone want to go? Let me know.....so far it's Karen and I.  Yesterday I had to volunteer for the free clinic work our concession stand at the park to raise money.  Karen came with and was a great help.  Didn't do much else.  Had an interesting phone call and that's it.  Today, I worked......ugh.....and tomorrow, I work. 
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well....what to say today.  Luke called me this morning.  Went to work at the tanning salon.  Came home, talked to Karen, took a shower and went to a meeting at the Chamber of Commerce.  The main highway is being torn apart and the bridge going into Michigan.  So I attended that meeting.   The last few weeks I've been really emotional...crying for no reason at all.  Ugh, what's wrong with me? After the meeting Karen and I went to AppleBee's for drinks.  Then I came home...and went grocery shopping for a friend.  Now I'm home again...duh.  Hi Jerry! :) How you doing? Just thought I'd give ya a little attention! Someone else tomorrow and so on.  Night all! Love all of you!
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I've decided maybe each day to make my titles questions? Nah? Who knows, I'm new to all of this.  I didn't do anything today....just went to work at the motel.  Talked to a few friends and felt down most of the night.  Not sure why, maybe it's the weather changes? Anyway I should be in bed cause I have to work at the tanning salon in the morning. Night :)
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I survived :) Karen and I went to the fireworks yesterday.  We were walking around and saw some guys that we knew back in high school.  Watched the fireworks with them and had a blast.  Shed a couple of tears even.  Then went to some Steve guys apartment to see another friend.  Oh boy, the memories...we had great talks.  After that Karen and I took Brad (one of the guys) out for his 27th birthday.  Had a couple of drinks, sang, and danced. Hit the road a little after 2....got home, got a phone call and went back out for a couple of hours ;) Note to self...haha....okay any way, now that you're all confused....atleast I know what is going on right?  Today is Monday, all I did was work.  Not too much else new.  Maybe tomorrow?
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So what did I do today? I dusted my room..kinda....did some laundry...kinda.  Then Karen and I went to Mickey Lou's and then off to Stephenson Island to listen to some music.  It wasn't too exciting.  It was either couples there or young kids.  No one really our age.  We pulled up to park and some younger kid pulled up behind us.  Followed us to the park and then stayed within our sight....then he left when we did...boy did he have some pipes. Talked to one of my mom's friends about her business and stuff. What else? Hmmm....talked to some friends on the phone and pretty much called it a night.  Exciting, I know.  That's it for now :D This title has nothing to do with anything, I just like the quote!
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I am at 1 a.m. on Saturday July 3rd.  I'm just not sure how I'm feeling today.  I really don't enjoy the 4th of July.  It is one of those days where I just hate being alone.  The other day...it's New Year's Eve.  All the happy couples just make me sick...lol.  So anyway, just when you think your life is perfect....CRASH...something happens.  I thought my life was going great..thought I had the perfect guy in my life.  But it turns out we want two different things....and this trying to be friends.....it doesn't work.  So now what? I start all over....lol.  Maybe I'll write more later...I can't keep my eyes open and I am not making much sense.  Night! 
    
</post>


</Blog>