<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just kidding, maybe this thing will work out after all.  I'm telling you, summer is screwing with my head.  I woke up at 12:30 in the afternoon today and fixed myself a bowl of cocoa puffs.  It was while I was eating this that the Lawn trash men come.  I hear the sound of the dump truck hissing to a stop, and I realize that it something is not right.  The garbage men come on Mondays and Thursdays and the Lawn men come on Wednesdays.  Now, when you are still half asleep and you think it's Tuesday, this can cause quite a surprise!  I ask my little brother what day it is, and of course he has no idea, so I had to consult the cable TV menu to find out it was in fact Wednesday and not Tuesday.  In other news, I saw The Others today starring Heath Ledgers... and all those other people.  It was surprisingly good.  I give it 15 thumbs up.  That's basically characterized my day to this point...  Yeah I know, sad.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it's currently 2:30 in the morning as I'm writing this, so I'm not completely in my right mind.  I'll probably wake up later today and say... OMG, what the hell was I thinking!?  But who cares.  My computer is also on the fritz and keeps freezing up.  It does this sometimes, and unfortunately, it's doing it right now, but what're you gonna do, right?  I'm not really sure why I'm making this blog in all honesty.  I guess it's because I've got a lot of bottled up emotions that I need to let out, but who am I kidding, I'm not going to talk about things that've happened to me before I made this.  But hopefully I can let out new emotions before they get bottled up ;).  You'll find through reading my blogs that I'm a passive, funny, intelligent, and all around great guy!  Really, I am, all of those things.  Ok, I'm 15 right now, but things change right?  Right now it's Summer Break (which would explain the staying upness) but I'm going into my Sophmore year.  But that won't be for a good month or so.  Lets see.  I like Tv... movies... video games... the occasional book or two.  Yeah, thats about it, lol.  Expect me to talk a lot about those subjects... or not.  Contrary to what you may think, I do actually have a life (or so I like to think)... so maybe I'll just talk about that.  Ok, My real name is Kevin, but I usually go by NiVeKeR14 on the internet (its a long story don't ask (ok so maybe it's not a long story, I'm just lazy, get off my back)).  BTW, it's pronounced Ni-vek-er-four-teen, but you can call me Vek, or Nive, or Kevin, or Kev, or Kevo, or the Kev-meister... ok, don't call me that.  I spend a lot of my time on the  urlLink H2SB  (Halo 2 Social Board) at a website called GameFAQs.  You might find me talking about that.  I also have my own website  urlLink NiVeKeR14.com  (don't be fooled by the name, thats not it's actual URL, too poor to pay for it).  I have a link to my forums at that site if you wanted to join in.  Well, thats all I can think of to say right now.  It's now 2:57 AM and I promised myself I'd go to sleep no later than 3 in the morn' (I've been staying up until 6 and 7 in the morning lately).  I could have gotten this thing written faster if my damn computer WOULDN'T STOP FREEZING!!!  Sorry, it did it again.  You'll find that while I do have a life, it's not very exciting.  So I use jarring humor and quick wit to make it seem much more interesting.  You should also note that I act much differently offline than I do online... call it an online personality.  So just bare in mind I'm not  really  an ass...
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thats right, I'm leaving to a friends house tomorrow to stay the night, so we can wake up nice and early to go to North Carolina.&nbsp; We are staying in a big cabin.&nbsp; So, I won't be posting here for probably a week, but when I get back, expect a nice long summary ;).  Lets see.&nbsp; Today I managed to pull off this cool trick in Halo that lets you skip a big part of the level on Assault on the Control Room.&nbsp; It's in the very beginning of the level, the first time you go outside on the bridge, you jump off the bridge to the left and if you do it right, you'll land on a crack in the side of the cliff wall.&nbsp; From there you can work your way down.&nbsp; It's very hard to get down without slipping and dieing.&nbsp; I tried it a million times with no avail yesterday, but I finally pulled it off today, then again when I accidently killed myself later in the level :).&nbsp; If you manage to pull it off, there won't be any Covenant for the rest of the level.&nbsp; It's a cool way to turn a level that would take a couple hours to beat, into a level that'll take only a few minutes to beat.  What else happened...&nbsp; hmm...&nbsp; Oh yes, on Monday my mom had me work for her.&nbsp; It wasn't that bad because I know she really needed the help, and I wasn't doing anything anyway.&nbsp; She had me do some paperwork.&nbsp; I started at five in the afternoon, and finished at three in the morning.&nbsp; Of course, it would have taken her about a week to do it, so she was very proud of me ;).&nbsp; I got fifty bucks out of it too, so thats always nice.  I was going to cancel Halo Tuesday at my house because of it, but my friend Chaz showed up at my doorstep at&nbsp;ten in the morning while I was still asleep.&nbsp; My little brother woke me up.&nbsp; On a side note, I'm the oldest in my family, the oldest sibling and the oldest cousin.&nbsp; Just that I'd let you all know that.&nbsp; My seven year old brother woke me up at ten in the morning to tell me that one of my friends showed up on my doorstep for Halo Tuesday which I canceled the night before.  I wasn't terribly angry, but I was a little disappointed I didn't get to keep sleeping.&nbsp; I called up everybody, but the only person that could show up was Aaron, so Halo tuesday was re-opened, just with a lower attendence.  And that led to today, where I managed to pull off the nifty trick on one of the levels in Halo.&nbsp; And thats pretty much all I've done since last I wrote in here.  I'll write more next week, I promise! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had the shortest trip to the mall in history today, but more on that later. &nbsp; This Friday, Rick and I decided to hang out again.&nbsp; Aaron decided to tag along, but we didn't mind.&nbsp; We were at my house playing Halo until Aaron went to work.&nbsp; I had to wake up at 9:30 blech.&nbsp; Lol, whatever, it was fun.&nbsp; Of course I won all the Halo rounds.&nbsp; I even wasn't even paying attention to the game for the first half of the match, and I still won.&nbsp; It's just too easy ;). &nbsp; When Aaron left for work, rick and I decided to hike to the mall.&nbsp; Not having a car, I literally mean hike.&nbsp; It took us about an hour to walk their.&nbsp; I was expecting it to take only 45 minutes so we could have a good 30 minutes to stay, because Rick had to be back at my house to hitch a ride at 6.&nbsp; Needless to say, my plan didn't work.&nbsp; We spent about five minutes in Gamestop, got some drinks and then we had to leave. &nbsp; We wouldn't have made it back either.&nbsp; Rick was able to get ahold of his ride with his cell, so we changed the locationg to a McDonalds we were passing by.&nbsp; So, I got a ride the rest of the way home, and got an Ice Cream.&nbsp; And Rick payed for everything... I'm so cheap.&nbsp; The sad thing is, I did have money. &nbsp; So today I had to mow the lawn.&nbsp; I burned a copy of Ricks Punisher Soundtrack while he was staying at my house, so I listened to that while I mowed.&nbsp; It is a very good CD.&nbsp; I recommend it.&nbsp; Even if you didn't like the movie, you gotta give the music it's props.&nbsp; My mom is expecting company in any moment now, so I should get off.&nbsp; Until next time, I wish you the best. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had another Halo lan party tuesday.  I say another because I also had a Halo lan party the tuesday before last.  It was lots of fun.  Once you go lan... you never go back?  So sue me, I'm not good at rhyming.  Aaron left for work and we went and picked up my friend Rick.  I haven't met with Rick in person in about two months, and I hadn't expected him to even come over.  Needless to say, he ended up staying the night at my house.  Including my brother, the most people we had playing at one time was six people, which is still very fun.  After Halo, we watched some movies, general hung out, and then played some more Halo.  We went to sleep, woke up, hung out, watched a movie, and the played some more Halo.  Aaron came over again too, but no second Xbox this time.  All in all, I had a very pleasing past two days.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just got done watching the movie Bad Santa.  BEST. MOVIE. EVER.  It featured Billy-Bob Thorton as the Bad Santa.  Which he plays a magnificent Bad Santa.  I really don't think anyone else could have played that role.  It's a terrific comedy with enough emotion to get you feeling, but not enough to stop you from laughing during the entire movie.  Warning, this movie IS NOT for the kiddies.  I repeat, do not let small children watch this movie.  I give this movie 57 thumbs up.  Now, I know what you're thinking.  This guy must be some kind of movie critic of something, and a damn good one at that, but I'm not ladies and gentlemen.  And I'm not only going to talk about movies.  But thats what motivated me to write in this thing again right now, so deal with it...  In conclusion, I'm no movie critic, but you must go see Bad Santa right now.  If you've already seen it... go see it again!  Toodles.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I realized today that I disagree with almost everything my mom does.  Everyday she goes on walks.  Today I opted to go with her so we could talk.  I didn't have anything I wanted to talk about in particular, just thought I'd think of something.  Yeah, I realized why I never talk with her.  It's because we're so different.  I just wish that when I was talking to people I could just scream, YOU'RE WRONG!  YOU'RE WRONG!  STOP TALKING BECAUSE YOU'RE WRONG.  But of course I can't do this, so I'm stuck not saying anything.  I am a very complicated person, and even though my mom and I agree about a lot of things, we can never agree with how to approach these problems.  And thats why I can't talk with her.  Same with another person who I don't care to mention here, sorry everyone.  In conclusion.  I have no one to talk to that understands me.  Maybe thats because I never try talking with people, but guess what, I've tried talking today and I've eliminated that person from my list of people I can talk to.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry for not posting in a few days, I've been busy with stuff.  Anyway, I am here to write about Spider Man 2, which I just got done seeing.  Spider Man 2 is officially my favorite super hero movie.  It has action, comedy, suspense, and all in all it's just plain cool.  Alfred Molina really brings life to Doctor Octavius.  In an otherwise unbelievable character, Molina brings life and down to earthness.  And Tobey Maguire is an excellent spider-man yet again.  You can really feel his struggle as his personal life falls apart because of his choice to be spider-man.  The fight scenes with Spidey and Doc Oct. are some of the best fight scenes I've ever seen.  You really get the feeling of two goliaths duking it out.  I give this movie 32 thumbs up.  I highly recommend it and everyone should go out and see it if they haven't already done so.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I like to think that life is a learning process, you make a mistake and you learn from it.  Needless to say, I made a mistake thursday night, or very early Friday morning depending on how you look at it.  But I learned from that experience.  I learned to never ever click things on your computer if you're not entirely sure what they'll do.  I also learned to never try and fix your mistake because you'll almost certainly make it worse.  And when you do try and fix your mistake, don't be dissappointed that you lost everything on your hard drive....  Luckily I had already learned from a previous occasion to make copies of your important stuff, so not all is lost.]  The moral of the story.  Computers secretly hate me.  You see, there are some people that computers out right hate, then they're people who computers love.  I'm one of the people who computers secretly hate.  That's where they will work perfectly for you until they find the perfect time to POUNCE!  And then they JUMP you by surprise and give you a serious of shock and awe tactics.  But, I've subdued my computer again, and all is basically ok.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My mom went to the Linkin Park/Korn/other artists concert tonight, so she left me to fend for myself.  I was watching my brother, but thank god my cousins nabbed him and swept him away to youth group at their church.  They tried to sway me to go, but I reluctantly denied, lol.  For dinner I had a bowl of Chunky's New England Clam Chowder, OMG it was soooo good.  I love it.  I also had a bowl of Cambell's Spaghetti.  It was ok.  Last weekend I forgot to mention I saw Aliens Vs. Predator.  It's really not as bad as everyone says it is.  Granted it could have been soooo much more.  But I enjoyed myself watching it, so thats really all that matters.  It's a good summer flick.  Had a quiz in Algebra 2.  It was just Algebra 1 review, I passed it with flying colors (I assume).  Also had a quiz in Chemistry, lol.  I don't think my chemistry teacher is going to be too pleased with me.  I only did half of my homework (give me a break, I was busy doing Algebra 2 homework and studying that monologue).  I was going to bring my Chemistry book to school with me to study... but no.  All we had to do on the test was write the symbols of the elements he listed.  Unfortunately I didn't study  at all !  I only got a 6 out of 11, and I cheated on half of the ones I got correct.  LoL.  I promise I'll start studying more once I get a part in the play!  I'll keep you updated. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today in drama, our "classroom" is actually the auditorium, but the Principle was having his senior class meeting in their during our period, so the class had to congregate in the Media Center.  To pass the time, and give us some more things to give us grades on, she gave us the assignment to make a short dialogue on a piece of paper. It had to be an argument of only two people and it had to take place in a restaurant, a movie theatre, or school.  I chose the restaurant, I had a customer and a waiter. The customer found a bug and his soup and the waiter argued about it. At first he said that there wasn't any bug, and then he said that the bug was suppose to be in the soup. Anyway, I had a lot of fun just throwing it together. I thought it was funny, maybe I'll post it when I get it back.  Speaking of drama, next monday we're having the school play auditions.  I'm really looking forward to this.  Wish me luck guys.  All I've got to do is memorize one monologue and perform it in front the teacher.  Here is the Monologue:    Audition By: Matthew Calhoun This comic monologue is printed here in its entirety, though written for a male actor, by changing a few pronouns, the piece could be adapted for use by an actress.       (An actor carrying an umbrella, enters. He/she  is anything but a leading man/lady: perhaps he is bald, perhaps pudgy, perhaps very short, perhaps… something different. But not a leading man. He speaks forward to the audience, which represents the two or three people auditioning him.)       Actor: My resume.  (He takes out a three-by-five card, and spins it forward, of the front of the stage.)  Oh, first I should mention that I could play any of the parts in this play. Any. I could play an ant, I could play Little Red Riding Hood, I could play Hamlet. I’ve never heard of this play, as a matter of fact. It doesn’t matter. I can do opera, I can do commercials, I can sing soprano, I can do my own stunts- I’m that versatile. Leading man, leading lady, gay, ingenue- you name it, I can do it. That’s how great I am. I see you looking over my resume. Noticing I’ve never had a part. It’s a real comment on this sick business we’re in, isn’t it? An actor this good  (he thumps his chest)  and he’s blackballed! Why? For refusing to show up at auditions! Auditions are beneath me. I wipe my feet on them. People should be begging me to grace their theatres- producers should be asking me to audition them! But those egomaniacs who should bow and scrape before me - they have forced me to betray my principles and come to this  (said with utter contempt)  audition.  (the word is practically spat, or vomited out. The contempt with which the actor feels this word is the key of the scene.)       So no, no, don't blame me for demeaning myself in this grotesque position… I’ve waited ten years for them to come crawling… but suffice it to say they were too wrapped up in their own insane… trivium to get the hint. But enough of them. Let’s get to the situation at hand. You’re sitting there typecasting me as a leading man aren't you? You’re thinking that because of my matinee idol glorious good looks, and rich, sensuous, sexy, seductive, fetching, effervescent, tingly and charming voice, I could only play a male lead. No, I tell you, no! Observe! An ant!  (He crawls along the floor in a normal way.)  And now, King Lear!  (He opens his umbrella and pretends, in an awkward mime, to be blown around the stage.)  I needn't mention, of course, that that was the fabulous storm scene, out on the heath. And now, Brutus, impaled on his own sword!  (Closes the umbrella, stabs himself with it in the stomach. Dies, rather flatly.)       And here’s a homicidal lunatic:  (he gets up, picks up the umbrella, waves it threatening forward, like a sword. This part seems real.)  Give me the part or I’ll kill you! I’ll poke out the vile grape jelly of your eyes with the point of my umbrella! I’ve been waiting ten years for this!  (Puts the umbrella down.)       OK. All the parts. I should play all the parts in you little production. Capiche? Capiche. Note the mastery of the Spanish dialect. I do it all. Now, with that in mind, here’s my…  (Abrupt pause) What do you mean my time’s up? I haven’t done my monologue yet!  (Beat)  What do you mean, next? Where do you get off saying next?! I memorized this thing! I took the subway here! I elbowed my way ahead of dozens of pushy actors and still had to wait a half hour to get in here! I wanna do my audition!     What really sucks is that I've got Algebra 2 homework every single night.  Oh, did I mention that I get transfered from English 2 to Algebra 2?  Can't remember if I said that yet or not.  Yeah, so I've got to memorize this thing (which I've almost got done) and I've got algebra and chemistry to study everynight.  Alright, enough bitching out of this guy.  I really  don't have it  that  bad. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wouldn't you know it we weren't even touched! We got mild rain and thats it. However, just 20 minutes east of us was COMPLETELY destroyed. I mean just flattened. They don't even know what the status of the people are yet because they can't get any vehicles down there because of the debris.  There have been about 15 fatalities already reported, but we haven't even begun to find all of the people. Our city was DAMN lucky.The really sad thing is that all of those people weren't even prepared because everyone on the news said it wouldn't hit them, it just shows how much we really know about hurricanes.  Orlando still doesn't have power... But never fear, I'm here to stay, for now at least. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just got my schedule changed.  You see, you need to have Algebra II either before, or while you take Chemistry, so I had my English II class switched to Algebra II, thats all that was changed.  We've also got a hurricane coming our way.  I'm not too worried, but just in case I never come back here, it's probably because I've been impaled with an SUV. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just got home from my first day of school. Plenty of stupid freshman to make fun of this year.... I mean... I'm always nice to the new guys  _>...  But seriously, so far I've gotten all of the classes that I wanted to get. I've got block scheduling so I've only four classes this semester, then next semester I'll have four different classes.  So far I have:  Composition Theatre- We "Screen Films" as my teacher says. It's cool because we're in the Auditorium and we've got a big movie screen to watch the films on. We're only going to be watching American films.  Drama 1: I should be in a more advanced theatre class than this, but whatever, I'm just happy to be in any theatre class. Besides, I wasn't in a drama class last year so it'll give me some catch up time.  There was some pretty hot freshman chics in here that I'd be glad to... "act" with.  English II Honors: No complaints (although my teacher is from Boston...)  Chemistry I Honors: Also no complaints, not to mention the girl of my dreams is in that class with me. She doesn't know she's the girl of my dreams, but I'm working on it give me a break.  Actually, maybe I'll just give up on my dreams and go for the hot freshman chics... 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a surprise! Everyone that said they were going to come actually came!  We actually didn't play so much Halo once the mass of people got here (three girls, what do you expect). I realized that I like one of the three girls even more than I thought I did. Wow... I'm not going to name any names, just in case she's might one day by chance happen to read this... god I'm a pussy.  And that is all I'll say on that matter. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We would have had Halo Tuesday but I had my Dentist appointment, so Aaron suggested I just move it to Thursday (he has to go to church on Wednesdays).  I'm going to have a lot more people over than I usually do, because Aaron is such a good little manipulator, he convinced a whole bunch of people to come.  It's about nine in the morning now.  Aaron should be coming in about an hour, but the majority of the people won't be coming until around two in the afternoon.  Lets see how many actually come in comparison to how many people said they were going to come.  Update on the event coming probably tomorrow. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry for not updating the blogs in a while.  I know I said I was going to make a huge entry for the vacation to North Carolina, but if there's one thing you need to know about me is that I'm a lazy jerk.  Sorry.  North Carolina was very, very cool.  Temperature wise also.  I suggest you go there.  I do not suggest however you walk three miles up and down hill to buy a loaf of bread like me and Aaron did.  It wasn't worth the effort...  We did that twice.  And we didn't even get any bread one of the times.  I went tubing for the first time.  I suggest it.  It is very fun, especially when the water is so cold it numbs your injuries lol.  I would like to mention, I did not wipe out once!  Except when I did it on purpose...  Went to Mount Mitchell, the highest peak east of the Mississippi River at 6,684 feet.  Unfortunately we were inside a day, so I didn't get to see all of North Carolina.  But being in a cloud is fun in and of itself.  Took some very nice pictures, maybe I'll put some up when I get everything sorted out.  We played a lot of Megaman 10th Anniversary edition at night before we went to bed.  It was the first time I'd ever played any Megaman game, and I was already better at it than Aaron.  I gotta give Aaron his props though, he was pretty good too.  I beat the eight Master bosses ;).  There was this street party we went to called Belle chaire.  Actually, I don't remember how to spell, but thats pretty close.  It was basically just an excuse for people to walk around drunk in the street, plus there was some very nice looking women there.  I didn't drink, don't worry.  lol.  The Ashville mall is simply superb.  Go there if you're ever in Ashville, NC.  I've been back since Saturday, it's Tuesday now.  Not much happen this past few days.  Watched the Stargate: SG1 and Atlantis episodes I missed thanks to tivo.  Tivo rocks. ;)  I went to the dentists today.  It was a big fiasco, but everything worked out.  It turns out my gums are too soft, thanks to plaque.  I need to brush my gums more, and they'll get better.  And thats my summary for the past ten days. :-D 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>