<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sorry- everyone already has a blog, but if it helps them maybe it will help me.  You have problems on a list that is three miles long. I have problems on my mind, but i still don't belong.    
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmm if your heart beat slower and faster at the same time wouldnt the two compensate and make a normal beat? or perhaps if one of your heart valves beat faster than the other there would be a build up of blood and you know what that means.... ny ny Beano.&nbsp; (?)  Anyhoo we just got back from the cabin- it was a good night.&nbsp; no party just kinda sat and hung out by the lake fire.&nbsp; So we were out there right.... and nathan had his guitar and was playing and i was totally content.&nbsp; i couldnt have been anymore happy just sitting and doing nothing besides listening to him and gazing at the stars, lake and fire (and perhaps his eyes a time or two).&nbsp; We ended up taking him home about 500 AM because he&nbsp;got really sick and didnt bring his inhaler. but it was cool cuz we got to see the sun come up- kinda- and the ride was pretty schweet.&nbsp;&nbsp;Aww what a beautiful kid.&nbsp; I love watching him play. I love how he gets pissed off if his guitar is not tuned just so... and how he will sit there and try to tune it, by ear, for hours.&nbsp; He&nbsp;gets so into&nbsp;what he is doing, and rightly so, he can play that thing like nobody's business.  Arg.&nbsp;  you can stop&nbsp;reading here because im just going to&nbsp;vent right now.&nbsp;   I love the way he&nbsp;has the coolest comments, or when we're being silly and he changes his voice- as we all tend to do-&nbsp; I love that he is the most polite person ive ever met.&nbsp; He asked if he could take his pants off when we were going to bed and&nbsp;he was on the otherside of the room&nbsp; for godsakes.&nbsp; I love that he is laid back and "an indecisive bastard" as he put it.&nbsp; I love that he has so much talent and is actually doing something with it and i hope they (he and joe&nbsp;etc.) &nbsp;will get out of anaconda and go somewhere with it.&nbsp; I love that he writes his songs&nbsp;with different perceptions&nbsp;of different people&nbsp; and i love when he sings- even if sometimes its a little off key&nbsp;he still has a&nbsp;nice voice&nbsp;(Im always out of key).&nbsp; A nice voice in general for that matter- what is it with me and voices? &nbsp; I love the fact that he would have slept on the rollaway, instead of the bed,&nbsp;if i wouldnt have insisted on taking it.&nbsp; I really love that i can remember one of my favorite things he ever said, give or take- "Im not a tough guy or anything, but I seriously wanted to kick his ass"&nbsp; haha ( i dont know why that stayed with me but it did.)&nbsp; I love that he felt&nbsp;sorry because&nbsp;HE was&nbsp;so sick he couldnt sleep, and thought it was an inconvience to take him&nbsp;home (&nbsp;I wish i could have helped him, he sat outside coughing up his lungs for quite awhile and i felt really bad) Aww.... Im such a loser.&nbsp;  Until Time Next  &nbsp;     
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jessie was getting out of my car right- and stetz was gonna hop up front, well he was on his way out and jessies door slam was on the way in....boom collision!!&nbsp; hahaha it was so GD funny!&nbsp; god damn.&nbsp; (haha i just defeated the purpose of GD)&nbsp; anyhoo.&nbsp; the poor kid- he sneaks out of his house to hang out then he gets nailed in the face with a door- made a pretty schweet, but bloody, mark where his glasses were.&nbsp; Hey hey hey.&nbsp; I accidentally threw caseys frisbee on a roof- my bad.&nbsp; Oh well, not like he hasnt messed or broken&nbsp; any of my shit.&nbsp; Yeah so i realized how retarded i am the other day.&nbsp; I have this set of musical instruments right, Costco shit :), and we had them out&nbsp;for the party.&nbsp; Few nights later the tambourine was sittin on the couch so i grab it and play right- well for some reason Abba comes on.... dancing queen or some shit, and ya know&nbsp;that part where its like "feel the beat on the tambourine"&nbsp;- i was&nbsp;playin with that very instrument.... how lame do you have to be to play the tambourine to an abba song- especially one that actually tells you to&nbsp;play it. &nbsp;shit man- my life...i tell ya.&nbsp; I have no complaints though.&nbsp; Im too tired to complain. (right now) come back later and i could probably bitch your ear off. &nbsp;  Welp this entry is short, but i just got done cleanin up for the birth givers return so i am done.  Get to clean Monaghans tomorrow!&nbsp; Hooray!&nbsp;&nbsp; heh maybe a cabin party is in the cards too i dont know.&nbsp; Well Ciao! Until Time Next   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok kids i found out why you cant comment.&nbsp; I apologize.&nbsp; I was lookin throuhg some of my stuff and i had it on a fucked up setting.&nbsp; Soory!&nbsp; so yeah feel free to let the juices flow in the comment box.&nbsp; Hasta  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Crab people...crab people.&nbsp;  Aww- le sigh.&nbsp; So hows things world?&nbsp; things are hoekay here.&nbsp; Somthin smells fishy in the soon-to-be ghost town though.&nbsp; And I'm not just talking about my stinky phenuter....&nbsp; ha ha&nbsp; i keed i keed.&nbsp; So this week looks prosperous... gotta water the flowers at the commons-get in tight with the garden club- and do a bunch a work around the ol dry cleaners, and there are key club meetings galore and pictures and caroll to look at, and physical to get (please dont take my blood, or make me pee in the cup.....please no, could be bad 4 (twenty) business :)&nbsp; (heh read that again if it didnt make sense the first time.......................&nbsp;^ ^^^^^^))&nbsp;&nbsp; Waaananaa&nbsp; jack bandit.&nbsp; -what the fuck?&nbsp; hmm.&nbsp; So yeah had another lil get together last night.&nbsp; it was pretty schweet.&nbsp; I had an ok time.... then this one kid came and it got a little better.&nbsp; Janni was there (once again, for those of you playing the home game hanni was once jon, then jonny, and now we modeled him after musical genuis yanni but&nbsp; we simply call him hanni for this is his new spanish name J as H) He never comes out... actually i saw him tonight too but hey.&nbsp; and Michelle and Leslie came and brought there special friends Grant and Noah- great kids- and samwell came and pretty much just played on the comp, and zacher and his twig and giggleberrys came out to play...hahaha he and jacklie played in the hot tub- and when i say play i mean as in totally platonic.&nbsp; and stez was there and casey and auntie Em and hank and you were there too,&nbsp;and nathan awww.&nbsp; and hmm who else? maybe that was it.&nbsp; but it was a gay old time.&nbsp; i couldnt get a hold of emilie.. no one was home when i called goddamnit shes a gooden kidden. Hmm i tired tonight i think i shall retire.&nbsp;  Until Time Next ... you rectal belch, you!    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Friday has come and gone.&nbsp;&nbsp; Aww night numero uno without the birth givers.&nbsp; Tomorrow i think we may have another little get together on our hands, if you know what i mean bwahahaha. Nothin big though... Adam and Casey set up some lights in the backyard- looks pretty schweet.  Me and jacklie sat in the hot tub while they messed around with the lights and such.&nbsp;  Yeah so i dont have much to say.&nbsp; Noah and Grant are in town with Leslie and Michelle.&nbsp; Schilly kids.&nbsp; I bet they are havin fun! more power to 'em.&nbsp; Welp thats about all for tonight.&nbsp; So remember..... Fight the power- Stay clean.  Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Shalom and congratulations to mi amiga Leslie.&nbsp; She did it.&nbsp; She translated the shit in the previous blog "A palpable hue of anticipation."&nbsp; What a smart girl.&nbsp; Sometimes I don't think she realizes how many things she has to offer.... She has been my best friend since we met in 6th grade, and she still continues to amaze.&nbsp; don't ever lose that light in your eyes sugar :)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  Leslie is one of those&nbsp; people&nbsp;who is radiant in every sense.&nbsp;&nbsp; I remember we used to talk about when everyone would go off in their separate ways, for college and whatknot, and she and I agreed that it would be extremely difficult to make new friends due to&nbsp;our tendency&nbsp; to be shy.&nbsp;&nbsp; However I don't see&nbsp;a problem for her there, I've seen the way people react to her- shes electric.&nbsp; Maybe thats not immediately apparent to her - but every new person we&nbsp;meet just thinks the world of her- and rightly so.&nbsp; Now I could go on about how pretty her smile is- how bright her eyes shine when shes happy- or how refreshing (and to me, flawless) her sense of humor is, but it would be impossible for me to enclose all of these things in just one blog.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; So I will just say this- her beauty is unparalleled, and her modesty is shaded only by her personality, which cannot be outshone.      
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ok this is the second time ive tried to write this blog.&nbsp; my comp was being gay 2 days ago and it wouldnt publish- so here we go again.&nbsp;  We were on the way to butte to see farenheit 9/11.&nbsp; thanx to some people and their damn kids (aka casey and samwel) we were 20 mins late and never made it in.&nbsp; It was ok though i spose- id already seen it in missoula.&nbsp; Jury is still out on this one....  So were sittin in butte with nothing to do and its just me nathan casey zacher and stez ended up going to hastings and wal mart-yay heh- it was ok though.&nbsp; We came home it was a lil after 12 1230 maybe and me case and nathan chilled here for awhile.&nbsp; watched some of tyson and phillips band on caseys cam- i want to go see those guys.&nbsp; i bet they are good live. Jaclie and adam came for a lil while but everyone pretty much had to go home so a lil after 1 they left....except nathan.&nbsp; he and i hung around till about 230.&nbsp; I felt kinda awkward almost- i was glad he was there with me but i didnt really know waht to say.&nbsp; we went out in my backyard for a bit while he smoked a bowl then came back in and watched part of freddy vs. jason. God damnit! I havent seen this kid since he graduated pretty much and now he comes strolling back into our lives.&nbsp; Great timing.&nbsp; I cant let my feelings get the best of me this time.... but hes just so... different- beautifully different ( in a very good way- not like Mr. strange ass mormon man- now that is different to the extreme-bad)&nbsp;&nbsp; Even if i did let my feelings through i know what his answer is. "i just want to be friends"&nbsp;&nbsp; fuck that phrase and all it stands for. &nbsp;That has been my moto pretty much since i&nbsp; discovered the male species, and now ironically and hypocritically ill have to use it soon with Mr. morman.&nbsp; How terrible is that.  How strange is that.&nbsp; that i would actually find someone who liked me.&nbsp; maybe there is hope for me yet.&nbsp; Pff not after i have the 'friends' chat with him.&nbsp; Now i know how jacklie felt with Tony. But anyways  Yesterday i had a party here.&nbsp; Nothin big- kinda tame, really.&nbsp; i had fun though.&nbsp; Nathan brought his guitar and we just kinda drank and chilled in my backyard while he played (what is it with the musical men?)&nbsp; Aww Sam was so funny!&nbsp; i think it was his first time ever being really drunk... he has always been kinda goody goody about it- but he was funny.&nbsp; He bonged 2 beers after he was already wasted and shit just got funnier. but all in all i had a good time.&nbsp; After everyone cleared out it was me jacklie stez and nathan.&nbsp; we talked till about 330-400 then i drove him home and stez left.&nbsp; Ohh and that sweet kid jacklie.&nbsp; I dont know anyone as caring as her.&nbsp; I had to get up early to go sing the anthem at the tourney (which i royally fucked up, being that i was hung over with 3 hrs of sleep and a shitty throat) but when i came home i crashed and jacklie was still here and she cleaned up all the cans and bottles we missed the night before and even washed some dishes- crazy kid.&nbsp; She left 10 dollars too, i dont know why she didnt owe me a damn thing. but i slipped the 10 back into her coat this afternoon :)  Ha well now that i have blabbed for fucking ever I shall retire. Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sausage away!&nbsp; Tonight was one big sausage fest... Haha you sick bastards!&nbsp; Not cock-sausage.&nbsp; actual smoked sausage.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; So here's how it all went down-&nbsp; Jacklie&nbsp;rang me and called out a DQ trip.&nbsp; So we gives Leslie a jingle and shes all like "Huh, what?&nbsp; so we picked her ass up.&nbsp; Then we went to vermeire graphics to get samwell and casey and they were all like&nbsp; "Who, what?"&nbsp; So they jumped on in - in between this we rang Michellie and she goes "Eh, what?"-&nbsp; so now we're back on the road headed to michelle and we're all like "Heed, down now!"&nbsp; so we get to michelle's and we got locked out and its rainin like a mothercocksucker so we huddled together under her door mabobber and theres a big foot print hole in her flowers now.&nbsp; So shes not home -we think- and we run like crazy motherbigchukars to lola's casa- for those playing the home game this is leslies home- and its a wicked run. 3 whole blocks for shat sake.&nbsp; So we get there and casey starts playin the gItar and shit flyin everywhere and theres like ninjas on the lawn so we took zee jeep back down to Michelles right and jacklie jay is all sittin there warm and cozy and sams all like would you like to touch my penis.&nbsp; then we drive me to work and the flamer comes with the fischer and shes all like ohhh i talked to erik... and I'm thinkin wonderful... i told him to go for it are you two hooked up yet?&nbsp; and i said get the fuck biatch.&nbsp; then ross was like you can close and dorothy starts peeling off her mole with her fuckin carpals.&nbsp; crazy!&nbsp; so then we started drivin around again in zee jeep and parked. Oh yeah and somewhere in there we bought sausage and were throwing them at pedestrians and cars and to make a long story harder to follow lola and mick left and we went and watched some robin williams and south park. Until Time Next&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ......Bwhahahahaha.  
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Extreme South Park Weekend is almost over -le sigh- it was a good run.&nbsp;  So art/park is now finished also- the club made 90 some dollars though so hey- it wasnt time to wasted.&nbsp; Yesterday was kinda fun.&nbsp; We ended up just messin around with the hoop.&nbsp; Got to see Nathan too.&nbsp; Havent seen him in a coon's age.. i mean long time.&nbsp; So we all just shot around- then this kid tried to steal a pop and leslie tackled his ass like nobodys business! he ended up fallin on her and hurtin her back but the good news- the pop, or soda for those who are stupid, was recovered. It was some funny shit.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Aww yes this riddle plagged me when i was a youngin and since i have nothing to say please riddle me this: (or should i say translate) &nbsp; Heres&nbsp; &nbsp;to&nbsp;&nbsp; pands&nbsp; &nbsp;pendas&nbsp;&nbsp; ocial&nbsp;&nbsp; hourin&nbsp; &nbsp;harmles&nbsp;&nbsp; smirt&nbsp;&nbsp; hand&nbsp;&nbsp; funlet&nbsp;&nbsp; friends&nbsp;&nbsp; hipreign&nbsp;&nbsp; bejus&nbsp;&nbsp; tand&nbsp;&nbsp; kindan &nbsp; devils&nbsp;&nbsp; peak&nbsp;&nbsp; of&nbsp;&nbsp; noone. &nbsp; If you already know-- dont help anyone else.&nbsp; but if you dont, please translate, put your translation in the comment box and if you are correct... well I'll write a whole blog about you... good or bad.&nbsp;  heh this is kind of gay.&nbsp; but i dont have anything else to write about besides my pathetic life grievences.&nbsp; so Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Aww good times.&nbsp; Art in the Park&nbsp; aka&nbsp; crazy old drunk people make out party. Adam O said he'd let us play his playstation, thank you jesus. finally my nintendo junk can be laid to rest- assuming i ever get to play.&nbsp; I missed most of the extreme south park tonight...weak.&nbsp;&nbsp; this angers me.&nbsp; but it was a good night.&nbsp; so theres this kid right... and well hes really nice, a bit odd most definetly, but nice all the same.&nbsp; what to do?&nbsp; he liked me last week, i dont know about now- i havent talked to him since they got home from the lions thing. &nbsp;i use to like him... maybe i still do, i just waited so long that i think maybe im starting to lose interest.&nbsp; maybe ill see him tomorrow- see what happens.&nbsp; dont ask me why i think about what i think about, besides movies, music, and politics, i probably wont be able to answer any questions- but the phrase 'used to' is that weird?&nbsp; or is it 'use to' is this correct english?&nbsp; it seems odd to me.&nbsp; you always hear it though like in songs and in conversation... "do you remember when we use(d) to..etc"&nbsp; if anyone can answer this question for me id much apperciate it! correct, incorrect whatever.&nbsp; when i typed it above i typed used to but then i had to go back and erase the 'd' because it was weird.&nbsp; hmm, can i have the correct spelling please lol- jessie bob, what a girl Well now that you know how gay my life is and that i have nothing interesting to say please go on enjoying your day!&nbsp; haha.&nbsp; see all you kids later Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Ahh Art in the Park.&nbsp; one of the only things anaconda has to provide its citizens with some entertainment.&nbsp;    Hafta work the key club booth thing tomorrow.... parta me says could be fun... itll make&nbsp;a great bar story.&nbsp;    I havent done a whole lot for key club this summer...feel kind of bad.&nbsp; but hey guilt is half the pleasure...or some such.&nbsp; I dont really have anything to say.&nbsp; We went out dinner over in deerlodge tonight- it was fun.&nbsp;   ...came home...fucked the sleve of his favorite jacket... huh, what- sure.&nbsp; I now realize i use ......&nbsp;&nbsp; too much.&nbsp; I shall try to resist.&nbsp;&nbsp; one of the few pleasures in my life gone- just like that.&nbsp;&nbsp; Now thats discipline.&nbsp;   Welp kids- have a good one&nbsp;&nbsp; and remember&nbsp;&nbsp; Only You -- can suck good, nay great, cock.   Until Time Next   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The man is dead.   I think i need to go to SPA meetings... in fact my friends agree.  I'll go (to South Park Anonymous) and I'll stand up and say... "My name is Kaitlin... and I... I'm addicted to South Park."  then the guy in the back will be like "Thats nothing, I suck cock for crack"  lol.  I think Michelle and perhaps Jessie (?) and I were discussing this the other day.  But i seriously have a problem.  We'll be sitting there calmly talking and I'll start talking like Cartman... or some other character on the show (not that you can tell, because my impressions are mediocre at best) but weird shit that is,or should be on south park comes out of my mouth.  Aww so is life.  It always seems like at least sometime in the year, once or nine time, Leslie or I goes into south park mode... ha i remember she watched the move everyday like 8 times... i bet she could recite it even now.  Some peoples kids... i tell ya.  Ive been on a serious nintendo junk for a few weeks now... grr.... the bad part... i dont have a nintendo.  i got this chair though and it sits there and i think god damn i need a remote to play with.  the remote to the fun just aint cuttin it anymore.  Maybe ill get my Super out- its been awhile.  I only have like 3-4 games though and i either cant get passed one spot and spend hours, days, nay weeks trying to beat it or i play the other ones i know by heart.  its a crazy world we live in.  I say it to you now.  ANYONE BUT BUSH 2004!!! Please folks... if youre reading and you intend to vote, remember these words.  The man is an idiot.  It boggles my mind that legal US citizens who lived most of their lives here that just happened to be born in another country cant be president (huh hmm.. michelle) but we can have a rich- dumbass oil man  who cant speak the language as the leader of our country... you cant speak the language- get the fuck out of the oval office.  crickey! Well enough from me.  I bid you adu or whatknot.  Until Time Next 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Aww yes my friends... South Park Season 4.  If there is nothing else in this world that gives me a break from reality (well, anything that is legal...bwahaha) it is South Park. Life in Candyland is just peachy.  I wish i could paint- it might be fun, but you know how people just stay in states, like if they get brain damaged at a certain age and they cant learn anything beyond that...well thats me, except with art- i have the talent of a 5 year old... hell maybe 4.  All i know is that leslies kid sister surpassed my artistic talent long ago.  Blogs are weird.  well mine are.  They remind me of that movie with Nicholaus Cage and Chris Cooper -Adaptation- Cage is always talking to himself in his head and he just goes off about stuff like how weird he is and his faults and what hes doing and well... to make a long story short thats how i feel when i write here- knowing damn well no one will read this, and praying that no one will.  It's better than a journal though, for one-I'd rather type,  and for two- well theres always that feelin of living on the edge, that ~what if someone does read this.. ha, how gay will they think i am... but i am pretty stupid, i guess its time for people to know that~   anyways on with the show.  My mom called me  elitist    today.  I dont think i am.  picky yes, god knows i am, but elitist... there are so many people out there 90 times worse than i can imagine, so i guess what i am saying is i disagree with my mom.   Aww Rian.. he is my favorite nephew.. and only one.  I love the kid- his laugh lightens my day.  Anyhoo... i think i have babbled enough for tonight.   So In the words of Cartman...  "Do not open your eyes until moring, or else i will kick you in the nuts...square in the nuts"  Until Time Next 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I find myself.... at a loss.  I'm always at a loss.  My horoscope says, and I quote, "Your Good Samaritan side is fading. You are used to thinking about others before thinking about yourself."  Could this be right?  I don't think so.  you know maybe there are truly people out there who do not think of themselves first, but i have yet to meet one, present company included.  I find that more often than not if i do something good for another person that im only doing it to help myself.  Whether it be trying to gain more trust from another person or even gain a connection.  There are so few people i feel connected to.  I used to feel like i was apart of something ya know.  Ha  how incredibly presumptious of me.  Bwahaha  as i look back and read this i can see why people like blogs.  it does kind of feel good talking about this stuff... its as if i had a close friend who was slighty interested in seeing  me , not in seeing how i can smile for- and please the crowd.  I read this kids quote and though i cant remember the exact words, it said something like,  "Those words, at best, were worse than teenage poetry."   How true about me.   Until Time Next. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well last nights party was kicked off by a good rainstorm.  It was fun though, well i had fun anyways.  The only part that sucked big white ass was that not everyone could come.  There was no Leslie,  no Michelle,  no Emilie, no zacher, stez, jessie....and a few more.  I missed those guys- it just wasnt complete without them!  Maybe next time though.  Nathan came!  I was excited.  and a lot of people came too.  well not a lot but over 10 id say. lol.  Ashley josiah and travis made a trip out so that was cool, but then josiah and i got in a fight over politics (pff i was messed up and i still kicked his ass in a debate, well i thought i did) and so he got angry and left lol.   Aww well.... now i have to start my 45 days over.  damnit i was doing so well too!  i bet i was at 30-sum.  oh well i can do it.  It was just that he offered so i had to oblige the offer man... that stuff is too expensive for me  to but by myself, and id probably get ripped off i did buy it myself.  I ended up sleeping on the floor cuz there was 7 people and 6 sleeping spots but i didnt mind.  Nathan and i stayed up and talked a little bit from across the room while everyone was sleeping, so that was pretty cool.  He said we have to go sleep out under the stars some night- that would be sweet- so yeah i dont really know what else to say so im going to head out.  I'll catch you later internet gods.   G-night and all that silly such Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Aww man, it was broad daylight.... I cant believe it.  I just reached down and took a nice long scratch.  It was crazy.  There was a bunch of people driving by (that had to happen, everyone i know just happens to drive by at that moment)- fucking henry winkler drove by on a harley and was like- "Ehhh"  and gave the thums up.  Fucking crazy.  But man.... did it ever itch. I never thought my knee could itch so bad. Jacklies back!  Hooraa!  she brought me the coolest present.  A pipe.  i was so excited, my very first pipe, and from tijuanna at that!  I think ill call him Paco.  Perhaps ill try it out at the party tomorrow night.  well tonight i spose!  Yay.  Man today was sweet.  got to see jacklie and nathan came and played with us cuz all of his family is gone finally.   I think today was the most productive day of the summer for me.  Went got my schedule, out to lunch, goosetown, volleyball, work, and then came here and played.   I hope vball is fun this year- last year man!  thats crazy too.  Eat shit merhensy!  Oh no, poor joe, he has no...VAGINA! :)  aww good things.  Mosseltoff.  i wonder how you spell that.   but anyway i watched a good episode of bill maher last night.  bill maher- he kills me.   Welp i best get some rest i think ill need it for tomorrow!  i hope everyone can come!  that would be really cool! Good night Internet gods. "Im thankful for tucker transportation, and the fucks they hire to drive" Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       JeesChries.   HOLY SHIT.   Tonight was a pretty normal night, Leslie and i had some fun and went to Anchorman, which i thought kicked ass.  Then it all took a turn for the worst.  I gave Leslie a ride home.  I came back, was getting out of my car when i decided i had to talk to erik.  he was just getting off.  So i drive down there.  And go talk to him- i say something like this     Erik, i dont know if there was something going on between us ( he nods his head yes and this is where i stopped)  Erik says.  yeah i like you a lot.  -this is where im thinkin ohh great, im going to hell for hurting a mormans feelings-  the rest is a little bit blurry so ill sum it up.   I say i think it would be cooler if we were just friends, and that i can see us having way more fun on a platonic level.  And he says.  yeah i was thinking about us and well youre going to be gone in a year and ill still be here ( like we'd still be together in a year) and i can see where you are coming from (hmm i really wasnt coming from there but ok)   So then he gets out of his truck and gives me a hug.  and we talk normal.  He goes Are you coming to my birthday shindig- yes.  And i said we were havin a little cabin get together (well knowing he wouldnt be able to come)  and you should come out.  And then i dont really remember stuff after that but then it goes something along these lines.  So you know what we have to do now.  And i said, no..... i have no idea.  (what was he geting at, i could not comprehend.... then it came)  Kiss.  I get to kiss you before you leave.  HOLY SHIT.   Who says shit like that right after theyve gotten the talk??? So what was i supposed to do?  run and hide?  well i didnt.  i closed my eyes.  and then it was over.  AAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHh What the fuck just happened!! Then he preceeded to give me another hug.  like i didnt feel dirty enough already.  Christ! So he says youre a good person and dont ever change and then i began to walk away.  And as he was driving by me he goes-  Now dont go home and cry about this. WTF.. seriously.  im still contemplating this whole situation!  He had to fuck with my mind.... AHHHhhh  what happens now.  Am i going to cringe everytime i see him... Arg.  Will i have to face his parents again?  eh... thats crazy i hope not!   And to make me seem more terrible than i already know i am, as soon as i got out of his sight i had to wipe my mouth off.... i was to disgusted.   when i was driving home i just felt gross and all i could think about were how bad his lips were chapped.  I guess he had worked for 8 hours or whatknot but hey. AHHHHHHH.  I'll be the only person in Le group to go to hell for messing with a mormon (not that i already wasnt going to hell for all the crazy things Le group has done) Ya know, he was probably the nicest guy that i would ever get and i sent him off packing.... just shows to go ya.   Oyyy i came home and just let out my frustrations.  thank god noone was here.  Then i talked to leslie and she calmed me down a bit- thanks guy!   im still kinda freaked out right now though.   I feel like i should be pacing back and forth, or verbally expressing how much i think Bush is an idiot and bears a striking resemblence to a monkey.   Aww maybe i should go to bed and tomorrow none of this will have happened.  No no.  i think i shower first and then i can go to bed clean.  then ill wake up and nothing will have happened.  yes good plan.  "I'm thankful that god is full of forgiveness." Until Time Next- when everything will be alright again  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Alone, alone alone.  jesus what kind of person spells alone with a G instead of an E  along/alone- not quite the same thing.  sorry.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       On my own again/ along again natually.  :)   Aww Joe just called.  I havent heard from him in forever!  It was awesome talking to him.  He's just a family friend, but he's a really cool old guy.  He's gay and its too bad that some people have problems with gay people cuz he is one of the coolest persons ever.   He said he's comin into town next saturday!  yay!  leaves sunday, but thats ok.  It's his birthday today and he's all alone, so we had a good talk.  Happy Birthday kid!  Other than that the day has been pretty uneventful.  Michelle and i went to goosetown though so that was good!  and then i went to work... hooraw.   Last night was pretty cool though.  Leslie and i made a cool slide show- its pretty schweet.   Then i took a hot tub and it was the coolest- i saw 21 shooting stars!  Who sees 21 shooting stars in one night, honestly.  but i did.  i was out there for about 2 hrs though.  but it was good.  well mostly.  i started thinking though- cuz there was nothing else to do besides think and enjoy the water.  when i start to think its scary.  i dont like thinking and reflecting.   i psych myself out.  The shit that goes through my head made me sad but i couldnt stop thinking - damnit i hate when that happens.  its different if youre thinking about something but its when youre thinking about nothing that anything can make its way through your brain, like how pointless you are and that you havent done anything youve set out to do or anything at all for that matter.  Point being i dont like thinking about nothing and maybe thats why i watch so much TV when im home... i get to think about what other people have already thought about and therefore make no challenge to myself.  but yeah.  Erik came to the show tonight. i didnt know waht to say to him so i didnt say anything really just made small talk when i should have been telling him that i just want to be friends -grr i still hate that phrase and the fact that i, of all people, will have to use it.  Hmm what else to say to the internet gods..... I cant think of anything.  So perhaps i shall depart.  Until Time Next   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ha.  I second that rainbow!   Tonight was pretty sweet!  Did some dinner at the mesquite place, which was only satisfactory since i didnt get my G-D pop till i finished eating, went to King Arthur.  I dont know if i liked it or not though.... Leslie and i were havin too much fun making fun of it to actually watch it- except the ice battle scene- now that was intense, am i right or am i right?  Aww it was funny.  Leslie and i cant watch movies together- whenever we do it ends up the same most the time- we laugh and make fun and the rest of the theatre cant hear over us.  Why dont they kick us out you ask.  Good question.  Perhaps it's because we work there. ha.  3 days a week for me man.  tough shit lemme tell ya.  But yeah makin fun of shit is definetly fun.  shizza havent done it in awhile.  I dont know anyone who can make fun of movies like leslie and i can- we're pros man.   After the movie Michelle and Leslie went home and adam Em and i played here for awhile and sam came a little later too.  Adam showed me how to convert MOV. files to AVI. files so now the movies i take on my dig. camera i can actually use!  i was excited.  It doesnt always work (theres always a catch) but its better than nothing.  Aww man and Emilie couldnt hear the shit adam was sayin cuz he mumbles and she interpreted it in some pretty interesting ways -hence, I'll rainbow to that. :)  Shes a kick.    Aww crikey.  I dont want summer to end.  i hate school and its my last year and i dont want to face that.  i dontwant to fill out the forms and i dont want to make choices and i definetly dont want to leave my friends! But anyhoo, this is like day 4 and 3quarters without seein nathan- weak dude.  michelle called him earlier but he wasnt home.   I wonder if he's done hangin out with us again.  Hmmm that would probably be better for me- but i dont wanna stop hanging with the kid- he's cool. Hmm i dont know what else to talk about.  Well i could talk about a lot but its rather a case of me wanting to end this conversation with myself and the net gods.  so i will.  I choose conclusion! "I'm thankful for the movie industry and the shit that they produce!" Until time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Aww today was a good day.  You know what they say- the sun will come up tomorrow.  and the sun did come up thank god.  Im lucky in many ways.  I got to see adam and sammy today!  Adam had work to do on me comp and sam just came with him it was good to talk.  Then i had to work and i saw leslie, she and michelle got back from idaho and said it was a pretty good time, and then came home and ate some subway and adam came down and then leslie came up and sammy showed back up And now im talkin to michelle on the net and shewrote me a comment that was so sweet! .  aww i missed my friends i dont know what ill do without them.  The only one still missing is jacklie- the tijuanna trekker herself.  Hmm the daily show is on now.  bill clinton is on tonight.  so i think i will watch this one- see what goes down.  g'night.  P.S. tomorrow will be fun! "Im thankful that the sun came up" Until Time Next    
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tra fucking laa. Finally got Monaghans cleaned. what a bitch. i was there for 6 hours- thank god for the sun screen. I fear I'll always be a white bastard. My part burt so i cant brush the hair and eventually it will peel. yay. And now ill bitch about something else. Hmm........... Tonight is numero dos without human contact. Ok so i did see the birth givers briefly, and i did go to work tonight but that doesnt count- just talked to spenser who proceeded to tell me that my sister was hot. Yes Tricia Hoiland, formerly Leary, was a fine bitch but now shes older and less pretty, not to mention a wife and mother. And i dont really care for High School freshman to think of my sister that way.... its great. Im sorry im such a fucking dog but hey. Im livin my life better than she did. No Im not..but i like to think i am- better for my self perception. Im mean. listen to me. Oh well. I love the sis but i hate being compared to her, im no comparison. anyway. i did see the parents tonight- guilt trip number 90,000 from good ol double D. (heh that makes me laugh) Faja- im sorry the phone was off the hook and you thought i was dead so you had to travel 27 miles back in to town deciding on whether or not to make my funeral a closed service. Shit happens eh. I talked to michelle today, briefly, so that was good- some friend contact. ? GD 2 days jacklies been gone- this is gonna be a tough week. I'm old and bitter. somebody buy me a lexus. ha. (it works) Nathans cousins from cali are in town so who knows if ill see him this week. he said we'd hang out sometime.... but who knows. i havent heard from him since friday. Arg its only sunday! AHHHHHHHHHH    I'm so tired of being a fucking statistic!  So I'll change my ways..... only to become but a different statistic  . yes. the fucking glory of america right here. Tonight that fat fuck janitor called me a liberal. Well thats makes person # 2 so maybe i am a liberal. its odd though the 2 people accusing me of being liberal id say are conservative bastards. Michelle made a good point though- she said that they probably dont consider themselves conservative either. who knows eh! Well ive bitched my frustrations out. well some of them. Bitching is stupid. I shall resist in the future. Theres no point to it really. So i figure ive watched a total of 16 and a half hours of tv since yesterday. Bwahaha. im loving it. Maybe if i didnt watch any tv i could convince Ralph Nader not to run for president. Haahaha i kill myself. I love the nightlife i like to boogie... bla bla bla bla all night long. hmm flashback. i think thats from Srg. Bilco. which i havent seen in a coons age. (Note to self: Dont say 'coon' at least i wont get shot here theres no black people- im not racist i swear that word just comes out) Now another movie begins on tv.. opening credits.... its greek, opening like my big fat greek wedding...but what is it. This is a new one to me. Hmm ill change the channel when i get off my fat ass. Aww jesus its a woody allen film. Im glad he hasnt made anything recently he pisses me off. Im glad betty stayed with me. I love my betty shes the coolest! She should have gone to the cabin though, she likes it there best and probably resents me now because she had to stay here to 'protect' my pathetic self. She could be out there roaming the lake, taking big shits that i wont have to pick up. (for those of you playing the home game shes a dog- and i think im dyslexic because i literally just spent a minute trying to type dog...kept coming out god) Hmmf anyhoo ill wake up tomorrow and double D and the mother and my betty will already have been at the lake for 4 or 7 hours. and ill watch more tv hooowah! But i am gonna get off the comp and back to my couch. "Thank you jesus- Im thankful for my faithful companion Betty" Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Stetz.... He says the coolest things.   It's not really what he says its how he says it.  it funny. Well today was jacqueline's birthday- Happy Birthday Jacklie (even though you dont read this ha)  I love Jacklie!  I love lots of people though!  I love Emilie- shes such a badass, she even sits through our boring politcal talks,  and Adam- hes the coolest nephew i have (hahaha who i might have gotten a little to close to back in the day)  and Amanda- defintely the coolest niece i have!   Leslie- well i wrote a whole blog on why leslie is the coolest girl...in the world :)  and Michelle- our talks are the best, she helps me out a lot  and Jessie- shes a youngin too but she sure knows how to party(been awhile though)  Jon- what a sweetheart (he smells the best!!!!!!!) Sammy-  he is a funny kid and very caring i hope he doesnt move away and leave me id be sad.  ohh and theres more.  The extended fam.  Whom i dont know as well but are still the coolest people Nathan, Stetz, Zacher.  hmm theres probably more.  i forgot and im sorry.  ill get them in here later though.  like casey- the real family so he doesnt really count, but a cool kid anyhoo. I dont know what i would do without these people.  My life would be empty.  and next year when we all leave i think im gonna have a tough time at first.  ehh we will see.  Bush is an idiot Aww jesus sorry i dont know where that came from just popped out.  Its true though. Last night we had a party at me cabin.  It was pretty sweet.  casey was fucking toasted  after drinkin 13 beers and bonging one last one he was pretty much a goner.   It was funny though Sam passed out at like 10 30 ..pff pussy :)   so it was me jacklie and nathan watchin casey jackassing around  Then casey dropped off and soon jacklie did and it was just nathan and i... nothing happened godamnit!  we just sat by the fire till like 4 30 then talked awhile in the kitchen...  He's cool.   DAMN ME.  why cant i just be more guylikeable.  there was Erik but hes a little mental so... doesnt count.  Well i know my problem, and i hate myself for it.  Anyway.  jacklie is off to tijuanna and michelle and leslie are in idaho with their men and i dont think ill be goin out for awhile so there will probably be a few more entries before the weeks over.   Tomorrow i actually have to clean monaghans damnit!  ive said it forever but tomorrow is the day.  have to do it.  well i dont know what else to say really so i guess im just gonna head- going off for a promising tomorrow.  -I'm thankful for cocoa pebble beach at night with the stars- Until Time Next   
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I can spell i promise!  well maybe not.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Ho Hum.  I was a downright bitch today. P.S. I'm sorry i didnt make it to the meeting today.   Warning  ---Stop Right Here!----   My poor mother.  I gave her shit for 8 hours today.  She took it well.  When she finally called me i shut up.  Good thing too i hate when i act like that.  I dont know why i do it.  part of me wonders if thats who i really am though- ive seen myself that way before and im sure it will happen again but i usually feel like i should be kicking my own ass.  I am scared when i grow up and settle down ill ease into that and my life will go to shit cuz nobody likes a Deuschy such as my other side.  I said rude things all day and i criticized everything!  And my poor mom she started talking about Denny.... ( dead husband, dad's brother..etc)  because we were in helena where they lived together and my sister was born and there was a real senserity in her voice ya know..... like remembering the good life that has long since passed you by.  we had to drive by their old house and there was a crack in her voice as she said that he was a very nice person, And i know she put it lightly for me, she would have cried- I know it!  if she wasnt being strong for me i think she would have lost it there.  she loved him way more then she ever loved my dad... not that she doesnt love him, but ya know first loves and she and Den had the whole fairy tale falling in love thing even though they lived in a shitty small place they were happy and really in love.  Ive only ever seen pictures of the man, but there was a softness in his eyes that i can sometimes see in my mothers eyes and i know shes looking for it in my dads eyes.... and well its just not there.   My dad seems to take advantage of all she does for him ( i do too, so what am i talking about?) he remembers how important she is to him a few time a year, but its sad that he doesnt sit her down and tell her that he loves her like 80 times a day- thats what she deserves!  At least i tell her i love her, even if im being silly when i say it, she knows i mean it.     Well to make a long story short i treated my mom like shit and i dont know why.  Dont know why i did it and i dont know why she let me- she always lets me... maybe she loves me too much, but im glad, she makes me feel relevant.  Ha- a person only a mother could love.  How typical. She said something in anger i dont think she would have said if i didnt really push her to it- wasnt even that bad, but i felt it- it hurt.   Remind me to tell my mom i love her tomorrow. If you read to the bottom of this blog i apologize!  Im stupid! "I'm greatful my mommy loves me" Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Haha thats crazy! i think the TV just spoke to me... (Im talkin about the title) The TV speaks to me often. Hmm, From Dusk Till Dawn.... i havent really been watching but i dont think im digging it. I'm talking about a Great White chiefy! :) So yeah. today was good. I woke up round 12 went to a bridal shower... god my face hurt- i think once i got in my car to start driving i still had the fake "smile for the family" smile on. Long gone now though- i hate that smile. I like real smiles and real laughs although i give more than my fair share of fake ones. Hmm i just realized my undies are inside-out. fucking Crazy. But yeah after the bridal shindig Michelle and I went to goosetown. It felt really good to do something. We decided that we'd start going regularly- we'll see. i hope so. Then went home, let the tv speak to me took a shower and went to get michelle for some dinner(gained back the calories.) Jacklie wasnt home and leslie already ate. Afterward we drove around. It was Awesome! we had such a good talk. I enjoyed it muy. It's good to talk about anything, or nothing whatever it may be. I like communicating, i cant stand the people who are intellectually lower than or at about the same level of just their stereos- or trumpets, ah hmm humm hmm. Dont get me wrong, music is life. But i mean it as if you cant get past... well fuck to put it bluntly i just mean those who are intellectually challenged. Hmm. perhaps thats bad to say but thats all that comes out.   Haha casey took this pic of Janni and sam pulled his ass out just in time for jonni's sweet little head to hit his cheek.  now that is a great picture!!  Aww janni he is such a sweetie i dont know if he was just being nice but he looked at my senr pics (why so early!) and told me that i was a vision.  Jonni jon jonny :)  beautiful boy.  No nathan today- perhaps tomorrow ehh?!  Well anyhoo im gonna hit the hay.  And for today....I'm thankful for my wonderful friends!!  (as michelle might say) Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hmm mixed feelings at the moment.  Im happy because i got to see Nathan and pretty happy cuz today was a good day all in all and michelle and i watered flowers and talked and it was really cool- perhaps the best talk ive had in ...... well a long long time.  sometimes its nice to be serious.  But anyways i feel kind of guilty right now.... or maybe sad... im not to sure.  I just read leslies blog and it made me feel 'blue'   blue yes thats the word for it.  She seems so.... alone perhaps.  I never wanted to see leslie like that, not that i havent before, but i hate it when shes sad because she deserves so much more.  And i know she doesnt want my pitty or my appology and i know that i dont help her sadness any... but i dont know what to do.  There are few situations i have gone through in my life where i didnt have the faintest clue on what to do...but this is one of them.   Im glad she has michelle to talk to.  Seems like shes the only one who can get through...but i dont know much- and i dont pretend to.  Tonight we were supposed to call les but didnt get done watering flowers till 10:30 cuz we had to fill the tank a few times and it was being a bitch, when we got here i kinda went up stairs and cleaned up for awhile and then it was pretty much 11.  most everyone was gone at like 12, except casey and nathan who stayed to play some PS2 , and it was kinda a gay night.  Casey said he did call leslie but that it was busy and then she wasnt on the net...or something, this was the translation i got anyway.  But i feel bad about that, she sat home, and like a D-bag I didnt get a hold of her.   Ya never know if ya can trust people to actually call someone when they are supposed to... cough cough  casey....  but i should have brought a cell or something- my bad there.   But anyways enough about that i cant dwell on what i did wrong today.    We did all go to the lake today.  Molly, the lil tike, came and was an absolute shit- which we didnt help matters cuz we egged her on.  I guess she wasnt that bad- but emotions ran high.  it was cool though  we swam which felt really good!  i needed that. i wanna go out there and just float one of these days.  Hmm not much else to say.  I'm thankful for the O'brien who decided to leave the PS2 for another day! Until Time Next  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>