<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i should be sleeping right now... it's 3.30 am...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink my so-called life... 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      What i learned from Max Bickford....  	i was watching 'The Educaton Of Max Bickford' a few minutes ago... and by that, i meant it ended a few minutes ago, not that it started a few minutes ago, in case some of you do not belong in the DNRC (in-duh-viduals) ... it was the September 11 episode... gotme thinking about some stuff... it's my blog, so i'ma write it down...  	firstly, i have a question. lets say you work in an orchard... your 'boys' have picked all the apples and arranged 'em in big, huge wicker baskets... you randomly pick one apple, bite into it, and find a fatass worm in it... but you eat it anyway... but that's not the point...   my question is, would you throw you the whole basket of apples (it's big, so there are probably 100-200 apples in it) just because one apple was bad? well, unless you're an idiot, you won't, right?   so why do people discriminate against one whole race just because of one bad apple?  	take, for example, Osama, or whomever masterminded the Sept.11 thing. i mean like, out of like, 11 MILLION arabs, a few jackasses wanted a free ticket to hell. so, why were anyone who were arabs discriminated? i mean like, according to what i heard in CNN or read in the news, anyone who were arabs, or at least LOOKED like arabs, were put down as potential terrorists. SOME people see an arabic looking guy walking down the street, they shun him and call the cops who go over and ask for his ID, with the safety pins on their Sig Sauers off. i mean, who cares if it was his GRANDPA who came from  the middle east, and he probably knows every word in the Constitution and/or the National Anthem  (which is more than i could say about most citizens in any country), but still, hey, he has dark skin, has a goatee (coz his gurlfriend told him it looks cute), he must have a bomb in his pocket and probably knows Osama. i mean, come on! can anyone stand up and tell me that's not bullshit?  	look, i respect the need for security. being lax in a time like this is stupid. that's like going to the projects wearing a Ku Klux Klan hood (remember Scary Movie 3 :D) . but (i think) there should be a limit to this... i mean, isn't america all about freedom? where's the dude's freedom in the above situation? i admit, i have never been in your situation, where your country is at war, and national security is threatened (damn, i'm lucky i'm in Malaysia... most peaceful place to be!!!)... PERHAPS i would be paraniod if i was in that situation. maybe not. hopefully not. but i plan to continue my education next year at Purdue University, Indiana. but that's not the point.  	what i'm trying to say is... perhaps we all should give people a chance... i mean, i am totally against labelling a whole race or summin just because of some idiots... because i know how it feels... as some of you might (or might not) know, malaysia is a multiracial country. the three major races here are the Malays (those who's ancestorial roots are in this country), the Malaysian Chinese (malaysian, but have ancestorial roots in China), and the Malaysian Indians (malaysian with ancestorial roots from India - my great-grandma moved from a village in South India and came here). Malaysia is more of a cultural mosaic, not a melting pot.  	in my school, a majority of Malaysian Indian boys don't really come from a privileged background. some of them have serious disciplinary problems at school. gangs, smoking, stuff like that. but, because of that, most people and teachers who see me, a big-bodied, tough-looking dark-skinned dude, they ASSUME i'm a gangsta-type dude too. But, the harsh reality is, i'm NOT! i'm a very gentle guy, polite, very well-mannered, and don't forget smart (no.3 in the whole school). but, newbie teachers, or those who don't know me, they see me, and they assume i'm a dangerous guy to be around with. of course, those who got to know me have a lot of respect for me (hehe... :D:D:D)   	what i'm trying to say is, don't judge a book by it's cover.  	anti-semitism is another example, but i really don't want to get into that now.  	i mean, what do you think about this? i hope reading this has somehow sparked off some neurons in your brains... i'm a very non-judgemental guy... i don't think that anyone is inherentmy bad, or good... your enviroment shapes the way you turn out... i mean, some terrorists... they are who they are because the enviroment shaped them... the people, the physical enviroment... i'm a peace loving guy... but with people with a set mindset who do terrorist actions, and wor-mongering presidents like Dubya around... it's just like a cycle... somehow it got started... then america under GBsenior went to war with iraq... then on September 11, some idiots retaliated... then another war-mongering idiot goes to war with THE WHOLE BLOODY COUNTRY over something some people did... then he moves to ANOTHER country... attacking it in a made-up accusation (where are those nukes, goddammit? :P)... sooner or later, someone's gonna strike back... and there it goes again... until we have someone smart enough to put a stop to this... yeah, after my death, most likely...  	i'm sorry if i offended anyone... that wasn't my intention... and like i said, i don't believe, like , all americans or all arabs are so-and-so just because of a few individuals... i'm an individualist... every person is unique... i just hoped i made you think about this...  -MistaMugie-
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Stolen from someone's Blog   www.mistamugie.blogspot.com  1) Starting time: 12.15AM 2) Full Name: Mugilan Joorindanjn 3) Nicknames: Mugie, MistaMugie, The Great Sex God, The Great God-Like Dude, Mugi-Mugi, Abang Mugie, and.... JMG!!! 5) Email: Rather not get a virus, so if ya wanna kno, send me a message =P 6) Eyes: Black! 7) hair: Black! 8) Height: 6"2' 9) Sibling(s): 1: Sister and one godsister 10) Ever been cheated on: Yes, bloody spanish lottery scammers... aaargh!!! 11) Ever missed school because it was raining: Yep! for the heck of it :P 12) Ever Set any body part on fire for amusement: my hair... once... 13) What's your favorite number? 1! coz i'm no1! :D 14) Ever have an imaginary friend? yeah... she's really fun to be with... we even have imaginary sex... okay now, THAT was wierd... 15) Ever wanted to hook up with a friend of the opposite sex? D'oh... of course... i look gay to you? 16) Ever cried during a Flick: Nope! not even [tit]anic...  17) Ever had a crush on a teacher: Yeah... lotsa times... 18) Ever thought of animated characters as hot: Yeah... especially anime chicks... i'm not into hentai, though.... that is just.. wierd... 19) Ever at anytime owned a 'New Kids On the Block' album: No 20) Ever prank called someone: doesn't everybody? 21) Been on stage: Yeah, since i was a kid...  -----------------FAVORITES--------------  22) Shampoo: Pantene Dandruff control... yes, i have dandruff... hate it... 23) Color(s): Black, blue, green... 24) Summer or Winter? Malaysia is like, eternal summer... except when it rains... 25) Thing online to do: check my email, my friendster account, tblog, and... i dunno... 26) Lace, silk or satin? Silk.. more sensual... 27) Like Anyone? Yeah 28) Who have you known the longest of your friends: Kohila, i guess... 7 years... 30) Who's the shyest friend you have: Reen!!! 31) Who do you go to for advice: Kohila, Reen, Din, Ejan... bestest friends a guy could get! y'all don't know 'em, but they're really great! 32) Who do you get along with: Almost everyone... almost...  -----------IN THE LAST 2 WEEKS HAVE YOU------------  33) Cried? No 36) Been sarcastic: Daily... i learn from the best... my EST teacher... Misz.Chin... really, every word she says just oozes with sarcasm... 37) Met someone new: Yes 38) Talked to someone you have a crush on: Yeah... this really cute gurl at my tuition centre... i said hi, she said hi with a really cute smile, and i just *melted*... 39) Missed someone: Yes 40) Hugged someone: Yes 41) Fought with your parent(s): No 42) Wished upon a star: No 43) Laughed until you've cried: yeah... the "she's awake!!!' part of Scary Movie 3.... other than that part, it's kinda boring... 44) Played Truth or Dare: yeah/// 45) Watched a sunrise/sunset: No 46) Went to the beach at night: No 47) Read a book for fun: yeah... i guess i'm a bookworm... 49) Are you lonely: Yes 50) Are you happy: Yes 51) Are you talking to someone online: Yes  ----------DO YOU BELIEVE IN -----------  52) God and/or Devil: Both? 53) Love: Yeah 54) The Closet Monster: oh yeah, and lets not forget leprechauns, shall we? [refer to Question 36] 55) The Big Bang Theory or The Shorted Big Bang Theory: Yes... does kinda make sense... 56) Heaven/hell: Yeah 57) Superstitions: Not usually  --------------------Anything----------------------  58) Name on birth certificate: Uhhh stupid look at my full name 59) Who named you?: My dad's friend... it means 'the person in the sky' so summin like dat... 60) Backstreet Boys or N Sync: Eminem 61) When was the last time you showered: 9.15am yesterday.. 62) What was the last thing that you said when u were online? hey! 63) What is right next to you: My bed... 64) What is your computer desk made of: Wood... 65) What was the last thing that you did? typed 'wood'. 67) Where would you want to go on your honeymoon: Phuket... or somewhere really quiet...  68) Who do you want to spend the rest of your life with: the one and only person for me... haven't met her yet... 70) What did you do yesterday/today: studied chemistry... mopped the house... ate... shat (past tense for shit, also known as shitted) 71) Thing that you find attractive about the opposite sex: for me, the smile is very important... if she can make my heart melt... the personality... i like girls who can make me laugh... a sense of humour... physically? a nice butt would be a major plus point... :D 72) How do YOU eat an Oreo: um... put the whole thing in my mouth, and chew, i guess... 73) All time favorite TV show: Phua Chu Kang, anything funny... Seinfeld, Futurama... 74) Dream car?: a Mercedes S-Class.. 75) What do you want to be when you grow up: Porn Star... actually, an aerospace and aeronautical engineer 77) Favorite music: Gangsta rap, dance... hip-hop... indie-pop... anything except girl/boy bands... 79) Favorite food: anything mom cooks... :D 80) Favorite day(s) of the week: Any fucking days off of school 83) If you could change your name, what would it be: Nobody. So when someone asks who robbed the bank, they would say, “nobody.”  84) Do you sleep with a stuffed animal: my teddy bear... :D 85) The most stupid thing you’ve ever done: i dunno.. lots of it... 86)First Son's name: lets cross the bridge when we get to it... 88)First Daughters: see 86 89) Favorite drink: Pepsi Twist Double Shot... plain water... mango juice... 90) You like scary or funny movies better: Funny!!! 91) On the phone or in person: on the phone...  92) Lust or Love: more love... but a lil'bit lust is necessary... 93) If you could change something about yourself, what would it be??: i dunno, hike up my IQ a few hundred points? 94) Do you consider cheerleading a sport: Not unless you consider stripping a sport 95) Do you have pets: My sister. 96) Who sent(OR DID YOU STEAL) this survey to you(FROM): some dude. 97) What do you think of this person: i dunno... 98) Do you want your friends to do this survey: i guess so... 99) Do you ever wanna do this again? Not this same one 100)What time is it NOW: 12.40AM...
     
    
</post>


</Blog>