<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       KNOW I REALLY KNOW YOUR 17 NOT 16. DO YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW OLD I REALLY  AM? IF YOU DO E-MAIL ME.                       I MISS YOU LOTS AND WANT TO TALK.                                          LOVE, MARIAH  
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was just in Wisconsin Dells one week ago. And while I was there I stayed like in the GHETTO it was the worst hotel I mean MOTEL. But the first day (last sunday) me and my friend went swimming at the Flamingo that was the name of the motel we stayed in. So I  thought that this trip is just going to suck!but after hanging on the oh  so cool frog at the outdoor pool me and my friend desided to go to the indoor pool, and in there I saw the most perfect and hot guy, he was playing  basketball inthe pool with to of his friends. My friend turned to me and said look at the one with short brown hair he is hot I said he isn't bad, but that wasn't the one I liked. I said do you like the one with small side burns and brownish swim trunks, she said ISH! As I just sat there she asked if we should ask them to come over I said yeah sure as I was looking at Mr. Perfect so we walked by and looked at them smiling I was looking straight at Mr. Perfect But I was thinking he probably doesn't like me I'm only 14 but soon 15 and he looks like he is 17 which in the end he turns out to be. But ask if they would like to come to the hot tub outside with us the one I like says yeah! the one my friend liked says sure but he doesn't come 'til later. So Mr. Perfect, me, and my friend go to the hot tub. We ask eachother where we are from we are from Minnesota Mr.Perfect is from Indiana,I ask how old are you he says 18, then he said 17 so he asks us we say we are 14, which I really am. He asks what our names are my name is Mariah, my friend just ignores him. I ask him back he says his name is ..............DYLAN!!!!!! Know I don't have to call him Mr. Perfect which I'm not kidding anyone he is. Not much later his teamates come and take him away cause they have to be at there own motel(they were staying at the Monaco)which was right next door. We saw him the next day about lunch time they were playing basketball at our motel, me and my friend went walking past them strutting our stuff j\k and I asked Dylan if he wanted to meet me later he said sure we met at the indoor pool me and my friend were a little late cause we had to go eat( which I ate way to much)we sat in the hot tub which was only hot cause I was in it no i'm just kidding it was hot cause Dylan was in it. Me and Dylan were having fun flirting and splashing water at each other. Then we went to there pool which was more fun cause it had an awsome diving board. we only went on it like 2 or 3 times each, I spent the rest of the time talking to Dylan, and my friend was talking to Willie(he is the guy my friend liked)Dylan wanted to make out with me but I didn't cause me and my friends mom were both wathing. Otherwise I told him I would of! Then me and Dylan were having swimming contests seeing who could make it swimming across the pool while holding our breath, but we both cheated. We cheated by grabbing each others legs or arms, then toward the end I pantsed him then on the way back he pantsed me,but they bearly came down.Then we had to back to our hotel, that sucked I could of stayed there all night with Dylan.Then the next day around 3 o'clock me and my friend walked by there motel and saw them they were about to go to a Tommy Bartlet show, Dylan said that he would meet us later at are motel they didn't come because they didn't get back 'til 11 15 so then the next morning is when we had to leave (they had to leave that day after there basketball game)then we were just walking around then Dylan came over then my friend asked where are your other friends? He said at the motel being lazy then she asked what he was doing and he said he wanted to see us again which I think he meant me well at least I hope so. So then we went over to his motel ( at first he wouldn't come cause he was afraid that his friends would make fun which they did ha ha. Then we got 2 pictures 1 of Dylan and the other of Dylan and Willie. Then me and Dylan walk to the office and get each others email addresses and he gave me his blog spot thing and then I made my own out of boredum. So that is how I met Mr. Perfect, which I miss so much.           
    
</post>


</Blog>