<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I type, Anarchy Online is reinstalling. Bad Maul.  This wouldn't be such a problem, of course, if I didn't have 2 open Star Wars Galaxies accounts, one with a Master Tailor with outstanding orders.   Sure, SWG is fun and all. The social aspects are neat, and SWG Fan Fest was a ton of fun. The Entertainer line of professions are quite cool (except for the fact that we demand more content and never get any), and I like being a crafter.  But the combat...  I don't know how it's any different from Anarchy Online. Don't ask me. It's still the same format; click some buttons and wait and hope you don't die, maybe heal yourself real quick.   Wait- there it is.  Profession balance and diversity.  I tried every AO profession during my 1-2 year stint there at least once for some length of time. I enjoyed every one, for at least some length of time. I didn't feel unbalanced in any of them, except for Adventurer (and that's because I screwed my character up royally). I wasn't trying to run huge raids or anything, just doing missions. And I enjoyed it. I could have 8 characters, so- hey, maybe I feel like some pet class work, and making some money, I log in my Meta-Physicist and run some high-level missions. Maybe I feel like missioning with some friends, I'll log in my gimpy Adventurer and rely on them for help. Maybe I feel particularly brave and log in my Doctor, do some healing. Maybe I feel like being really, really short and sneaking around; I'll log in my Agent. Maybe I feel like running fast and shooting crap, I'll log in my Fixer. Maybe I want to punch things, here comes my Martial Artist. Maybe I want to nuke things and make pretty effects, out goes the Nanotechnician. Maybe I want to use robots and shoot things, yay for my Engineer.   There was so much class diversity, depending upon my mood, I could do whatever I wanted. Or if I didn't feel like really playing at all, grab the pack full of social clothes on my gimpy Adventurer and go do some casual roleplaying. There was SO MUCH TO DO. Everyone always said 'blah blah blah, no high end content.' I never hit high levels, so my characters were always growing and changing. I was always finding something new, due to my many different characters, and I could change at the drop of a hat. Reset points allowed me to toss my skills around, depending upon what I found important. I could be a very fast runner and not have to worry about angry animals with high Run Speed bonuses, or reset all my sword skills and throw them into pistols and change weapons. Sure, it took some work- I needed all new implant layouts and armor- but I was able to change the direction of my character entirely.  The other thing I loved? The community and the world. So many people helped make Rubi-Ka seem truly alive, with a lived in feel. Ships flew overhead. Billboards glared at you in Omni-1 Entertainment advertising everything from armor to drugs to whores (not kidding about those last two...). If you liked to explore- great. There were plenty of hidden 'hot spots' all over Rubi-Ka to go check out. If you didn't, there was very little unnecessary travel. If you're beyond a certain level, just hop in the Grid (the internet in 29000, apparently) and go there. Or take the whompas, though those won't get you everywhere. Roleplayers made up events to create a living, breathing world- illegal leet fights, pitting creatures against eachother, murders, assassinations, parties.   I suppose old habits die hard- it's all coming back to me already. How to cast my pets, how to blitz a mission, how to use the grid, how to find a group, how to dance. How to cast a nano, how to build implants, how to heal someone. The GridStream Productions parties, the indoor missions, the loot you found on almost every dead mob, the abbreviations, Jobe, Omni-1 Trade. And of course, that little voice when you first log in.  Welcome to Rubi-Ka.  Checking integrity....3/50...
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aaahhh. Mr./Ms. Reader, I suppose. Here's a little help from your friend.  Take pen and paper and WRITE IT DOWN!  As you might have already noticed, this blog is called Inofittive. It's called Inofittive because it sounded like a cool name at 4:00 AM.  Got it?  Riiiiiiight.  Inofittive is called Inofittive because, and now, listen carefully- Inofittive is called Inofittive because that's what you get when you combine the opposite of 'out of it' with 'innovative'. Not that this blog is either of those. Now that you're here, try to enjoy it. Read a post or two, or three. Write a comment, send me hate mail...you get the idea. Mainly speaking, try to stay alive.  --  Righto. If you recognized that paragraph, you are a cool guy and have officially played HalfQuake Amen. If you didn't recognize that paragraph, you need to go play HQA right now. Then, and only then, you shall become a cool guy. Or girl. Or transvestite. Whatever.  What REALLY is Inofittive? Someone was like "hey, you're a decent writer. you should start a blog." and I was like "hell no." and they were like "i'll kill you in your sleep if you don't." and I was like "well, ok."   As for the actual content, it's basically whatever I want to put here. Reviews, stories, etc. "REVIEWS, you say?! What makes you a critic?!" you say. Nothing. I ate, drank, played, saw, met someone, listened to something and decided to write a review of it.   Don't like it? Don't read it. No, seriously. Go away. You smell.  Also, please note I probably won't review anything I either didn't really like or really hate. If you want me to review something, comment about it. Maybe I will.  Now then, sit back, relax, and enjoy the show. Except you're going to have to click the links yourself, I'm not doing that for you. Gross.
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tonight, inspired by a Something Awful Forums thread, we have a story. We'll be going into a thankfully not LSD-inspired flashback into my past...      [insert screen wavering and turning white and the 'dream sequence' harp noise.]                        In second grade, for whatever reason, I decided I had a HUGE crush on some kid.    So of course, what do silly second grade girls do? They write love notes. And boy, did I write love notes. I'd sign them as anonymous and stick them in his desk at recess. For a few weeks, people were none the wiser.     Eventually, though, it got out that I liked this kid. For some reason, I wasn't made fun of for it, though I think the poor boy was. :( At the time, it seemed utterly hilarious to chase him around trying to kiss him at recess. The whole school lolled and for a while I was quite popular.    Of course, I realized it wasn't working. He wasn't falling for me like the way I thought he would! So my second-grade brain spins around a bit and finds a perfect solution!    At the end of recess, all the kids would have to stand in a line outside the classrooms before they could be let in by a teacher. One fateful day, while we were all standing in line, I ran up to the kid, kissed him on the cheek, and raced back to the end of the line.     Looking back, I probably could have gotten in trouble for sexual harassment, but our teacher was young and had a good sense of humor and found it hilarious. Score one for me.    That wasn't the end of it, though. A little background: in second grade, I was in a 'split class'- that is, we were one half second graders and one half third graders. It worked out better than it sounds.    The third graders in the class often volunteered to clean up the classroom and clean out people's desks for them. One day, they're cleaning garbage out of the desks, and they get to the boy I liked.    "Ohmygawd, what's this?" One of them pulls out a massive ball of crumpled binder paper scraps. The two gently pull it apart and start reading the scraps- and start lolling their asses off. "They're LOVE NOTES!"    In retrospect, I probably got made fun of to hell for it, but at the time, I thought I was pretty damn cool. :(    I still go to the same school as him. From what I hear, we have a lot in common, but I can see it now- the second I open my mouth, he says "Hey, aren't you that girl that kissed me in second grade?"  
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have discovered the coolest thing EVER.    Its name is "RandomEngy does Half-Life SinglePlayer in 45 minutes, 45 seconds".     You heard me correctly. Someone with waaaay too much time on their hands (who is, apparently, a random engineer from the TFC community) beat HLSP in 45:45. This is friggin' amazing- no, make that aweinspiring.    http://www.planetquake.com/sda/other/halflife.html    This is Half-Life like you've never seen it before. Remember that pesky dam level? RandomEngy's just too cool for stuff like that, and uses the tau gun to jump up on to the canyon wall. He swims into the void, SKIPPING THE ENTIRE LEVEL. Chicks dig guys that play videogames, and they  really  dig guys that play 'em well.    But he doesn't stop with tau jumps. No, no- that just wouldn't be stylish enough. He skips most of On A Rail, too- how does he do it?    By turning about and using tripmines to create a staircase over some pesky rubble.    Now c'mon people, that's just  KICKIN' RAD.      .....but it doesn't stop there.    No, no. He's rocked your face off, he's owned your socks  right off you feet,  but NO! No mercy, because he's about to do something even cooler. You don't see it coming, but      BAM!     And  there it is.  He turns to the floor, pulls out the snarks, and uses them to boost himself over a fence.    HOLY HELL!    But no. No, that's not all. "THERE'S MORE?!" you cry, but yes!  KEEP YOUR FORK, CAUSE THERE'S FUCKIN' PIE!     Your face has been rocked so hard it's melted off, and your socks have been owned so badly they're across the room in a laundry bin, but there's one thing left yet!!    Remember Xen? Remember that horrible, awful, terrible, really-no-good bad cluster of jumping puzzles?     HE SKIPS THE WHOLE THING     Yyyyeeeep. RandomEngy whips out the tau gun and jumps past the entire first level.    And that, my friends, deserves the Nobel Prize of video gaming.    ....    ...actually, I don't even know who RandomEngy is. I just thought the...speedrun was....cool....    :(  
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, this blog entry was ORIGINALLY going to be about my experiences at camp. Then I accidentally hit ctrl-a after an hour of typing and deleted the WHOLE THING.  I'd paste the resulting curses I smashed out to a friend in all caps, but I have friends my age that read this, so it will be censored by the ERSB:  Missmaul54: S*** F***ING H******T C*****E SCHOOLGIRL ROBOT P*** F***BUCKET NutPxxxxxx: what. Missmaul54: i spent like an hour typing a blog entry Missmaul54: then accidentally hit ctrl-a Missmaul54: and just deleted the WHOLE **** ******** **** ********* SAILBOAT **** THING Nuxxxxxxx: osnap. Missmaul54: oh my god i hate the world.  So there you have it, kiddies. No stories for you, thanks to CTRL-A.   To go on and finish typing what I started, the Yay Pit is finally back up. Wheeeeeeeeee!!! Now I can get hit on by horny 8-16 year olds!!! (Yes, I've had 8 year olds try to cyber with me. Nasty.)  I'll post some actual content soon enough. I just got back from camp, bear with me. I just bought Condition Zero, so maybe I'll talk about that next entry or something.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As of tomorrow, I am off to Education Unlimited Computer camp. It's a week long and I'll be back soon. Hopefully I'll be able to post pictures/stories while I'm there.  I'm currently packing, and it's taking forever. I keep thinking I've forgotten something, or have to hide something, or get rid of the stuff under my bed.. >_  In other news, I got my hair cut short. Yaaaay. It's a helluva lot easier to take care of, and I can take 3 minute showers now- no double shampooing required, just lather-rinse-exit. Excellent. Unfortunately, I have to get my hair cut quite often, because if it gets much longer than it is it'll look bad.  The best part is I don't have to worry about it anymore. I can pretend I'm at a Pantera concert, sweep it out of my eyes, and it still looks fine. I hardly have to brush it, or make sure short hair is tucked behind my ears. Currently, I'm just enjoying headbanging randomly and not having to lunge for a brush.  See also: Mohitos are tasty. I don't know exactly what's in it, but something like  Limeade Mint Ice Seltzer  Normally there'd be rum in it, but I'm underage. It's pretty good, try it.  Oh yeah, happy July 4th and all that. Yadda yadda yay go america fireworks hot dogs blahblah have fun. :D  On that note, I'm off to continue packing. So many socks to fold...SO MANY SOCKS... >:|
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Courtesy of Small, I have just been introduced to Invader Zim. Courtesy of a school friend, I have been introduced to Squee.   Jhonen Vasquez is   If you've never discoverd Invader Zim, here's the premise: Aliens known as the Irken have decided to take over the universe (presumably the second time). Shortly after finishing assigning each of the top Irken soldiers to their own planet to conquer, Zim returns from his banishment to Foodcourtia. Of course, the leaders are all too happy to send him on a mission far, far away just to get rid of him- unfortunately, Zim really does find a planet out in the middle of nowhere, known as Earth. Armed with all sorts of Irken gadgets and a crazy robot-dog-thing named Gir, Zim single-handedly wages war on Earth- and the token conspiracy nut, Dib. Wacky hijinks occur.  I can't really explain it any more clearly than that. You just kinda have to see it. The first season is currently available for $25 or so, with 9 episodes and some extra content on it. Nifty!  --  In other news, I am currently listening to an Asian man reproduce Van Halen. On a violin. You heard me correctly.  Sharing the <3: http://www.bobbyyang.com/video/750kb.htm
    
</post>


</Blog>