<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's 11:20 pm and I'm still awake.  Why?  Well I'm 34 weeks pregnant and I have heartburn that would drop a goat... and you know goats, they eat anything so imagine the heartburn goats must get.   I have 900 channels and there's nothing on television. Well, Will and Grace is on but that show is a little tired these days.  I miss Becker.  I'm surprised that what's-his-name was actaully pretty good in that show. Oh, shit I can't remember his name. I hate it when that happens, when I can't remember something that's right on the tip of my brain. Tom something. Tom? No. Watch, I'll remember in like a week and just blurt it out in the middle of a conversation and people will look at me funny like I'm some kind of autistic person with problems.   So I can't sleep because I can't get comfortable and my throat is on fire from whatever the hell causes that when you have heartburn. Plus I keep burping so Hubby has kicked me out of the bedroom and told me to sleep in the recliner. Well, fuck you very much. So maybe I can be kind and reciprocate when he snores loud enough to make the dog bark.  I don't know why but it seems like it's harder for me to get comfortable than anyone else, because I have to have the covers  just so , and my hair has to be in a certain way and the pillow has to be sufficiently fluffed to support my head but not so fat so as to cause me undue neck pain, and by the time I get all situated I end up having to go and piss (one of the 50 times I get up at night to go pee with this pregnancy. Talk about overkill.) which makes me have to do all of that all over again. It drives Hubby crazy cause the bed squeaks and it takes me all of 20 minutes to finally get comfortable enough to sleep. I read about people with OCD having "rituals" they have to go through, like how they have to line up food just so before they eat it, or how they have to turn a page in a book in exactly the right way or end up having to read the page all over again (I think that was in Miss America by Howard Stern.) and that got me thinking that maybe I have OCD because my bedtime ritual is about as annoying, but seemingly of total and utter importance to my having a good night's sleep.  That, and lately I'm obsessed with the doors in my house. I have to make sure  all the doors  are closed in my house, sometimes checking on them twice or three times, before I'm satisfied enough to leave the house. And I've become fastidious in my cleaning habits, and when things are out of whatever crazy ass order I need them to be in I go stark raving mad. Is this a pregnancy thing? I've always been strange about the bedtime thing, but it's only lately that I've been becoming outright  angry  at things being out of place or doors being left open. Something more to ask my doctor I guess. Poor woman, I know I've become a nuisance to her with my constant barrage of questions about the baby.  "Is it okay to do this, is it okay to do that, what's this funny pain, why am I peeing so much, the baby didn't move 10 times today is he okay..."  I'm driving her nuts. I can't wait to see how she deals with me in the delivery room since I'm having no drugs... Who knows. She might forcibly give me an epidural just to shut me the hell up.  Speaking of delivery rooms... is it wrong of me NOT to want my mother to be in the delivery room with me?  A little backstory on my mom. She was my sister's caregiver of sorts until my sister died this past December. Now Mom lives with my brother. I offered to have her out here in Cali for a week, 10 days so she can be there when my son is born. Now, I'm having second thoughts. Ever since Hubby and I started the childbirth classes I'm coming to realize more and more that I don't want her there, I want HIM. Only. My mom is a little nutso.. and I say that in the nicest way. She's like the crazy-old-lady-down-the-street-with-all-the-cats-who-hates-neighborhood-children-and-has-100-lawn-ornaments type nutso. Endearingly nutso. (unless you make her mad, then Oh, hell.) So anyway, I know that she's going to try to take over in there because she's a slight know it all (gee, where do I get it from?) and I don't want her to piss Hubby off as she is wont to do.  I guess I'll talk to my dog about it and see what he thinks. My dog is pretty smart, for a dog. And he listens without judging which is nice. I can rant to my dog and he just puts his paw on my knee and burps as if to say, "Hey, don't sweat it. By the way, smell my ass-breath."   So anyway I'm still awake and this is turning into a novel. Is there a limit to how long this thing can be? Am I using up too much bandwidth? I learned a new word today, bandwidth. It means... something about taking up space on the internet. I must not have been too interested when I read about it because it's already out of my mind. As are most things. I never get an opportunity to exercise my brain now that Hubby is working every day. Nobody is home with me except my dog, and while he's a great listener, he doesn't contribute much to the conversation.   Has anyone noticed how shitty a singer Paul Schaffer from the David Letterman show is? He's doing "Try a Little Tenderness" and he sounds like a Karaoke Nightmare. Dear Mr. Schaffer, please stick to what you know... kissing Dave's ass and fruity ties. Thanks, the Management.    Anyway that's it for now. I've drank enough water to flood a small midwestern town and most likely will be back up typing more useless drivel once the many pee trips to the bathroom annoy me enough to send me back out here to watch more TV.  Peace.   Ted Danson. That's him. Fuck. See? I told you! And by the way, if this entry seems like just a block of text that's totally uninviting to read, please tell me how to fix that because I just previewed my entry and my paragraphs didn't show up.  Paragraphs are the essence of any good story and makes them  flow , so the reader's brain knows when the one idea ends and another begins. Come on, blogspot, don't force me to type without paragraphs!  That is all. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm at a loss.  I love my Hubby. I love this man more than I love myself. When I look at him I am filled with so much love I think my heart could burst. I dont think I can accurately describe exactly HOW MUCH I love him.  So, why do I feel so lonely and sad all the time?   He got back Sunday and was awake for a short time before going to sleep at 9pm or so. He was tired from working all weekend.  Yesterday he got home at 3pm and went to work on my car at around 4 (so I took a nap), and was back by 6 (when he woke me up from my nap) and then was in bed again by 8.  I got to see my husband for like three hours yesterday.  When he IS awake, we barely say five words to one another, unless we're arguing. Lately, we argue a lot. Mostly, he sits in his chair with his eyes half closed and glazed over watching the Sci Fi channel until he goes to bed.  I have nobody to talk to. Nobody. And I can't find the words to tell him about this because he always interrupts with "I don't understand." What don't you understand, Brian? I'm lonely and depressed. I need to feel included in your life and right now I don't.   I hope things get better after the baby is born. Right now I sit around and watch the same shit every day on TV and poke around on the stupid message board and have no conversational ties with my own husband. How sad and pathetic is that? And I feel like crying all the time because I don't know how to tell him that I'm not happy here anymore. I love him, but I'm just not happy. Maybe it's situational.  I know he's stressed out, and I'm definitely stressed out because of the pregnancy being so taxing physically and mentally. But we were stressed out in Savannah, and he was working long hours in Savannah and things were SO DIFFERENT. We talked to each other, and cuddled, and giggled, and  had sex  and did fun things and Iwas happy. I felt paid attention to, I felt special because he devoted his life around me, and I him.  Now it's like I revolve around him and he can't be bothered.  Yes, he still kisses me and hugs me and calls me sweet pet names that I just eat right up, but then he's distant and reserved and "tired" all the time.   I don't know what to do, and I freeze up when I try to tell him all of this because I don't know how to say it without upsetting him, and it seems like he gets upset so quickly these days. But I can't just sit here and let my brain wither away and watch my sanity disappear. I'm tired of crying when we fight... hell, I'm tired of fighting with him, period.  Maybe it's all hormonal. Maybe I'm reading too much into it. I mean, he's just tired. I can totally see why he's tired cause he works like a dog. But he's leaving for school so soon and will be gone for so long I just wish he would fake it or something until he leaves, and then he can be tired all he wants in Virginia at school.   God... I'm tired myself. I woke up this morning when he went off to work and now I can't get back to sleep. Maybe I'll try again and see how it goes.  It's so hard to sleep in an empty bed when I'm so used to sleeping with him.   I hope this all gets better soon. I can't bear it any longer and fear I might just go stark raving mad and end up institutionalized with Courtney Love, or something.  -Me
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So the Ex-Asshole called me today.  Called me asking for HELP.   Apparently, the fool thinks that I'm always going to be there for him, or something, like I'm always going to extend the olive branch to that abusive emotional cripple.   He says to me "The truck broke down in Baton Rouge and I need you to call your brother (who lives in Alabama) and see if he'll let me borrow his tow dolly for a few weeks."  He neglects to mention this is Farley's truck and Farley is still in California. (the Asshole just got back to Savannah from there recently and apparently there's still more of his company at Ft. Irwin) Why he's helping Farley and why Farley can't handle his own business is beyond me.  But the Asshole made it seem like it was HIS truck that was stuck in Baton Rouge and he was in dire straits, until a little creative questioning on my part caught him in his lie.  So I told him no. I wouldn't help him. I gave him Doug's number in Alabama and told him to call there and ask.   Thing is, The Asshole and I were in this POW/MIA group called Rolling Thunder, and that group gives out patches to its members to put on their motorcycle vests. Since I moved I'm no longer a member and it's been so long since I've paid dues, the Chapter is after me (And The Asshole) for the cost of the patches plus court costs (they've taken us to court, you see) or the return of the patches.  The Asshole was going to Virginia anyway, and he said he'd give them to the Chapter President for me, so I sent them to him, trusting him to do this one thing for me since I paid for the divorce and didn't ask for any alimony and relinquished my rights to his retirement and everything.  This was in MARCH.  The Asshole STILL hasn't sent the patches back and now the Chapter President is getting pretty testy with me, which I totally understand.  The Asshole said he packed them. HE PACKED THEM?? Why didn't he fucking send them to Art when he got them?? In MARCH?? The fuck does he mean he packed them? Is he moving somewhere? Good! I hope The Asshole moves himself right into the middle of a Third World Country ravaged by War and Ebola.  AFTER sending the patches back. And he has the audacity to call me and ask me for help?  I get angrier and angrier the more I think about it. How DARE he?   And I'm in a tough situation cause if I call him out and curse at him he'll never send the patches back (that's how he is, if you pressure him he balks.) but I can't STAND being nice to him.  I can't really take him to court because I'm in California, he's in Savannah, and the patches (or $100 plus court costs) have to get to Virginia somehow. Can I take him to court in California and get a judgement against him? I'm calling Legal Aid on Monday. Fuck this, I'm 9 months pregnant and don't need this hassle.  Speaking of pregnant, can you believe The Asshole was fishing for information? He obviously heard from the Rumor Mill that I was preggo, and was like "So, how's your health? Anything  important  coming up in the near future? Anything I should, you know,  know  about?" Like the baby could be his, or something! Ha! What a LAUGH!!! Like it's any of his business anyway. Asshole.  I Hate hate hate hate hate hate hate hate hate hate hate hate hate him. I think I'm going to call him tomorrow and threaten his ass. No more nice ex wife.  -Me
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hubby is gone on a long 4 day training exercise in some fantastic place called "Pickle Meadows".  I'm all by myself.  His phone gets no reception up there in the mountains. So if I go into labor I have no way of contacting him... except maybe by the Red Cross, and how long does that take? Will they get him into the hospital before I have the baby?  Irrational pregnancy fears again.   Nothing much going on lately, other than I'm getting enormous and I'm ready to have the baby like now. But I have to wait until Hubby gets back.   More later.  -Me
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I keep having this dream that Hubby is cheating on me and it's starting to affect my daily life to the point where I'm suspicious of everything.   I guess because I read a couple of Jackie Collins' books before bed and dream about 'seemingly perfect marriages ending because the husband is cheating'.   So I'm doing stupid shit that I wouldn't normally do, and I think it might be just hormones and I'm DYING to talk about it with Hubby but he told me before that his ex-wife Terri the Whore used to accuse him of cheating too and I don't want to piss him off.   I look through his phone and he's still calling women from his old job that he doesn't work with anymore. Granted, some situations have arisen that make it necessary for him to still be in contact with him, but then again why would one of them text message him at like 9pm on the 4th of July telling him "Happy 4th, Be Safe"?  I'm reading more into that than I should, I know.   But then today I go to wake him up from his nap (he got home early today cause we have chilbirth class tonight) and there's this expensive looking JG Hook watch on the bed. I'm like, "HoneyBee, who's watch is this?" and he says "I don't know. Wake me up at 5."  The fuck?  You don't know whose watch it is? Did you find it somewhere? Don't you think it should be in the lost and found at work instead of on your wrist?  It looks brand new, too. I mean not a scratch anywhere on it.   Also, our sex life isn't great at all. He's given me reasons and everything, but when we're all alone why is it weird for him to have sex with me? We used to have sex like three times a night (for REAL) when we lived in Georgia and then we move out here and... nothing. But he's tired of having this discussion with me, because it makes him upset. Well goddamit I'm upset too.   And then, he's going to school (To Ft. Eustis, where I went to AIT) for 13 weeks to re-class, and I'm dreading it so much that I can't breathe sometimes when I think about it. Not only is he leaving me seemingly by myself (I'll still have family) with a new baby, but he's going to the same place I went to for AIT and I know that if there ever was a chance forhim to cheat it's there. I know how sex-hungry those AIT girls are, and how they'll try to seduce any man they can get their hands on... Hubby's a very attractive guy, so I know he's going to have pussy thrown at him from all sides. And I'll have no way of knowing. And the worst part is that I trust this man with my life but I'm SO paranoid about him cheating on me!!  I   hate   this. I really do. I've been cheated on by every man I've ever been with and if he's cheating on me I think I'd die.  I mean really I think I would die of a broken fucking heart.   Why is it, ladies, that we always think we aren't good enough to keep a man?  Right now I'm so huge and I feel so unattractive and right when I need constant affirmation that he still finds me attractive and desireable, he's like a block of ice-- a total 180 from how he was in Savannah-- and now all these weird things happening with the watch and his phone calls...   Someone hit me with a goddamn brick to knock some sense into me, or something. But this is all driving me crazy.  I can't wait for these hormones to dissipate so I can be normal again.   I'm crying. Fuck.  I'm so miserable today with this pregnancy and these hormones and these horrible thoughts in my head.  Fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck fuck.   Good news is today CSAA called me for a job interview, and even offered to hold the job unitl October when I'm ready to put the baby in Daycare (6 weeks is old enough, right?) and then start my training and everything.  How awesome is that?  And I can't enjoy it cause I'm a paranoid stupid fucking bitch.   -Me
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What a cute movie.   Well Hubby and I are thinking of doing the same thing.   Moving.  We found this cute little farmette out in the country, with two houses (one relatively new, nice pre-fab and the other a fixer-upper) on 5 acres going for less than what we paid for this monstrous house we live in now.  Hubby wants a lot of land because he and his Uncle used to raise and show German Shorthaired Pointers in field trials all over Northern California. His Uncle just went professional (they'd been doing the amateur circuit for like, ever) and Brian wants to get back into it too. This little farmette would be perfect!  Plus I hate this neighborhood, I hate the neighbors, I hate the houses on top of houses, I hate that there's no trees and no yards and regulation after regulation in this psycho-ass neighborhood.  So this might be a good thing.  We've discussed it and if it's feasible and we can actually accomplish it, we're going to put in a bid on that farmette and move the hell out of the city.  Thank god, because I'm totally a farmgirl at heart and want to have room to have a garden with all the damn lawn gnomes I want.  Plus, with 5 acres, we might be able to get a horse, which I would love!  The only problem is the fixer-upper house. It'll take forever to fix it up, but Hubby loves that stuff, and it's a beautiful old house with all hardwood floors and a wraparound porch and a big side window with a windowseat... And hubby can do all the repairs and I can pick out the decor and stuff, and then later on we can move into that house and maybe rent out the pre-fab home to someone else.  This potentially could be a really good business venture... Hubby's the business minded one and he seems pretty excited.  I'm just glad to get the fuck out of this house!   Cross your fingers for us! -Me
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hubby is out. At a Swingers Party. Yes, swingers. Wife-swappers. The "unsavory element".  His brother Mike owned all this DJ equipment, and since Hubby loves being the center of attention (he's so cute. Awwwww.) and I was a DJ myself for like 3 years, we decided to buy Mike's equipment and go into business for ourselves.  Mike has... well I should say "we have" since it's ours now... some really nice equipment, albeit a little old, and we got it for a steal. I'm talking a Peavey amp, two CD players (one plays Karaoke CD+Gs), one minidisc player, a nice Mackie 1202 dash something (I forget the model number but I was drooling over it.) mixer, JBL speakers, a disco ball, a million CDs... the  works .  So Mike had all these contacts around Sacramento for people looking to unload some gigs, so this guy named Dennis called Brian up and gave him three shows. One tonight, one for a few months from now (which he probably won't take because of the new baby), and a New Years gig.  The show tonight, Dennis said, was for a group of people who get together every year for a social dinner / dance type thing for their "club".  "Club?" Brian said, interested.  "Yeah," Dennis said, "They're swingers."   ....!!!!!  So anyway apparently these swingers actually have a   club   with meetings and dues and membership cards and everything. They get together once a year at the Best Western (oh, what luxury!) and rent out a conference room and then like 50 or so hotel rooms for their.. uh... swinging. They get together once a month or so to discuss swinger things I guess, and then swap wives. I've never heard of swingers actually having their own freaking  club , so that's pretty funny.  Well, the best part is, they can't "swing" with people outside the club. Couple A, for instance, can't officially "swing" with Couple B unless Couple B is a member if Swingers International, or whatever the fuck this club is called. I guess because, like the porn industry, they don't use condoms and want to make sure everyone is "clean" before swapping wives. Which is actually pretty responsible because all the "swingers" I've ever known are just men with wives that fuck everything and the men just call themselves "swingers" because they're pathetic and defeated and won't get a divorce because nobody else would touch their ugly ass. (It's a bar called the Hideaway, folks, the crappiest dive bar in America! lol)  So anyway, Hubby told me all this because when he first mentioned that it was a swinger party I raised my eyebrow as if to say, "The fuck? A what party? Explain."  I have nothing to worry about, even if they didn't have all these rules and guidelines, because Hubby and I are madly in love and I know that he would never touch another woman, as I would never touch another man.  He still has issues when people flirt with me when we're out (Who flirts with a 35 week pregnant woman, by the way! How pathetic for the dude that flirts with one! lol) but he knows that I'd never leave him. I love him so much and try to tell him and show him every day.  He actually didn't want to do this gig because apparently his ex wife Terri the whore always freaked out about Brian cheating on her.   She's such a pathetic woman, this Terri. There's this legal issue between them involving a vehicle that Terri took when she left him and subsequently got reposessed or something, and now they're coming after Brian because his name was never taken off the title and it wasn't addressed in the divorce for some reason, apparently because the bitch lied to him and told him it was taken care of... I don't really know what the fuck is going on, because I really try to stay as far out of it as I possibly can because it's not really my business. But anyway, he served her with some papers recently and now she's got their son (her son, actually, Brian adopted him when he was 6) turned against him, probably telling him that his dad is an asshole and he doesn't love him and doesn't want to have anything to do with him... you know, the usual 'parent-against-parent-using-the-kid-as-a-pawn-typical-jaded-bitch-bullshit' women like her are famous for. My dad did it too, talking the "Your mother is a bad woman and she did this and this and this and she doesn't love you that's why she didn't fight for custody of you, blah blah blah" game to poison my mind against her to get back at her for leaving him. Anyway, you get what I'm saying.   So this happened a few days before Father's Day, and all of a sudden on Father's Day, Hubby gets this text message from his son's phone saying "I hate you I never want to see you again", or something to that effect. So we knew that she got the papers, at least. We don't know if it was Terri the Bitch using her kid's phone or if it was his son, but it hurt Brain pretty bad. On FATHER'S DAY, of all days.  I know that this baby is not a replacement for his son, because he loves P. as if he was his biological father. He raised this boy and poured his heart and soul into him and just  loved  being a father. A daddy, really, because any asshole can be a father. It takes a special man to be a "daddy". So now, Brian's getting his heart trampled on by these two and it's killing him.  So here I am pregnant with this "new baby" and selfish me, all I can think about is "Has this cunt ruined his heart and burned him so bad he won't be able to love his son because of how she turned P. against him?" And that's just a silly thing to think because I have seen this man's capacity for love and he has one of the biggest hearts in the world, but is it a legitimate fear that he's going to be wary of his new son doing the same thing P. did? I only say this because he was cautious in the beginning of our relationship and didn't want to get into anything serious because Terri the Whore burned him so bad. He needed affirmation almost daily that I loved him and you know, I didn't mind. I tell him I love him a hundred times a day, I show him I love him with my every action and every moment of every day I have him on my mind. The outpouring of love I have for this man cannot be described in words for fear of making it less than it is by not having words strong enough or beautiful enough in the in any language in all the world. Can I get any sappier?   Anyway, so is it going to happen the same way with the baby? Or will it be different because the baby will not only be his biological son, they'll be able to bond with each other from birth and Brian will be able to watch his son grow up in total adoration of his daddy, as most boys do? I know Brian is going to live this baby, no question. What an irrational fear to have, right? But that's how I feel sometimes and it's scary.    This makes me so angry, that this horrible bitch is so vindictive she'll go to no lengths to make Brian's life miserable. I watch him call his son day after day after day and get no answer, and Brian never cries, but I see those tears well up in his eyes and I want to go over to her house and maim that fucking bitch.  Is it wrong of me to hate her so much for something she didn't even do to me? This woman and I have never said three words to each other (mostly because my mother taught me if you have nothing nice to say, better to keep your mouth shut.) and yet I have this deep resounding hatred for her because of what she's doing to my husband.   I know, I know. I need to stay out of it. I don't talk about this to Hubby.. I think that's tacky. If he brings it up and confides in me, I never offer my opinion, even if he asks. I only tell him that I'm there for him when he needs me and that everything will work itself out. He really doesn't need to hear me go off on a rant (and people that know me know that when I go off on someone it's  bad  news) about his lousy emotionally retarded ex-whore. Er, wife.  I just need to vent, because if I don't get it out I'm not sure I can keep myself from either calling P. and asking him just what the fuck his mother has been telling him, or calling her and giving her a fairly large piece of my mind. (and of course offering her an even larger piece of my fist.) I HATE HATE HATE her.  And impotent hatred is not healthy. Nor is it productive.   So God, if you're up there, please let this all work out okay, and if it's your will let Brain and P. get their relationship back, and let this evil bitch Terri burn in the fieriest pits of hell.  Thanks, God. I owe you one.   So anyway, time to go take a bath because my feet are swollen today and try to pass the time until the love of my life comes home from his Swinger party.  With his membership card. Haha.   -Me
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So first, the doctor said that I'm fine, that my pee looks fine and that I look hydrated and the swelling in my feet has gone down. Strangely, the burning stopped this morning, but she said that if it starts again to give the on-call doctor a ring and they'll order me a pee test.  So next appointment in 2 weeks, where I get a vaginal exam! Hooray! She's going to tell me if the baby is head down or not, if I'm dilated at all, and if I have Group B Streptococcus, I think it's called. Well whatever it's called it means the doctor getting that damn cooter-spreader out of the fridge (ladies, you feel me?) and digging around in there with a 5 foot long Q-Tip.  So anyway.  That being said...  My mother called me yesterday asking me if I remember where my sister's class ring is. So I told her no. And she launches into this sob story about how she's desperate to find it because it's the only thing of Missy's she has left to hold onto and it was Missy's favorite thing in the whole world -- which I can understand because Missy busted her ass selling magazine subscriptions for that ring-- and she  needs  it and am I sure I don't know where it is?  So I tell her again, no. We've gone through this before twice since she died, and both times I told her that I think Missy gave it to someone.  So my mom tells me that she's already contacted one of Missy's old boyfriends (David N.) who lives in Ohio with his two strange ass kids to see if Missy might have given it to him. This guy moved away about two years before Missy died so my mom just wrote this guy a letter saying, for all intents and purposes, "Hey, Missy died this December. Do you have her High School Class ring?" What a shitty way to break the news to someone about their ex-girlfriend!  So then she asks me "Do you remember where Dave M. said he was moving to in California?"  I was like... woah.  Dave M. was the manager at the bar/ restaraunt where I worked as a DJ. Dave, in the beginning, was my friend, and I introduced him to my sister, and he became the great love of her life. He treated her like crap, because (and I'm not saying this to be a bitch.) Dave wanted to get into my pants and I refused him, so this asshole turned his sights to my sister to try to weasel his way in closer to me. I know this because he told me so. And I never told Missy or my mom cause it would have broken their hearts. So anyway, Missy struggled against Dave's on-again-off-again romance with her like a true martyr, even after Dave got busted for selling coke in the restaraunt where we worked and lost his job, and then left Missy for Susan, one of his customers. They were still "friends", she said. Friends, meaning Missy would invite him over for holidays and random dinners and buy him presents that she couldn't afford and then get mad when he wouldn't return or reciprocate her feelings, but then she'd take him back when he came calling with some lame-ass apology. (when all he actually wanted was for her to keep showering him with gifts and free sex) Sorry, I just... Dave pissed me off really bad because he was the one who called me and informed me of my best friend Ann's death (she worked with us as a cocktail waitress on Karaoke nights and became my best friend) by saying "Hey, Mary. Uh, Ann's dead, have you heard? Are you coming in to work Karaoke tonight, because it's still on, even though... you know, Ann won't be here."  (She went out on her night off the night before and got drunk, drove home, and died in a car crash.) So anyway, to make a long story short, Dave decided to pack up his stuff and Susan the whore and move back out to his hometown here in California, somewhere on the Northern Coast. And my mom thinks I know where he is.  And she wants to write him a letter asking him if he has Missy's class ring. Right.   This makes me so mad because my mother and my sister are   notorious   for not only re-gifting (especially shit that I gave them they'd give to me for my birthday...) but for giving away things that supposedly meant something to them. My sister loved the University of Alabama Football team, for instance. So one year for her birthday I made like a billion calls and finally talked to the football coach's secretary and got her a signed football from him for her birthday. So what does she do? A year later, she gives  that very fucking football  to my dad for Christmas.  What. The. Fuck. ?  So anyway I can't think why my mom would want this ring back  now , after all this time of not having it. I can't understand why it's so important to her to have... because it's just a  thing  and not really any part of  her ....  I'm so confused. So now she's going to go on this crusade to find this ring. More power to mom.   Sad thing is, it might be in a bunch of boxes of stuff I have in storage... Missy left me a lot of stuff when she died, including her jewelry box, and it might be in there, only I can't bring myself to go through it because the memories still hurt pretty bad.  *sigh* Goddammit. What do I do?   -Me
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dear God,  Thank you for making this Earth as wonderful as You did. I think You did a stellar fucking job, especially when You made Ireland, ice cream, babies, Johnny Depp, and SpongeBob.  But I think that You really crossed the fucking line when You thought to make Urinary Tract Infections. If You really are a woman like all the Wiccans and Hippies and Californians say you are, then no wonder You made Mary have Jesus for You because these Urinary Tract Infections really goddamn suck. (No offense.) I would be happy to trade You whatever You want for this infection that I have right now, because let me tell You, God, it's a damn inconvenience. I have some really nice comic books stored away, or I can make You a three-layer chocolate marble cake with cream cheese icing which I'm sure You have in Heaven, but probably low-carb or something to make it healthier. (Do they have Atkins in Heaven now that Dr. Atkins passed away? Just wondering.)  Anyway, get back to me. I appreciate it. And again, thank You for ... You know. Everything.  -Me  If only it were that easy, talking to God. I'm sure that Christians maintain that they have a Bat Phone directly to the Almighty herself  (Himself? Itself? Who knows.) and they talk to Him or Her all the time, but .... if they did then I'm sure quite a lot less old ladies would get gipped out of their money by the assholes on the Old Time Gospel Hour. Am I right? Can I get a Amen?   Amen   So anyway, I have a Urinary Tract Infection. I haven't been to the doctor yet, that's later today. (Friday. Jesus, it's Friday. Muuuuust sleeeeep...) But I know I have one because it feels like I'm pissing razor blades. It wouldn't be so bad if it were like, once or twice a day or whatever... but being pregnant makes me pee like 50 times more, and having this UTI doubles that.  So I'm in and out of the freaking bathroom like 100 times a day. And right when I sit back down on the couch or get back in bed I have to pee all over again.  And this makes me question the existence of God. (As if my Catholic upbringing didn't do that years ago, right?) Because how can a God who loves us so much make such a grade-A fucking miserable thing like a Urinary Tract Infection? I can just see God right now, up On High or whatever looking down on Creation going, "You know... it's just too... perfect. So here's some War, and some Famine on top of that, and uh... here's Barney the Dinosaur, that oughta make them miserable, and .... one more thing, what else? OH! I know! Urinary Tract Infections!! That should piss them off. Silly Humans. "  I have drank an entire bottle of Cran-Apple juice. I hate Cran-Apple juice. Know why? Cause it tastes like shit, but you know why else? Because it makes you PEE! And does nothing to alleviate the pain of pissing razor blades like good old fashioned drugs can.  Please Lord, let her give me some drugs tomorrow. Please let it not be too late in the pregnancy for drugs. Pretty please, and I'll throw in an Amen on top if that suits you.  Oh, the baby's moving. You know, that has to be the greatest thing in the world, right? Too bad Hubby's sound freaking asleep right now so he can't feel it and talk to the baby like he normally does. But, like every other rational adult, he's in bed asleep right now. I wish I could be in bed asleep right now.  But sadly, I have to pee again.  I might as well just take in a pillow and a blanket and go right to sleep on the john. It's not like I don't already have hemorrhoids- however the crap you spell them.  Funny story, the pregnancy book I have says "In order to avoid hemmorrhoids, don't spend a lot of time on the toilet."   Okay, have these people BEEN pregnant? Don't spend a lot of time on the toilet? What between peeing all the time and being constipated (you really needed to know that, didn't you? haha.) half my fucking  day  is spent on the toilet.  *sigh*  Well there I go again, and yawning to boot so I'll just end this by saying I'm still really pissed off at You, God, for giving us Urinary Tract Infections.  But thanks for everything else.   -Me
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's so hot here in California. And when people say "Oh, but it's a dry heat" I want to  slap  them, because even though it's dry it's still fucking hot. I'll take the humidity of the South over this freaking oven anyday.   Anyway. The baby has been jumping up and down today like he's doing floor exercises in my belly. I wish he would stop, but on the other hand I really enjoy feeling him move. I'm so paranoid anyway that I freak out when I don't feel him.  This morning I woke up to him doing something weird though and it's really got me feeling scared that I did something bad like sleep on my belly or something. It felt like he was... I don't know. I can't decribe it other than it felt like he was struggling in there, or something. Like he was trying to fight something. That's the only way I can describe it. And I don't know if I'm being paranoid and it's nothing to worry about or it  is  something to worry about and I'm not going to the hospital because I think I'm psyching myself out and it's really nothing.  Luckily I have a doctor appointment tomorrow so I can ask her then.   I freak out about this baby coming out okay because my sister was sick for a long time and she died recently. Is this normal, I ask myself, to be so insanely paranoid about death and dying that it's always on my mind?  I worry about Hubby riding the bike to work because someone could kill him, especially these stupid California drivers. He's already laid it down once, going 30 on an on-ramp and I saw how cut up he was and how stiff and in pain he was after that.  I worry about him riding in the helicopters at work. He told me yesterday they flew out to Tahoe and when he was checking out the bird before they came back there was oil or hydraulic fluid all over the place and they flew back anyway cause he didn't want to stay in Tahoe overnight. Why would you tell me this, Brian, when you know how insane I am?  I wake up in the middle of the night in cold sweats because I dream about the baby dying of SIDS. Or that he comes out deformed, or that he comes out with some horrible problem or otherwise not a normal healthy baby. It's scary, and I don't want to wait the however many weeks I have left in this pregnancy to find out. The doctor won't give me another Ultrasound cause they're supposedly unhealthy for the baby... but I'm so freaked out that I'm actually thinking about just going to the hospital with some made-up pregnancy problem just to see him on the Ultrasound screen again, and make sure he's okay. And how fucking stupid is that? Not to mention a waste of everyone's time.  Funny, that's the same kind of shit my sister used to pull. I don't dispute that she was very sick, but it seems like she used to invent shit that was wrong with her because the attention had shifted from her for a few minutes and she didn't like that. She was 34 years old and acted like a kid. I got to the point where I just got exasperated with all of her ailments and then when she died... I remember talking to the doctor at the Emergency Room, pretty much telling him in not so many words that I thought what my mom was telling me was full of shit and what was his take on the matter?  And then they took her off the respirator and she died not hours later. And I felt so horrible. And I wasn't there. I didn't want to go, even, when my mom told me that she was in the hospital again I remember my exact thoughts were "Oh, hell. Again? What's she dying of  this  time?" and I decided not to go home because I had been summoned to the hospital for her "last days" so many times before. I thought that this was another of those times... even though Mom said she was on a repirator in a coma.  In ICU for fuck's sake.  Brian says that I couldn't have done anything to help her, and that blaming myself for her death is the same as blaming myself for the Black Friday stock market crash. But I still feel horrible that I didn't go and be with her when she died.  But thinking about it, would I have been able to handle it, watching her die? I don't know. It's still way to hard to think about even now, 7 months later.  I couldn't even go to her casket at the funeral because I just couldn't bring myself to look at her. I did finally go and tell her goodbye, though.  She looked so different, but there she was. My sister, older than me by 10 years and already dead.  God, it's so hard. I thought writing would purge some of the sadness, like lancing an infected wound or something. I guess there's still some left in there.  Maybe I'll never get over it and will always break down into tears when I think about her.  I don't want to cry when I think about Missy. I want to be able to remember her and the good things we did and the good times we had, but my brain inevitably turns to the day of her funeral and there go the waterworks again.  Shit. I hate to cry.   -Moi
     

    
</post>


</Blog>