<Blog>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Dear public diary :    2day is a holiday. So now i am at home, no1 2 chat wif. Sakura is getting better n better, she can draw a little already, but the problem is now, she don have idea, while my comic has already go 2 chapter 2. I wonder y Kira and Enishi very seldom online already... I miss them... And 4 the past few days, i kept dreaming bout him... Yezterday nite also dream about him... twice. Tats so weird... Am i missing him, or is it juz... some dream? Oh well, i'll find tat out myself. But i miss him soo much...     var chatterbox = 'no';  19.july.2004        urlLink target="flooblechatterbox"  onClick="window.open('about:blank','flooblechatterbox','toolbar=no,location=no,directories=no,status=no,menubar=no,scrollbars=yes,resizable=no,copyhistory=no,width=480,height=400');return true;">  align="absbottom">Talk   in my  urlLink flooble chatterbox, a free javascript chat tag board / shoutbox / tagboard program for your xanga, diary, blogger or weblog     urlLink technical interview puzzles, riddles and brain teasers      if (!chatterbox  chatterbox != 'ok') {  document.write('This  urlLink flooble chatterbox  is'); document.write(' temporarily unavailable. It will be back up shortly.'); }      
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Dear public diary :  ~Start day~ I went 2 skul quite early again 2day. I found out y Sakura lost her hobby, its becoz her RO stuff kena spot check n kena rampas. She was so sad and desperate, she could sacrifice anything 2 get it back (wow!). Tomolo she'll get her things back, n eventually things will return 2 normal, i hope ^^ Soo... Right now my comic is only 3 pages... No1 chat wif me... N i feel sooo inssecure, lack of love, but still happy. I understand myself now... I need a fren who will notices me all the time, n understand me, won't look down on me or say anything bad behind my back and of coz, won't ejek me 1 (Not like Daph n Chang). So far, i still cant really find a fren like tat, only Sakura understands me... Only her....
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Dear public diary:                            11/7/2004 Day by day pass by as all the people around me changed so much. ~Start day~ I came 2 skul quite early 2day... They susun the table from the take report card day(the tables n chairs were jumbled up). Daphne become a bit more moody than ever oledi... Sakura LOST HER HOBBY OF HER LIFE - DRAWING COMIC!!! WTFHM!!!! SHE ISN'T INTERESTED IN DRAWING COMIC ANYMORE?!?!??!! And... Chang become a bit more better liaw, she kena demerit 30 2day... now 60 sumthin oledi... Sherwynna oso 60 sumthin oledi... Darn i scared they kena gantung man...... Sob.... I like the way it is... y does every1 have 2 change?!?! Nooooo!!! MY SI FU IS GONE!!! MY DRAWING SI FU!!!! My 2nd plot si fu not available at the moment but NOOOOO!!!! I wan it back 2 normal.... N fong these days like don like 2 talk 2 me anymore.... After all these years i helped him n tried 2 b there 4 him whenever i could, he became soo.... quiet around me. When there's someone around, then he will start blabbering wif me. Darn..... Is it me, or is it the world changing around? I really like it the way it is..... Why change?
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear public diary :  I woke up at 6.30a.m. 2 get ready n go 2 tanjung aru's Taman Lalu lintas 2 teach the competitors the things 2 learn. Im teaching 2 form 1 gurls wif Chin Tze Tzing. 1 is so damn serious n the other 1 is too playful~! After tat i went for the doomsday - take report card but nothing bad happened, only tat i m forbidden 2 join perbarisan oledi >.< Well, n then i come back on9 until NOW! WohoooO~ Weee~!~~ So boring oh..... until Wils join d chatroom!! The fun all come~ Well, tats all gua... Haiz so short...byebye
      
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        ellow humans! thanks for reading my boring blog once again... i'll send in some pics or competition soon, in order 2 join, u need 2 sign up for my page ^^ Prize is gonna b quite good, i guess! Well, here goes   competition of the month : DRAWING COMPETITION (no  urlLink hentai  plz) Whoever can draw the best  urlLink pictures  will win a prize. (oh if either aurey or wils win, i'll  urlLink mail  the prize^^) Prize r officially mystery (i donno wat 2 give either =P)   Rule 1 : no  urlLink hentai  (will b considered out if u do this) Rule 2 : no spamming (as if u can) Rule 3 :  urlLink mail  ur drawing to the below :          P.O.Box 11656,          88818 Kota Kinabalu, (ppl who live in Sabah can stop here)          Sabah, Malaysia. Rule 4 : Theme : Random(tat means u can draw watever u like, EXCEPT HENTAI!!!    -For more info,  urlLink contact  Char at comic_lene@hotmail.com-
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey ppls~ thanks for taking ur time 2 c my out-dated blog... Dear public diary : 2day is Saturday n im in cyber wif sakura. We're having fun ^^ Well tats all for this morning O.o, bye. 3 July 2004
      
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          var chatterbox = 'no';         urlLink target="flooblechatterbox"  onClick="window.open('about:blank','flooblechatterbox','toolbar=no,location=no,directories=no,status=no,menubar=no,scrollbars=yes,resizable=no,copyhistory=no,width=480,height=400');return true;">  align="absbottom">Talk   in my  urlLink flooble chatterbox, a free javascript chat tag board / shoutbox / tagboard program for your xanga, diary, blogger or weblog  |   urlLink technical interview puzzles, riddles and brain teasers      if (!chatterbox || chatterbox != 'ok') {  document.write('This  urlLink flooble chatterbox  is'); document.write(' temporarily unavailable. It will be back up shortly.'); }    
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        yello!!! Now's nite...lemmi write my diary...(wow... 2 blog in 1 day) Dear public diary : I got back from tuition n it was kinda bore the ass outta me... Now im online with NO ONE willing 2 chat wif me.... tat's all, bye
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey~ Chiko is back in da house~ ^^ How r ya ppl? Y so far still 0 comments 1...so bad lar u all....sob... Nvm  Dear Public diary: Today is not so bad, well, Daphne bad mood at Pendidikan Seni period... ~start of the day~ i went 2 skul at 6.30a.m. sumthin...a little late than usual...but still on time ^^ I saw Sakura in front of the class talking 2 Mizu(Mizu is Rebekah) so i put my bags down at my seat n ran out of class 2 join them. Me n Sakura laughed at Fong's japanese name - Baka Hsaru(stupid monkey) LOL!! Then i talked 2 her about Nishi n Kira and she talked 2 me about her Havy n Neo(i think she did) She gonna draw 3rd chapter soon!! YAY!! The part tat is going 2 b more of ME!!!(Chiko chan^^) *ahem* as my comic, now i drew about Sakura's fear... It's about her onichan, Game Guy, well, he sorta been kidnapped and leaved Sakura. Sakura was kidnapped 2 a dungeon with full of bones n skulls(human bones n skulls)... She managed 2 escape anyway... Tats y she's afraid of bones n skulls... (back 2 reality) Me, Daphne n Chang sit in 1 table in the bilik masakan (1st n 2nd period of the day - Kemahiran Hidup) n talked about how r we gonna make out pizza... Well, KH teacher seems 2 going 2 teach us 2 make pizza... after all the exams~ Yay~ and yummy~! CHANG ACTUALLY WANT 2 PUT HOT DOG ONTO THE PIZZA!!! Then Daphne laugh hysterically n said : "if u put hot dog, by the time the pizza come out of the oven, the pizza is going 2 b named 'Flaming hot dogs pizza'!!" (imagine tat....LOL!!) So after KH we went through another BOOOOOOOOORING geography period...but it went by fast since it only take 1 period n then...RECESS!!! I went 2 find Sakura n her fren, Siew King at the canteen. We talked for a while again n then i went back 2 class for pendidikan seni - PS (yes, tat is the time Daphne start 2 bad mood). PS teacher actually wants me 2 join a cartoon competition!! FUN FUN FUN FUN FUN~ ^^ Well, now im waiting for her 2 giv me the form!! Well, after tat i went for chinese class... But went by fast too... n then i went for my meeting n i bincang about my part in the singing competiton (me is being the host for the show^^) n then i come back n now writing this blog. I'll write again and nite, cha-neh(byebye)~~!!
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        HeY!! This is already like my...3rd webbie!! Hm... Well... *Ahem*     Dear PUBLIC diary(lol) : I'm quite cheerful in skul 2day... until the last period... Which is... *deng deng deng* GEOGRAPHY!! Well, it wasn't geography's fault, Daphne and Christine hav 2 juz MAKE my mood go bad... Sheesh!! I mean, wat kind of best friends r they?? Well... They consider me as best fren, and i don. Cuz i prefer 2 have Sakura as my best fren ^^ Well... I had fun 2day... 2day i have 2 sweep the class with Natalie(anotha fren of mine who is getting more n more intovert) and i had 2 walk AALLLLL the way 2 in the middle of 1B and 1M to throw the rubbish in the ...well... i donno how 2 say la...tat thing tat matches wif broom 1... 2 throw the rubbishes. After i come home, online for a while... and then no electricity, so i went 2 take nap, until my dad wakes me up for the password 2 enter the computer and unfortunately i cant sleep back because my cousins r outside playing badminton wif "who's ur daddy!" or "What the hell!!" sounds... Sheesh it's only their American cousin came back n speak... U know... Those accent. And no, im not jealous of their cousin >.                                                             1/July/2004
      
</post>


</Blog>