<Blog>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The sad saga of the broken treadmill has led me to some self-discovery.    First, I'm very pleased that I don't have to pay someone to install the parts into it.  Sears would charge a pretty penny to send a repairman over here, and I feel confident that they would not hesitate to charge more than once in this saga.  So that's a victory in itself.  Second, I'm proud of myself and my persistence in pursuing the repair project through all these many calls.  It's annoying but I'm not letting it stop me.  Third, I've discovered that I really miss my treadmill.  I miss being able to walk after work each day.  Sure, I could walk outside.  Of course, it's presently 90 degrees out there.  And that's been the temperature every day lately.  So I *could* walk outside but I'd get a better walk on the treadmill.  Fourth, in an effort not to be stalled in my fitness goals I persuaded my partner to join the local rec center with me.  I think she's shocked that I would want to do that, since I've never been very athletic.  The thing is, I know that if I'm to become healthy I have to become more active.  And the local rec center offers a lot of options for that.  Plus it's reasonably priced and what we pay helps support the center for everyone.  And finally, I got creative today and looked into my college catalog.  We live very near a community college campus and I've been taking classes there for a couple of years.  It turns out that they have a fitness center on campus.  For the cost of one credit hour I can use the facility from August 23 through December 12, and taking a Physical Education class includes what amounts to guidance by a physical trainer!   So GO ME!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been struggling with my treadmill for the past three weeks.  I love my treadmill, don't get me wrong.  But it's broken.  I've called and called for help.  The treadmill is a NordicTrack C1800.  Not very top of the line, but not entry-level.  Including delivery it was around $900 when we bought it, but I digress. We bought it in March last year.  So it's out of warranty for labor, but parts are still covered.  First call to tech support I was pleased to learn they'd let me install the replacement part myself and save the labor charges.  The tech put me through the diagnostics and concluded that the problem was a bad motor controller board.  This seemed reasonable based on the symptoms I had observed.  He ordered one to be sent to me, which I duly received 3 business days later.  This was on the weekend of the fourth of July. I installed the part.  To my dismay the problem persisted.  I called again on July 6.  Next diagnosis was a failed power board.  One was ordered.  I received it within 3 business days.  Installed it.  And the problem persists.   I called again this afternoon.  At this point we have diagnosed the likely problem to be a failed motor, which may be feeding current back to the motor controller board and zorching something.  I am now awaiting the delivery of a motor and a motor controller board.  And today's tech had the courtesy to upgrade the shipping to UPS Air so I should have it in hand on Wednesday.  And then we shall see if the problem is fixed.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      through.    Someone recently said "my family is so whitebread", meaning "middle-class and normal".  Mine's more bananas and nuts.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Rear wheel of bike mounted on Mag Trainer.  Notice the slick tire...very quiet on the trainer.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Bike on Blackburn Mag Trainer with block under front wheel.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, got the picture to work in my profile. Consider that to be a "before" shot.  "After" shot will be coming later.  Meanwhile, what's to tell? Well, let's see... Oh, yeah, I officially have a home on the internet now!  Woohoo!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      the first blast of hot air from the whoopicush.  Just a brief note to get this started.  I'll have more to say later. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>