<Blog>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Excuse my ramblings this morning.&nbsp; When the rest of the world is sleeping, here I am at work.&nbsp; I really do not like this shift.&nbsp; I bet I could get 8-12hrs of sleep before I have to come in at 11p and still be tired.&nbsp; I just do not think that the body should be awake when the sun is asleep.&nbsp;  Have you ever tried to sleep with a toddler running around the house?&nbsp; It just does not work.&nbsp; I mean, like today he started crying and woke me out of a deep sleep (I am one of those sleepers who if a tornado took the house away,&nbsp; I would still be there sound asleep in bed)&nbsp; I went tearing down the stairs to see what happened, here I am imagining the worst (as any mother does) and it turned out he and my husband were just playing.&nbsp; I was not a happy camper......I went back to sleep, but that I do not think I ever recovered from the interruption of sleep.&nbsp;  So at this moment, I can not wait to crawl into bed for a couple of hours....it is my day off today, so I am only going to sleep for a couple of hours so I can go to sleep this evening. &nbsp; So anyway, it has been a very uneventful couple of days.&nbsp; I think all that we have going on is preparing for the fair.&nbsp; I am working the fair, overtime baby, and going to the fair....and working my job.&nbsp;  &nbsp; So what do you think of this whooping cough "epidemic".&nbsp; I feel like I have been transported to the middle of the SARS epidemic that happened last year.&nbsp; We went to the hospital on Saturday and they handed all three of those blue masks to wear.&nbsp; All right now, I have a small head....a mask that fits my husband, does not fit me and surely will not fit my two and a half year old.&nbsp;  Try to get a two year old to wear a mask....Yeah right.&nbsp; He has been vaccinated, so no worries here.&nbsp; The poor dear, the mask covered his eyes, nose, mouth, chin...what a site he was.&nbsp; You think that if they want everyone to wear a mask, instead of having universal masks, they would have adult mask and child masks.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Okay that is my rant for the day. &nbsp; I am going to say good night (or morning) now.  &nbsp; Miranda Conner Well I hope you enjoyed reading my ramblings..... 
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Happy Saturday ya'll.&nbsp;&nbsp; Not too much to report here.&nbsp; Just another normal day in the Conner household.&nbsp; It was an absolutely gorgeous day today, so when I got off of work, I went on&nbsp; a walk with Daniel and finished mowing the lawn.&nbsp;For some odd reason, work just drains me so when I come home all I want to do is sleep, but today I was determined to stay awake.&nbsp; Activity of some sort, I guess, seemed to do the trick.&nbsp; Well, just thought I would say hello real quick.&nbsp;  &nbsp; &nbsp; Miranda  
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, it took long enough, but summer is finally here in North Dakota.  July 10th was as good as any other day for the sun to start shining and the temps to reach above 80.  I would have much preferred this weather to have started in lets say the end of May, but I guess what do I expect when it snows on May 12th.  RIDICULOUS!!     
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well,today I ventured into the self-tanning realm today.  Interesting.  I thought that I was going to be blotchy, although it is color guided and all that, but I think it turned out all right.  It is a very scary thing to undertake though, there is no way to take it off once applied.  So if you have streaks, the best thing that can be done is to rub a lemon on the area, exfoliate alot and don't leave the house until the self tanner fades away.    What else can I write about...colored my hair last night too!!  I change my hair according to the season, dark in the winter and light in the summer)  So, I was coloring my hair more blond than normal.  Now, I have naturally auburnish hair, so if I do not pick the right shade of blond, you could cash my hair in (that is how gold it gets).  I am happy to report that it turned out fantastic.  For all you women out there who color their hair, if you have not tried the L'Oreal Haircolor/hightlighting kit, you should.  It is a goof proof and cheap way to get a great haircolor and highlights.    Well, I am just terrible at blogs, who wants to read about the mundane stuff in my life?   You all have a great day!!  Miranda 
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I am going to vent some.  Panhandlers, why???  Does it make sense that you can not have fireworks in the city, pit bulls, rabbits, or snakes, but yet you can stand on the corner of the street and beg for money?  The only punishment those people get is to be sent on their way.  I just do not understand.  I mean, it is a menance and it scares people.  GET A JOB, I want to scream at them.  There is one individual in town that we get calls constantly about....he always gives the same story then when he gets the money he goes to the bar and gambles it away.  First, it is naive of the people to take pity on the man and give him the money, but it is pathetic that this individual is so worthless that he can not get a job anywhere.  The job market is not the greatest right now, but gas stations and fast food restaurants are always hiring.  I am just frustrated that there is nothing that is being done about this problem.  There is nothing they can do, they say.  Arrest him for harassment, soliticing without a license, SOMETHING.  Anyway, enough venting.  I am having a pretty good day.  I just celebrated my two year anniversary.  The first time we have hired a babysitter since October and it was worth it.  We went to dinner and putt putt golfing.  It was an overall great evening.    There is a new fashion trend sweeping my closet, ponchos.  They are great.  I think they are very classy and they just look great on when paired with a complementary tank and pants.  I now own five.    Well I guess I am done for today.  Have a great day!!!  
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      To anyone who is reading my postings, Happy Fourth of July.   Here I am sitting at work, which is probably better, because the weather is terrible today....rain forecasted for most of the day with a high of 61. I can not wait to be live someplace that when it is summertime, it actually feels like summertime....(and winters are not like living in the artic.)  I am still not getting a hang of this blog posting thing, I guess I have a hard time verbalizing my thoughts.    Anyone have any kids out there?  I have a two and a half year old little boy....what a handful he is.  He is so funny right now because he is on a Spiderman kick...anything and everything having to do with the web slinger is what he wants.  We got him a mask and spidey gloves, he wears them (upside-down) around the house.  Last summer it was Elmo....I guess he still likes Elmo, but he has watched the Spiderman movie about 15 times is the past week.  It is so cute.    Miranda Conner
      
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, up until today, I really had no clue what a blog was.  Bear with me while I get the hang of it all.  I am not quite sure what I should write...I have never been much of a journal keeper.    I guess I can talk about a very interesting book that I just read, The DaVinci Code.  I can tell you that this book had me riveted from the very first page.  I normally like to read books, immerse myself in the content and let the rest of the world dissapear.  Not this book though....I was reading nect to my computer, searching some of the "facts" that the book proposed.  I even broke down and discussed the book with some other people.  This book had me looking at the works of Da Vinci in a different light.  I have always enjoyed Da Vinci's work and other artists from that era.  I recommend this book to anyone who wants an awesome read.    
      
</post>



</Blog>