<Blog>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's back to work I go! &nbsp;  Mood:&nbsp; Ehh....   Days until hellions return to school:&nbsp; 13  &nbsp; Well, today was the first day of teacher orientation...it actually wasn't so bad!&nbsp; I'm pretty impressed with the county as a whole as of right now...and my school seems like it's going to rock!&nbsp; The administration seems very supportive, which is a bit of a change from last year.&nbsp; Of course, we don't have any kids at school yet, so what truly happens remains to be seen!&nbsp; Time shall tell... &nbsp; I found out I'll be teaching&nbsp;in a trailer all day -- they think with the same teacher all day, too.&nbsp; That'll be a blessing if we get along...but horrible if we don't!&nbsp; I have 4 different preps...Applied Algebra, Concepts of Probability and Statistics, and 2 other ones that I can't remember...I'll have to fill you in tomorrow, dear blog.&nbsp; I have 6th period planning again, which ROCKS my face off!&nbsp; And, the icing on the cake -- we can wear sandals and capri pants!&nbsp; Even as teachers!! &nbsp; So, tonight, after dinner, I decided I was going to floss my teeth like a good dental hygiene girl...and the floss got stuck.&nbsp; I yanked on it, and   HALF OF MY FREAKING TOOTH CAME RIGHT OUT OF MY MOUTH!  &nbsp; I mean, to how many people does that really happen?!&nbsp; At least one...moi!&nbsp; I have dental insurance through Carroll County still, so I know I'm covered.&nbsp; But, alas, I have no idea with whom the insurance is!&nbsp; I'll have to call the central office tomorrow to find out who I need to call to get this biz-natch fixed!&nbsp; I'm absolutely terrified of the dentist...I've got to see if I can find someone who'll gas me!&nbsp; I wonder...can one drive after one's been gassed?&nbsp; Is it safe?&nbsp; Will I die?&nbsp; Does anyone know?&nbsp; Anyone?&nbsp; Bueller?&nbsp; Bueller? &nbsp; OK...I gotta run...time for beddy bye!!!&nbsp; Muchas kisses to all of my adoring (all 2 or 3 of you) fans!! &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mood:&nbsp; 9 pounds lighter!  &nbsp; Ahhh...another weekend come and gone.&nbsp; Bummer.&nbsp; I have to start WORKING tomorrow, which is smelly to me.&nbsp; I have one entire week of Teacher Induction Program, then another week of pre-planning.&nbsp; THEN begins 40 weeks with hellions!&nbsp; There's just so many of them!!!! &nbsp; Yesterday I went to Athens to go to Emerson and Parker's birthday party.&nbsp; Pete came with me; we had SOOO much fun!&nbsp; They had all kinds of indoor inflated fun-filled toys with which we could play until our hearts were content!&nbsp; We boxed in a moonwalk with oversized gloves, got stuck in the "squeeze" of an obstacle course, and slid down many slides.&nbsp; Unfortunately, the frizz factor of each of our hair was slightly escalated because of our escapades!&nbsp; &nbsp; After the fabulous birthday party, Pete and I went back downtown and went shopping!&nbsp; We got smoothies and saw a lot of cool vintage clothings and such, then went to the mall -- where they had a Hot Topic!&nbsp; Pete got an uber cool trenchcoat-y, Matrix-esque coat.&nbsp; He looks tres cool in it!&nbsp; I tried it on, too, but I just looked like a bum.&nbsp; Literally, a hobo.&nbsp; A vagabond, if you will. &nbsp; After I dropped Pete off at the dorm, I went over to an old high school friend's apartment, and we hung out for a while, catching up on old times.&nbsp; I met some new folks, saw some old folks, and generally had a good time.&nbsp; I was there for a long, long time...then we went to see a movie...us old friends.&nbsp; I actually ended up spending the night there, and came home this morning.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Tonight I decided that I'm going to start my new exercise regimen.&nbsp; The A'Rents live in a perfect walking-for-exercise neighborhood, with lots of little hills.&nbsp; You get the perfect amount of up- and down-hill action!&nbsp; Oooh, baby.&nbsp; So what sparked my regimen desire?&nbsp; Well, I stepped on a scale today to see how much damage had been caused since May 20th or so (the last time I weighed myself)...and I was actually 9 pounds lighter!&nbsp; Heck, yeah!&nbsp; Go Jill!&nbsp; So, the loss of weight  without  exercising is prompting me to see how much I can lose when I'm  actually trying !&nbsp; I think I walked about 2.5 - 3 miles...but I'm not sure.&nbsp; I'm going to drive it tomorrow, just to figure out the mileage.&nbsp; Go me!&nbsp; Go me!! &nbsp; OK...I guess I should close for now...I need to get some water before I dry up like a raisin!&nbsp; Ahhhh! 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mood:  Bored stiff Days until Nick comes home:  11!!!   Yet another day has passed...only 4 more days of summer freedom, then I go back to school.  I'm actually looking forward to it.  As much as I enjoy being a lazy whore, not having anywhere to go is getting to me!!  If I hadn't had these two classes, I don't know what I would have done!  Then again, if I hadn't had these two classes, I would have been able to visit Nick more...  So, I think I'm going to use some of my GHP money to buy myself a digital camera.  I want a small one, like Pete/Chris'.  Nick has a good one, but it's so incredibly... cumbersome.   What do you think, Shredder?  A good idea?  This way, I'll be able to post some pictures to DeviantART, too.  Since I have ZERO artistic ability freehand, maybe I can be artsy with my camera?  Today I pretty much slept a lot.  I had a headache (what else is new??)  I won't be surprised if someday I'm told I've had a huge brain tumor forever.  It's just not  normal  for one to have this many headaches!  I read some chapters on learning disabilities, and read some other stuff...then slept the rest of the day!  I did, however, have some cherries for dessert, and they were dee-lish!!  Tomorrow I have to wake up to let the termite guy into la casa de mi padres, then I'll probably do more schoolwork.  Kenny's supposed to come visit for the night, and I haven't seen him since Christmas, so I'm going to hang around LaGrange until Friday.  Friday, I'll take all of my clothes and other things, and head to the in-laws.  I also have to go by the sink-picker-outer-place and choose our upgraded sink.  Saturday, I'm going to Athens for Emerson's birthday party and to see Petie, then back to McDonough.  Sunday, I hope to pick out the lights for the new house, then to go back home and rest for the big week of ::Space Ghost Bellow voice::>   Teacher Induction Program   ::/Space Ghost Bellow voice::!!  We have to be at the school at 7:30 each day, which means Aliendad will want to get there at 7:00...*sigh*  I guess I'll end there for now.  I have a busy next few days ahead!  I'm sure I'll manage to be quite bored, still...  Peace out!
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's my first bloggy post ever!  ::smile::  I've been inspired by the likes of Petie, Chri-stop-her, etc., and have decided to grace the world wide web with my blogful presence!  How very exciting!  Actually, it's quite an inopportune time to start a site like this...since I'm leaving Saturday morning for a whole week!  I have an education seminar in Gatlinburg, Tennessee, and my parents and I (mis padres y yo) are going to stay for a couple of extra days for a mini-vacation.  The seminar takes the place of a semester-long college class, so I'm excited to take care of it in 3.5 days!  Nick's still at GHP...only 25 more days until he comes home!  Woohoo!  Glomp!  (Is that right, Chri-stop-her?)  Anywho...I'll write more tomorrow...and I've got to see if I can customize this page a bit -- I have NO idea what I'm doing!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>