<Blog>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      today, BORING! did nothing else but do household chores! ugh! i cleaned the house, wash dishes and do laundry!! my lil' sis ddnt even help! gud thng my other sis was here to help. but that's not wat i wanted to do today! i wanted to do sumthng fun like.....*thnking*..... can't thnk of anythng!=) anywayz, i want to see spiderman 2 again! that movie was AWESOME! i rily love it! i'll call up my frends and tell them to watch it with me!=) hpe my parents will allow me. nyahahahaha!! i'm a bad girl!! well, not rily!;) gtg!! hollerz!!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       well, at last sumthng fun happened nman!! yay!!! snaps 4 me!!! jke!!Ü knina kc&nbsp; marvie  wanted to see the movie  "a cinderella story"  starring c  hilary duff . eh fan sya ni blondie eh!Ü at frst yoko sumama kc di nman me fan. but i changed my mind cuz i also wanted to see  spiderman 2  again! kc yng cinemas d2 pwede mo psukan even though di ka magbyad! so, kmi lng nanood. actually, the movie wasn't rily bad. but not one of my faves! anywayz, ryt after the movie we looked for the cnema kng san yng spiderman. pumasok kmi sa isa kc wide open yng door. and wen we came in, la pa pipol inside! kmi yng frst! nyahahahaha!!!Ü lucky di pa nagccmula yng movie! nkalibre kmi ng movie!! yng movie lng ni blondie yng bnayaran nmin!Ü     &nbsp;   nkauwi na kmi ni marvie ng 10 pm....phew!!! long day! well, 4 me it was fun cuz i hven't had this fun snce.....hhhmmm.... last week?! wen we went to san francisco.Ü gtg na cuz it's almost midnight! gotta sleep! byerz!!!Ü     
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        2day's  ate lyka's  20th bday! hooray!Ü sbi nya evrytime i mention na 2o na sya, umaasim daw ang face nya! she can't believe it daw eh! nyahahahaha!!!Ü asarin ko pa kya?! jke!;) anywayz, we're going to the church again cuz that's our bday ritual! nyek! sumtimes ayko sumama! sori kng an bad ko! anywayz, we're going to hve a simple celebration ult ngyon! sbi kc ni dad sa bday na lng daw ni kuya (sa 24th) kmi llbas! it's fine with me! at least nkasave! hehehehe...Ü kuripot! jke!Ü kc nman y wud u go out 4 dinner 3 times kng pwede i-celebrate na lng 1 time?!    &nbsp;   *~*~*~* 
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        let's sing! "oh boring day! oh boring day!" jst kdding! well, i'm not joking about my day being boring!;) lgi nman eh! nothing fun hppened again! kya la me tlga makwento 2day! boring day, boring blog! 4 pete's sake! btw, who's pete?! i dnt knw anyone named pete!&nbsp;anyone here knws pete?! ahahahaha!!! [sarcastically] nice jke carmela! geez...i'm going mental!Ü no wnder my blog's name is crazy girl!Ü newayz, 2day i started reading the book "Hiroshima" 4 my summer hmewrk! yay! snaps 4 me! *snaps&nbsp;4 herslf* kc nman ang boring ng book! who wud want to read it?! oh i knw! nerds! sori 2 those who are!Ü gotta wrap this up na cuz swmming pa kmi eh! hollerz!         &nbsp;               
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      here's wat happened 2day:  1. i woke up at 9 am!! yehey!!! aga na! i surprised myself! l8 din ako ntulog lst night!Ü  2. i was watching harry potter 2 a while ago then i dcided 2 turn d channel na lng kc may dvd nman kmi eh! nyahahaha!!Ü  3. i watched "i love the 90's" sa vh1 kc nkkaliw eh! la nman kc me alm about early 90's! (duh!)   4. ate lyka and i went to target and OH MY GA! we're again tempted 2 buy all the beauty products!! srap blhin ng buong store! kya nga lng we're trying 2 lmit ourselves coz may cable pa na bbyaran c ate eh! cable kc mhal...dmi kc channels eh! but it's rily gud! na-use nmin tlga yng ibng channels lalo na nng harry potter season...u knw, wen they were interviewed sa dfferent shows! hihihihihihi!!Ü  well, that's jst about it! boring day again! and watever i do, my summer will always be boring!=( gtg! hollerz!Ü
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hir i am again! i was ryt. i knew that my day wud be boring! nthing rily fun happened! doing d laundry isn't fun! washing d dishes isn't either! my gosh, prang maid na ako d2! kmi ni ate! gnagwa nla kming maid! hey, i wud love 2 do most of d haushold chores if they pay me! let's say $20 a day?! ahahaha...jst kdding! that's too mch!Ü  ♥•♥•♥•♥•♥•♥•♥ ♥•♥•♥•♥•♥•♥ ♥•♥•♥•♥•♥ ♥•♥•♥ ♥•♥  a while ago we went swimming ni ate. that was relaxing. and obviously that was d only fun thng that hppened 2day. but it's not rily that fun though. (ang gulo ko!) nagnight swmming kmi kc wlang pipol sa pool eh! solo nmin! actually we chcked the pool b4 kmi nagswmming and may pipol! so we waited until they were gone! hihihihihi... unfriendly kmi!Ü nag-pilates nga ulit kmi a while ago 4 20 mins lng.  well, that's jst about it! i'll hve to wrap this up cuz there's nthing to write na! hollerz!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well, 2day at least i woke up at 11! an hour early than yesterday! i'm proud of myself!! *claps* newayz, alm ko na hndi pa end ng day but i knw it's going to be soooo damn boring!! and the worst part is, ang init pa!! gudness gracious!!! i rily hate summer!!! hpe it's already fall season pra nman cold na! kso nga lng pag fall na, strt na ng skul!   OH MY GOSH!! can't i hve fun?! i still hve a dialectical journal to do 4 my summer hmewrk!!! who'S doing this 2 me?! did i do anythng wrong?! (shux nman! and drma!!)  until hir na lng muna! i'll jst add more stuff later to write dwn wat happened sa arw ko! ciao!!Ü   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      first of all, i woke up at 12:30 and saw that evrybody's awake. gosh, i ddnt even expect na 12:30 na pla! ntulog na kc ako ng mga 3 in the morning kc wen we arrived i ddnt feel like sleeping pa eh! i also took a bath cuz i felt so sticky! (i knw it's gross) then i fell asleep! hba pla ng sleep ko!Ü wen i woke up, i freshened up and ate cereal! i knw na it was lunch time but i felt like eating cereal! wat cud i do?!Ü   yada yada yada... blah blah blah... well, nthing rily interesting happened after i ate cereal! wat do u want me to say?!Ü  our dad told us to dress up cuz we're going to church cuz it's marvie's bday! we always go to church wen it's sumbody's bday! so, i dressed up and wen to mass! kla ko we were going to eat sumwhere pro d pla! but it's ok! i dnt wanna get fat!!;) my mom cooked and we had ice cream! wlang cake this time and i dunno why! but again, it's ok cuz i still dnt wanna get fat!Ü then, some of marvie's friends came over and they watched a movie! jst a simple celebration! but it was fun!Ü  lst yir kc we ate in a buffet and oh my gosh, i still rmember na i felt soooo heavy after! yko na ng gnun na feeling ah!  well, that's jst about it! jst a simple celebration for marvie's 9th birthday! our day was fun!Ü gotta go! pilates pa kmi ni ate eh! hollerz!Ü
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      jst got bck from san francisco!! i was sooo tired last night cuz we got home at like 12 midnight. it was a very long drive! we stayed in SF for like a week. i rily enjoyed it cuz i got to go around SF by walking! it was very tiring but fun! the last tym i was there, we ddnt rily go around SF cuz we were in a hurry! i also enjoyed the cold weather out there cuz here in my place it's soooo freakin' hot!! hpe i cud stay a bit longer there wid my cousins! unfortunately, we had to go home cuz it's my sister's bday 2day and my other sister had to go sumwhere else. well, gotta go cuz i need to dress up. we might go out for dinner 2day 2 celebrate her bday. bye!! hollerz!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        guess wat time i woke up 2day... 11:30!!  that's the earliest!! i made a  record!!!  yay!!!Ü   2day's  Dan Radcliffe's 15th birthday!!  yay! snaps 4 him!!!Ü my ga, he's 15!! dti nkita lng ntin sya mga 11 or 12! gudness! blis tlga!!!Ü   2morrow nman  birthday ng bro  ko. he's turning  24.  sbi nla dad ppnta daw kmi sa isang  beach . i dnt knw wer it is. but i hpe we'll hve fun!Ü   kmi ulit ni Ate gmawa ng  laundry  2day! lgi nla inaasahan dun! mejo nkkainis na nga eh! then, after the laundry they'll let us fold the clothes pa! hhhmmmppp!!  i. just. hate. it!!!    haaayyy... weekend  again! 2 tell u the truth, i hate weekends kpag  vacation  kc mom ko and2 lng sa house then uutusan nya kmi sa lhat ng  chores!  but i love weekends kapg school time na!! hehehehehe!!!Ü may  xcuse  kmi evrytime she'll tell us to do chores!! nyahahahaha!!!Ü   sad ako 2day coz di pa updated yng  fanfction  that i'm reading. i've been waiting for it the whole day! nkkabitin eh! but i'll jst gve the writer some time!Ü   well, that's evrything that hppened 2day!  2morrow again  (probably)!! byerz!!Ü      
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         12:45 noon .&nbsp; i woke up at that time. it's becoming a  habit  of mine na late matulog. actually, halos di na nga matulog eh! i should change it na coz wen school starts...i'll hve a hard time  adjusting.       &nbsp;     oh my ga ...the hp fanfiction is soooo  sad!!  i almost cried!! *sniffs* evrytime i remember that,  naluluha  ako! it's actually not done yet. the writer's still  updating  it actually.&nbsp; mdaming sad moments dun sa story nya. but it's rily good!Ü      &nbsp;   we watched  Legally Blonde  (hehe..sori! yun lng kc yng interesting movie nng time na yun eh!Ü) and a lttle bit of  The Hot Chick.  i knw na it's&nbsp;not rily good 4 my age yng movie coz of the  language  and stuff but i find it rily  funny!  nkktawa c yng actor eh! i can't rily spell his last name so wnt type the name na lng.Ü&nbsp;     &nbsp;   yesterday i found out na yng  girl  dun sa  Hot Chick  and the one sa  Mean Girls  and the one sa  The Notebook  iisa lng! her name's  Rachel McAdams  (i thnk). she rily looked like a  high school girl  sa Mean Girls pro sa Notebook she looked  old . not that old! sori, but i jst can't believe na sya pla yun! she had dfferent  hairstyles and color  for each movie eh!Ü     &nbsp;   nag-night  swmming  ako 2day 2gether with my sisters. it felt rily gud.Ü gaan ng  feeling  ko kc na-work ko yng body ko eh!  pilates  pa ako ngyon 4&nbsp;an hour.     &nbsp;   that's jst about it!  tomorrow again!  byerz!!Ü     &nbsp;     ps.   2morrow's dan radcliffe's 15th&nbsp;birthday!!!Ü       &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;    &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       got to chat with  yuri  4 a very short time at around&nbsp; 5 am !! tihihihihihi!!!Ü &nbsp;dnt ask!;)     &nbsp;   nagcomputer ako coz i was soo bored. the  sun  was actually rising pa nga eh! kso mejo dark pa rin ang surroundings ko. i was also reading a well written  harry potter fanfiction . nyahahahaha!!Ü sori, past time ko yun! actually the fanfiction&nbsp;was rily good! i rily like it kya nga i was hooked up dun!Ü nkkakilig pa nga eh! and i believe that the person who wrote it was a  harry n hermione shipper!  hihihihihihi!!!Ü ala lng!     &nbsp;   i went to the  public library  2day coz i hve to return a book. nagbyad pa ako ng due date fee ko! coz the other book that i borrowed was 1 wik due na! ahahahahaha!!Ü tnatmad kc ako ibalik! but gud thng i only hve to pay  $1 !! mura noh?!     &nbsp;   after the lib, we went to pick up  mum &nbsp;from her office. maaga kmi nkadting sa office so kuya and i dcided to go around  lancaster  muna. we went to the  east side  (we live in the west side) coz we hven't rily seen it eh!Ü pagblik nmin sa  office  ni mum she was there w8ing na! ngalit nga sya eh! nyahahahaha!!!Ü     &nbsp;   nthing rily hppened after our little  adventure!  i jst went straight to our pc and continued reading the  fanfiction!  hehehehe!!! bored ulit eh!Ü gtg na!!  hollerz!!Ü     
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       at least i wke up at  12 noon  2day! an hour early than yesterday!Ü ahahaha!!  hooray !    &nbsp;  yesterday, our cble was cut off 4 no reason but 2day, it came bck!  yay !! this event dserves another hooray!!Ü at least we saved  electricity  nman yesterday! kc all day nka-on yng tv eh!Ü actually, we ddnt save a lot of energy kc pc nman nmin yng nka-on the whole day. hehehehe!!!Ü it actually made no dfference!    &nbsp;  nng bumalik na yng cble nmin we watched a movie (duh!) called  The Cutting Edge !! i sooo love that movie!! like i said yesterday nng nanood kmi ng Center Stage na i wanted to dnce. now nman i wanted to  ice skate ! hehehe!! gulo ko noh?! i'm still a kid! (not rily a kid!) &nbsp;i hve a lot of  options  open 4 me!Ü     &nbsp;  kc yng movie is about a a guy and a girl na mgkapartners sa ice skating and they're  struggling  through the competition coz of their problems. yng girl din kc  stubborn!  nng una di nya gsto yng new partner nya. her old partner left her kc eh. yng new partner nya was a  hockey  player. she thnks na di kya ng guy ang  figure skating!  but she was wrong! then they fought a lot sa movie. and sa end they fell in  love  na!Ü    &nbsp;  nagswmming kmi ni ate lyka 2day. tgal na nmin di gnagwa yun eh! for only a short time lng nman!     &nbsp;   yun lng happenings 2day! gtg na!  bye!!Ü    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        2day i woke up at  1 pm ! nyahahahaha!!! morning na kc me ntulog eh!Ü kla ko nga mga 10 pm pa lng!     &nbsp;   gosh, this day was one of the  worst  summer days evr! first of all, super init!! secondly,  wla kming cable !! bummer huh?! sbi ng bro knina daw may cble guy outside and i thnk he was fxing or disconnecting sumbody's cble or upgrading sumbody's cble! i dunno...he may be doing any of the three. pro b4 the guy came daw ayos pa yng cble and wen he arrived, dun kmi nwalan! we called  adelphia  (cable company) and they said they'll be sending sum1 over. kso wlang dmating!  wlang hiyang cble company yan!  tnawagan ulit nmin and they said 2morrow na daw. aayusin na daw 2morrow! yay!! may cble na ulit 2morrow!!! hehehehe!!!Ü pro  screw the cble company!!!      &nbsp;   gud thng we hve&nbsp; dvds  nman in xchange sa cable! we watched  daredevil  (not rily interested with it) and  center stage ! i rily love that movie!! dhil sa movie na yun gsto tuloy mging  dancer . it might too late na pra mging  ballerina  and be that gud like sa movie. srap gyahin ng steps nla!Ü     &nbsp;   well, that's jst about it! nthing rily hppened xcept na lng sa mga mentioned! another  boring day  huh?! gtg na! byerz!!!Ü      
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       eio! haaayyy...another week starting! gosh! blis nman! yoko pa pumasok! nyahahahaha!!Ü  &nbsp;  newayz, as 2day is sunday, of course we went to  church . that's the very 1st thng we did 2day! nux nman!  very gud ako ! snaps 4 me!Ü then we went home, ate lunch...w8...i ddnt eat lunch nga pla kc i ddnt feel like eating eh. i ate breakfast din and i was full!:) tpos  marvie's friend  came over (again). marvie asked  mum  kng pwede daw pmasok yng frend nya and mum said yes. gulat na lng c mum kc kla nya until the lving room lng frend nya! pnapsok ni marvie until our rooms! sbi ni mum wen she said yes she only wanted her frend until the lving rum kc  private  na yng rooms nmin eh! mum wasn't xpecting na she'll go  further inside  our apartment! nkktwa nga c mum eh!Ü  (notice the wrd "mum"? british-like!!Ü)  bti nng pmunta yng frend ni marvie i was still wearing my church clothes  (no, i wasn't wearing a dress) ! nkkhiya kc if i wud be wearing my house clothes na eh! hehehehe!!!Ü  &nbsp;  yesterday, marvie and i went to the movies and 2day c kuya and ate lyka nman! they watched  kill bill vol.2 ! i've seen the frst one and it was very  bloody ! yuck! they were inviting me to come wid them sbi ko ayko kc nga&nbsp;bloody and bsides, i'm not allowed kc  rated R . oh well! i had fun nman yesterday with marvie!Ü  &nbsp;  that's jst about it! tomorrow nman!  carmela out !Ü  &nbsp;      
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       all i can say about this day is... boring!  super! sori if i always say that word pero that's the  perfect  one to dscribe my day.      woke up at about  10:30  2day. went straight to the  computer  to check my mails and stuff. well, the usual  things  i do wen i'm on the cmputer!Ü      ate some  english muffins.  they're pretty good. we baked  cookies  again. la kc makain eh! hehehehe!!!Ü jst felt like baking some! the cookies are rily  good!  srap with  milk!  yummy!!Ü sori,  mtakaw  wen it comes to cookies! can't help it!      anywayz, 2morrow's the  birthday of Harry Potter  (from the books) and  JK  (the author). people are actually  celebrating!  i wanna join nga eh! may celebration sa  Los Angeles!  nyahahaha!! nkikiparty lng!Ü go on, say it a little louder na i'm rily  crazy!  i won't care!      the  fanfic  that i'm currently into is again,  updated!  yay!! *claps* i'm sooo happy!! gnda tlga ng pagkasulat sa knya! i gave the  link  of that fanfic, look for my other  entries  below. if ur interested!Ü      so little  upd8  2day. sori about that. nthing to say eh! g2g na! byerz!!Ü  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       that's the  song  that woke me up this morning. i dnt rily knw the lyrics pro i knw the song. it woke me up at  7 am!!  woohoo! hehehe!!!Ü aga ko na ata naggising these days! anywayz, kya ako ngising sa song na yan coz it reminded me of someone! it rminded me of  Nina!  she's our  niece  in San Leandro (near San Francisco). grbe, kulit ng bata na yun! love k nga eh! nging close kmi wen we were staying with them. that's her  fave song  kc eh! she would play it a  million  times sa isang araw! phew!!Ü     &nbsp;   i was watching the  news  nng bgong gsing ako (u read it ryt, i  care  about the world!). boring stuff ang nsa news! halos same lng! like  Kobe Bryant's case ...Catherine Zeta-Jones receiving&nbsp;death threats and a lot more! they would repeatedly report about the  weather and traffic!  i was like  "shut up!!" . i knw it's going to be hot and traffic! geez!! no need to tell more!  *rolls eyes*      &nbsp;   i fell  asleep  din a while ago (afternoon). di ko npgilan eh! hba din ng tulog ko! i woke up for a while then went bck to sleep! hehehehehe!!!Ü     &nbsp;   i went to a  harry potter webbie  2day and i read na  "Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince" &nbsp; may be out by the end of this yir or start of nxt yir. i'm rily crossing my  fingers  for that. the sooner the better!Ü it may be possible daw kc according to the sources&nbsp; Scholastic (JK's publisher)  sent a letter to a bookstore and they said na it may be out na nga  sooner  than we thought. yay!!! JK said din sa webbie nya na the 6th book is  right on track  evn though she's xpecting a  third child . well, i'm rily happy for her!Ü     *here's JK Rowling's official website for more info:     urlLink   http://www.jkrowling.com/       &nbsp;    &nbsp;   gtg na! i'm actually watching a movie called  "Ice Castle"  and it's a gud one. a touching movie. byerz!!Ü    &nbsp;     
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       eto na yng song na stuck sa head ko these days....it's by  Ashlee Simpson.      &nbsp;   On a Monday, I am waiting  Tuesday, I am fading  And by Wednesday, I can't sleep  Then the phone rings, I hear you  And the darkness is a clear view  Cuz you've come to rescue me  Fall... With you, I fall so fast  I can hardly catch my breath, I hope it lasts  [Chorus:]  Ohhhhh  It seems like I can finally rest my head on something real  I like the way that feels  Ohhhhh  It's as if you've known me better than I ever knew myself  I love how you can tell  All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me  All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me  I am moody, messy  I get restless, and it's senseless  How you never seem to care  When I'm angry, you listen  When youre happy, it's a mission  And you wont stop 'til I'm there  Fall... Sometimes I fall so fast  Well, I hit that bottom  Crash, you're all I have  [Chorus:]  Ohhhhh  It seems like I can finally rest my head on something real  I like the way that feels  Ohhhhh  It's as if you known me better than I ever knew myself  I love how you can tell  All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me  All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me  How do you know everything I'm about to say?  Am I that obvious?  And if it's written on my face...  I hope it never goes away... yeah  On a Monday, I am waiting  And by Tuesday, I am fading into your arms...  So I can breathe  [Chorus:]  Ohhhhh  It seems like I can finally rest my head on something real  I love the way that feels  Ohhhhh  It's as if you've know me better than I ever knew myself  I love how you can tell  Ohhhhh  I love how you can tell  Ohhhhh  I love how you can tell  All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me  All the pieces, pieces, pieces of me...     
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       my title's still from the  song!  hehehehehe!!!Ü   anywayz, i woke up 2day at  7 am!  woohoo!Ü u knw y?! kc lhat ng tao sa bhay umalis (4 dfferent reasons) and  marvie and i  were left. dad said he was going to  call  ng mga 7 pra gsingin ko na c marvie (4 school). they placed the phone bside me then tmawag nga cla tpos yun! hehehe!!! di na ult me  nkatulog  after that. bsta most of the time wen i'm  awake  na di na mkkatulog.   i was flpping through all the  channels  and nkita ko ult yng  chamber of secrets. Ü i was tempted to watch it again but i always remind myself na may  dvd  nman kmi. and bsides,  prisoner of azkaban  is a lot fun to watch all over again. btw, i found out 2day na the prisoner of azkaban dvd will be released on  november 23  this year. yay!!! i'm soooo xcited!!!Ü dmi daw  special features !! sbi din daw&nbsp; warner bros.  will be releasing a  3-pack dvd  (ss, cos and poa). dnt hve to buy that one na cguro kc we hve the frst 2 nman eh!  here is a lnk kng ano daw yng  potential  look ng 'prisoner' dvd:     urlLink  http://www.mugglenet.com/viewer/?image_location=potentialdvd.jpg        anywayz, ate lyka's with her friends 2day sa  universal studios.  she was evn inviting me 2 join them kso i  refused  kc la nman me mkkausap wen i'm with them eh! and i've been to a  theme park  na dis summer and that's fine with me na. then, kuya's inviting me nman to go to  LA  2night kc ssunduin nman c ate eh. di pa ako sure kng ssama ako. but i thnk  dad's  coming with him.Ü    that's a wrap ! upd8 na lng ult 2morrow! or 2night! or midnight! wenever!  lol!  2morrow na lng! hollerz!!Ü          
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        haha!! jst got my title from a song! do u knw  ashlee simpson's "pieces of me"?  that's wer i got it!Ü  LSS (last song&nbsp;syndrome) &nbsp;na ako sa song na yun! evryday ko na lng naririnig eh! kya  pardon me  na lng kng wlang cnnection yng title ko sa mga ssbihin ko ngyon!Ü     &nbsp;   anywayz, i woke up at  10:00!!  hehehehe!! aga na! well, 4 me at least! kc yoko pgsabihan ako na ang late ko nman gmising! so even though i was still sooo  sleepy  nng 10, i let myself get up from the bed na lng.     &nbsp;   nothing rily hppened (again). jst a bunch of  stuff  na u dnt rily hve to knw nman.     &nbsp;   we were suppose to go  swmming  2day kso  Ate  had 2 go sumwhere kya di kmi ntuloy.  nag-pilates  na lng kmi ng 1 hour! phew! it was tiring but it felt rily gud!Ü     &nbsp;   kuya baked  cookies  ulit ngyon i and it was sooo gud!!Ü dmi ko nga ata nkain eh! i ate it 2gether with a  glass of milk!  tihihihihihihi!!!ÜÜÜ     &nbsp;   i am so hapi 2day kc updated na yng  hp fanfic  that i was hooked up to! yay!!! tgal ko din nagantay 4 that! well, i hve to w8 again!  boo-hoo!!:(      &nbsp;   uuumm...i dnt rily knw wat to say na.  2morrow again ! byerz!!Ü &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;  if evr ur interested in reading the fanfic that i always talk about, click here:    &nbsp;&nbsp;  urlLink ">Link    urlLink http://www.cosforums.com/showthread.php?t=19401    &nbsp;&nbsp;          
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        first of all, i jst wud like to say  sorry  coz i ddnt get to upd8 my blog yesterday! but i'll tell u wat hppened 2day and yesterday...Ü     &nbsp;    Saturday...July 24, 2004     it was my bro's  24th birthday!  we went to  ventura harbor and santa barbara beaches  to celebrate! di ako nagswim kc i ddnt bring my  swimsuit  coz i ddnt know we were going to the beach eh! kla ko jst to go around the place. di pla...anywayz, naglkad nalng kmi by the beach. i evn got my  pants  wet kc lkas ng waves evn though i folded it right up to my knees. but it was a fun walk! i jst missed the beach. hpe nkaswim kmi. we dcided to eat sumwhere in santa barbara. so, we went around  downtown santa barbara  to find a restaurant. gnda ng downtown nla! spanish-like place!Ü srap maglkad around kng may money ka to go  shopping.  it evn looked like  alabang town center  eh!Ü kso we ddnt find any restaurant so we jst dcided to go home coz we were all tired. bmili nalng c mom ng  kfc chickens  4 dinner.Ü     &nbsp;    Sunday...July 25, 2004     woke up at  10:30!  i took a bath immediately kc we were going to  mass.  we went to church at 12 noon. then, we had  salad  4 lunch! it was rily good! then i had  rocky road ice cream  4 dessert. mmm-mmm goooood!!Ü then, la na hppenings after that! i was the one who washed the  dishes  2day. aaaawww...jke!;) di pa kmi kumakain ng  dinner.  la pa kmi gana. maybe i'll eat  spaghetti  later! hehehehe!!Ü     &nbsp;   yun lng hppenings 4 yesterday and 2day! 1 more week  august  na! gosh, how fast! i dnt like it! gtg na! byerz!!Ü     &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       haaaayyy...2day was a  relaxing  day. mganda lng araw ko.Ü      sbi ni mom pnta daw kmi sa  palmdale mall   2 buy sandals 4 marvie kso sumakit tummy ni mom! di kmi ntuloy! it's ok...sbi nya 2morrow na lng daw!Ü hehe...babaw ng  kaligayahan  ko noh?! oh well!Ü      finally, we got 2 play  badminton  again! shux, i jst miss that game! kso pangit nman magplay d2 kc lging  mahangin!  the  shuttlecock  would go sa side di nman nmin kya habulin! hehehe!! sbi ni ate nwala yng  "badminton spirit"  nmin coz tgal na nmin di naglalaro! hehehe!!Ü back home kc we would always play sa lbas, then no wind only  cars  would interrupt us. *sighs* miss ko na ang house, manre, my friends and evrything! dnt lose hope na lng! i knw na may  possibility  ako mkauwi! *wenk*      so,  pilates  pa kmi ng sis ko for an hour tonight. then, i'll be taking a bath and sleep! sunday ulit 2morow...nu ba yan. hve to go sa  church  ulit! g2g! buh-bye!Ü  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        once again, i 4got to  upd8  my blog! i'm rily sorry for that! so,i'm going to try my best na  bumawi!Ü         Thursday...    it was  vanessa's birthday!!  so, humingi ako ng  fonecard  sa dad ko to call her. i tried to call at about  2 am (5 pm sa pinas)  kso no ring sa other line. i tried to call  kath  jst to test if the fonecard's working. and thnk god, it wrked coz nkausap ko c kath! i told her  evrything  (not rily evrything) that i can sa time limit nmin! naubos ko yng card so humingi ult ako 2 call vane nman! the fonecard worked kso la nman daw sya sa bhay and said na i should call at about  8:30 pm  dun (di nman kc alm ng smagot na it's a call frm USA).  8:30 pm dun,  5:30 am d2!  gosh! no choice, had to sleep muna khit 4 jst  an hour  coz it was already  4:30 am.  thnkfully, i managed to wake up nman ng 5:30 am. called her, got to talk to her, kwentuhan kmi until our time lmit's done.       Friday...(2day)    woke up at  12 noon.  npasrap ang tulog ko! hehehe!!!Ü haaayyy...weekend again! geez...how fast! so, i ate lunch, surfed the net, read a book and hir i am now updating my blog!  phew!  long day noh?! j/k!!Ü we're still going to do the  laundry  2day! ayko nga eh kso i hve to. *rolls eyes*       g2g na!  short update  lng noh?! nxt time again! buh-bye!!Ü   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        hey! at last! i ddnt 4get to upd8 my blog! yay!! hihihihihihi!!!Ü      it was pretty boring 2day. it's always boring actually. i ddnt sleep until like  3 am  coz we baked  cookies  again! hehe!! jst felt like baking eh!Ü may breakfast na kmi! jke!Ü      2day, i finally dcided to read (again) the book 4 my hmework kso  nkatulog  din ako! believe me, it's that boring! khit sbihin pa ntin na ur rily awake mkkatulog ka din! *sighs*      may gud news 2day 4 harry potter fans!  Ralph Fiennes and Miranda Richardson  are confirmed 2 join the gang for  'Goblet of Fire'!  yay! i knw u dnt know them coz i dnt either! they're  british  kc eh! ralph will be  Lord Voldemort  while miranda will be  Rita Skeeter!  it's a rily gud news! may news din na may nkakita sa mga harry potter stars sa  Beacon Hill.  i dnt knw wer it is but of course sa  UK  yun! they were shooting the  'portkey scene'  (going to the  quidditch world cup ). so that means the guys playing  Cedric and Amos Diggory  were with them! cool!Ü      btw, if ur curious who the hell are Ralph Fiennes and Miranda Richardson, here are some  links  to see their  pictures :    urlLink   http://images.google.com/images?q=ralph+fiennes&amp;amp;amp;amp;ie=UTF-8&hl=en&amp;btnG=Google+Search             urlLink   http://www.miranda-richardson.com/          g2g! take care ya'll! smooches! bye!!Ü    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       *sighs* i 4got to  upd8  my blog last night. nwwala na kc sa isip ko eh! oh well! wat am i doing now?! updating it!Ü      woke up 2day at about  9:30 am  (miracle?! not rily). gnising kmi ni kuya coz sbi nya we'll be  washing  our car 2day (the black one). di kc pwede maglinis ng car d2 sa parking lot ng  apartment  so we had to go to our aunt's house. pgdating nmin sa house, we washed it immediately. then, our aunt saw us and she  treated  us sa isang taco place called  Del Taco.  ddnt notice na lunch time na pla nun! we had a gud time then she dropped us off sa house nya coz we weren't done yet! after washing the car, we went home na!      the moment i stepped inside the apartment, i turned on the  tv  and flipped the  channels  kso wlang mgandang shows. pnanood ko na lng yng biography ni  Christina Aguilera.  grbe din pla yng mga journey nya b4 she was evn popular. bta plang sya she was already  singing.  knuwento din nya yng days nya sa  Mickey Mouse Club  with Britney, Justine and a bunch of talented kids. bsta, she went through a lot of thngs b4 she evn got to wer she is right now.       about  yesterday  nga pla (wasn't able to upd8 nga kc eh), la nman happenings. i just went 2 the  library  to borrow a book 4 my  freakin ' summer hmework. wat else?! la na eh! yun lng!      g2g! i'll try to  upd8  my blog 2morrow! hpefully i wnt 4get! byerz!Ü  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Saturday, July 31, 2004      Happy Happy Birthday to JK Rowling and Harry Potter!  yay!! i thnk JK is already  39  (?) and Harry is chronologically  24 ! jst like my bro! wow!!Ü anywayz, yesterday we went to the  movies!  evrybody felt like watching eh! c dad naiwan kc our aunt needed him (bsta about sumthng). kuya, ate lyka and mom watched  "The Bourne Supremacy"  while marvie and i watched  "Shrek 2".  actually, i wnted to go see 'bourne' kso sbi nla smahan ko daw c marvie sa  ogre . yoko na manood ng 'shrek' coz  overxposed  kc sya d2. bwat products d2 mkkita mo yng ogre. no thank you! *rolls eyes*         Sunday, August 1, 2004    gosh, august na. one of the  hottest  months! noooo!!! i dnt rily like summer! sna  fall  na! anywayz, i woke up at about  10 am . i had  pancakes  4 brunch. then we went to church at 12 noon. usually we go at  9:30  kso di na nmin naabutan (as u can see i woke up at 10). after mass we went to  stater bros . (a grocery store). bought some fruits, bread, chips and a lot more! we went home, ate lunch (khit hapon na) and watched a  tennis match . we were watching  Federer vs. Roddick . do u knw those guys?! i dnt rily knw Federer but i knw Roddick kc nging boyfriend ni  Mandy Moore  eh! hehehehe!!Ü so, hir i am right now,  updating  my blog coz i ddnt hve the chance last night.      g2g na! take care ya'll! byerz!Ü    
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        oh man! for 2 days i 4got to upd8 this thing! what the  hell  is happenin' with me?!       Wednesday    well, 4got what happened sa day na toh! oh well! let's jst move on sa thursday...       Thursday    maaga kmi gmising kc we had 2 go to our aunt's house to help her clean up kc may  party  sya. we scrubbed the  floors , shined the tables, and fixed evrything we can! naabutan nga kmi ng  gabi  eh! haaayy, i was sooo tired! we worked like  house-elves!  lol! while cleaning, the worst thing hppened pa...my  allergy  attacked! gosh, how i hate mgkasipon! my eyes were  watery , barado yng nose ko and i was sooo tired and sleepy! i had 2 take a  bath  muna b4 i can go 2 bed. so i did and went to sleep na!       Friday    well, it's actually  9:42 am  kya la pa nman nngyayari! i surprised myself coz i woke up at 7 am! yay!!! i dunno y! so far, i ate  oatmeal , answered emails and a survey, visited  hp websites , and uuuummmm... i thnk that's it. hihihihi!!Ü well, all i can say right now is  GOOD LUCK TO ALL OLYMPIANS IN ATHENS, GREECE!  hehehe!!!Ü olympics starts 2night eh!      g2g! tc ya'll! smooches!!Ü   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       well,  4got  2 upd8 again yesterday! hihihihi!!Ü *sighs* it slips my mind!!       Monday    dnt rily remember wat hppened khapon! la din nman kc ata hppenings eh! let's jst 4get about yesterday and i'll tell u about 2day...;)       Tuesday    gosh, u guys hve no idea how  hot  it is over here! temperature would reach up to  110 degress  (fahrenheit)!!! *gasps* i rily can't w8 4 fall! oh  autumn!!  come to us na!!! lol! newyaz, i went  jogging  with my bro 2day. i wanted 2 do something  physical  eh! and pra msanay din ako kpag sa skul pnatakbo ulit kmi ng  1 mile!  hehehe!!Ü well, it felt rily good! after nmin mag-jogging, i stayed  outside  na lng kc it was  boiling  hot inside eh! c kuya nman he watched  "Seabiscuit"  while marvie and i were outside. blah blah blah... nkinood na din ako ng movie kc npagod na ako eh! i had no idea na the  story  of that movie was gud, and  touching.  4 me, it was a good movie! di nga lng ako snay kay  Tobey Maguire  na red hair! hihihihi!!! evrytime i see him i would say  "spiderman!!"  or  "peter parker!!"  lol! role of the  lifetime  nya yun eh! so, hir i am, updating this thing and i'll do  pilates  pa then take a bath!      g2g! see ya guys later! smooches!!Ü  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        my body's  sore!  kc nman di na kmi sanay maglaro ng  badminton!  my right arm (which i use to play) hurts and evn my  ass!  (wahehehehe!!!Ü) dunno y that part hurts!  *winkwink*       haayy..went to  church  (of course) at 12 noon. ohmyga! suuuper hotta! tanghaling tapat pa! gud thing  mlamig  sa loob ng church! hehehe!!Ü ryt after church we went to d  palmdale mall!  sbi ko nga kc yesterday we were suppose to buy marvie  sandals  kso di natuloy khapon. 2day kmi pmunta! lam nyo ba, malls here are  BORING!!!  gosh! hrap mghnap ng gsto mo blhin! not like sa pinas... easy lng mghanap and  fancy  pa ng malls! d2 prang  palengke!  hehehe!!!Ü newayz, we had a hard time looking for a pair of sandals. marvie's such a  whiner  pa! "ma, im' tired! ma, can we eat?! ma, i wanna go home!" shut the  hell  up! geez! hehe...sorry po!Ü so, we bought some  milkshake  sa mcdo and walked under the  sun  to go to another shoe store! believe me...i was on  fire  while we were walking! u can fry an egg na sa head ko! hehehehe!!!Ü kso la din kmi nhanap na sandals! ugh! i was also looking for a pair of sandals for myself! i'm looking 4 a  high-heeled one!  i'm currently into high-heeled boots, sandals or jst shoes! nyahahaha!!Ü la kmi nhanap so, we went hme na lng! the only things we bought were  mom's handbag  and 2  blouses  4 me. nice shopping huh?!      so, we did  laundry  2day. then clean, then eat and rest! hehe!!Ü jst a normal but boring  sunday afternoon!  got to chat with my girlz  roz, yuri and karen  (sglit lng c kj).we talked about a lot of thngs like  emma watson, katie leung, ralph fiennes ...let's jst say we talked about harry potter mostly! sbi nga ni roz,  contagious  ako! according to dr. roz i hve  "imaddictedwithharrypotter-miosis" !! lol! a newly discovered  virus!!  ahahaha!!Ü kulit! kc pti sya mejo hooked up na rin sa hp! ahahaha!!! i rily am contagious!Ü newyaz, roz sent me a pic of  "no name" .finally, i've seen the guy's face! he's actually cute! but dnt get me  wrong!  i'm not falling 4 that guy!Ü      g2g na! gosh,  long  enrty huh?! hihihihihi!!!Ü bye!! mwah!!Ü    
     
    
</post>


</Blog>