<Blog>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If you have stumbled onto this then you have also stumbled onto an Australian volunteers thoughts and experiences from the field in Papua New Guinea.  Over the time that I will be here I will hopefully post some of my experiences that I no doubt will happen as well as various thoughts, observations or whatever that comes into my head.   As a bit of background so that things I say make sense, I am up here on my own free will as a volunteer through the organisation Australian Volunteers International.  I have a 2 year contract with the Papua New Guinea University of Technology.  My position is with the Department of Open and Distance Learning, and what I will hopefully be doing is establishing Study Centre computer networks so students can use computers to do distance learning.  That's the plan.  I will keep you posted as to how I do. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My little Haus Meri that I mentioned last email came on Tuesday morning and she stayed the whole day, cleaned everything in sight.  I gave her a tip of 2 Kina (big of me I know).  I felt guilty about her staying all day as I didn't have a key to give her to lock up and leave, so I did walk back home at lunchtime and asked her if she wanted to go home, but she wouldn't have a bar of it saying she still had clothes to iron, floors to mop.  She wanted to come on Thursday as well, but I told her once a week is plenty, for a single guy.  I have met quite a few of the other Volunteers around, who are from VSO (British mob) and GDS (German Development Service).  A couple of the VSO guys are actually working at the uni, and one has a car.  I have already buttered up to him and have managed to jump on board for a few trips into town, which has been handy and means that I have now stocked my fridge with a slab of SP Lagers (the local brew, tastes like cat's piss, but you get used to it).   Well my next-door neighbour Martin and myself are trying to organise a joint house warming party for this weekend, for all the local volunteers to get together and christen our places.  Martin only moved in just before Christmas and then went back to Oz for a month.  We should have had it organised for last saturday, but I have not got my phone connected yet and Martin's has been dead.  Trying to get Telikom to do anything is like trying to get Telstra to do something.  Work has changed gears and instead of being in Neutral we are now moving along in First.  Last week I built 6 old donated laptops that I needed to give to the site coordinators who came for a seminar.  This was no mean feat, as out of the 20 laptops we had, only about half work. I also had to give a little presentation on the technology we are going to be using, for the project, which went down pretty well.  It looks like my first trip around the country should be in a few weeks, and the destination is lovely Manus Island a few hundred k's north of the mainland near the equator.  It is supposed to quite pretty with great places to swim, which will be good as Lae doesn't have any.  Martin has offered to lend me his snorkel, goggles and flippers.  It is pretty tough, but someone has to do it.  The reason for going is just to collect some old radio equipment that DODL set up about 6 years ago, but they never use, so I will probably fly up and then catch the boat back.  Well the staff club has opened up, which is conviently located on the walk back home.  They have a TV there that I think will suffice for me to catch the news occasionally.  It is amusing over here in the fact that if you join any club (Golf, Workers etc) they give you a key to the front door, not sure why though.  Having no TV has not fazed me yet and I have not really missed, I might even be able to get away with not needing one at all.  We shall see.  Books have been my main source of entertainment, and the library is well stocked.  I shall probably get a decent laptop soon through work so I can watch all my movies that I have brought along.  My Pidgin is slowing coming along.  All the guys in the office want to help me out and they have decided to speak to me only in Pidgin.  This has been half successful as they soon forgot and went back to speaking English to me.  I have been asking questions on how to say things and phrases and as I said it is slowly coming along.  Pidgin is a bit of laugh, when you read signs around the place.  Went for a trip on Saturday up the valley, where there are quite a number of cattle properties.  Signs along the way warning about cattle straying onto the road say, "Luk Aut: Bulamakau long rot!" (say it as it is spelt).  As a side note, Bull is "Man Bulamakau" and Cow is "Meri Bulamakau".  It is pretty funny.  Another thing that cracks me up is that people here don't buy cigarettes by the packet, but individually.  Your waiting in line to get something from the Kiosk and the guy in front asks for 3 smokes and the girl opens up a packet and pulls out 3 and hands them to him. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am making quite a lot of new friends. In fact I would say that I have made more new friends here in a week (outside of work mates) than I ever did while living in Sydney.  It is quite a lot easier obviously when you live in a smaller community.  For example I met my next door neighbour last night, and we had a chat over a glass of wine in his place for a couple of hours.  I have probably only talked to the next door neighbours in Bourke st maybe 3 or 4 times.  My next door neighbour up here is an Aussie guy, who lectures in the architecture dept.  He is not a volunteer, but was actually born up here, but has lived most of his life in Oz.  We got on really well.  This morning I was held up by a little local lady outside my door as I started off to work.  She had a reference and was wondering if I wanted a house cleaner and someone to iron my clothes.  For the equilivant of $4 I now have a Haus Meri, who will come once a week, and do all the things I used to avoid in Oz like clean the toilets and bathroom, and iron my shirts.  Whose complaining?   Yesterday I visited the Rainforest Habitat, that they have on campus.  It was pretty good.  Got to see Tree Kangaroos, and the PNG echidna which is bigger than the Oz variety. They have birds of paradise there, a saltwater croc and cassowaries etc.  So I had fun with my camera snapping away.  I was the only visitor at the time so one of the workers let me into the tree kangaroo/echidna pen and I got to wander around and get up close to them. If anyone comes and visits me, this will be on the destination list.  Went out on the town on Friday night to a local club with some of the AVI volunteers who live in town.  It is certainly no London or Sydney, but I am sure it could have been worse.  The local beer was cheap at least.  They have an obession it seems with 80's music though.  Speaking of price, anything local is very cheap. You can buy fresh food and vegatables at markets for next to nothing, and there is a little campus market which is about 100m away from my place.  The price for about half a dozen Kau Kau (Sweet Potato), is 1 Kina (40 cents).  Carrots are a similar price/quantity.  1 Kina for a pineapple, same for a coconut.  To go into town on a PMV it cost's 50 toea (about 20 cents).  A local newspaper costs 1.50 Kina.  It gets expensive on any imported goods.  Electrical products are very pricey, and there seems to be a massive markup somewhere along the line. eg a DVD player costs 1000Kina ($400), where a similar one in Oz would be $150.  So far I have done all my own cooking, but I need to get myself some more utensils like a wok etc.  Last night I had chicken with kau kau chips, plus some veggies.  Not too bad if I say so myself.  Milk is a problem over here and it is like asian countries where they only have UHT or powder milk, something I guess I will just have to live with.  Lae is not the prettiest town in the world and it is very spread out, it gets dusty when it doesn't rain, although last night we had a massive rainstorm that absolutley downpoured. It caused a brief blackout this morning with the wind.  The university campus is pretty quite and laid back, but then the students havn't arrived yet.  It is a flat place with mountains all around it in the distance.  Through my bedroom window I get a great view of mountains that rise up to 4000m.  They constantly have cloud whisping around them, pretty picturesque, although there is a powerline across the street that runs through the scene.  On my 20 minutes walk to the office, I pass through sports fields, where they play cricket on the weekend at the moment and Rugby League during the southern winter months. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have now been here for more than a week and I am starting to settle into the pace of life here, which is pretty laid back.  I am now in Lae after flying over from Port Moresby on Saturday.  And I started my job at the Uni yesterday.  Though so far I have not done a hell of a lot, just the usual start of a new job stuff like ID cards, forms, bank accounts etc.  My house is pretty cool, I have a little 2 level, 2 up, terrace style place on the campus grounds that is about 15 minutes walk from the office.  I havn't moved in yet as power and other things are still being sorted.  So I have been staying at the Uni Guest house which is pretty good, as I get my meals all cooked for me.   It is hard to get over how lush and green everything is coming from dry and dusty Oz.  Lae gets something like 4500mm every year, but so far it has not rained here yet.  Apparantly when it does, it can last for weeks. An umbrela is on the shopping list.  It is also pretty hot, especially when the sun is out.  I went for a walk yesterday morning and went I got back I was dripping with sweat, I am getting used to it though.  As I knew it would be, the humidity is the killer.  Port Moresby was as everyone had informed me is a bit of dump.  The first thing that you notice is the tall fences topped with razor wire everywhere.  The second thing you notice is the red spit stains on the ground from everyone chewing Buai (or Bettle Nut), it is a pretty disgusting habit that a lot of people have.  Black teeth and a red mouth are a pretty common sight.  The course that we did in Moresby for the first week, was useful but laid back.  We learnt a bit of Tok Pisin (Pidgin) and useful phrases etc, that we put into use on a field trip to a Market via PMV (public motor vechicle).  The best part was spending time with the other Australian volunteers I came over with and hitting the pool at the motel at the end of the day.  We did a few touristy things, not that there is much of that to do there.  We saw the National Parliment and sat in the viewing gallery for a session. Pretty boring.  We went to the National Library, a bit depressing as they had no money and could not even get the air-conditioning fixed, therefore the books were starting to mould.  The National Musuem I have heard is good, but when we arrived the security guard had gone home after locking the main door.  It seems no one else had a key to let anyone inside.  Stories like this are pretty common over here.  For example, another good one is one day during a session of the National Parliment, the building went into blackout, apparantly the power company turned off the power after they had forgot to pay their bill.  My boss is a great guy, he came and picked me up from Lae airport on Saturday and took me to the uni guest house.  Then we went into a club in town that he was a member of and we sunk quite a few of the local beer SP Lager (the beer slogan written in pidgin is pretty funny, "nambewan bia").  We chatted about the job and everything else, like family etc.  Everyone here seems to have a big family, which is not really surprising.  He also picked me up on Sunday and we went for a drive up towards Wau (where gold was first discovered) and visited a village on the way back.  No one was home though as the village Volleyball championships were taking place, that was an amusing sight.  He is also a big hiker, so he is going to organise a trip up Mt Wilhelm at Easter, which is the highest mountain here at 4500m, and a possible Kokoda track attempt early next year.  The Kokoda track is a pretty serious adventure that usually takes most westerners between 7 & 10 days.  In Moresby I met some locals who had done it in 3 days. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Some news that I only found out about since arriving.  My new hometown of Lae actually sits astride of one the most seismically active faults in the world.  It floats on the edge of the great Indo-Australian plate, which is steadily marching northward and the comparatively tiny Bismarck plate (more of a saucer).  This in turn is sandwiched up against the massive Pacific plate which is slowly heading east.  You do the maths!  At some point no doubt I am going to feel a bit of a shiver as the two big fellas, work out their differences and play piggy in the middle.  So far so good, with not much activity, and apparently there hasn't b  een much  for decades.  Lets hope though that when the bigfella's are dancing the tango, they don't end up shaking their booty.   You learn to live with some unexpected occurrences up here, but even so it is hard not to feel sorry at the moment for 200,000 people that live to the south, across the main river in the area, the Markham.  Three weeks ago the only bridge over the Markham, linking the communities of Bulolo and Wau to the rest of the country, was closed to all traffic, and only foot traffic was allowed.  One of the piers, due a big rise in water level, started to float, and so that section now has a noticeable sag. People got on though and hand carted goods over the bridge between unloading trucks and the waiting ones on the other side.  That was until a week ago, when the water, which is still quite high, washed away the abutment on the Lae side, leaving a 5m gap betwe  en the  bridge and the bank.  So in effect that has now severed all cargo access to 200,000 in southern Morobe.  And this will probably remain so, until the experts stop scratching their heads, and work out how to build a new bridge, which is not as simple as it sounds as the Markham valley is basically all gravel without any bedrock, for a long way down.  It is not just civil infrastructure that suffers either.  All of last week a major microwave link that Telikom owns failed between here and the capital Port Moresby, which completely halted the mobile network and data lines for this part of the country.  That meant the Uni's Internet connection was offline for all of last week.  Transport is not exactly something that runs to a timetable or is diverse in it's options.  Public Motor Vehicles (PMV’s) are the only way to get around all the cities and towns apart from Port Moresby, which is lucky enough to have Taxis.   PMV's are an experience just in themselves with most of them second-hand Japanese mini-buses with 25 seats that have not been maintained for god knows how long.  I must have by now been on the full range of quality available, from the newer ones, that still have the stuffing in the seats to the, lets just say barely held together ones, where stuffing in the seats is considered a luxury and air-conditioning comes not only from the glassless window but through holes in the floor.  One  that I went on yesterday, seemed to give discounts if you helped push-start when the engine stalls.  With almost daily reports in the newspapers, of another PMV crash, X number dead, it is better to grab a lift with someone you know who's going to town.  Though the good thing is that because there is no timetable to worry about, you just rock up to a bus stop, and jump on a waiting bus.  When it fills up, which doesn’t take long, off it goes.  This only really works though in non peak times.  If you try on a Saturday morning there will be a massive crush to get on any PMV that shows up.  This is mainly due to the PMV operators looking for the easy money and not doing the longer routes, like out to the uni, so you have the compounding problem of more people wanting to use the buses and less of them available. The other issue, that I discovered first hand on Sunday, is like a lot of other places in the world  when you get the crowds you get the pickpockters.  Though maybe it is my now ingrained wariness in those situations, or perhaps that the kid was an amateur, but I easily caught him trying to dip his sticky little fingers into my empty pocket.  I have seen the art performed enough to know the modus operandi and therefore the respective counter-measures.  Well apart from all that gloom, the best thing this country offers, has to be the food.  Being a tropical country, food is literally everywhere, and it does not take too much to grow anything.  I thought of myself as a gangrene thumb, but as I discovered anyone can grow things here.  For example I have thrown herb and spice seeds out the back and without any help, they are now shooting up.  At the markets it is a veritable cornucopia, which the produce ranging from the ubiquitous Kau Kau (Sweet Potato - I didn't realise there were so many varieties) and Bananas (again many varieties  - don't get your cooking vs ripe mixed up) through to the tropical fruits, Paw Paw, Guava, Mango,  Pineapple, and then onto the more normal western veggies, like Carrot, Beans and Onions. If you are concerned by Genetically Modified crops and only buy Organic, well you don't have to worry here as they have not even heard of the term GM.  Everything is way it was intended.   And with my liklik (little) market being only a 5 minute walk, there is no excuse not to eat healthily.  Don’t get confused by the term Market, and think of check-out chicks and shopping trolleys.  Over here it is slightly different.  It is more of a take your own bag, wander around a bit looking for the best stuff, ask "hamas" to get a price for that nice looking pineapple, fill up your bag making sure not to step on the sellers mat and then wander around for a bit further passing an eye over all the produce, type of market.  You may also chat to someone who knows your name and you may have met once before but have forgotten, buy some roasted peanuts as a snack and then head home saying “apinun!” (evening) to the giggling kids on the way.  It is a lot of fun and can turn into a small social event (see attached pic for an idea of what part of it looks  like).  Apart from that the best part for me at least, has to be the community life that I now have, living on the campus.  I know all my neighbours, and will always bump into someone that I know if I go for a walk.  Also being someone who is different and without an established family network, I have the benefit that everyone wants to help me out, so that means that I have got offers to stay in almost all parts of the country and visit a brother or sister of so-and-so or if they are going that way, I should go along so they can show me that part of the country.  Because aside from all of the problems it does have it really is a fairly spectactular country, with everything from massive mountains to crystal clear beaches (palm trees overhanging - think of those travel brochers you have seen) and from smoking volcano's to mighty rivers.  OK, I thought I would give some tips in case one day you head off to the airport, jump on a plane, it gets hi-jacked and you land in a foreign city but am not sure where.  If you see some or all of the following things from the window, you just may be in Papau New Guinea.    The security guards are using a bow and arrows, instead of a gun.  About ten guys with push lawnmowers are tackling the grass between the runways.  A DC10 is burnt out, sitting beside a hanger with most of its parts stripped.  The locals are more interested in trying to sell you something than save you.  The hostage negotiation team doesn’t show for two days, as they were on strike.  The sign above the terminal building says PORT MORESBY INTERNATIONAL AIR ORT.    
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well it is now over 4 weeks since I lodged a form for a phone at home.  My hopes were raised on friday morning, by a call from Telikom, saying that they tried to connect my phone a couple of times the week before, but nobody was home when they came.  Funny that, perhaps it is because I work and live alone?  I told them to come around to the dept and collect me and I will let them in so they can connect the phone.  But of course nobody came.  Joy in the office seems to think it was probably because it was a payday.  Every second friday every one who earns a salary gets paid.  Obviously as you can imagine it is also the day that most of the problems and no work happens.  I rang them this morning and they were going to get back to me.  I am sure it will happen at somepoint soon.   Well the weekend, was pretty good.  Friday night was an experience, though because of the weather.  Martin (next-door neighbour) and then David (British volunteer here at the Uni) came around and we had some drinks, and then David left at about 7.20 to walk home so he could collect his car to pick me up so we could go into a club.  10 minutes after he left it started raining, really heavily!  Martin rushed round to his place, getting wet on the way at about 7.50 and then David showed up at about 8.  David was saying something about the water in the my street, being really high, and if I could tell him he was not dreaming it.  Yeah whatever I thought.   Well for about 50m along the street the water was coming over the headlights of David's Land Cruiser, making amongst other things a bow wave and it extremely hard to drive.  And this had all happened in just 30 minutes.  I was impressed.  When we got back at 1 the water was completley gone.  Saturday night was a Kava night.  Kava if you don't know is the drink of choice in Vanuatu and Fiji, and is made from the Kava root.  They grow it over here too, but it is not really used a lot.  PNG of course is the land of the betel nut.  Anyway basically it makes you pretty calm and mellow, but unfortunatley first you have to turn it from root form into liquid which is a bit of a mission, cutting up and then grinding etc.  Secondly you have to get past the taste, which is not unlike drinking muddy water.  If you dont baulk at a couple of coconut shells worth, you will be pretty mellow after about 30 minutes.  I think you can buy it from health food shops in tablet form, as a anti-stress medication. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Christianity is the dominant religion in PNG.  Unless you come here though you don't fully realise how successful the missionaries have been in converting the "savages".  Coming from a secular society like Australia where religion has more or less taken a back seat to everyday life, I have found it is interesting to see a society that is quite the opposite.  Everyone seems to be from a particular denomination (with some obscure ones in thrown in) and you learn early, if you are inclined like me, to either tell everyone you are an atheist/agnostic/Buddhist etc or pick a denomination that is not represented locally.  This is wise advise as you will find within the first few weeks plenty of people who will inquire as to what church you belong to.    Whether you agree with the what the missionaries have done or not, one thing that is certain is it has certainly changed the lives of the average Papua New Guinean.  Church life has now become a fantastic social event for the people.  It gives them something to do, it allows them to sing and they get to mix with their friends.  Perhaps the reason churches have been so popular here, and the missionaries so successful is that they so allow for social activity, something that previously was limited to the odd sing-sing once every blue moon.  It is amazing to see how many different denominations have taken root here.  If you look at the history of colonisation it is not hard to realise why.  Papua New Guinea has been on the world map longer than Australia has, and the coastal people have had contact with the outside world for centuries.  It was commonly thought (for some reason) by the early 20 century colonists that the interior of PNG did not contain much in the way of human habitation.  Hence the shock that was to be had by both the locals and the explorers when in the 1930's white man first ventured into the highlands and discovered twice as many people there than were on the coast.  By the 1930's the industrial age was well and truly in swing, so information about the multitudes of heathens needed "saving" went far and wide and quickly.  After the war the race was on by all the missionary Christian groups of the world to "save" these multitudes from their heathen ways.  So now you have the bizarre situation in a town like Goroka with a population of around 25,000, having 43 denominations represented.  Unfortunately from a secular point of view living in PNG does have it disadvantages, though nothing that can't be put up with.  These seem to be mainly the incessant bombardment of religious tenets.   It ranges from the ever present street side preachers, gospel music at the supermarket, people asking you to come to their church and the constant e-mails that are sent around via the universities e-mail system.  The Uni All Staff distribution list has more or less been taken over for purposes apart from University work.  People use it as a soap-box to preach their gospel, invitations to join their crusade (not sure what happens there, though it brings visions of men in armour with St. George crosses) or come to a lotu (pray meeting), warnings of some new devil like technology that everyone should be wary of, showing times for "The passion of the Christ" at the campus Christian centre and this weeks TV schedule for the Hope channel.  It gets a bit much at times.  The culture in other respects though has grounding very much in the past.  It is funny to think that a simple thing like a mother breast-feeding her child in public is frowned upon in supposed liberal countries like Australia or the UK (though with Howard in office prehaps I should rephrase that), but here in what you would assume to be a more conservative country it is not uncommon to see mothers with one breast poking out of there top suckling a little one.  One image that I don't think I will forget in the near future was while buying bananas at a market.  The woman selling the produce was wandering around showing me the best bananas, while all the time having a wide eyed child attached.  I am not sure who had the biggest cultural shock the kid seeing the whitefella or me doing business with a breast-feeding mother.  In western culture seeing two men holding hands and walking together, it would be safe to assume that the pair were gay.  Now as I said before PNG is a very conservative country due to the influence of the churches, which is why seeing men holding hands here seem bizarre.  But the holding hands act is quite a common occurrence.  It does not mean the men are gay, but most likely just good friends.  It seems that the stigma associated with that act in western cultures has not transgressed to PNG life, and the act is still a throw back to a part of their pre-colonial culture.  The act of taking another mans hand takes place all the time.  If you happen to meet a friend while walking, you will always shake his hand before having a conversation.  From my upbringing it was usually the case of only shaking hands upon the first meeting of someone, or if you have not seen them for a long time.  Oddly enough though physical contact is usually only done between same sex groups.  Acts of male-female contact is rarely if ever seen in public.  In fact the entire relationship between men and women is very different to western culture.  It is not uncommon for a husband and wife to live in completely separate towns and only see each other occasionally.  This is what my boss does.  It seems they make up for lost time when they do get together as approximately 50% of the population is under 20 years of age.  Living seperate lives does not mean that they are not good parents.  Fathers dote over their children just as much as mothers do, they just may see less of them. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have been and returned from Goroka again, but this time it was for work and not a holiday, although it seemed a bit like one.  Drove up on Thursday with the printer guy from the office, Sanga, who can only speak in pidgin.  Managed to get by on the communication front without too much hassle.  Although I am still mixing a few words up in my tok pisin (pidgin).  An example would be "Wanem" and "Likem".  The former means "What" and the second can mean either "I want" or "I like".  So occasionally I will say "Mi wanem dispela kau kau" instead of saying "Mi likeim dispela kau kau" (I want that sweet potato).  Anyway my vocabulary is slowly increasing and like I said I am getting by most of the time.   Up in Goroka I stayed with my “wantoks”, Monica and Widya, while I dumped my colleague off at a guest house.  Much more homely with friends.  On the Friday night I met a new volunteer from AVI who has been there a month now (hard to believe I have been here for four) whose name is Jennifer.  She is working in the local government in some capacity that I can't remember.  Monica told me beforehand that she was a bit weird, and I tend to agree with her now, though perhaps just a tad eccentric or crazy is more apt.  I did invite them all along to my Tropfest film festival that I am having mid June.  Monica and Jennifer will come down, but Widya, is too much of a stick in the mud to even attempt to bother to see any other part of the country.  There are some people I just don't understand and those are usually the ones that have no desire to travel.  Ohh well.  In case you hadn't heard I received the DVD of the 2004 Tropfest finalist, so seeing as I wasn't there this year I decided to host my own. I sent out a cool e-mail to all the local volunteers and ex-volunteers in Lae that I know, the response has been good so I should get about 20 people turn up.  I am going to borrow a multi-media projector and use a laptop and sheet to recreate the atmosphere of the Domain in February, or so I hope.  Something to keep a real tropo sane at least, nothing like a big bash to do that.  On the drive back from Goroka (4½ hours) on Saturday I made the mistake of stopping in at the frontier town of Kianantu (picture a one street town, add about 2000 people wandering aimlessly up and down, and you have it).  The reason was because there is a cool Cultural Centre (apparently) that I was told to visit by various people.  Well after trying a few combinations of my limited pidgin to describe to Sanga that I wanted to see the Cultural Centre (conversation goes something like this - "Mi likeim long lukim long Cultural Centre" somehow that phrase just kept getting misinterpreted - I think it was the words "Cultural Centre".  Perhaps I should have used this phrase "Mi likeim long lukim haus bilong olpela sompela" - I want to see the haus with old things), I eventually found a sign for the Kianantu Lodge that had I also heard about and headed towards that.  Something in my brain twigged that the cultural centre and lodge were connected.  Anyway I was wrong, so after drive up a hill on rough road and talking to the security guard, I discovered that the centre was back down on the main road.  Sanga at this time became animated as he now knew what the hell I now wanted, so he took the steps in directing me to the building that I was after.  Before I got there I dropped Sanga off (who is actually from Kianantu - hence my initial thought that he would know where the place was), as I thought he may want to meet up with his wantoks while I wandered around looking at pottery and rugs etc.  I do have a kind streak you know.  Well it then turned out that the centre was not open anyway (later I actually found out that the shop was open and where I had been directed to was the factory), as it is closed on the weekend (so much for tourism in this country), so I now had to find something to do for the next half and hour while I waited for Sanga to return.  One of the cardinal rules in this country is never expect a Melanesian to abide by time.  Most of them don't even have watches, those that do will still look at the sun first.  So half an hour turned into a 3/4 of an hour then an hour wait.  Have you ever had to wait in a nothing town with nothing to do for that long?  Well I can now tick that box.  Actually I ticked it a while ago waiting on the border between Russia and Mongolia (5 hours then) - but hey that is another story.  I used the time to collect some provisions consisting of a can of drink, some scones and chewing gum, and then walked up and down the busy street, whence upon I decided to wait for my colleague to return.  Eventually he did but not before telling my I have to drive down the a side street to the market where he then had to go and collect his "picinini bilong mi" (kid).  This involved him trotting off again past the market to some villages.  Before he left, I told him if he wasn't back in 10 minutes he could catch the bus back to Lae.  I think it was the first time I had seen a local run.  He was back in 5 minutes, kid in tow.  Well last night was a big night in the social lives of PNG'ers everywhere.  It was the annual clash between New  South Wales and Queensland in the Rugby League State of Origin.  It beats the hell out of me why a bunch of people living in another country would get so passionate about a particular team that they have no connection with what so ever.  But they do and they really do get passionate about it.  So far no stories have emerged, but I'm sure it will that a loser was pissed off with his wife/girl friend/mate who supported NSW (who deservedly won) and decided to beat her/him up.  Apparently it happens every year.  Last year some guy was killed in one of these fights.  As to myself I went into town with my boss to watch the game at a club.  It was good to give it to him afterwards as he supports those noneities from north of the border.  Well as you can see I have attached a pic from my trip back from Goroka.  I hope you enjoy.  It is from the spot at an altitude of around 1500m where you start to descend from the highlands down to the Ramu/ Markham valley, which Lae lies at one end of.  When I stopped I whipped out the camera and did some shots, and stitched it together into a panoramic.  From the point where I took this photo, it is about another 150km to Lae (way off to the righthand side of the pic), or if you head to Madang (off to the left) another 200km.  The valley itself is about 20km wide and 300km long and is pretty much dead flat the whole way.  The reason is because it sits astride the point where the Australiasia plate meets the Pacific plate (so does Lae incidently), and causes a type of rift valley.  Of course the camera can't quite convey the actual experience of standing there and looking down into the valley with the wind still nice and cool, watching the smoke swirl from the sugar cane burning in the Ramu Sugar fields, but at least you get an idea of what it's like. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have now completed a trip off to beautiful Madang.  It was a good experience, but I am not too sure if it is a road that I would really want to travel along everyday, as some of the bus drivers do.  The road is pretty good, apart from the odd pothole all the way until Usino (if you have a map it is where road changes direction from the north-west route to north-east) then it starts to climb over small mountains, and is mostly unsealed.  Lets just say that the 70km stretch was a good test of the driving skills, as it had been raining for five days straight.  On the bad sections it was a case of plough through and find the smoothest path, no time to take pictures.  The ute which is as good as they get in PNG, struggled up some of the 20° inclines with the load of computers I had on the back and the full cabin, mostly finding being happy in second gear.  Down the other side of the hills it was more of a case of hoping the brakes don't give out, as even in second I had to rely a lot on them.   Madang itself is a pretty town based around a peninsular.  It is very green and pretty clean.  But as I said there had been a fair amount of rain there over the last week, so a couple of trees had fallen over in the soft earth.  Apparently it had been raining since Sunday with no let up before finishing an hour before we arrive on Thursday.  Friday was perfect weather, if not too bloody humid with all the water about, and the fact the that room I was in setting up computers had no ventilation let alone fans or air conditioning which was a bit much.  The room is going to renovated into a proper computer lab after the start of next semester, once there is the money to do it.  At the moment the PC's are just going to be used for tutors only.  At some point they are going to fly me back up once they have things a bit better organised so that I can configure things.  This trip was mainly to deliver some of the second hand computers to them so that they are doing something, instead of occupying my second bedroom as a lot are doing at the moment.  I met up with some volunteers in Madang, quite a few are from VSO (the brit mob) so I was told by the local VSO people here to get in touch with them, which I did.  There is no one there at the moment from AVI, so I had to contend with poms.  It was all good but and it was good to meet some new people.  I have told them all that if they come to Lae to look me up.  The 5 hour trip back on Saturday was pretty similar to the one there, but with less equipment in the back.  It didn't stop us though from buying (not me) hoards of stuff along the way at the roadside markets.  Sago and big bags of coconuts seemed to be the popular choice.  We also had an esky full of fish that, Tony (husband of Admin lady in our department who came for the ride) had caught with his in-laws on Friday, they gave me a couple of them which I now have to cook soon. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I made a flying visit (literally) with my boss George to Aitape on Monday, staying 24 hours and then flying back.  Now if you don't know Aitape (pronounced i-tap-ae), it is on the north coast of the mainland between Wewak and Vanimo.  It has the infamous distinction of being the centre of a disaster not long ago, so like Newcastle after the earthquake in '89 it always gets referred to as being the town where the Tsunami hit in '98.  The flight up and back was as always in PNG a bit of an adventure with six take offs and six landing in two days.  There is no direct flight there, so we followed the coast flying in a 12 seater 2 prop Spanish built "Bandirante" to Madang.  That plane was supposed to take us all the way on to Aitape, but there was apparantly an "electrical fault" in the HF radio, which meant we waited at Madang for ages before they put some of us on a small 4 seater "BN3-Islander" to Wewak.  Flying from Madang to Wewak is supposed to take 50 minutes in a Bandirante, but in our little "flying shoebox" it ended up taking 80.  There was actually a volunteer from France on the flight, heading to Wewak for a holiday, he got the lucky distinction of sitting in the co-pilots seat.  If you could have had a conversation over the noise of the engines, I would have joked with him not to flip any switches.   I was directly behind the pilot who was a big guy, which caused his seat to almost bang into my knees.  Accompaning us on the flight were a bunch of newspapers and a pallet load of day-old chicks, cheeping the whole way.  The plane turned out to be good, because it afforded great views of the mighty Ramu (see attached photo of it variable path) and Sepik rivers, the latter has the same esteme in PNG as the Amazon does in Brazil.  The Wewak to Aitape flight was back on to a Bandriante, and amazingily we made it to our destination only an hour behind schedule.  The runway there is the same as the one built during the war in 3 days by the Americans, with the distinctive and amazingly versitile Marsden matting.  I think the strip would probably have to be the only original WWII strip still used in commerical operation in PNG or possibly the Pacific?  Considering this was now 60 years ago, it is some achievement.   As a side note, Marsden matting has done wonders for fences in PNG, they are used as posts, gates and panels.  Stock yards in particular have benefited.  Aitape could be best described as a 2 horse town, one street running through the centre, a post office, grocery store, a couple of houses and thats it.  Comparing Aitape to my home town of Paterson in the Hunter, the latter would come out looking like a metropolis, and that's saying something.  The reason I went was to look at a college which is being set up.  We are going to be using this school for our courses and programs, and the boss decided I could do with a trip up there to see how easily the place could utilise computers.  I got to meet back up with one of the volunteers that I came up here with, Gerry, who is the station manager for a 300ha property currently running about 150 brahman cross.  He is a bit of a character and could probably talk underwater.  I also got to meet a brand new young volunteer couple, Emmi and Gavin, from AVI who are going to be managing part of the local catholic diosese.  They have only been in the country for two weeks and already she has had Malaria.  We did our inspection and talked to the teachers at a local high school, who will be doing some volunteer tutoring.  We also talked to year 11 and 12 students who could possibly be potential clients next year about the courses that we are going to be offering, may as well drum up some business.  Flying back we managed to get the same plane the whole way.  The terminal at Aitape airport consisted of a red ute and some portable scales (see photo).  Len the director of the college we visited and Gerry dropped us off, you can see them in the other photo as I am about to board to the Bandirante for the flight back, Len is on the left, Gerry in the middle.  The flight back was not as interesting as the one up, as there were no electrical faults this time.  We also arrived back at Nadzab (Lae ariport) exactly on time.       
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      To keep yourself sane you have organise some sort of social activity, hence I had my Tropfest festival last night.  Read on to make sense of what I am talking about.  In February every year, Sydneysiders come together in the Domain for the worlds largest short film festival called  urlLink Tropfest .  Living as I did just around the corner from the Domain, where it is held, I used to go when in town.  This year I obviously couldn't go being 3000km away, so I decided to bring the festival to Lae.  My sister procured the DVD of the 16 finalists, exactly what was shown on the big screens in the park, and I sent out an  urlLink e-mail invite  to all the local volunteers and ex-volunteers, making it worded and looking like an official festival.   My department has a multimedia projector, Martin's dept has a screen, I borrowed some speakers from Mike and I managed to get a DVD playing laptop from Rachel who came and visited along with Monica and Jennifer from Goroka.  I hung the screen up against one of my living room walls and arranged the furniture, including Martins lounge chairs to face the screen.  At the back I put my dining chairs against the far wall.  So it was all set and ready for the show.  People arrived at around 7 and then at 8 we kicked off the short films to an audience of about 20.  After the first 8 we had intermission and then continued on with the rest.  At the end it was a case of try and pick the winner, and then we watched the awards ceremony to find out the real winner.  All up I am pretty sure it was a good night had by all, and it was certainly a different one than the usual, stand around chat and drink.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well another story is here.  No big long flowery (or thorny) one this time.  Will keep it nice and short.  The reason for this is that my attention span and energy at present has been greatly diminished - possibly due to those blasted mosquitoes and their off-loaded cargo of little wriggling parasites currently invading my body.  It was a good long weekend all up at my volunteer mates - Helen and Wendy - place at Salamaua, across the gulf by way of a "Speedie" or boat with outboard motor attached, that takes a cool 45 minutes, cruising up and down the swell.  Once there it turned out to be a another world (cliché alert) from Lae at least.  It could well be the typical pacific island brochure style of place - beach, plenty of palm trees, villages set back under the palms etc, but of course it is very basic, no running water and electricity from a generator for 4 hours a night.  They do have a flushing toilet though, but without the running water it requires a manual topup.  No problem.   The girls teach at the High School there, and they have been at it for a year and a half.  Both fresh faced and straight out of the good old British Universities.  Helen even went to Cambridge - a smart lass indeed.  I kept thinking to myself this place must have been a massive culture shock to the system when you first arrive.  If it was they have certainly adapted and become PNG meri's now.  Both carry their bilums on their head and go barefoot everywhere like the locals do.  I had only seen them in Lae, so seeing them in their own environment was very interesting.  On Friday night after I arrived I started to get quite painful headaches, not something that I normally get.  I was offered some Panadol, which was accepted, unusually - if you know me well you will know I never take headache pills, but this time my head felt it was warranted.  Saturday we were planning on doing a trip with some of the students to go gold panning, but in the morning it was bucketing down, so that plan did not happen, no point getting needlessly wet when you up to your waste in a creek panning for gold.  So instead when the rain stopped mid morning, we all went on a 1½ hour hike with a bunch of students out to a waterfall in the foothills behind Salamaua.  On the way back my energy was really drained, I started to see double vision, things blur and it felt like I was going to pass out, all new experiences.  I made it back to the house, but I knew there was something up and it was all starting to look like the big M.  At the house the headache returned, so the Panadol became used, and I had to lie down for quite a while.  The Panadol did some magic and before long I was eating dinner and we were playing board games - entertainment without TV, reminds you of black and white days, no?  I had brought along a bottle of Vodka, which was apparently the first time anybody had to their place, so we sat about and played Risk, with whoever winning having to down the inch left in the bottom (the rest was consumed during the game).  The winner happened to be me, and lo and behold Malaria was forgotten.  I remembered though later in the night as I was drenched in sweat, with a full body shake, that I was still sick.  In the morning I bit the bullet and started a 6 day treatment course that the girls gave me, as the diagnosis all round was Malaria.  Both of the girls have had it twice and highly recommended the treatment Artemether, and being the only thing available I was sold.  Still it did not stop me from seeing places.  On Sunday we went down to Salamaua itself, met some expats staying at there houses there for the long weekend, got offered and accepted a beer and homebrewed Whiskey (47% alc vol), then me and Wendy borrowed a dugout outrigger canoe from a local guy Wendy knew, paddled it with a few navigational difficulties to start with over to the headland, climbed the hill, saw the Japanese guns from WWII, paddled the canoe back and walked back to their house.  After all this I well and truly needed a rest.  In hindsight, I shouldn't have done any of these things with most of my red blood cells being popped open by growing parasites.  Monday was a public holiday, so I caught the boat back as it left from the high school at 7, and made it back to my house at 10.  The fatigue had entered a new stage and the first thing I did was sleep for 2 hours.  In the evening I was caught without any Panadol and suddenly I felt very sympathetic of Migraine sufferers.  My head started to explode like a suicide bombers.  Any slight movement, moving the eyes, opening my mouth, no movement at all, it was pain and bad pain.  All I could do was lie on my bed and wish it to go away.  So I have now had my memory refreshed that there is a good reason to live with someone, they can look after you.  Tuesday morning I was OK, after a sheet sweat-drenching night.  I rang up work gave them the news, then I went and visited the Uni Clinic, just to get a blood sample to confirm.  Talked to the doctor anyway and he said I had done the right thing by picking it up early, and starting treatment.  So since then the symptoms are becoming more mild and I am actually at work today.  I have had Malaria and am surviving, another tick on the PNG list box.  Ohh I now have got some Panadol in my cupboard as well, it is behind some glass with a little red hammer beside it.     
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well here's the report of my latest big trip all the way up the Highlands Highway to Mt. Hagen, defacto capital of the Highlands, and the one that I have had the most experiences on.  So I thought I would share those and a few observations as well.  The purpose of the trip was the same as the others, to deliver computers to our study centre in Hagen.  I was heading up there with the boss, George, this time, instead of like the previous trips where I went with one of the office workers.  There was a couple of reasons for this: it is a long trip so it is good to have a couple of people who can drive the vehicle, George is also a Hagen man with a house and family there, so he obviously knows the area extremely well, and as he hadn't been home for a while, he decided to give himself a free trip there, with the added bonus of getting a "living away from home allowance".   So we agreed to a plan to leave Lae at 8 on Saturday morning to get a good run and so we didn't arrive too late.  I got to the office a little before 8 so we could load the Ute with the PC's.  The boss wasn't there so I surfed the internet to check my e-mail, send e-mail, surf some more, make a call to see where he was - no answer - more surfing, pace up and down, and finally see him two hours late.  There should be a course or book you can do/read: "How to be diplomatic, when you have been put out by your superior".  Well the way I handled it was not to mention it.  It seemed to work and from a few drops bit of information he passed on, I gleaned that he had been at the Aviat club last night.  I had been out too - at the staff club, sinking beers - but it didn't stop me from getting there on time.  On the road things settled into the usual long driving trip.  We exhausted the solitary cassette that George had stashed in the glove compartment for such occasions, which contains such classics as Rod Stewarts - "Have I told you lately" song - twice.  The "He ain't heavy he's my brother" song and etc.  Luckily I brought along, as per the other trips, my saviour, the iPod with 8000 songs, with enough variety to please anyone.  It was not long before George was like a kid in a lolly shop going through the collection and finding artists like Creedance Clearwater Revival, The Eagles and ABBA.  Thankfully he could not find Kenny Rogers, which thankfully I don't have - you have to set some standards.  I also steered him into finding some Eric Clapton, Bob Dylan, Jimi Hendrix and Dire Straits.  So the trip became somewhat of a blast from the past, into the 70's and early 80's.  It was agreed that I would drive to Kianantu (the infamous nothing town from the last e-mail), and then George would take the reins, but when we got there we decided I would go all the way to Goroka.  After Kianantu, G started to tell me about how notorious the area was between there and Goroka for hold ups.  Masked men jump out in front of buses, waving guns and rob the passengers of their hard earned money made at markets.  The good old fashion style highwayman, but certainly no Robin Hood's - steal from the poor and keep.  G kept telling me that one of the worse areas was at a top of a hill that takes quite a while to climb up.  The raskols (pidgin for troublemaker/vandal/thief/anyone who's bad basically) see the vehicles on the roads below and get ready to hi-jack them.  As I approached the top of the hill I saw two Toyota hi-ace 15 seater buses pulled over on the other side of the road.  I also see some men milling about outside of them.  I see one at the back of them with a scarf wrapped around his face.  I recognise that he is pointing a gun at our car.  I hear George yell "Go, go, go, don't stop".  I duck down and plant my foot down on the accelerator wanting it to go faster after the climb up the hill, which with a load of computers it was not too happy about.  I need to change gears to gain that extra power, but ducking makes this tough to do.  I start to think whether my door would stop a bullet - probably not.  And I hear one of the bandits outside through my open window shouting something.  We make it over the hill and around a few corners untouched, gaining speed on the decline.   It all happened quickly.  The first thing George says is "You should have taken a photo of that".  He knows that I like photography, but "What The ...?".  Hang on I think.  Driving a car while ducking down.  Trying to change gears.  Worrying about getting shot.  Yeah I could of taken out my camera from my bag behind the seat, and shot the bandits through a lens instead.  No worries.  A safe distance away we pull over and flag down an on coming truck to warn them.  Then we proceeded and stop a Hi-ace and then after that, the real prize that the raskols would be after, two 25 seater Toyota Coaster buses, coming all the way from Mt. Hagen.   All the drivers (and passengers hanging out the windows too) were thankful for the tip off.  After all this drama, we kept on going to Goroka, and George then proceeded to tell me about other incidents that he had been involved in the past, with one time his car actually being shot at and smashing a window.  He also said that the raskol I could hear yelling was actually telling us to keep going, they weren't interested in our red Ute it seems anyway, though a gun being pointed your way makes you think otherwise in the heat of the moment.  At Goroka we changed seats after getting some food at a Super-Market and a couple of beers at the Bird of Paradise Hotel (aka the Bird - nice place if you ever go there).  From now on I would be heading into new territory.  It was also getting late.  We left Goroka at 2:30 and it was still a 4-hour drive to Hagen.  The rest of the trip was incident free, but I got some new perspectives on what the Highlands is really like.  From the top of the Daulo pass (2478m - higher than Mt Kosciuszko, highest mtn in Oz) you get a fantastic view back over the valley that Goroka lies in.  From then on you pass from the Eastern Highlands province into the Simbu province.  Once this happens the road get noticeably worse.  Obviously they don't spend the same sort of cash on maintenance as they do in EHP.  I also got to see that other danger that is driving in the highlands, something that I had not really encounted on my stay here so far.  Pigs.  Every little roadside village that you pass through seemed to have them wandering all over the road.  Now some people I talked to before leaving Australia already know this, but I will say it again, If you hit a pig and kill it with your car it is only a close second behind hitting and killing a person.  Therefore I was glad that George had taken over as I am sure that he could handle the situation better if we unlucky enough to enrage the locals by wrapping one of their prized swine around our wheel.  At this point I might as well mention what the roads are like in PNG, so some people don't get the wrong impression.  To start with the Highlands Highway, is more like a country road in Australia, two lanes, one going, one coming.  There are certainly no dual carriageway's joining the towns together.  Then because of the terrain, especially in the Highlands, the roads meander a lot and there are a lot of corners, making it a good challenge to drive.  If you are a motorcyclist you would probably love it.  Thirdly, people build their huts and villages right on the roadside, and if they are not doing anything, they will probably just hang around sitting on the side of the road and get up when a car approaches.  And finally villagers will use the road as a walking track, so you are constantly giving a toot of the horn in case they don't hear you approach.  We passed through Kunidawa and the road became even worse, and then eventually we passed into the Western Highlands province, and roads were not much better.  So by the time we got to Hagen it was 7:30, all up an 8½-hour trip, not including stops.  The proposed plan to stay at Georges village quickly went out the window as it was another 40 minutes past Hagen, so instead we stopped in at the motel I was checked into for the night after and checked in for this night instead.  Then we went around and I met all of George's family and Leo the principal of the secondary school where I would be setting up the computers.  The next day, Sunday, I collected George and we headed out to pay a visit to his dad, who lives about an hour away in a village off the road to the Southern Highlands.  When we got there the entire village came out to greet us.  I was immediately the subject of much curiosity, and this included the usual hand shaking of every one there.  All the pikinini's (kids) came up and were very interested in me, I was probably the first white person most of them had seen.  There is certainly no TV in these types of villages.  George's dad was a little fellow who came up chest high on me, but it didn't stop him from nearly pulling me over when he gave me a bear hug.  In the afternoon I had a new New Guinea experience to attend - a compensation ceremony.  Leo the principal I met the night before, had been doing some extra-marital affairs, which had come to attention of the wrong people.  Basically he had befriended a divorcee, but the family of the ex-husband claimed that he owed them, because the ex-wife was still their's.  In PNG women basically still get bought and sold by family's as wives.  In fact women are basically treated as second-class citizens, and certainly not commensurable to men.  The beef that Leo had had resulted in this compensation ceremony that I now had got to attend, which is unique to the Highlands.  Leo had basically admitted to being wrong and therefore the whole process would go quickly.  A spot was picked, the two families came together, plus all the other hanger on's - like me.  So there was in total over a hundred people.  Everyone sat in a circle, and then Leo's dad started the proceedings.  He talked in Melpin, their tok ples (local language), which sounded a lot like an Aboriginal language, and explained why they had all come together and why Leo has accepted to pay up.  Then they bought out the pigs, four of them and they were tied to stakes, and then Leo came forward and pulled wads of cash from his pockets, put it together, held it up and proclaimed this was 6000 Kina.  Even I realised that this was a lot of money for them.  The cash was handed over to the other family who accepted it.  Then the father of the ex-husband went on in a big speech for about 15 minutes, which sounded like he was talking about everything from the matter at hand to national politics.  Then someone else got up, had his view on the matter, then another person, then another, another and another.  Every bloke there seemed to have his own view.  Eventually the whole thing ground to a halt and everyone seemed happy, especially the other family who started to distribute money, to anyone they considered important enough to get a piece of the pie.  It seems I had got off lucky, and only had to witness a 1½-hour process, mainly because it had been all agreed beforehand.  George told me that when there is no agreement beforehand, the compensation can start at 10 in the morning and last until 5 in the afternoon.  On Monday I went and delivered the computers to the School (Leo was not there) but found out I could not set them up because the room was not ready.  So we just stacked them in a storage room and agreed that I would come back at some point, probably by air to set them up.  Beats me why these study centre coordinators tell us one thing and then when I get there find out another.  Both me and George were not particularly happy with this.  It was the same when I went to Madang.  Ohh well.  In the afternoon, George and me took a trip out to his village, so he could show me around.  He has a house there and it was quite a good little cabin.  Inside it was very commodious, furnished with soft lounges and chairs and even a fireplace included, something that can be needed in the highlands.  I was eying the place off as a potential retreat; unfortunately the place is too far away from Lae to be readily accessible.  Two creeks run past either side, burbling over rocks that can be heard from the house, which creates, not unlike rain on the iron roof, a very pleasant effect.  It was a pity that I didn't get to stay there on this trip as G had business to attend to in town this night.  So it was back off to the motel for me.  This time we left early on for the trip back, and this time I got to see what the landscape was like on the approach to Hagen, something that I missed out on the way due to it being dark.  There were coffee and tea plantations doting all over the countryside of the Waji valley and glimpses of the highest mountain in this part of the world, Mt Wilhelm (4509m - and one that I will be climbing at the end of the month).  I also figured out something that I had been wondering ever since I arrived here.  Why aren't there any road signs anywhere?  Then when I saw a village hut with a road sign above the door saying, "Hump", I figured it out.  Road signs make great house building material.  Plus I thought the sign was appropriate, what else is there to do in a village?  We made it all the way to Goroka and then stopped there for a while.  I got dropped off at our study centre to finish a couple of things that I needed to do from the week before, and then we went and had lunch at the Bird.  I offered to take over the driving, but George wanted to, as the hold-up mountain still needed to be crossed, and this time George wanted to do it.  On the way there, we came across a police truck carrying about a dozen heavily armed cops with M-16 machine guns and shotguns in the back, heading the same way as us.  We both thought it provident to stay behind these guys as they could certainly deal with anything on top of the mountain.  To keep behind them, as they were quite a bit slower, we did things like pull over for a pit-stop (a bloke thing, if you know what I mean), and buy some bananas from a road side stall (50 toea - 20 cents - for 10 bananas, can't beat that).  Eventually we made it to the bottom of the mountain, with the police truck slowly going up.  So we followed.  Then the truck stopped, they flagged us to stop, and seven cops jumped down from the tray, ran to us and took cover off our back and jumped in.  It seems we were going to provide cover and disguise if needed at the top.  It also seemed that the truck was deployed down the highway for the sole purpose of trying to get the raskols.  Our now pernicious red Ute slowly took off, overtaking the stationary police truck.  I did a rough count of the weaponry we had, 5 M-16's, 2 Shotguns and a pistol.  I got my camera out, this time I would be prepared.  I reclined my seat so that I was more hidden, but still could see.  I became nervous because I now knew how cops dealt with raskols especially ones that carry guns.  There is no "stop or I will shoot" in PNG.  If you have a gun and obviously have the intent to use it, police don't attempt to safely wound you in the arm or whatever.  You will get pumped full of lead, as simple as that.  George told me a tale how ten years ago in this very spot, there were similar hold-ups happening.  Armed police were deployed into buses that were becoming the victims.  A few times buses went safely through without incident, but one particular time 16 unlucky raskols decided to hold-up a bus carrying the cops.  Seven raskols were killed, four were wounded and the rest managed to get away.  That's why I was nervous, would I become a witness to a massacre, or worse would I be in the crossfire.  The upside of the events ten years before was that the raskols were shown a lesson and there were no incidents for about six years.  As we approached the top, we came across a number of vehicles parked on the side of the road - the same spot we flagged down the truck on the way to Hagen.  There were a couple of buses, it seems they had been informed of raskol activity that had been happening not so long ago.  Great I thought.  The stopped drivers saw the cops on the back of our Ute and changed their initial signal for us to stop to a wave us through.  Great again.  We timidly approached the top (well me at least), and saw there was no one about.  No held-up buses and no raskols.  Good.  The cops banged on the roof jumped off and ran around to see if they could spot anyone.  One of them sighted someone fleeing across another hill, and fired off a burst of his M-16.  If they weren't running they were now.  We said goodbye to the cops and continued, with me at least thankful there was no incident.  The only regret that I now have is that I did not get a photo of seven cops sitting in the back of our Ute, brandishing their arsenal.  At Kianantu I took over the driving, and we made it down to Lae 3-hours later, untouched.  After a total of 10 hours of travel, I walked back into my home.  It felt good to be home.  Looking back I can certainly say that it had been a trip that I will remember for a while.  Though I am now looking forward to the next one with all the vagaries that come in PNG. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I found this story on the web whilst searching for something and I thought I would include it on here as it is quite good.  It shows how a trip can (and probably will) go  buggerup  whilst in PNG.  The original location can be found at  urlLink http://www.csd.abdn.ac.uk/~ereiter/personal.html .    A Papua New Guinea Story  by Ehud Reiter  Part 1: On how I spent two days waiting for an airplane in a small "end of the road" town in PNG Part 2: On how I spent a week in the PNG "cities" of Mt Hagen and Wewak, trying to track down my lost companions Part 3: On the sad tale of a truly "buggeredup" trek through the PNG Highlands     A Papua New Guinea Story  Part 1 of 3: Waiting for the Plane to Yengis  On how I spent two days in a small "end of the road" town in PNG  Prelude:  I had signed up for an trekking tour in the Highlands of Papua New Guinea.  After only one day of trekking, however, we realized that due to overweight packs, it would be impossible for us to finish the trek on schedule, so we decided to send as much excess luggage as we could (including most of the food) back to our starting point, the town of Kompiam, where it could be flown to the mid-point of the trek, the airstrip at Yengis.  Thompson, the local guide we had hired, said he would take the luggage back and fly it out, and at the last minute I said I would go with him.  Wedn, afternoon: Myself, Thompson, two carriers, and about 80kg of excess luggage set off for Kompiam.  There was a lot of tribal fighting in the area, and we passed a burned-down primary school and many abandoned huts.  For the first part of the trip we were escorted by a group of impressive-looking local warriors (with feathers in their hair and "arse grass" on their behinds), who carried spears and bows & arrows to protect us in case we ran into an enemy tribe.  Unfortunately, though, these brave fellows decided to call it quits and go home as soon as we left "friendly" territory.  Fortunately, the enemy tribe did not make an appearance, and we arrived in Kompiam in one piece.  The local people think white men are wimps at walking, and I dare say they are right.  We covered in 5 hours the same distance that took the full trekking party 8 hrs to cover on the way out, and the only reason we didn't go even faster was my presence.  I have never felt so wiped out by a walk, and had to be helped over the last hill (45-degree slope, very muddy and slippery path) by our carriers, who were twice my age and were carrying packs which were 50% heavier than mine.  We finally arrived in Kompiam around 5:30PM.  Kompiam was a government town, which provided services (primary school, airstrip, small hospital, police station, etc) to the surrounding villages.  It was also, in the most literal sense, the end of the road.  The permanent population was only a few hundred, although there were always several hundred villagers from the surrounding area who were in town for one reason or another.  There were no tourist accomodation of any sort, so Samson, the local district manager, very kindly offered to put me up in his house. I spent quite a bit of time talking to Samson, and gathered that he came from a pretty successful family, and in fact one of his uncles had been ambassador to the US - until he killed someone in a drunk driving accident and was forced to return home!  It just goes to show you that diplomats literally do get away with murder ...  Samson was from a coastal tribe, and assured me many times that the coastal regions of PNG were much more "civilized" than the Highlands.  Thur, noon:  The plane to Yengis wasn't due until Friday, so I spent the day hanging around town.  Samson's brother and some of his friends showed me around, and took me down to the local river to take a bath. I wandered around the trade stores, talked to some school kids, and in general took it easy.  I was somewhat surprised when, in the middle of the afternoon, I came upon an argument between two men, one of whom accused the other of stealing $50 (a significant amount of money in PNG) from him.  The amazing thing was that the argument, which included some nasty threats about what would happen if the accused ever showed up anywhere near the home village of the accuser, took place while the two principles, together with myself and several other spectators, were all lying on the grass beneath the shade of a large tree.  No voices were raised, and no open signs of anger were shown.  An on-looker might have thought they were discussing the weather, not making accusations and threats against each other.  It made me wonder how peaceful other "tranquil looking" Third World towns and villages I have seen were.  Thur, afternoon:  Samson took me over to the local Baptist Mission, so that I could make reservations on the Friday MAF (Missionary Aviation Fellowship) plane to Yengis.  As Kompiam had no telephones, telexes, or whatever, the mission people told me they would have to make the reservation in the evening, by radio.  I was told to go to the airstrip on Friday morning, and just wait until either a plane showed up or until I recieved a message from the mission saying that they had failed to make a reservation for me.  The mission itself was a big surprise.  I had (somewhat romantically) imagined myself as the only white man within 100 kilometers (except for my trekking companions, of course), so it was a shock to appear at the mission and discover a community of 10-20 white Australians, living a European life style (electricity, running water, flush toilets, ...). The contrast between the way the missionaries and the townspeople lived was quite striking (and, of course, the contrast between the missionaries and the villagers was even more dramatic), and I couldn't help but wonder how much these missionaries really were "in touch" with the locals.  When we got back from the mission, I discovered that Thompson (the guide our group had hired to lead the trip) had left town and gone back home.  Apparently, he had decided that the 50% advance we had given him, together with the airfare money to fly to Yengis, was sufficient, and he saw no point in finishing the trip.  I later found out that Thompson had quite a bad reputation in general, and had been fired from a previous job because he had been caught stealing from the till.  When I eventually wrote a nasty letter to the company which "organized" this fiasco, their choice of Thompson as a guide was my biggest complaint.  Fri, 8AM:  Samson dropped me and the 60kg of excess luggage off at the airstrip (Thompson had thoughtfully taken about 20kg of gear, of which perhaps half actually belonged to him).  Kompiam airstrip consisted of a runway and a small corrugated iron shelter, where I was to spend the next several hours waiting.  A small Cessna appeared around 9:00, but it wasn't going to Yengis. The pilot told me, though, that a larger Twin Otter would come by later, and it might be heading that way.  About 10:00, a man from the mission (a local, not an Australian) showed up, told me everything was arranged, and proceeded to "check me in".  I have never before been "checked in" in a corrugated iron shelter, but the man did it all, including carefully weighing my luggage and charging me exactly 9 Kina ($11) for excess luggage!  It was actually quite fun waiting for the plane, because various townspeople dropped by to keep me company.  The most interesting was a guy who was running the local "vocational school".  The vocational school consisted of 2 thatched huts next to the airstrip, but apparently it was enough to make the "headmaster" a regular on the international development circuit.  He told me he was going to a conference in Okinawa in a week, had just come back from a workshop in Israel a few months ago, and had been in Canada a few months before then.  And here I thought I was a real traveller ...  But then, you always meet surprising people in Third World towns.  On my previous trip, to Ecuador and Peru, I had asked the owner of a $2/night hotel I was staying at (in a small village in the Ecuadorian Amazon) where her children lived, and she answered that while most of her children still lived in the same area, she did have one son who was going to Princeton ...  The Twin Otter finally showed up at 1:30.  Feeling quite relieved that the plane had actually appeared, I went over to talk to the pilot, only to discover that he wasn't going to Yengis, since he had already been there, and had no intention of going back!  5 minutes of pleading, of pointing out that my companions might be in serious trouble if they didn't get the food I was carrying, had no effect, as the pilot pointed out that he couldn't go back to Yengis even if he wanted to, because he didn't have the enough fuel.  So, there I was, sitting in the "end-of-the-road" town of Kompiam with 60kg of junk, including about 15kg of freeze-dried food, and separated from the trekking tour I had paid $$$ to join.  Meanwhile, my companions were out in the bush, with no food and no guide.  The situation did not look promising ...   	A Papua New Guinea Travelogue [continued]  	Part 2: Searching for my Companions  On how I spent a week in the PNG "cities" of Mt Hagen and Wewak, trying to track down my friends, with no luck until ...  Synopsis: I had signed up with an organized trek in the Highlands of Papua New Guinea, but had been separated from the group when our guide and I had gone to the town of Kompian to fly some excess luggage and most of the food to the trek's half-way point, the airstrip at the village of Yengis.  Abandoned by the guide, I waited two days for the plane, only to discover, when it arrived, that there had been a slight change of schedule ...  Fri, afternoon:  A bit stunned that the Twin Otter wasn't going to Yengis, I went back to the corrugated iron shelter and sat down, feeling pretty lousy.  Just at this moment, the Australian from the local mission who had supposedly "booked" me on the flight to Yengis roared up on a motorcycle, gave something to the Twin Otter's pilot, shouted a "Sorry, Mate" to me, and roared off.  I must admit this didn't make me feel much better.  Fortunately, Samson, the local district manager who had befriended me, also appeared on the scene at this point, and offered some more constructive advice.  Since the next flight out of Kompiam wasn't until Tuesday, Samson suggested that I had better get on the plane anyways, and reach some place with telephones, banks, and so forth.  We discussed the choices, and decided that Mt. Hagen, the plane's home base, was my best bet.  So, I got on the plane, with my 60kg of excess luggage and freeze-dried food, and waved good-bye to Samson and to the 200 or so villagers and townspeople who had come down to the airstrip to see what happened to me (and who formed a circle 10-deep around Samson and I as we discussed what I should do!).  The Twin Otter took off, and made various stops on its way back to Mt.  Hagen.  At one of the stops, we picked up another trekker, Monica.  Monica had actually come from Yengis, via some devious route, where she had been with an Australian army trekking group which had been supposed to meet up with my group.  Monica had flown out because of a knee injury, and she told me that as of Friday at noon, no one at Yengis had heard anything of my group, which meant that at best they would arrive at Yengis sometime on Saturday (a day behind schedule), and at worst they were badly lost.  Friday, night:  Monica and I arrived in Mt. Hagen, where one of the mission people kindly offered to drive us to the Baptist mission guest house, where we could spend the night.  The driver turned out to be an old resident of Kompiam who had gone to medical school in Australia, become a doctor, married an Australian woman, and returned to PNG, where he settled in Mt. Hagen. Local villager makes good, I guess.  He still had some ties with Kompiam, though, since it turned out that he owned most of Kompiam's trade stores!  The Baptist guest house turned out to be a very nice place, which was fortunate - I needed someplace quiet where I could just relax for a bit. Like most of the places I stayed in in PNG, it was in theory a hostel, where singles were supposed to share rooms with other singles, but in practice was empty enough so that I got a private room.  Saturday, noon:  I went wandering around Mt. Hagen, visiting the weekly market.  Mt Hagen has an evil reputation in PNG, as one of the towns where the "rascal" (crime) problem is the worst.  There were guards in all the stores, and several times people who I met on the street warned me that "bad men" were around, and that I should be careful.  Hagen is often described as being like the "Wild West", meaning that police presence is minimal, and the only thing that really stops criminals is the fear of vigilantes (killing "rascals" is a very popular pastime in PNG, since it's about the only time you can kill someone and not worry about legal or tribal reprisals ...).  Anyways, the market was colorful, and I managed to escape without being attacked.  Back at the hostel, I finally managed to reach the tour operator in Australia, and fill them in on what was happening. They said they would try get in touch with my trekking group [they failed], and suggested that I hang around Hagen until Tuesday, and then fly to the town of Wewak, which was the ending point of the trek.  They offered to pay the airfare from Hagan to Wewak, but nothing else, which annoyed me (since I had paid for an all-expenses tour, I thought I deserved to have my expenses paid in Hagen!).  Sunday and Monday:  I spent these two days at a country lodge near Mt. Hagen, generally just hanging around.  On Sunday, I went to mass at the local Catholic church, where I heard an Australian priest deliver a sermon in Pidgin English, which was full of references to "strongpela tok" (= "strong-fellow talk" - Pidgin is a lot of fun!).  I noticed that several of the local villagers who had told me they were going to church were nowhere to be seen - it turned out they had stopped somewhere for a quick game of "spears" (= darts), and were still playing, roaring drunk, 5 hours later.  Just like back home in the US! I happened to ask one villager who wasn't completely drunk what he thought of the coastal tribes (remembering that Samson, the Kompiam DM who was from the coast, had told me that the coastal tribes were much more civilized), and he replied that they were real pansies, since they used sorcery to fight their tribal wars, whereas real men (= Highlanders) fought wars the proper way, with spears, bows, and arrows.  Tuesday:  I arrived at Wewak from Mt Hagen (another Twin Otter) at noon. During the flight, I sat next to a fairly grubby looking national who told me he was a gold dealer with 2 kilos of gold hidden in his boots! There were several big gold rushes on in PNG (I had by this time met several stone-age looking natives who proudly showed me their penicillin jars half-full of gold, and heard plenty of stories about newly rich 10-year olds buying fancy sports cars, crashing them on their first drive, and then promptly buying another one ...) and he apparently had just spent three weeks buying gold at one of the gold fields.  The gold he bought for $10,000 at the fields could be sold for $30,000 back in the capital city of Port Moresby - provided that no one knifed him and stole the gold in the meantime!  Being a gold buyer was definitely a high-risk, high reward job.  Before I left Mt. Hagen, I went to the MAF (Missionary Aviation Fellowship) desk and asked if my companions were scheduled to fly out from Yengis on the twice-weekly flight to Mt. Hagen.  The woman very helpfully told me that she doubted it, seeing as the flight had been cancelled because the plane was "buggerup" ...  Wewak was a small town on the PNG coast, near the Indonesian border. It had a jungle climate - hot and steamy, but beautiful tropical beaches. Apparently, it was also the "in" place for travellers, as it was the only place in PNG outside of Port Moresby where I ran into other foreign tourists.  Around 6PM, Grant, the agent from the tour company who had done most of the "organizing" for my trip, showed up with another tour group.  I went over and started to tell him about the group's misadventure, only to find out that he had absolutely no interest in this.  He said he was on vacation now with his girlfriend, just another customer on a tour, and he was not going to do any worrying about my group.  Wednesday: I joined the other group on a trip to the village of Tambunum, where my group was supposed to be finishing up and the other group was supposed to start a canoe trip from.  It was quite a ride, in a Land Rover type vehicle over some of the worst tracks I've ever seen.  In fact, every half-hour or so I would reassure myself that the track couldn't possibly get worse - but it inevitably did.  There were several points when I thought we would have to turn back, but our driver (one of the best 4WD jockeys I've ever seen) somehow always got through.  Tambunum village was known as a "crafts factory".  It was the biggest craft-producing village in the biggest craft-producing area of PNG. The locals were even building a small lodge where they would put up tourists who wanted to buy crafts directly from the craftsmen.  The lodge wasn't ready, though, so we slept in a longhouse - a large open house which was on stilts.  The most interesting part of the longhouse was the open ground beneath it, where all the cooking was done, crafts were made and put on display, people hung around and socialized, etc. The longhouse interior, in contrast, was just a fairly boring sleeping area.      Arriving in Tambunum, I discovered that ... (drum roll) ... there was no sign of my group.  The Army trekking group had indeed arrived from Yengis, more or less on schedule, but neither they nor anyone else had heard or seen anything of my group.  At this point, Grant, the tour company agent, finally started taking an interest, and said he would ask people at the village to send a canoe up and look for my group [he did ask, but the village people "forgot" to do so].  Thursday, day:  Still no sign of my group.  The Army people and I piled into the Land-rover, accompanied by as many villagers who could fit in, and headed back to Wewak.  Aside from the overcrowding, the trip was much less exciting than the one coming up, because this time the driver managed to get proper directions, which no one had thought to give him before we left Wewak.  Back in Wewak, I met a Norwegian anthropologist, who was hanging around Wewak trying to get an MAF plane to take him to the village he was doing research in.  He had been waiting two weeks already, and probably would be waiting longer, as one foul-up or another kept him from taking one of the "regularly scheduled" MAF flights.  The two of us watched "The Mosquito Coast" on video, and had a good laugh when someone told Harrison Ford in a shocked voice "...but that country is still in the Stone Age" (imagine being in New York and watching a movie where someone arrives in Buffalo and says "Wow!  The big city"). The "jungle" scenes in the movie looked remarkably like what we could see out of our window ...  Thursday, night:  My last night in PNG.  I had finished making some final phone calls to the agency in Australia (no word of my companions), when I heard a knocking on the hostel door.  Wondering who it could be at 8PM at night, I opened the door to discover some incredibly dirty and haggard looking travellers.  I admit that I didn't even recognize them until one of them said "Ehud ..." - it was them!    	Papua New Guinea Travelogue [continued]  	Part 3 of 3: Stuart's Story  On the sad tale of a truly "buggeredup" trek through the PNG Highlands  Synopsis: I had signed up with an organized trek in the Highlands of Papua New Guinea, but had been separated from the group on the second day of the trip.  After being unable to make contact with them for an entire week, I had assumed they were lost and in serious trouble - until they turned up on at the doorstep of my hostel, haggard and dirty but at least in one piece.  After they ate, shaved, and showered, I sat down besides Stuart, an Australian schoolteacher who was in the group, and got him to tell me his story.  Somewhat cleaned up, it went as follows:  "As you know, we started out from Kompiam on Tuesday morning, with four tourists [me, Stuart, and a Canadian couple, Jim and Jean], the Australian leader [Ron], a local guide [Thompson], and one porter [Sam].  We made slow progress on the first day, mainly because our packs were too heavy, especially Jim's and Jean's.  Jean, who only weighed 50kg or so, had a 25kg pack, and Jim, who weighed 90-100kg, had a 40-50kg pack.  Most of the gear they were carrying wasn't needed for the trek, and should have been air-freighted to Wewak.  Ron, our leader, should have checked their packs before we left, but, unfortunately, he had not done so.  So, the first day we did not get anywhere near where our itinerary said we were supposed to be.  We set up camp in a cleared area where some huts had once stood (the huts had been destroyed in tribal fighting), and, after a bit of searching, found some water.  We heard all kinds of yelling at night, which we presumed came from tribal groups making night raids on each other and buring down yet more huts.  Ron assured us that tourists were never affected by tribal fighting, but I admit that I slept nervously.  The next day, Wednesday, we walked until lunchtime, where we ran into our first real village.  It was obvious that it would be very hard for us to finish the trek on schedule unless Jim and Jean lightened their packs, so we tried to hire porters.  Unfortunately, because of the tribal fighting, none of the villagers was willing to accompany us.  After some talking, however, Thompson, the guide, said the villagers were less afraid of walking back along the trail to Kompiam, and he could hire carriers for that route.  He volunteered to take some carriers, the excess luggage, and most of the food back to Kompiam, where it could be flown to Yengis on the Friday MAF flight.  Since there was less fighting at Yengis, it should be possible to hire carriers there for the remainder of the trip. We discussed this, decided that we could dispense with Thompson's to-date unimpressive abilities as a guide, and thus agreed, thinking that we could still use Sam, the porter, as an interpreter to talk to the locals and get directions.  At the last moment, of course, you [Ehud] said you would go back with Thompson to Kompiam."  [Later events made me wonder about Thompson claiming he couldn't hire carriers to go forward, but could hire carriers to go back.  I suspect he could indeed have hired carriers to go forward if he had wanted to, but was already looking for an opportunity to abandon us.  As mentioned in part I, when we got back to Kompiam, Thompson just went home, and made no attempt to fly to Yengis.  I also must admit that the main reason I volunteered to go back with Thompson was that I was already disgusted with the "organization" of this trip, and was hoping that by flying to Yengis, I could link up with another trekking party organized by the Australian army.  So, I, too, was planning to "bail out" of this trip!]   "After you and Thompson left, the rest of us put our packs back on and headed on down the trail.  We made good time at first, because of the lightened packs, but more things started going wrong.  We realized that the prepared "itinerary", which Thompson had made up, was a complete figment of his imagination, and bore no relation to reality.  We had some topographical maps, but they were based on 10-year old aerial surveys (some parts were completely blank and marked as "obscured by cloud cover"), and the "trails" and "villages" shown on the maps were completely mythical. Furthermore, we met very few locals (only one or two a day, until we got to Yengis), so we couldn't ask directions.  To top it off, water proved extremely hard to find, and one night we couldn't find any at all.  Since our food was all freeze-dried, this meant we went to bed hungry as well as thirsty.  Ron, our leader, was not much help.  He was a nice guy, but was unable to take charge and organize things when the trek started going badly. Jim, Jean, and I ended up looking after Ron more than he was looking after us.  Anyways, the "trail" we were following was always very bad (overgrown, narrow, steep, muddy, and slippery), and sometimes became almost impassable, when the mud was so thick that lifting our feet free of it to take a forward step took more effort than climbing a steep mountain trail back home. Finally, we reached Yengis on Saturday afternoon, a day and a half behind schedule.  We were pretty stunned to discover that you, Thompson, the excess luggage, and the food had not shown up in Yengis.  Things were looking pretty bleak when "Johnny Cash", who ran the local aid post and in general was the "big man" in Yengis, found us.  Johnny had heard about us from the Australian army group who had left Yengis Friday morning, and he told us that he had received the radio message you sent from Kompiam, saying that you [Ehud] had been unable to get to Yengis and would take the luggage to Wewak.  It was somewhat of a relief to discover that you were safe, and that the luggage had not vanished.  Johnny Cash was a life-saver.  He spent the whole afternoon telling us in detail exactly how to get from Yengis to the village of Eram, where we were supposed to be picked up by some canoes.  He also let us sleep in his house for the night, and rounded up some trade store owners who opened their stores so we could buy supplies to replace the food that you and Thompson had taken.  We said good-bye to Johnny and left Yengis on Sunday morning.  Our spirits were a bit improved, since we now had good directions, and since we were getting used to the trails.  On the other hand, though, we were a bit worried about missing the canoes.  They had been told we would show up on Tuesday morning and to wait for us if we were late, but we weren't sure how long they would wait.  We made very good time to Eram, arriving there only a few hours late, on Tuesday afternoon.  Unfortunately, the canoes were nowhere to be seen, and the local villagers told us that the canoes had in fact shown up on Monday (!), stayed just a few hours, and then gone back home.  Niugini Tours, the agency in Sydney which "organized" this mess, had struck again, this time by giving wrong or at least unclear instructions to the canoes, so that they showed up a day early and did not wait.  The situation looked pretty bad.  The distance from Eram to Wewak was far too great to even consider walking, and no airstrips were nearby, so we had to arrange some kind of river transport.  There were plenty of canoes available in Eram, but no gasoline for their engines.  Fortunately, the next day (Wednesday), some canoes showed up from down-river.  They weren't going back for a few days, but they agreed to sell us two liters of gasoline, which we hoped would be enough to get us to the next village.  We bought the gas and headed down-river in a rented canoe.  The gasoline in fact ran out before we reached the next village, but we were close enough so that we could paddle the rest of way in an hour. There wasn't much gas here, either, but we scrounged enough to get us to a bigger village down-river, where gas was indeed available.  We slept in this village on Wednesday night, knowing that we would be able to reach our pick-up point at Tambunum village only a half-day or so late.  We arrived in Tambunum around noon the next day.  There, though, we discovered that Grant, the Niugini Tours agent who was supposed to meet us, had not waited the half-day, but had left on a canoe trip of his own, up a different river.  Worse, the 4WD truck that had brought Grant up from Wewak and was supposed to take us back, had also not waited for us, but had headed back to Wewak early in the morning.  Once again, unclear instructions from Niugini Tours screwed us up royally.  It was impractical to take our canoe down-river and up the coast to Wewak, and there was no motor transport in Tambunum.  The villagers suggested that we cruse up and down the river and check the other villages to see if anyone had a truck we could rent.  Fortunately, this strategy worked, and we were able to hire (at an exorbinant rate) a truck in a nearby village to take us to Wewak, where you see us now!"   After finishing his story, Stuart went off to bed.  The "buggerups" were not quite over (the commercial flight which was supposed to take us back to Port Moresby and Australia on Friday was seriously delayed, because the Prime Minister of PNG had also decided to go somewhere that day, and when his plane had mechanical difficulties, he decided to "borrow" the plane we were supposed to be on), but at least we were all safely out of the bush.   So, what can I say about travelling and trekking in Papua New Guinea?  It's a fascinating place to visit.  I've never been as close to the Stone Age as I was in PNG, where most people still wear "arse-grass", and tribal fights with bows&arrows are everyday occurrences.  The most memorable part of my trip was not the "adventure" aspects I've highlighted here, but the many long conversations I had at night with various people (nationals, expats, anthropologists, Peace Corps volunteers, government officials, teachers, etc) about what life was like in a country just barely out of the stone age.  The local people (nationals) are usually very friendly and helpful. The friendliness and helpfullness of Samson, the district manager of Kompiam, and "Johnny Cash", the aid post worker in Yengis, saved the trip from being a total disaster.  Expect plenty of "buggerups", and give yourself lots of extra time to cover things going wrong.  Above all, AVOID Niugini Tours.  Would I go again?  Absolutely - but next time, I'll forget about taking a tour and go on my own.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      One of the things I love to do, is plan a holiday.  And up here in the Land of the Unexpected it becomes almost a big a challenge as going on the holiday.  My mother is coming to visit for less than 3 weeks in September and I am going to show her around some of this amazing country.  Luckily my mother is a cool sort of character, which makes it easy to take her places a lot of unadventurous people would bypass.   When thinking about the trip I wanted to make sure she gets a real feel for the type of place this is, in the short amount of time that she will be here.  A slight problem caused by my organisation AVI is that they have decided to have the in-country meeting for all the volunteers in the first week that she will be here.  They did time it correctly though to coincide with the Goroka show, which is one of the reason Mum booked her tickets for that time of year.  But it will still cut a bit of the time we have to do stuff together down.  Straight after the show I have booked us in to fly with MAF to the  urlLink Crator Mountain Wilderness Management Area , a place that I remembered Monica (Volunteer friend in Goroka) telling me about, as she went and visited there in February or March.  There are a number of villages that you can visit in the area, but because mum is keen on her hiking I chose Maimafu which is a great spot for hiking.  Coincidently I have just found out it has a fantastic runway landing strip that is one of the steepest in the country at 14°.  I was surfing yesterday and found a couple of pics ( urlLink approach pic  and  urlLink coming in to land ) of the runway to get me excited.  I sent these onto mum and the response I got was "exciiiiting yea" and "I am soooo looking forward to this", that's encouraging I thought.  After 5 days there at Maimafu, hiking, climbing Crater mtn and chilling with the locals, we are flying back to Goroka to catch a PMV down to Madang.  Madang we will probably visit a few local islands - I have some contacts that I can stay with while there - and go out to Kar Kar island, and perhaps even climb the volcano.   Once that has been done, we will fly back to Lae to save time and she can chill out at my place, and celebrate my birthday before she fly's back to Oz. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Friday afternoon ... and it was a deserved case of Thank God it's Friday! Our (in which I mean DODL's) registration for the second semester had been going on all week, which from my now two times that I have been associated with it, is a time to dread. Last week it was compounded by the fact that we were very understaffed. Colleagues going on "working" road trips to the highlands or going on leave to go to a crusade camp (a heavy Christian/born again/"Praise the lord!", thing they do all the time up here). So this meant for the week I got the enjoyable task of sitting outside and writing receipts to a constant stream of students who have just paid their course fees - good to know that my full range of skills are being utilised, not only do I get to use a keyboard but I can write as well.   So Friday was a particularly baaaaaad day - I will emphasize bad again. BAAAD! The students have had two weeks to register and they all decided to show up on the last day. The leave it to the last minute thing seems to be universal, though it does seem worse here, or perhaps that is because I have been on the receiving end. The line to my desk at one stage was about 150 students long, and this was at the point when the cramping up had started in the wrist, knuckles and anywhere else in the hand used to hold a pen. By the end of the day I was getting pretty moody, so I felt almost felt sorry for the poor students who turned up late expecting to register after I gave them a dressing down. But then I remembered that they have had two weeks to do it and still turn up late, so I just continue to give them an ear full.   When all the students were done and dusted and it was time to pack up and go home, there was an all round sense of relief from the team. We had registered around 1500 students - mostly ones doing the university bridging courses, but with a few doing our Diploma in Commerce.   I headed home, had a kip and then some kai kai (dinner) before I met up with David and Rob and headed into the Aviat for a few refreshing beverages. Paul from the office was there, so we had a bit of moan about our other colleagues who weren't there in the trenches with us for the two weeks. After enough of the amber fluid to forget the week David, Rob and me called it a night and headed back to the Uni.   Saturday night and for me that meant going into town to the Lae International to watch the Bledisloe cup. Well ... I wont say much about that, so moving on, I met up with David again along with Helen (Salamaua girl) and her mate Monica, from London out for the week (she is on a 3 week holiday with a week in PNG, one in Oz, etc), and headed off to the Aviat again, but this time it was to have a bit of a boogie, as they had a band on. The previous times I have been to these nights at the Aviat, they have been a bit of a disappointment, and invariably fights break out or whatever, but this time it was actually really good and I had a most enjoyable night.   My previously gangrenous thumb is slowly turning to better shade of green, with a little bit of help. Sunday saw me decide to do a bit of gardening out the back of my place. A dead spot exists that I was going to use to grow veggies, herbs or whatever, but I have now decided just to plant some nice plants - ferns, bush etc. So wielding my bush knife in true PNG machete style I found some plants that I liked around nearby and by one quick swipe got myself some cuttings. A bit of a dig in the ground, stick those limbs upright and hey presto you have gardening PNG style. I decided that I didn't like any of the other plants around so I left it until I had had a wander down to the academic area, and saw some nice plants there to nick.  I was also telling the local security guard for our street, about my landscaping tendencies in pidgin - conversation goes something like this:    " mi likem long plantim gutpela plant long baksait long haus bilong mi ." (I would like to plant some nice plants at the back of my house).  " mi save sompela nis plants, mi bai kisim tumorro ." (I know some really nice plants, I will bring tomorrow).  " tru! em gutpela, tenk yu tru " (really! that would be great, thank you very much that's very kind of you).  " em alrite, no worries " (that’s alright, not a problem old chap, anything for my brother from the south).   The translation may not be 100% exact but you get the idea. I do like writing in pidgin, it cracks me up.   Anyway moving on. Sunday night and I once again turned my house into a cinema for the screening of Big Fish - a DVD that my sister Sue purchased for me. I had again David, Helen and Monica around for the movie and I must say it was a really enjoyable film. I made popcorn and we had jelly babies and the seats were much better than your average multiplex. Who needs to be pissed off by having no cinema in town when you can project a movie onto a wall and get a picture a couple of metres big. Just need to get some better speakers that's all.   Yesterday I returned home from a much more maligned day at the office, in fact I hardly did anything and I walk out the back of my place to see a completely reshaped area. Not only had my friendly guard planted a few plants (about 20 by my count) but he had put in a border using stones and left a gap with a little bit of gravel to walk through. Unfortunately by the time I had got there he had left for the day so I have not had the chance to thank him. I will have to make a slight alteration though, and move the gap from being in the centre to directly in line with the backdoor. But apart from that, in a few months I should have a fully-fledged healthy garden. Actually this is more my kind of gardening, get a bored guard to do it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      OK, maybe it is because I have been here a while now, but there are a few things now that are starting to bug me.  So I thought I would have a bit of a whiny session and put all of these pet hates into a list of the top 5.  Let me add first though that these are bearable and it is just me having a whinge.  I will make up a list of the top 5 things that I love just to counter this one, and to let you know it is not all bad.  So anyway here they are counting backwards from 5 down to the real annoyer.   5. Loitering:  OK I might be a hit harsh, seeing as the unemployment level here is very high, but it gets on my nerves how people will just loiter around for a whole day waiting for something to happen.  You go  into town to the shops and you will have to walk past a dozen people just  sitting around chewing Buai, looking at you as if you are today's  entertainment.   If some sort of action happens, ranging from construction workers laying water piping, to a raskol being chased by a security guard and to a preacher spealing out his gospel it will always attract a massive crowd because people have nothing else to do.  Invariably though it is usually men in this category because due to the Melanesian culture the women will be out in their gardens, or down at the market selling there produce.   4. Blackouts:  Power problems are a really big issue here, it seems to be going off and on every other day, which makes it is a massive pain when you are typing away, and the power goes out, and the two hours of database changes you have just done are all gone.  Of course you learn how to deal with this and make sure saving is taken care of, or in my case make sure a UPS is purchased to give you the opportunity to save and shut down.  What is worse though is when you think you are doing the right thing, and save all your docs and files onto the University Staff server, which you were told was backed up, only to find out after the thing dies from the power going off and on that in fact it had not been backed up for 6 weeks, in which time you have created a complete database of computer assets - about 6 weeks worth of work.  Ahhh.  Lucky I am an easy going guy.  If only I could infiltrate the ITS dept and fix their systems up, and teach those no hopers a thing or two.   3. Personal  hygiene:  OK, again I might be being harsh here, as most people live in simple village huts on the edge of towns, but it still doesn't stop the fact that the smell in our department dramatically increases in the afternoon when we are open to all the student enquires.  It is a strong musty odour that permeates throughout the office, seeping into every corner.  I know this as I am about as far away from the front desk as you can get.  In the first weeks that I was working here it made me nauseous and even gave me headaches, such was the combined strength of the dozen or so sweaty students.  I think I have either now grown accustomed to it or perhaps it is the fact that I am now making sure that if it becomes too unbearable I open the louver windows in my little office, in the hope of extinguishing the smell.   2. Dogs:  I used to really like dogs.  Unfortunately the dog tolerance level has now been stretched.  On their own they are great.  But when you get the cocktail of there being masses of them, throwing in the fact they are treated like dirt, mix in copious amounts of doggie hormones running wild - looking for a bit of lovin' - and it's pretty bitter drink to swallow.  Fights break out all the time, anytime.   Howling is started by a single specimen and then the whole place erupts in a communal howl, not good at four in the morning.  Watch where you step or you might be spreading it around all over the sole of you shoe and footpath.   1. Spitting:  It is not hard to work out why this is a pet hate.  I was warned before I went to China, by people and books, that the spitting there was pretty bad.  It was not pleasant, but it was not that bad - though in the mornings the Chinese do get a good hack going trying to clear the sinuses - pleasant.  But now that I have been in PNG I can safely say it is on another level here, in type and quantity.  Here the problem is not only just people spitting on the ground, which happens all the time - can't they just swallow it  - but it is exasperated and made ten times worse by the added combination of Betel Nut (buai) chewing.  With the Betel nut, you get the unsightly look of a massive wad of red being deposited anywhere convenient.  You can tell when it is coming, the cheeks are bulging, and they are looking around for the nearest spot to let loose.  In the centre of towns this is usually in a communal rubbish heap turned unsightly bright red with gallons of spit, add the fly's that gather and this becomes quite unpleasant.  You have to be careful where you go, sit and who to talk to otherwise it could be unpleasant case of you wearing some red stuff.  Personally I have nearly been hit whilst departing from a PMV - always a particularly dangerous time, once those piles of junk are stopped people feel the need to lean out the windows - and have worn some by a drunk guy who wanted to have a conversation with me.  Flecks flew when he talked about what a great relationship PNG and Australia had or how the Maroons were going to win the State of Origin series or some other such  spakman   (pidgin for a drunk guy) talk.  I had to occasionally wipe the stuff from my face. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I felt my first real shake last night.  I was sitting at my new computer (more about that later) and suddenly the house started to tremor.  Patches (who I am looking after at the moment) got up and barked and then it was over.  It only lasted about 5 seconds, but it was the first time that I have actually acknowledged that that was an earth tremor.  Previously I had felt small shakes but they had not been that significant to even worry about.  I am surprised that I have not felt anymore significant ones as I am right on top of a fault here.  Bruce, who is a cousin of Dad's through marriage, and are currently in the country - a nostalgic return as they lived here in Lae in the early '80s - said that once when they had a quake, he looked outside and saw a wave go across the lawn.  Haven't seen that yet, but I sure it would be a cool sight, as long as the building you are in doesn't collapse.   A bit of my time now has been spent setting up my new iBook.  I bought it on the Apple website and got it delivered to the oldies.  Bruce and his wife Cheryl kindly brought it up here when they arrived last week.  They stayed at Martins next door, and looked after his place while he was away with his wife in Madang.  It is mid year break at the moment here at Uni so everyone is taking holidays, getting visitors and going places.  I wont be doing the holiday thing though, not until September at least when Mum comes and visits me.  Will be off for 3 weeks then, and guess I will take her on a bit of a trip around the country.  Seeing as Martin has been away I have had to look after his dog, Patches.  This has not been particularly hard, but it is a bit painful as she is like a shadow, and wont let me out of her sight.  To stop her coming down to the office in the morning, I have to pretend to head out the backdoor, wait till she is outside, close it on her and then head out the front door.  Today I took pity on her and brought her along, so she is currently waiting for me outside the office door.  Not sure how is she going to react when Martin comes back, hopefully she will completely forget me and go back to following him like a shadow.  Not that I don't like her, but it is a bit much at times.  Bruce and Cheryl, have not been your average tourists, in fact they are doing things that I have not had the nerve to do yet.  They arrived last Wednesday and came straight to my place.  Then on Thursday, they took off and like a duck to water, jumping on the PMV's, touring the town, walking through the main Market taking photos, getting told by everyone left, right and centre that this is not safe to do, being followed by security guards in case they become a target, being looked after by some random punter at a PMV stop, taking them to where they want to go and making sure they arrive safely (in fact this has happened to me quite a bit as well).  It is surprising how many times people will go out of their way to help you.  I think they think just because you are white, you have no idea how things work.  Perhaps we don't, but you can usually get by with your instinct - though sometimes our instincts need to be honed especially if yo have never been to a third world country before.  Crime usually makes all the headlines, but 99% of the people will do as the above and go out of their way to help.  I got stuck in town once, trying to catch a PMV back, a guy pulled up and asked where I was going, I said to Unitech and he took me out and dropped me off.  Did not know the man from a bar of soap.  This would not happen in Australia or any other western country, as there is fear on both sides.  Fear that the guy in the ute could be an Ivan Milat, and fear that the person needing the lift is just as bad.  Here there is still suspicion, but because of the colour of my skin, I am not touted with that.  Someone who stops and offers me a lift, I know that they are pretty genuine.  The suspicion here though between the locals is pretty bad.  Due to all the raskol activity, everyone thinks everyone else is a pickpocketer at the Market or PMV stop, or someone who is going to cut the fence to Unitech and rob a house (actually this happened last week in my street - no houses were robbed though).  Anyway B & C have been having a good time.  They headed off to Madang on Saturday morning, not having a place to stay before they went.  Hopefully they found somewhere, in fact I am sure they did as I have not hear from them.  I gave them a few contacts in case they got stuck and the address and number of a nice little resort that is up the coast a bit.  They will be back here in the next couple of days though. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Since going up to the top of Mount Wilhelm, the idea of bagging more of Papua New Guinea's peaks has suddenly become an attractive prospect.  With the aid of the  urlLink Wantoks Communication site  and the  urlLink Peak Bagger site  I have made a list of the peaks in PNG over 4000m.  I also tried to use Lonely Planet's "Bushwalking in Papua New Guinea" but found that the list it had at the begining was just too unrealiable (well it was written in 1983).  To my surprise there is more mountains above 4000m than I thought.  The list below is what I have come up with:  1 - Mount Wilhelm - 4509m - Bizmarck Range 2 - Mount Giluwe - 4368m - New Guinea Central Highlands 3 - Unnamed peak - 4254m - New Guinea Central Highlands 4 - Unnamed peak - 4175m - Finisterre Range 5 - Mount Ignutam - 4146m - Bizmarck Range 6 - Mount Sarawaket - 4121m - Sarawaket Range 7 - Mount Kabangama - 4104m - New Guinea Central Highlands 8 - Mount Victoria - 4036m - Owen Stanleys Range 9 - Mount Capella - 4015m - Star Mountains 10 - Mount Bangeta - 4005m - Sarawaket Range   You will note that a couple of them are not named which seems very odd considering they are 3rd and 4th on the list.  The 4th highest for me seems the easiest to do next.  It is located close to the Finisterre village of Teptep which has scheduled flights with MAF from Nadzab every Wednesday.  There is a guest house there and by my accounts on the topographical map of the area it is only 20km to the peak.  You could pack a tent, a sleeping bag and thermarest and probably do it over a couple of days.  I have already suggested it to George and I will just have to see if anyone else is interested.  Who knows we might be the first people to ever scale it.  Perhaps they will then let us name it? 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As I have said before "You have to keep yourself entertained in PNG". When I wrote it I am sure that I wasn't thinking this would extend to swallowing up an entire weekend with walking for over 15 hours, sitting in a car the same amount, getting 30 minutes of sleep on Saturday night, experiencing freezing cold weather, serious exhaustion and the aches and pains of all that walking. But this is exactly what kept me "entertained" on the weekend past and I can say that it was all worth it.  Ever since I decided to come to PNG, one of the things on my list of must-do's while I am here is to climb Mt Wilhelm. At 4509m it is the highest mountain not only in PNG but Australiasia. Easily beating by double Australia's highest, the bump that is Mt Kosciusko (2228m), and the visually impressive but not quite there Mt Cook (3754m), NZ's biggest.   The attraction was the height of the thing. Since being impressed by going up to the top of Klein Matterhorn in Switzerland (by cable-car, mind you) and seeing the sign proclaiming 3883m, I have taken note of the highest place in altitude that I have been in the world. With a place close to hand here that is higher, it did not take me any convincing to try and better my previous best.  Of course the other attraction is the challenge at climbing and reaching the top, the thrill of making it. Cable-car's don't exist here. I have talked to most of the volunteers I have met here about climbing it and it seems that most of them had attempted it, but all but a couple had failed. The failures had come up with various reasons for not making it to the top, altitude sickness from the fast ascent, too much partying beforehand and not wearing shoes (Helen and Wendy, I now think you are completely long long). So I thought why don't I try it and see if I can do it. Bragging rights and all that.  The only thing I needed was a willing accomplice and here it seems I had it made with George, my boss, being a keen hiker/mountain climber. He had already climbed the thing quite a few times - 16 by his count - but wanted to do it again as the last time he had done it was 1998. Since I first met him face-to-face at Nadzab airport, we have talked about climbing Mt Wilhelm. He told me back then that we would do it at Easter. Easter came but due to landslips caused by the highlands rainy season the trip was postponed until the Queens Birthday long weekend in June. This came, but coincided with bridge upgrade work on the highway, which meant they were closing the road for the entire weekend. So then we decided we would just do it in a normal weekend, and not worry about using a long weekend. The next free one for both of us was the one just past.  So the amended trip was planned and because of the less time we were going to execute it in blitzkrieg fashion. We would leave Lae straight after work on Friday, staying the night in Goroka after the 3½ hour drive. Drive up to Kunidawa and then turning off the Highlands Highway and go to Gembogl (the closest village to the mountain) at end of the road. Leave the car there, walk for 4 hours on Saturday afternoon to the established base camp huts at the two lakes, Piunde and Anude (mother and daughter). Have dinner and sleep there. Leave at 1am, Sunday morning, and climb to the top of the mountain, arriving at dawn (I'll explain why later). Come back down, in the morning light all the way back to Gembogl, arriving at lunch. Jump in the car and head all the way back to Lae. Well it sounded reasonable at the time.  Friday came and I had got myself prepared. I was using just a day-pack for the entire weekend, which was half filled with my camera and the rest of the space clothes and important bits like my maglite torch with spare batteries. Strapped on the outside was my rainjacket shell and water bottle.  At 3pm the team that wanted to go, converged at Georges place. The call for interested parties had gone out and it turned out that it would be just four of us heading up from Lae - George, Knox (our storeman at DODL), Norman (from UDC - the University consultancy arm) and me.  The trip up was uneventful and we got to Goroka, and dropped our kit off at the cheap accommodation we had arranged. Then we hit the Bird of Paradise hotel to get dinner and a few drinks. I met up with Monica and Jennifer here (AVI guys in Goroka) and had a chat.  The next morning we headed off and drove to Kundiawa as planned and then drove up the rough road to Gembogl at the of the valley. The valley was impressive in itself, with extremely steep sides and gardens built into those slopes. The trip took 2 and half hours, so by the time we arrived we running behind schedule.  At Gembogl, which is practically the end of the road, we left the car at the high school with the headmaster, who happens to be - like most people in the highlands - someone that George used to work with.  We also met up with Ben who works with Norman at UDC.  He is a local from the area and arrived earlier to arrange a few things for us. One of these was Steven who would be a guide for the trip.  We didn't really need him, but he turned out to be helpful and good fun.  The first part of the trip was to head to the lakes.  So at 1pm we headed off up the road, which then turned into a track.  It was perfect walking weather, cool and overcast, but it still meant that I had a real sweat happening after not long. By the second stop after two hours of walking, I was absolutely stuffed.  I realised that my fitness level was pretty inadequate, and I started to wonder how I would cope for the rest of the hike. I took it easier and kept pushed myself to keep going, it was just the first of many walls that I would have to walk through I told myself (correctly proven it turned out to be too).  We made it to the lakes at 5, walking past waterfalls and up grassland areas. The trees which had started down below as part of established forests, were by the time we reached the lakes, small and stumpy.  I asked Ben how high the altitude was and he said it was around 4000m.  At over 3500m there is the chance of getting altitude sickness, and the higher you go the more likelihood of it happening.  I was feeling light headed, by convinced myself this was just from the physical exertion of coming this far.  The weather was cold but not freezing, and it certainly was not cold enough to stop George from getting his kit off and plunging in to the lake.  After a toe dip from me into the icy water I told him he could do it all by himself.  Instead I stayed in the house cook near the our arranged mountain hut and warmed myself up by the fire.  Dinner was two-minute noodles and baked beans, followed by fruit cake for desert, all washed down by cups of Milo.  At around 8 it was bed time.  So George, Norman, Ben and me crashed in one room and used the hut supplied bedding, while Knox slept in the house cook.  I was tired enough to really want to go to sleep and I knew I had to sleep, but I did not factor in the fact that Norman sounded like a truck going down a steep hill with it's air brakes in full song.  It took me over two hours to get to sleep, and when I finally did it seemed that it was time wake up.  That time was midnight and I roused myself out of bed and got ready. This meant that we left behind anything of non essential items, and just carried what we needed to trudge up the supposed 4 hours to the top.  The night air was, considering where we were, quite pleasant when we headed out.  We circled around the bottom lake first and then we started the what turned out to be almost continuous climb for the next 4 hours. My Maglite provided the source for me to see the way, and coupled with the half moon, we were able to progress at a reasonable pace.  While walking it seemed that I was having to take double the amount of breaths that I would normally take to get the same amount of Oxygen out of the thin air.  My pulse raced from the effort.  We took frequent short stops because of this and this enabled me to keep going.  After about an hour a wall was hit and the question of why bother reared it's head.  This was pushed aside and I kept going.  The group seemed by this stage to spilt into two.  Norman was not coping at all and started to slow down the whole group, so the group started to spilt into two with me, Knox and Steve in the front and the others coming behind.  George and Ben were mainly doing this to coax Norman along.  After two hours we started to see some lights from Ramu sugar factory down in the Markham/Ramu valley, which was easily a couple of hundred kilometres away. Then the views became obscured as unwanted mist rolled in around the top of the mountain.  This made it extremely cold as the wind also became whipped up.  My hands felt it, as I didn't bring gloves along, even though I did try and get some in Lae, but funnily enough there is not a big demand for them there.  I had to alternate between holding the torch in my left and right hands and eventually sticking it in my mouth, while my hands recuperated in my pockets.  After 4 hours of walking I was starting to wonder if the bloody thing would ever end.  We made it to "Wilhelm's rest" and we were informed that it was only another 30 minutes away to the top.  This would enable us to get up there before the dawn and see the sun come up and watch the clouds roll in.  The reason you see for going through all this effort of walking in the dark, freezing cold etc, was because in the tropics, the best time to be on top of a mountain is at dawn.  Once the sun comes up the clouds will build and obscure it all for you.  Unfortunately though, we were already in this situation.  I guess it can't be right 100% of the time.  The final 30 minutes dragged on to 45 and then onto an hour.  We had slogged for 5 hours and still not reached the top.  It was 6am and the sky to the east was becoming lighter.  We really needed to get up there to see anything if at all.  Me and Knox with Steve leading had left the others behind at Wilhelm's Rest. I kept asking Steve where the peak was because we were now surrounded by multiples of them and they all looked to be the one.  After going past 3 of these faux peaks Steve told us that this one was it.  Both me and Knox let out a "woohoo" of joy as we were standing directly beneath it and it would only require another 5 minutes of scaling up the rocky face.  I was completely and utterly exhausted at this point and just wanted it to be over - to be able to stand on top and know that I have completed it.  What Steve was pointing to though was not the peak we were below but a vague shadow that we could just see through the mist.  I didn't even believe that it was a mountain at first and thought it was a trick of the light at this time of the day.  A shadow cast by another peak.  But it was the real one and it meant we had another 15 minutes to go.  I groaned inwardly, but again kicked myself on.   The final ascent involved almost rock climbing like skills, finding handholds and the like to get up.  Steve helped me and Knox over some of these and this meant that I was the first to get to the peak.  As I stumbled over to the sign sticking up and saw the words written Mt Wilhelm - 4509m.  I didn't know weather to laugh or cry, so I did both at the same time.  To make it up there was the happiest moment of my life (of the ones that I could remember at that exhaustion hazed moment).  Knox came up behind and we shook hands and hugged.  Then we both sat down out of the wind and rested while waiting for the others.  I closed my eyes and must have slept, because the next thing I knew was Steve coming up with the others and shouting to me to take photos of the sun coming up.  I did and then we took the obligatory pics of standing at the summit.  In the wind it was extremely cold with it sleeting. Climbing up the mountain you don't notice it as much but once you stop it is felt.  Unfortunately the view which I had been told so much about - being able to see Madang and the north coast, seeing the south coast etc - was not there because of the mist that had come up.  It did though afford us glimpse's of the east coast and the Finnisterre mountain range as it swirled around.  George and me stood up on top and got our photo taken.  I looked at him and thought, then told him that he must be completely crazy.  He had not worn a hat or trousers the whole way.  On the back of his head after the picture was taken I could see a frosting of ice.  We didn't stay at the summit for long, perhaps 30 minutes all up, before we headed down.  It was good for the sun to be up so we could see the way but it also meant we had four hours of walking ahead of us.  At the end of this my legs were like jelly trying to step down all the rocky steps.  Going up is certainly easier on your legs than coming down.  Back at the hut at 11 we had a nap for 30 minutes, before having some lunch consisting of more two minute noodles.  Then there was another 2 hour walk back to the high school, which was one of the longest two hours I can ever remember, it seemed like it would never stop.  My right knee was also very painful making it hard to walk, I must have overstretched it at some point coming down.  Finally we hit the road after some more food and drove all the way back to Lae.  I took over the driving at the bottom of the Kassam pass and drove down the Markham valley, getting home at 11:30pm.  My exhaustion was absolute and as soon as my head hit the pillow I was out.  I woke up 7 hours later in the same position.  It was a brilliant experience and something I will do again one day - but not for a while.  I will also have to find another mountain higher as well, to better my PB.  There is one in West Papua (Irian Jaya, Indonesia) at 5025m ... hmm.    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Another trip to the Western Highlands and in particular it's capital Mt Hagen has been completed.  After driving up incident free on Friday, working Saturday at the school setting up computers and then having a lazy Sunday at the Hotel I actually thought this trip would pass by without any eventualities happening - comparing it that is to my last trip anyway (see  urlLink Highlands Hwy Survivor ).  Then Monday morning when it was time to turn tail and head for home, George (my boss and travel partner) told me first we had to go and pay our respects at the funeral of one of our work colleague's brother who had died.   Paul's brother had passed away in Moresby on Friday, from Asthma complications or bronchitis or something like that.  Paul and his brother are from Mt Hagen, so Paul went down to Moresby from Lae and retrieved the body and returned to Hagen with it on Sunday.  Monday was set as the first day of the funeral, which would last three days until the body would be interned on Wednesday.    Once George had told me that we were going to a funeral, I changed into some semi-decent clothes that I brought along for the trip and George picked me up.  We arrived at the bottom of the driveway up to Paul's clan's area with a group of about 20 other people.  Most of these were people George knew and there was the obligatory handshaking of everyone by me as I was introduced.   At this stage I realised that wearing a shirt, a pair of trousers and my doc martins -  my usual work attire - was considerably overdressing for the occasion.  Funeral's it seems in PNG - or at least the western highlands - don't have the same sort of unwritten dress code that exists in Australia and I imagine all the other western countries.  I was standing with a group of mourners dressed in the usual PNG highlands attire, which basically consists of the pickings from second-hand clothes stores (the next time you throw that heap of clothes into the St. Vincent's de Paul clothes bin outside the local church, bear in mind that it will end up being worn for another good couple of years all over PNG, until it finally falls apart), mixed and matched in all sort of unusual combinations.  There was even one elderly bloke, who was wearing a nice tweed jacket, elbow patches and all, combined with  as gras  (arse grass - a bunch of leaves covering your arse, it is traditional highlands dress) hanging from underneath the back of the jacket, dangling above his bare legs.   After all the handshaking was completed the group proceeded to slowly walk up the drive.  As we got closer I could hear what I would describe as rhythmic wailing coming faintly from the direction of the ceremony.  We stopped as the wailing was getting louder, a respectable distance from the proceedings and one of our members took up a song.  After a time others joined, then everyone was singing in the local language.  To best describe what the singing sounded like, think of a Aboriginal song in chorus. I am not sure of the details of the song, but no doubt it was to do with sorrow.  The group moved on.  My doc martins by this stage were slipping through mud, caused it seems by the combined effects of heavy rain the night before and hundreds of people trampling over the same spot.  The ceremony area was obscured by village buildings along the whole of the path to it. I may have not been able to see proceedings but I could certainly hear it.  Similar songs were being sung as the one our group was singing which in turn was mixed with wailings and stomping of feet.  We entered the clearing and I finally got to see what was happening. The area was about the size of an Olympic swimming pool with the edge lined with onlookers who I assumed to be members of the clan. At one end of the clearing a group of people were standing around a effigy of the body. This was the family group and ones causing most of the wailing. To the side of the mourners, were the warriors. About a hundred strong lined up into ranks. They had painted their bodies with mud and brought along their weaponry, including spears, bows & arrows and axes. Most of them were wearing traditional dress of as gras and the like, but some just wore their St Vinnies best.  They were marching around the area, chanting and singing their warrior songs to make sure that the other side knew that they had to accept the spirit of the deceased or they would come in and force them to accept it.  Our group came into the area and solemnly walked around the same circuit as the warriors, all the while still singing the same song.  We encircled the mourners, coming face to face to them and their grief.  This ceremony also goes by the name of  bikpela kry  (big cry), and now I understood.  It was expected for you to show huge emotion. This meant that everyone there was wailing, crying, blabbing and basically overcome with grief.  It was a shock to see Paul who I always thought of a tough guy, letting go, with tears streaking his cheeks.  He saw me and beckoned me over, so that he could hug me and I could offer my sympathy.   Despite everyone else breaking down, there was no way that I could turn on the waterworks for someone I didn't even know.  I looked around to see if I was the only person who was like this and I saw George standing there looking like me, as if he was a bystander at a car accident - intrigued at the sight, but not emotional.  Later he told me that he has a real problem crying in public, understandable I said, most guys in the western world are exactly the same.   Up close, the effigy of Pauls brother, which should have apparently been the actual coffin, looked more like a coat rack than a person.  It consisted of a branch cut from a tree jammed in the ground with a hat sitting on top and a Hawaiian shirt on a coat hanger, both items which belonged to Paul's brother.  Where the face should have been was a photograph of him.  This was the centre for the grief and anyone new who arrived made there way to this, to touch it and weep.  It was unfortunate that the actual coffin could not be there, instead we got what looked like an unstuffed scarecrow.  The reason apparently that the coffin could not be there was because being hot weather, they wanted to keep it at the Mt Hagen morgue until time of burial.  I am not sure if this is correct or not, but it was the explanation I got.   While in the inner circle of grievers, the warriors still marched around the outside.  After a while they changed from marching in ranks to an attack mode. Racing around in a hunched stance, spears raised, arrows pulled tight on their bows and axes ready.  A couple of complete circuits were completed while in this mode, before the inner group that I was in, parted back from the coat rack.  The warriors now, with their lungs pumping out a war cry, came around behind and through the group to gather up the effigy.  They carried this aloft and down into a hut at the end of the grounds.  This signalled that the first part of the funeral was over.   Everyone now relocated to another part of the clearing and formed a circle.  The important people sat on seats but most people including me either sat on the grass or stood.  Firstly the formalities were done, which meant that someone explained how the guy died, when, where etc.  Then others got up and expressed their condolences.  Then finally as in the other time I have witnessed one of these events at the compensation ceremony of my last trip here, the talkfest started and every topic people wanted to air was raised.  There is one thing to be said about highlanders, they love to talk.  These talkfest's are very orderly, no one interrupts anyone, everyone can get there turn at the topic they want to discuss, or to readdress and put there spin on a topic already raised.  There was only problem for me, I had no idea about what they were saying, only picking up the general English word every once in a while, and I was sitting directly in the hot noon sun, which I later found turned me a bit pink.   George and Me took our leave at an appropriate time and headed back on the long trip down the Highland's highway to Lae.  It was a late leaving, which made the time we got back about 9.30.  The trip after dark turned into a bit of a nightmare for me.  I was given the reins after Kainantu, and got the pleasure of driving through the dark.  Fun fun fun.  One of our headlights was not working and road is a shocker even if you drive during the day with potholes appearing as numerous as holes in Swiss cheese. Also the numerous trucks heading up to the highlands don't bother turning off their hi-beam, making it virtually impossible to see anything as they pass.  Anyway we made it back safely, though in hindsight next time I will insist on staying the night in Goroka. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I had heard that Lonley Planet was updating the current guidebook to PNG (which dates back to 1998), and now I know for sure.  I just stumbled across the trip journal for one of the authors on the front page of the LP website.  Check it out at this location  urlLink http://lonelyplanet.mytripjournal.com/rowans-PNG-authoring-trip-2004 .
     
    
</post>


</Blog>