<Blog>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. Are you single or not? single :) 2. Do you currently have a crush on someone? no 3. Does your crush know? um... 4. Nicknames: Manda, Mandy, Dander, A-man-duh!, Squishy, Celineiac, no name, that girl obsessed with Celine Dion 5. Eyes: Blue 6. Height: 5'7ish 7. Siblings: none 8. What are you wearing right now? mahogany tank top, jean capris, my Celine necklace and big hoops 9. Do you have your a/c on? I think so 10. Birthday: sept. 6 1989 11. Where do you live: in a house 12. Sex: female 13. Righty or Lefty: Righty  ON GUYS FOR GIRLS TO FILL OUT (for girls only)  14. Boxers or briefs: boxers 15. Tall or Short: Tall 16. Western, Preppy, or All-American: umm...idk 17. Good or Bad guy: good i guess, but not goody goody 2-shoes 18. Hat or no hat: dont care 19. Ears pierced or not: one ear pierced, that's sexy 20. Tan or Pale: tan 21. Dimples or not: dimples are sooo cute! 22. Athlete or Academic: academic, but not too nerdy 23. Accent or not: accent!!!   ON GIRLS FOR GUYS TO FILL OUT (for guys only)  27. Regular underwear or thong: 28. Painted nails or not: 29. Bra or sports bra: 30. Cute n' mysterious or wild n' sexy: 31. Dressy or casual: 32. Dark hair or Blonde hair: 33. Long or short hair: 34. Dark or light eyes: 35. Long or short nails: 36. Hat or no hat: 37. Good or bad girl: 38. Hair up or down: 39. Jewelryor none: 40. Tall or short: 41.Curly or straight hair: 42. Tan or fair: 43. Freckles or none: 44. Indoor chick or party chick: 45. Accent or not: shy or outgoing:  EVERYONE  51. Root Beer or Dr. Pepper: hard call... I'd say Dr. Pepper tho, unless it's Sprecher... 52. Mud or Jell-O wrestling: jello wrestling, only bc i like jello better than mud 53. Sunshine or rain: Sunshine 54. Vanilla or Chocolate: depends, but most of the time, chocolate 55. Skiing or snowboarding: skiing 56. Day or night: night! I HATE mornings. 57. Summer or winter: another hard call... I'll go with summer cuz that's my birthday 58. Pie or cake? gah! too-many-hard-decisions! lol I'd say cake tho. yummy. 60. Silver or gold: jewelry silver, everything else gold 61. Diamond or Pearl: diamond 62. Sun set or sun rise: sunsets, especially in Hawaii :D besides I'm not up early enough to see sunrises 63. Have you ever broken/fractered a bone? yup, my wrist in 1st grade 64. What's your favorite color(s)? purple mostly, but I like any vibrant or pastel colors pretty much. 65. Do you hate any one: not at the moment (except Mariah Carey... does she count?) 66. What's your favorite band? tossup btwn Good Charlotte, Evanescense, and Steriogram 67. Do you have a HUGE crush on someone? not right now 68. Have you ever been in love? ya 69. Ever been hurt by a member of the opposite sex? yes! *cough cough Alex cough cough* 70. Who's the loudest friend you have? SASHA!  71. Who's the quietest friend: probly Caroline or Kim... maybe Alexandra? ooh! Emily from camp! eh...who knows. 72. Who's the craziest friend: ALL my friends are crazy! jeez. 73. Who makes you laugh the most: all of my friends... but probly Chelsea or Alex. 75. Who do you tell EVERYTHING to: Val, Chelsea, and Alex mostly 76. What is your idea of the perfect date? something that involves stargazing and preferrably Celine... but if not, a barefoot walk on the beach in Hawaii or Door County sounds fine to me 77. Name as it appears on your birth certificate: Amanda Lauren Armstrong Rehrauer I think... maybe w/o the Armstrong? who knows. 87. Date that you regularly blow out your candles: what?? my birthday I guess... what kind of a question is that? 80. Pets: Bogy! (golden retriever) 81. Tattoos: no 82. Piercings: ears 83. Birthplace: good ol' Milwaukee 84. Current Residence: wisconsin 85. Favorite food: too many yummy foods 2 pick from 86. Favorite drink: smoothies, soda, and artificial grape juice. the koolaid kind. 87. Been to Africa? no 88. Been toilet papered by someone? ya, but idk who tho 89. Loved somebody so much it made you cry? ya 90. Been in a car accident? thank god no 91. Favorite WORD(s): hexametaphosphate, methylchloroisothiazolinone (lol I like reading ingredients to stuff when I'm bored! like syrup and shampoo and stuff.) onomatapia, choisir (it didn't say in english!), yayishness 92. Last book you read? idk I don't read that much... probly Harley (for like the 15th time lmao) 93. When was your last hospital visit: idk I don't go to hospitals much 94. What color is your bedroom carpet? brown! YUK! 95. Who is the last person you got email from before this? sasha 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OnE HuNdReD AnD OnE QuEsTiOnS >Please fill it out too and send it back!!! Okay, you all know the >routine...copy (not forward) this email and paste it onto a new >email that you will send. Change all the answers so that they apply >to you, then send this to a whole bunch of people you know INCLUDING >the person who sent it to you. The theory is that you will learn a >lot of little facts about your friends. > > (except not really. but still here ya go.) 1) Starting time: 9:38PM 2) Full name: Amanda Lauren Armstrong Rehrauer 3) Nicknames: Manda; Mandy; Dander; A man, duh!; Squishy, Celineiac, that girl obsessed with Celine Dion, no name  4) School: Homestead High School  5) Email: ducky61803@yahoo.com 6) Eyes: blue 7) Height: 5'7-ish 8) Siblings: does my dog count? 9) Ever been kissed: yes :) 10) Ever cheated or been cheated on?: YES!!! *cough cough alex and val cough cough* 11) What do you want in a relationship?: somebody who cares about me and likes me for me (all together now: awwwwwwww!!) 12) Ever missed school because it was raining?: lol no! but good idea.  13) Kept a secret from everyone?: yup 14) Had an imaginary friend?: I LOVE YOU WENDIE!!! 15) Wanted to hook up with a friend?: *no comment* 16) Cried during a Flick?: yeah- A Walk to Remember 18) Ever thought of animated characters as hot?: um, no. 19) Ever thought your best friend was hot?: *shivers* definetly not. 20) If someone you didnt know were to just ask you out, out of the blue, what would you say?: i depends on if he was hot or not! lol no jk id probly get to know them better. 21) What the first thing about a guy you notice?: the way he acts and the way carries himself  -----------------FAVORITES---------------- >  22) Shampoo: bio from bath and body works and beach blonde 23) Color: i like pretty much anything either bright and vibrant or pastel ]24) Summer/Winter?: summer  25) Online?: um.... if youre asking if i'm online, then obviously, but otherwise..... ????? 26) Lace, silk or satin?: silk i guess 27) Like anyone: wait r we still doing favorites? what r u talking about?! that doesnt make sense! dont confuse me...its not nice! (in the words of Sasha) 28) Who have you known the longest out of your friends: either Kira or Chelsea 29) Who's the loudest: SASHA! 30) Who's the shyest: Alex probly 31) Who do you go to for advice?: Val 32) Who do you get along with?: everybody, I'm pretty neutral ---------IN THE LAST 2 WEEKS HAVE YOU------------  33) Cried: i don't think so 34) Been mean: probly but i cant think of anything  35) Acted blonde?: um, duh. 36) Been sarcastic: ya like everyday 38) Talked to someone you have liked?: ya 39) Told someone you loved them?: umm...my mom...does that count? 40) Hugged someone: ya  41) Been depressed?: a little, does not going to the John Mayer concert count? 42) Wished upon a star: yea 43) Laughed until you've cried: no but i've laughed hard 44) Played Truth or Dare: not in the last 2 weeks 45) Watched a sunrise/sunset: yeah, it was really pretty too 46) Went to the beach at night?: no but it sounds like fun  47) Broke up with someone?: no 48) Just sat and thought, looking for answers?: yea, it was quite nice 49) Are you lonely?: yeah  50) Are you happy?: most of the time  51) Are you talking to someone online?: sorta... they're talking to me but i'm away. haha. >-----------DO YOU BELIEVE IN.......------------ >  52) God/Devil: ya 54) The Closet Monster: AHHHHHHH NOT THE CLOSET MONSTER!!!!!!!!  55) Santa Claus?: :) 56) Heaven/hell: yep  57) Superstitions?: yeah, just not telling ppl important stuff otherwise you'll jinx it.  ---------ODD QUESTIONS---------  58) Half empty or half full: half full  59) Who named you?: parents  60) Favorite quote: i dunno...i like lots of quotes 61) When was the last time you showered?: earlier today 62) What was the last thing that you said when you were online? sash!! omg i just met a new celine fan!! 64) What is your computer desk made of?: wood and glass (there's a glass top on it) 65) What was the last thing that you did: atalked to my aunt and uncle on the phone, they're in las vegas right now  66) where do u want to go on your honey moon? someplace hot, like australia or something 67) Who do you want to spend the rest of your life with: someone who cares about me 68) Night or Day: i'm a night owl but i dont mind the daytime 69) What type of weather?: warm and sunny  70) What did you do last night?: wouldnt you like to know ;-) jk jk jk i watched tv til 11, listened to music and slept on the floor with my dog (but not WITH my dog... lol) cuz he was scared 72) How do YOU eat an Oreo?: twist it and then lick the cream then eat the cookie. or if I have 2 oreos ill twist them and then stick the opposite sides together for a double stuff. 73) All time favorite TV show: degrassi: the next generation or in case you havent heard of that, vh1's best week ever or spongebob 74) Dream vehicle? vw bug!! 75) What do you want to be when you grow up: um.......... 76) Favorite music?: anything by Celine Dion or whatever's on the radio that isnt rap 77) Favorite band?: if you mean BAND, then Maroon 5... but musician, Celine Dion :-D  78) Favorite food?: greasy fatty goodness!!! and peanut butter toast.  79) Favorite Songs?: anything by Celine Dion and whatever's on the radio that isn't rap 80) Favorite days of the week?: days where I can sit on my fat ass and do absolutely NOTHING!!! 81) Favorite Animal: GOLDEN-RETRIEVER-MANATEE-PANDA-THINGY!!!! 82) Where would you rather spend your day? somewhere with my friends, like Hawaii :) 83) If you could change your name, what would it be?: idk(val's name would be evelyn)(however it is spelled) 84) Do you sleep with a stuffed animal?: I used to... then I found out that I threw them out of the bed.... now I dont/  85) The most stupid thing u ever done: oi too many to name  86. First Son's name?: Micheal  87) Husband/ Wife: ?? 88) First daughter?: Chloe Nichelle 89) Silver or Gold?: silver 90) You like scary or funny moviesbetter? both... but i'd have to say scary 91) On the phone or in person?: depends... if i like them, then in person, but if I don't, then on the phone, lol 92) Lust or Love: Love  93) If you could change something about yourself, what would it be?: ai more like what wouldnt I change?! but i'd hafta say i'd like to be a little more confident in myself and more in shape. and more attractive to guys cuz i think i have like guy repellent or something. lol. but not really cuz it sucks. 94) Do you have pets: Bogy!!!! 95) What kind of pet do you want! ?: the golden/setter at the OHS 97) Favorite carnival ride: tilt a whirl-ish rides 98) Who sent this to you?: Sasha 99) What do you think about this person?: hyper and random, but fun 100: Favorite baseball team: GO BREWERS!!!!! lol the brewers suck! but i don't watch baseball anyway. 101. Time Finished: 10:35 (but I took like 45 min. on the phone)  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YES! more quiz results!   urlLink   Are you ying or yang?    urlLink   "Choose" your RFR character! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so here's the thing...  John Mayer/Maroon 5 concert tonight and I'M STILL NOT GOING!!! WAAAAAAAH! k i'll stop now. but seriously it SUCKS!!!!  ummmm not much else to say. just I'm so friggin bored. what else to tell tho... I never really told you much about myself tho. but if ur reading this u probly kno me anyway. so screw that idea.  COUNTDOWNS: John Mayer and Maroon 5 concert: TONIGHT!!!! :'( Flute camp @ UW Whitewater: July 11th- 8 days Band camp (whoopty freakin do!): August 16th- 48 days 1st day of school (nooooooooooo): September 2nd- exactly 2 months MY 15TH BIRTHDAY: September 6th- 65 days  ummm ya thats all.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First blog entry! yay! k thats it.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>