<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   As I've mentioned, I like teaching 13 year olds. I like teaching science. It's the all-time best subject to teach: I get to do it all. I can include a little math, a little reading, a little writing, my students can work alone or in groups, they get to do wonderful things like build and launch rockets--we get bored in the classroom & we can go outside for a 15-minute field trip. Is there a better subject to teach? No way.   I report back-to-work in a week. I know, it's difficult to feel much sympathy for someone who is off for ten weeks in a row, but consider that three weeks of that were spent taking a graduate class and then two more weeks were spent taking a forty-hour work-related technology course, so I really only had five weeks off. Can't really complain about it, but find myself dreading going back.   The dread thing was really confusing: I love the beginning of each and every school year. It's a fresh start with new kids, new ideas, new opportunities. I knew that part wasn't what bothered me. Then I realized what was upsetting me: having to listen to the daylong lecture on the latest district mandates. There's one every year and each August the list gets a little longer and more tedious. What I dread is having to sit there and listen to directives from up high flow downhill to the classroom. People who have the least understanding of what it takes to actually teach make the bulk of the decisions about how we teach.   I will listen, take notes, and attempt to keep my mouth&nbsp;shut. I will mentally create three categories. One, the mandates that absolutely must be followed; two, the mandates that I can appear to follow while doing them in the most minimal way possible; and three, the ones with which I will not comply. This is not done from a sense of rebellion, it comes from a deep belief that what we as teachers are told to do is counterproductive to what I need to accomplish.   This is the frustrating thing about being an experienced teacher: we are treated as interchangeable parts that have to be managed by those "above" us since we couldn't possibly have a clue about what do otherwise.   I am a professional. I have a B.S. in geology, a degree that required a great deal of math and science coursework--imagine that! I am actually content qualified to teach what I teach--what a novel&nbsp;concept!&nbsp;I have an M.S. in educational administration. I have completed the internship and passed the certification exam that gives me a mid-management certificate. I have all the qualifications one requires to become a principal. I am working on my Ed.D. in educational leadership. I stick with it, write that dissertation, and I will be "Dr. Jane".   People keep asking if I'm going for a superintendent position. Originally, I thought that I might be heading that way. However, the more classes I took, the more I listened to the conversations of my administrative classmates, the less I saw myself moving into that arena. What I want to see is teachers take control of what happens in their classrooms, their schools. Administrators often say that they went into administration because they wanted to have greater influence over what happens in a school and saw becoming a principal a way to make that happen. Trouble is, it seldom works out that way.   In seventeen years of teaching, I have directly impacted over 2000 students. Regardless of who sat in the principal's office, I have been the person in direct contact with the kids. I have done my job in the way that I determined that it needed to be done. Good, bad, or just clueless in the principal's office and it hasn't made all that much difference in how I taught. Some years it was easier because I had the support of a good administrator, but in the bad years, I still did my job.   Principals come and go on any campus. I have worked with six different principals. That averages out to about three years for any one of them. Three were only there one year, one I worked with for two years, another is going on to five years, and the longest was seven years. They do create the campus atmosphere and set the tone for the staff, but what I chose to do is impacted by them only slightly.   On the other hand, I work with people who were on staff when I started teaching and some who came aboard shortly after. We've been on the same campus since the doors opened. How can anyone not understand that people who have been in place this long are key players in shaping the culture of that campus? That we understand our students and neighborhoods from which they come better than any principal who is new to our campus?   The biggest problem teachers face is understanding just how powerful a force we can be when we are willing to speak up for ourselves and students. We have a good understanding of what does and what does not work with our students, but we are seldom asked to share that with anyone. We are all too often willing to hear the about the latest innovative program and think that's what we need to do--or for the more battle-weary among us, unwilling to protest it. We are our own worst enemy.   So...my modest goal is to help blaze the trail towards a more vocal teacher presence in the decision-making process. If we want to make a difference, we need to be heard. Superintendents need to understand that if they do not connect with classroom teachers that they are undercutting their own chances for success.       

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Okay, so it's not like I don't already enough to do: I'm in the midst of working on my Ed.D. (the "practical" Ph.D.), beginning the process for National Board Certification as a teacher, and lead two girl scout troops, but darn it, this looks like fun.   So, you're probably already asking yourself "Where does this totally-normed chick get off referring to her site as "The Freak Show That Is My Life"? Stick around, it will all begin to become clear.  I'm a middle-school teacher: grade 8 science. Have been doing it for seventeen years with periodic sprinklings of grade 7 science, grade 7 or 8 mathematics, or well, who knows what this school year might bring?   When I tell people that I'm a teacher, their first response (usually not spoken, but seen in their eyes)is "You must be stupid otherwise you would be doing something better." Then I tell them that I LIKE working with 13 year-olds, they physically move away because now they know that in addition to being stupid, I'm also insane.   Not convinced yet? My husband's a cop. We have interesting after-shift conversations about the latest drug bust, car wreck (complete with descriptive interludes of exactly what can happen even if you were wearing your seatbelt), or shootings. After arriving on the scene of a drug-deal gone bad, he asked the victim where he had been hit. The vic's response? "Everywhere."  

						
</post>


</Blog>