<Blog>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Every time I sit in the valley of the pain, which blows wind of sadness me in the face, then I look on the lake of the tears. The trees begin to then always bleed, children bite its teddy the head off. The dear granny kills the Grandpa, who cannot resist in the wheelchair with the axe. The soil begins itself to move, becomes a fleshy muzzle. Devours me, reaches for me. On the mountain the scythe man stands and signs to me too, calls my name into the night. Come to me, resounds it in dark nothing of the illusions. And on the other mountain, lovely and nevertheless so far, the light, the release. In the deep dark courses of the past the died I waits! The cries become louder, cruelly loud. In the distance the monotonous grollen of tanks, which want to destroy the valley. The valley of the pain into my heart. An practice-experienced holy, liveless being because of the soil, smiling ends. There she calls again, the bottle, which waits for you, in the valley of the pain on the meadow of cruelties. Nobody hands you the hand, all signs of the distance, will acclamation you: "everything becomes good"! Ever more deeply I run into the forest, trees reach for me, stones kill me. And there, it is again, the nut/mother, that kills its child. Raben circle, draw their courses and cross mean way. Souls burn in the fire of the longing and wait for the fact that one fetches them. The night in this valley does not yield the sun, always away lasting darkness. Masks and voices which to you say, let us trust me, I listen. Then the impact in the face of the truth and again carries your best friend a label on their round belly. What can one bear, in the valley of the pain? How long can one live there? How long? How long? And why? 

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   There are two kinds of fools. The one say: That was always like that, and therefore it is good! And the others say: That is new, and therefore it is better. In former times humans had fear of the future. Today the future must have fear of humans. 

						
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   let me look.. 

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Which if the world would be probably dark would be if sadness and pain daily a laughter rarely and hardly possible which would be if the night the brightest, which we know would be and which light strangely, holy well which would be if we all directly, if individuals were not any more and nothing more were which us floats we would probably take the fate instead of us to resist..instead of us to live... 

						
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   That summer rain sizzles against the windowpane. The sky cries. From mourning? Before luck? Lightning twitches over the horizon and illuminates for one moment the grey world. I think about the life. Mine live and its sense. There were many sad moments, in which I was despaired and helpless. But also again beautiful instants, full joy and luck came. I understand only now that it is that, which makes the life so worth living - the reason, why I love it in such a way. It is the fact that after each rain again sunshine follows. As now. The thunderstorm twisted itself. The sun breaks by the clouds. And in the sky is a beautiful rainbow   

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Stranger Around me well-known faces stranger eyes strange word who are you? In me a dark memory the same eyes the same words I asks itself nevertheless who is it? The more frequently I your empty eyes look your empty words hear know I you the less to foreigner see into my face recognize their me? or perhaps am I the foreigner? Words Everything into words, in my head locked into my heart burned nevertheless never spoken as sealed my lips and I are already a thousand times meant are afraid the words could me tell my internal outward to turn to word can lie already a thousand times wanted I it loud to express which I feel, what I white outward its which I inside am who I am is nevertheless deeply euphemistic which I think words are veils behind those itself the sense hidden until you undress him of words are a loud silence mirror image in the mirror look I into a face nevertheless never see I me fragments of my spirit sit down there to a picture together unclearly and my mirror image distorts the hated form the disgusting light look me from it from dead eyes to that is only my ugly face nevertheless never am which I see in such a way I my mirror image and it would like to see smashed bursting to thousand pieces of broken glass to I in each small fragment is. 

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Not for a long time you already are in this world. Not for a long time you spread this mourning around you the rum already construct yourself like a fortress. Does not sit there above you alone in the tower, stairs leads up to you. You see it from the window, rain, cold weather come into your small dark room. The tower is high, the soil is hard. The window with the time disintegrate ever more from the inside. Now fits you through, now can you finally this tower leave. You rise to the inside of the window, spread your black wings and jump. You try to fly, there your body by pain are fulfilled, your wings... you it were forgotten?? How could you only forget, did think you, you could escape from the tower, which leave fortress? You fall, can still hold you nowhere. So much mourning, so much pain, so much hate... no fear as you into a new, you unknown realm falls nevertheless. A realm without fortress. 

						
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ..love and hate warmth and cold weather of everything at the same time confusion from the day into the night which has my past life brought? Pain and its full humans nevertheless completely alone everything did not let my heart become stone able love and hate to recognize not in the layer pain and luck to separate. To feel fear before it warmth and cold weather to affect without thereby a difference. In an abyss of emptiness fallen by no voices sounds fear before its fear of the weakness fear before it to be used fear before strong its. Am I good or bad target I good or badly its? Do I live well, if I am bad? Do I feel that bad, if I am nevertheless good? Am I at all? 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   You have friends, but even though you’re lone. You wanna laugh, but your smile is gone. You give a happy impression, but you’re sad. They think you’re good, but you know you’re bad. You laugh, but inside you cry. You life, but secretly you wanna die. You say that you love, but in reality you hate, They think they can help you, but it’s too late.  

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   We float on the waves. Sink down there into the depth. Searches Atlantis and cry, if we found it finite, deeply on the reason of our hearts. There it lies forgotten and waits for our home coming. In the ocean is time. 

						
</post>


</Blog>