<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Believe it or not, I've made my move, relatively unscathed.  What a long, hard couple of days, though.  Is it Murphy's Law that people who say that they will help you move always seem to find a reason at the last minute to back out?  I was unable to get the day off, and so it was Dave and a friend with a horse trailer.  Yup..two people to move our worldly possesions.  However, it got done, and the stuff that didn't...well, it was stuff that could fit in a car.  Thank goodness!  BUT...now the daunting task..yes, unpacking.  Oh, how I hate unpacking.  I don't know what's worse...packing or unpacking.  The house is littered with boxes and bags, everything looks so cluttered, and I haven't got a CLUE where to start putting things.  It's so overwhelming.  My response to being overwhelmed tends to be to just sit and stare at it, and then turn on the TV..or in this case, write a blog.  In any case, my long weekend will be filled with boxes and the ever exciting NEW adventure...WHERE are we going to put THIS???  Anyhow, Happy Long Weekend everyone...talk to you soon!  -J.  
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, tonight is the last night that I will have internet access.&nbsp; For a couple of days, anyways...tomorrow, the computer is going to be dismantled and moved over to our new house. So, all of my profound thoughts will have to be jam packed into this blog tonight.  The weekend was fairly good, except for this stupid hot weather, which, if you've read any of my other posts, you'll know that I hate it! HATE it!!!!  We did some packing, which is turning out to be a bit frightening...we thought that we didn't have much stuff left to pack.&nbsp; Boy, were we wrong!!!&nbsp;   We went to our friends house (Jeff and Dawn) for supper on Saturday, which was really nice.  My brother and his wife were in town from Calgary this afternoon.&nbsp; They were at an anniversary celebration for her grandparents this past weekend.&nbsp; It was held in a town about an hour from Saskatoon, and so they came and spent the afternoon with us, and brought us a new china cabinet!!  And tonight, Dave went to work, and I'm sitting here, sweating.&nbsp; The house just doesn't cool off.&nbsp; At least our new house is cooler!&nbsp; Thank goodness!  But, my profound thought is this:&nbsp; I am truly thankful for all of the good people in our lives.&nbsp; God has blessed Dave and I with an awesome marriage and really wonderful family and friends.&nbsp; It's so nice to know that a support network is in place if we need it, and even if we don't.&nbsp;&nbsp; A true friend doesn't care if you pop in on them, or if they pop in on you and your house is a disaster.&nbsp; You can sit and chat about anything and everything, and when the visit is over, you feel refreshed and just really good about yourself.&nbsp; So, to all of our friends and family, we love you and we cherish you!&nbsp; Thanks for all of the support during our big purchase and move!  Good night and talk to you FROM OUR NEW HOUSE!!!!  -J. 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, approximately a week ago, I was out watering my garden after a long day of gardening, and this tiny, little kitty comes bounding out of the grass towards me.&nbsp; She was orange, white, black, and tabby, all in one, with this loud, whining mewl.&nbsp; And cute!!  Well, my  urlLink cousin , Janine, is going to be moving into our old house that we've been renting.&nbsp; And, she has a cat, Salut (I think that's how you spell it?).&nbsp; She has been pondering finding company for her, as she is sometimes gone on weekends, and it can be a long, lonely time for a cat.&nbsp;   When this little one came bounding out of the grass towards me, with no tag or owner, I immediately gave her a call.&nbsp; After 2 minutes of hemming and hawwing, she said she'd take her, if we didn't mind babysitting for a couple of weeks, until she moved up to Saskatoon at the end of the month.  Let me say this.&nbsp; It has been an interesting week with a new kitty in the house.&nbsp; Our two cats, ZoomZoom and Ruby, have NOT been keen on this at all.&nbsp; There has been much growling, hissing, and gnashing of teeth, so to speak.&nbsp; Callie, as Janine has named her, seems pretty much oblivious.&nbsp; She just goes about her business, exploring her new home to be, eating, sleeping, and tormenting her babysitters.&nbsp;&nbsp; Wait...did I say tormenting her babysitters???   Yes, she likes to crawl up on our bed at, oh, say 4 in the morning, and lick.&nbsp; Lick, lick, lick.&nbsp; Lick the face, lick the nose, lick the lips (YUCK!!), lick the fingers!&nbsp; I try to push her away...she comes back...I swear, she could be a door-to-door salesperson with the persistence that she displays!&nbsp;   Tonight, I had to give her a bath.&nbsp; She was outside (we have a cat run attached to this house), and I kind of sprayed her a bit with the sprinkler.&nbsp; She was muddy, so I put her in the bath tub.&nbsp; Surprisingly, she did pretty good with it!&nbsp; No hissing or scratching.&nbsp; Now, I'm not saying she LOVED it, but she did pretty darn good.  As much as I love this little kitty, though, I'm going to be happy when Janine comes up here and takes ownership.&nbsp; I think her ears and nose need a good licking instead of mine. =)  -J. 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To all you whiners who were complaining about the cold, rainy weather...Are ya happy now??? Frick, do I hate this hot weather crap.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Not to mention the fact that my husband and I have spent the past 4 days cooped up in our new home, doing a bit of a facelift...yes, I particularly enjoyed it when I was sanding plaster down, and it was sticking to my sweat.&nbsp; Perhaps it's a new beauty treatment?? &nbsp; And speaking of sweat...I never knew the places my body could sweat from.&nbsp; Have any of you ever experienced sweat forming on the fronts of your legs?&nbsp; Well, it happens.&nbsp; Thank goodness for my ever trusty "d0-rag", because it absorbed all of my forehead and head sweat and kept if from running into my eyes. &nbsp; However, on the bright side, we got pretty much all of the work done that we wanted to.&nbsp; The living room and dining room are freshly painted, the bedroom is freshly painted, the living room carpet and bedroom carpet have been ripped up and removed, and the hardwoods have been re-done (the simple way - with a kit, no sanding...that will happen later).&nbsp; And, I think it all looks pretty darn cool. &nbsp; However, I think that air conditioning is definitely on the wish list.&nbsp;  &nbsp; In the mean time, I'm completely exhausted and ready for bed.&nbsp; Rejoice, for tomorrow is a brand new day, back at the grindstone we all love to call "work". &nbsp; -J. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *LOL* I just saw this  urlLink link  on  urlLink another blogger's site.  -J.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, tonight, Dave and I actually started having a go at our new house.  Dave busied himself with tearing up the carpet in the living room, pulling off baseboards, and lifting up all of the carpet tacking around the room.  I, on the other hand, began the mortal combat with the fricking wallpaper.  Sheesh, I hate that stuff.  For the most part, it peeled off really nicely, but, these people, before layering on the latest pattern of paper, didn't properly remove the old stuff.  So, we now have little brown flecks of dried on paper underneath the current paper.  What a mess that is for me!  Also, we are going to have to do a TON of plastering in the bedroom. (This is the room that has been violated with the hideous aforementioned crap.)  Not too mention that these people were smokers.  Now, if you do smoke, I'm not pointing the finger.  We all have our addictions.  But, really, if you smoke in the house, you wouldn't believe how it stains the walls and ceiling.  It was so gross.  Well, tomorrow my battle with the enemey shall continue.  And, I WILL prevail.  Die, wallpaper...DIE!  -J.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I survived the appointment.  As it turns out, I have inflammed, irritated facet joints on my left side (these are little joints between the vertebrae in the spine).  My doctor just knew where to press to make it hurt.  Anyhow, I am now the proud owner of some really great anti-inflammatories and muscle relaxants.  Here's hoping that they work, and that they work well, because I've got painting and hardwoods to work on this weekend!!!  On a different note, I have an addendum to my list of things never to say to a sonographer.  Actually, it might be more of a rant.  IF you are coming for an obstetrical ultrasound, and you bring your spouse along, that's completely fine.  But, when I ask you (you, being the pregant woman) to slide your pants and underwear down past your bum (and we do this so that we can ultrasound your cervix, and get a good look at the baby's presenting part, whether it's head or bum), PLEASE, please, PLEASE, could the husband/spouse/father of the baby, please keep the "Well, that's how we ended up here in the first place!" comments to yourself!  I have NO desire to hear the story of your child's conception.    Okay, nuff said.  -J.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No, I am not in need of an exorcism.    Today was the big possession date of our house.  It felt totally surreal.  But, good, I think.  These people seemed to like the wallpaper, though.  I am not a fan of the vile stuff.  It seems like it will peel off pretty easily, so I won't have to go to Home Depot and buy some fancy, fandangled gadget to remove the stupid stuff.  It's really interesting to peel it off and see what's underneath.  Take our master bedroom, for instance.  Hmm...totally going off on a tangent here, but has anyone ever figured out WHY it's called the master bedroom?  Is it because the masters of the house sleep in it?  Anyhow, there's this hideous taupey-floral paper, with a navy floral border around it.  Yuck! :P  It peels off easy, and underneath it, it looks like a raspberry peach sorbet.  Yup, pink and peach walls, with some BROWN floral wall paper bits underneath.  WHAT where they thinking???  Also, we pulled up some of the living room carpet.  What beautiful hardwood underneath!  I don't think it will take a whole lot of effort to shine it up.  For those of you still interested in my achin' back syndrome, I have finally bit the bullet.  I am going to see my doctor tomorrow.  It's funny...going to the doctor shouldn't scare me, but I can already feel my nervous stomach a-rumblin'.  I mean, it's just for my back, right?  How bad can it be?  I'll keep you posted.   Anyhow, it's late and my eyes are starting to cross.  They've been blurry for some time now.  I think I've been playing too many computer games.  Yes, I do enjoy my computer games.  I'm particularly a big fan of Zuma.  Has anyone else played that one?  -J.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, my title is long, but it was the best way to sum up what happened in my little world today.  Okay, so, to recap for all of my many faithful blog readers (of course, this is said tongue in cheek), Dave and I are just wrapping up the whole first home purchase thing.  We had an appointment with the lawyer at 0700h, which surprised me, but what surprised me even more, was the fact that we were already his third appointment of the day.  Apparently, he's an early lawyer-worm...first appointment was at 0500h!!  So, we're standing outside the building, and we're early, both of us incredibly nervous.  And, the door is locked.  We both look at each other...what are we going to do?  "Do you have the cellphone?" "yeah..?" "Do you know his number?" "No...".  Then, this freaky security/janitor dude comes and lets us in..wow, he was some weird!  He told us to wait right there and the lawyer would come and get us.  Well, 10 minutes later, and 8 people have come and gone.  And we're still standing in the lobby, waiting for the lawyer to come and get us.  Long story short, we were supposed to go on up, because the entire building opens at 0700h, anyways.  And the lawyer came and found us, because someone had told him that there were two people standing downstairs, looking completely lost. That, of course, being us.  What can I say?  I was raised on a farm, and I listen to what people tell me to do!  This security guard could have been capable of opening up a can of whoop-ass on me, for all I knew!  However, I digress.  We have officially signed the papers.  The monies are in place, we've got our house, and the possession date has been moved up to July 12.  And strangely, we both felt really sick after we left the office.  It was kind of a "Oh shit...what have we DONE???" sort of feeling.  In fact, I made Dave run me home quick before he dropped me off at work, but I could feel my anxious bowels working overtime.  Yuck!  Well, that's enough for today.  This kind of sucked, but I didn't really have any "witty" thoughts today.  Stay tuned.... -J.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay.  I've been a full-fledged ultrasound tech for a little over a year now, and I've already come up with a repertoire of comments and things that you: a)should never say or b)should never ask  Now, I realize that having an ultrasound can produce a variety of emotions - from pain to embarrasment to joy, and so if you are an offender under either a) or b), it's okay.  I don't hate you.  I'm just trying to prevent future misunderstandings from happening.  First of all: 1./  Don't tell me that your bladder is full when it's not.  I can tell when you're lying.  I'm the one taking the pictures, remember?? 2./  Don't tell me that your fasting when you've eaten bacon and eggs for breakfast.  I can figure that one out, too. 3./  Please don't fart on me.  I know that gas happens, but there is absolutely NO need to squeak one out on my leg. 4./  Please don't ask me the gender of your baby when you are only 8 weeks pregnant.  I'm good, but I'm not THAT good. (For your information, this is best determined around the 20 week mark, or even later, and even then we can't see things, due to fetal position) 5./  I know that when you are fasting, your breath tends to become fetid.  However, fasting doesn't mean that you can't brush your teeth.  Just don't eat the tube of toothpaste.  And please, when I tell you to let your breath out, don't blow it in my face. 6./  When you are told to leave your underwear on, please do so. 7./  For the men.  Truly, we don't enjoy scanning your testicles.  It's just as embarrasing for us as it is for you.  So, comments like "Thanks for being so genital with me!" are not really appreciated.  I could go on, but I'll save them for another bloggy day.  Okay, now, I don't mean for any of this to sound cruel.  Just some little snippets of information to take to heart.  And, in case you were wondering...we truly ARE all shades of grey inside.  At least, in my world we are. =)  -J.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I believe that this site proves that  urlLink George Bush  poops.  Well, at least he farts.  But does Paul Martin?  Maybe someone could make some money here...any entrepreneurial minds out there?  Because I smell some money in the making!!  -J.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, in my line of work I see some pretty bizarre stuff.  And, I mean bizarre.    Take today, for instance.  I had the opportunity of interacting with a gentleman, who had an unfortunate thing happen to him.  This poor lad had been beaten with a baseball bat in a certain area of his anatomy.  Yes, his nuts were beaten to a pulp.  In fact, it was so bad, that this person will most likely have to have surgery, and they will most likely have to remove the injured testicle.   Where's the humanity in this?  I, personally, do not have testicles.  However, I am presuming that they are quite sensitive.  In fact, I KNOW that they are.  You should see the look of agony that crosses my husband's face when one of our cats decides to step on his!  He tends to lurch up and groan, with a look of pain washing over his face.  And then he promptly picks the cat up and places it on the floor.   What's the moral of this story?  Well,  I suppose, if at all possible, protect those little gems, and if you have cats, sit on your couch with a phonebook over your lap. And if you play baseball, keep the bat ABOVE your waist.   That's my pontification for today.  -J.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I came across this  urlLink link  tonight, and it has to be one of the funniest things that I've seen!!  -J.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, so not like anyone noticed, or even cared that I didn't have anything to say yesterday, because I have one of THE most popular blogs here on the world wide web, but I was unable to write.  And yes.  I realize that that sentence is grammatically incorrect.  And frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn.  Whooo-eeee!! Crusty?  Maybe.    So, picture it.  Sicily, 1917.  Well, actually, Saskatoon, two weeks ago.  I had my weekend off, and Friday, my back started giving me a load of grief.  By Sunday, I was flat out, in bed.  Monday morning, I tried to earn my hero cookie and go to work.  I sat there, had my morning "coffee" with the gang, and was promptly sent home.  Thank you Robaxacet, you're a Godsend!!  The next day, I was much better, just having twinges.    Well, guess what.  Sunday, July 4th, the same thing.  Twinges.  Monday, I actually EARNED the hero cookie, and walked around the office, looking like Quasi Moto.  I'm certain that my patients thought I had been afflicted with some sort of disease.  One of my co-workers told me that I was walking around like someone had stuck a pickle in my bum!  Then, to top it all off, a migraine came to town.  I know, bitch, bitch, whine, whine.  But it really sucked!!  Today, I had to travel out of town, and again, I'm looking like Quasi Moto.  But whatever.  I will survive.  I will get better.  This won't stop me, and it sure as heck won't get in the way of my house painting that is coming up!  If anyone has some good backache remedies...wait a minute...someone would actually have to READ this to suggest any.  Never mind.  On the upswing, I finished my day early, so I dragged Dave, my husband, to Home Depot, where we checked out paint chips.  I think we've decided on some colours.  The dining room is going to be Tomato Red.  The living room is going to be done in a faux finish, called "frottage".  The base coat is called Del Sol, and the "frottaged" part is called Marigold Blossom.  It's an orangey-yellow color.  Very warm and inviting.  At least, that is what I think.  Well, enough whining for today.    Have a good one!  -J.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This is the link to Janine's blog.   Enjoy!!  -J.
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So this morning, my cousin left, and once again, the reality of my situation set in.  The ultimate chore awaits me.  What is the ultimate chore?  PACKING!!! Augh!  Yes, my husband and I have just purchased our first home.  And with that comes the anticipation and excitement of finally being able to make something our own.  However, the dread and fear of packing also rears its ugly little head.   I really shouldn't complain.  It is truly a privilege to be in a situation where you can buy your own home.  And, the new methods out there are fantastic...no need to have that huge bulk of money saved up anymore, provided you're not a credit risk!!  But the waiting...Oh! the waiting!  And again, I shouldn't complain, but I am so anxious and excited to get back into the house and see what it looks like.  I truly can't remember!  Our possession date is July 15, which isn't far away, considering as how we closed the deal last week.  But I've got so many plans for the house!  I suppose it could be a case of "cart before the horse" syndrome.  Before I go and buy the paint and picture myself living in a dream home, designed the way my husband and I want it to be, I need to finish the packing, and prepare for the move.  My husband, David, works night shifts.  I suppose it would be fair for me to say that I've got big plans for him when he wakes up.  Poor boy!!  Well, I'd best close.  Things to do!  -J.
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, it's cool and rainy here today.  Just the kind of weather that I really seem to enjoy.  Call me crazy, but this is the kind of weather that makes me a happy camper.  And, for the record, I hate camping.  If there's no bed, flush toilet, or private room with 4 walls, I'm not interested.  My cousin is still visiting today, so we hung out and did some shopping.  Just girly stuff.  Tonight we're going to see a movie at the cheap theatre.  "13 Going on 30".  Chick flick, perhaps?    Well, that's all I have to say for now.    -J
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So....this is weird.  I've never "blogged" before, until tonight.  I am a blog virgin no more!  Does this even work?   And who is going to read this?  Does anyone really care about what I would have to say?  I guess we shall see.  I'm hanging out with my cousin right now, listening to some mellow piano music.  Acutally, she's singing some Willie Nelson...the classic "You Were Always on My Mind".  We're conspiring that we will each start our own blogs and link to each other, and create our own network and community.  So, we'll see if it works.  If you're reading this and am interested in what I have to say, keep coming back.  In fact, I will be curious to see if anyone finds this page and comments on it.  Perhaps I'm setting myself up for disappointment.  Ta ta for now!!
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I absolutely love the Olympics.  It was a joyful day for me when the decision was made to have an olympic games every 2 years, instead of having both summer and winter in the same year.  The colours of the opening ceremonies (by the way, weren't they fantastic today??), the sounds, the sights, the sparkling of all of the camera flashes going off in the stands, the roar of the crowd, the whole world pulling together, uniting for a common denominator of sport and game.   I particularly enjoyed the portion of the opening ceremonies when they had a "pregnant lady" descend down into some water and her belly lit up, representing hope and new life....it was stunning!  I think that some of my favorite Olympic sports to watch include diving, rowing, swimming, but most importantly, the gymnastics.  In fact, I can feel a trip down memory lane coming on...  When I was a little girl, it was the summer Olympics of 1984.  I would have been 6, going on 7.  I was in Maple Creek, staying with my  urlLink cousin , Janine, because I was taking swimming lessons in the summer.  We would play in the backyard, and perform and do gymnastics for my Aunt, Janine's Mom.  We were experts at cartwheels, round-offs (I think that's what they were called), and all sorts of other "interpretive dance" and gymnastic type activities.  Now, our idols, or the people whom we pretended to be were based upon a very scientific method of deciding.  It was the colour and design of our bathing suits!  As I recall, my bathing suit had a criss-cross back, and was royal blue, with red and white.  Therefore, I was none other than Mary Lou Retton!  Now, Janine's bathing suit was red and white striped, so she was Sylvie Berniea (sp?).  Yes, it was good times.   We had a lot of fun back then, and maybe that's just one of the many reasons why I enjoy the Olympic Games.  I wish Canada's athletes the best of luck.  Make us proud and do your best.  That's all we ask.  -J.  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is my husband, Dave's 32 birthday.   It's hard to believe that we met when he was 26 and I, a tender 21.  He was at the upper limit of my "age requirement" when we started dating.  This year of the 32 will bring many new and exciting things for Dave...finishing off school (he's taking Biotechnology at  urlLink SIAST ), fixing up our new house, working his last days at Western Grocers, possibly having a pregnant wife...we'll have to see what the year brings in that respect. =)  Anyhow, I wish all of the best to my wonderful husband on his birthday.  He's the best man in the world, and I love him very much.  And, if you share is birthday, a happy one to you, as well.  -J. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whooooeeeeee....have I got Momma Itch!  Dave and I have often talked about starting a family - about how we both WANT children, when is a good time to have them, are we ready, what about finances, etc, etc.  And some days, the itch is stronger than others.  For some reason, I was thinking about my rocking chair - yes, we even have a rocking chair, which, for me, brings out the momma urge even more so.  But first, a little background.  Dave and I were married on November 10, 2001.  We went down to Oregon for our honeymoon, and while there, we stayed in a place called Bend.  They had a store that sold hand-made Amish goods, and the store was filled with the most wonderful, home-made, solid furniture.  There was bedroom furniture, pie-safes, rocking chairs, quilts, etc.  My Grandma S. had given us some money as a wedding gift, and had told us to buy something with it that would always remind us of her.  Well, we bought a rocking chair!  It has arms and braces made of willow that's been molded, with boards of oak.  There's even a foot stool!  Anyhow, this rocking chair holds a special place in my heart, because I'd like to think that someday I'll be able to rock my babies to sleep, soothe their tears, and cuddle with them, all in this chair.   But with these dreams comes some fear and angst.   What if Dave and I can never have children?  What if that rocking chair remains empty?  What if we never hear the pitter patter of little feet on our hardwood floors?  I know that it is senseless to worry about such things, when we haven't even BEGUN to try to conceive, but it's a niggling thought, just in that back, dusty corner of my head.   I pray that God will bless us with kids...but what if it's not in His plan?  It's just a scary thought.  In my line of work, I see so many people who are pregnant, and don't want to be, and are there for an ultrasound, just to make sure that the pregnancy is still early enough to terminate.  And, it breaks my heart.  The gift of life...so precious and fragile, and so easy for some to discard like a piece of trash.  I SEE the 6 week fetus' heart beating...living...unwanted, and tragically, so unfair.  Anyhow, I DO pray that my rocking chair will hold my babies, and that we will have a wonderful family.  And if the Good Lord has a different plan for our lives, I guess we'll just have to deal with it.  -J. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I slept in this morning, and woke up feeling really blue and blah.  Do you ever get those "it's the last day of the long weekend blues and I have to go back to fricking work tomorrow" blues?  Well, if so, then you can empathize with me.  And then, this Elton John song popped into my head...which has nothing to DO with MY kind of blues, but it just felt right to post the chorus, courtesy of  urlLink Sing 365.com     "...And I guess that's why they call it the blues 
</post>


</Blog>