<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Mom always hated that expression.&nbsp; My now former co-workers always got a kick out of it.&nbsp; There are few places in the US you can list a house a sell it inside a week.&nbsp; The DC metro area being a big one.&nbsp; So, we have sold this place, and I shall be in sunny Ft Myers, Fl by the 15th.&nbsp; Hubby and the beast, aka Chipper the yellow lab will join us by the 21st.&nbsp; So begins our new Barbara free adventure.&nbsp;&nbsp; I will open a private practice, one of my latino co-workers is willing to walk me thru the entire process....Love to Juan Carlos Silva, Ph. D,&nbsp; my beacon.&nbsp; I am taking bets on who will visit me.... I know Connie will come, dragging Bethy along.&nbsp; I hope she brings Buddah and Lisa too (Buddah is her brother, Dan)&nbsp;&nbsp; I know Auntie Ra and Uncle Tony will come visit often.&nbsp; I hope to get Mom down here, and acclimated.&nbsp; Stop all your screaming my siblings, when you look at the cost, this is THE best for place for her to be, so shut your pie holes!&nbsp; Just look at the free vacations....all you need is air fare, so bite me, collectively.&nbsp; Oh, and Alex, they have nursing shortages here too.....so come on down, you are the next contestant on this is your stress free future.&nbsp; Manuel, you too....since I'll be home, and I'm steering Mom this way, there are a mutlitude of options for Little Gabe.&nbsp; And for you whiners, the auto train, look into it.....cheap transportation, and for the Harry Potter set a dream come true!&nbsp; You can sleep most of the trip!&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Anywhoo...I hope you kicked ass on the bar exam Ra.....you are way smarter than you EVER give yourself credit for.   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       How funny is this.... Barbara apparantly called the main au pair office early last week and said she couldn't live here anymore.&nbsp; Seems we had a discussion about money, and the fact that there were some things she'd have to pay for, like her cell phone bill, my bent axel, the tire she blew, etc.&nbsp; She didn't think she should have to pay for any of this.&nbsp; So now, the au pair co-ordinator has to pick her up and take her to her house.&nbsp; Desiree is allergic to smoke, so Fran Drescher cannot smoke AT ALL, and she cannot use their computer AT ALL because Desiree is a CPA and can't afford to have the virus nightmares we've had.&nbsp; She also can't use the phone to call Italy or NY cause Desiree doesn't want to get huge phone bills.&nbsp; Desiree is not recommending her placement with another familybecause she smokes like a fiend, doesn't drive and doesn't supervise our kids properly, since she spends her time doing job searches in NY,&nbsp;so back to Italy she goes.&nbsp; Barbara never said a word to us, so it's a good thing I have one week left of work cause Miss Selfish thought she'd be getting us by leaving us with no child care.&nbsp; Well, the joke's on her, isn't it?&nbsp; In a few weeks we'll be moving to sunny Florida, and all this crap will be a distant memory! &nbsp; &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, tell me, why is it so hard not to smoke around my youngest who has asthma?  I don't do it.  Yes, bad Mom I am, I smoke.  But I don't smoke around my kids.  If I feel I NEED to smoke, I go outside.  My au pair is not supposed to smoke while on duty, but she does.  Pisses me off.  Like I WANT to spend another 4 days in Children's Hospital like we did back in October.  Not fun.  Like I want to spend a few days praying to God and Padre Pio that they spare him such hardship.  Whatever.  UGH!  I miss Kim.  South African au pairs are the best.  Kim never smoked around the boys.  Ever.  I am so sick of the idiot, I can't take it.  Is it October yet?
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, so here we are, the 4th.  Living in the Nation's Capital, can I say I'm scared shitless?  I always am around these events.  Makes me think of 9-11.  Nuthin like watching a plane slam into the Pentagon to change your world view, is there?  I want to go to the Mall to see the fireworks, but I am also afraid.  Afraid of what you ask?  You live here, then get back to me on that. It all just brings back ugly "flashbacks" of the Pentagon,of Joe driving like a maniac, trying to get home, picking our oldest up from school, and getting home, cause if we were gonna die, we were gonna be together.  Sick, Huh?  God I still have nightmares of that day.  Not that I'm taking any political view, I am a registered independent, but ladies and gents, freedom ain't free.  Never was, never will be.  I am sickened by the the poor Muslim soldier that was reported as beheaded.  How sick is that???  Bastards!  May God, Buddha, Allah, pick your deity, have mercy on his soul and grant him peaceful passage to the beyond...  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I did it!  Go me!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      To put a picture in my profile.  Can't seem to get it to work.  UGH!  How frustrating.  I'm wondering if it has anything to do with the 3 spyware programs I have.  Why so many?  The following is a real conversation between myself, and the Idiot, aka, my au pair: Me:  Barbara, you seem to have infected my computer.  I keep getting error messages. Barbara: What do you mean?   Me: Well, my explorer keeps shutting off, and it was fine, until you last checked your email  What the hell did you do? Barbara:  Nothing.  Are you sure it's me? Me: Well the virus software said it was you.  The programs were loaded when you were the only one home Barbara: Well I was reading my email... Me: And???? Barbara: I scanned them with yahoo, but my junk mail had disturbing messages Me: Like what? Barbara: It said "Your nude photo here" So I scanned it Me: And then you opened the email? Barbara: Yes, the scan said no virus was detected Me: Well, that's how you messed up my computer Barbara:  How? I don't understand Me: Obviously it downloaded something.  What the hell are you doing reading your junk mail anyway? Barbara:  Well it said it had nude pictures of me Me:  Did you pose for any? Barbara: No Me:  Then they don't have any.  It's a lie to get you to open the email (you freaking moron I thought to myself) Barbara: Really?  They lied? Me: Yes (thinking, How freaking old are you? You went to college and they gave you a degree????  Were they high?) Barbara: I'm sorry. What should I do? Me: Don't open anything from anyone you don't know (you IDIOT!)  OMG!!!!  Anyone have any tips? I downloaded hello from picasa.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, so here is my first post.  I have an au pair (nanny) from Italy.  Her phone card challenged friend has just tried to call 3 freaking times at 4am!!!! Every time she called, the phone card would disconnect her, and the idiot kept calling back.  I took the phone off the hook.  I was so pissed, I started a blog.  Welcome to my hell.  She also called 6 times yesterday morning at 7am.  Screwed up my sleeping.  UGH!!!!!  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>