<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      16lbs 14oz.. He's in the 95% percentile for weight, babies his age.&nbsp; What a big boy.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The tourists here in Bancroft are so awful. They do NOT stop for anyone to cross. I waiting at an intersection for more than 10 mins, before walking out and making them stop for me. My mother managed to dart in front of traffic, leaving me behind. I started yelling to her from across the street, something to the effect of Tourist being rude,&nbsp; they have no consideration for anyone but themselves.. I think they did here me, because they did slow down. :) Before Grant, I'd be complacent and just wait. He made me this way .....  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Mason loves his car seat..wouldn't you tho?? It's so comfy looking.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We bought the "Alpha Omega Elite" carseat for Mason about a month or so ago. It is a three in one; rear facing until 22lbs, forward facing until 40lbs I think and than a booster seat. We decided to put it in the car today. Wow, what a time we had. Grant was so fustrated! His car doesn't really fit it well.&nbsp; I think it's about time we got a four door. Finally, after about 1 hr, we got it in, all situated and safe.&nbsp; We went for a test drive, with Mason in it, and he just loves it!!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Mason and I had a good time in Sarnia!!&nbsp; We didn't do much, because it was so hot there!! But Mason got his four month shots.&nbsp; He kinda yelped when he recieved it, but was super after.&nbsp;   I am such a first time mom :) I noticed that Mason was peeing a lot, so I had to call the Telehealth line, to see if it was normal. Well, all the nurse said was to watch what the pee looked like, to see if it was wierd colour or if it had a smell. I don't make it a habit to smell his pee, and I started to smell it. It did have a funky odour, so everytime he peed, I'd smell it. Well, Let me&nbsp; tell ya..It's not a good idea to do that. I wasn't feeling the best at night :P&nbsp; And, the smell was just from his diaper.. yuck!  We got home around midnight on Friday, after going to this fancy place called Baldwins in Aurora :)&nbsp; We were definitly under-dressed for that place.&nbsp; We did end up eating at the Purple Pig, a&nbsp; place more fitting for us.  &nbsp; 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Not a good picture of us, but a good picture of Theo Huxtable .. see him on TV???&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Mason can now roll both ways. From his tummy to his back and from his back to his tummy! He doesn't like being on his tummy to much tho. We put him in his playpen, and went outta the room. When we came back to see him, he was on his tummy, sleeping!  What a good boy!  I went to Weight Watchers today, and I lost 4lbs...not to shabby!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We travelled up to Petawawa this weekend, our old stomping grounds.  Grant's friends up there are dumbass's. I'm glad we aren't living there anymore.  We visited one of his friends with three boys, ages ranging for 15months to 6 years old.  I almost had a nervous breakdown there. The kids were NUTS.  They were hitting and beating each other, jumping from the back of the couch onto the hardwood floor, AACK.  The 15month old smashed his head off the floor, but just shook it off.  Their parents didn't do anything to stop it.  His other friend that we visited wants to get rid of their Rottweiler.  He's such a great dog. I'd so take him, if we had a house :P We went to Walmart up there as well, and stocked up on baby supplies. We bought a new stroller too. Just a lightweight one. But the handle is so short, that you can't take long strides with it, or else your toes will bang off the wheels!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I'm going to be in Sarnia all next week. We're meeting up with Val and Wayne at the Toronto Zoon on Sunday! Should be fun, I haven't been there in the longest time.  Than, I'll be off to Sarnia and Grant back to Borden.  My mother is going to have a whole week to herself, whatever will she do?  It willl be nice to get out of Bancroft though :) Mason is almost 4 months tomorrow, and he's supposed to get his four month shot! Well, the doctor that will take him here, won't see him until August 20th! By that time, he'll almost be ready for his 6 month shot. So, I'm going to go to a walk in clinic in Sarnia and get it done. Mason hasn't been checked out since, well since he had his trush looked at.  I want to get an exact measurement of his weight. I think he's around 17lbs! Big eh??
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Mason has the worst temper I have ever seen on a young child.  I was out for a walk today, and he was all nice and sleeping. He woke up and all of a sudden, he just started to scream and cry! I think he may have had a nightmare.  But, he wouldn't stop crying. He screamed all the way home, about a 10 min walk. I felt so dumb, people must have thought I was beating him.   But, he didn't have many tears. It was just his temper! We are going to have to beat it out of him.. opps haha not beat it.. but get it out of him. Mason is a punk!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Grant called tonight. He got some news from his warrent officer about us moving to Kingston.  We were originally supposed to go there in August, but Grant's course got cancelled and now it's not running until November. But, Grant has applied for "on the job training" and his boss said that we possibly might be going to Kingston in September or even soon! You never get an exact day with the military! And.................. we got a washer and drier for free today! The military is good for something. I guess they were extra, and Grant's commanding officer said that we could have them! Neat eh??
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So I joined Weight Watchers the other day.  My goal is to lose 40lbs! This one chic there lost 105! So if she can lose all that, I'm sure I can lose my weight too.  I can have 24 points each day (every food has a certain point assigned to it). I'm doing pretty good on it too, I haven't snacked at all!  Today, my mother and sister and I went out for our weekly lunch, and of course they order french frieds with gravy, cheesburger, onion rings. My mouth was watering, all that savoury food. I ordered a chicken sandwich on brown, with water :) Also to aid me along on this weight loss journy, I've joined a gym. It's kinda like Curves...I think it's working, I have lots more energy!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Big Blues!!!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sunday July 4th, Its raining outside; thundering and lightning.  I better get this done quick, before I get zapped!   This is our first posting to our blog site!!  How exciting eh??
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I belong to a message board, for ladies that had babies in March. This one lady posted, saying that her financial situation is bad, and if anyone could send her samples, or coupons that it would help a lot. She has twins. So, I was thinking of sending her something, but in the end didn't. I'm glad I didn't. I found out today, that she was selling all the stuff she got on Ebay!   I can't believe some ppl can do this.. What a punk!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    We've noticed a strumming motion that Mason made with his hand. So , we got him a guitar and he actually strums it and places his hands on the thing like he knows how to play it. Ive got a great short vid of it too..if you're interested..let me know and I'll send it to ya!&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    We're starting him off early. &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Mason's goofy smile&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Grant called today, about our housing! He said that we are going to have a house.. addy 7a ortona point.  Its a duplex, so hopefully it's not a bottom floor, top floor kinda deal with two houses. Hopefully it's side by side. Anyways, the kicker is.. the rent is 840 a month plus utilities. But, a paragraph was underlined, saying that the rent can't exceed more than 25% of the families total income. Well, 840 exceeds that. Grant is going to the housing agency to apply for a reduction of rent. Hopefully we'll get it. If we would have known, we would have looked at other places to rent, we were told that renting a PMQ was cheap.  The PMQ will be ready for occupancy on Aug 25th. We're not sure when we'll be moving tho... 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well, the update SUCKS. Grant didn't hear anything about our house this past week at all.  The guy in Kingston, that was supposed to get ahold of the ppl in Borden, went on course on Wednesday.  So, Grant's company clerk and her boss has been working their butts off, trying to get some info! Lets hope this week
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yes, Yes. I have fallen on to the Canadian Idol bandwagon.  I think that the singers this year are so much better than the singers last year!  My fave person prolly would be Jason, he's so much fun.  I think Kalan will go all the way, because there are a lot of teeny bopper girls here in Canada, who will vote for him because hes cute. But he's also a good singer, so I dont mind if he does win. The judges seem to like Caleb a lot.. He's got soul. I don't see what's so good about him.. He's the only black dude in the competition, and I guess they do want that soul in it.. I dunno..
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      About a month and half ago, I bidded on an exersaucer on ebay, and won the auction.  Well, the seller was so immature. She told me she couldn't find my Postal Code, so I'd have to go and find my own shipping. I went on united states postal service, and found a good shipping quote.  She told me that they wouldnt' take it, so she'd make it smaller. I waited, and waited and waited, and she didn't email back. So.. two days ago, Ebay emails me, saying that this seller and I have mutally agreed to cancel the transaction. That's great, cause I don't want it anymore, but the seller didn't inform me that she was going to do this. We got an exersaucer from a garage sale on my street, but it's a boring one with hardly any toys on it.  We saw them in Zellers for 50 bucks cheaper than anywhere else we've been. What's wrong with them??
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ahh I really do need to move out of Bancroft, and my mothers house. Don't get me wrong, my mother helps me so much with Mason it's great. But, she does get on my nerves a lot too. There are some issues with her, my father and my ex-sister-inlaw.. And I hear her talking about it every single day. She doesn't let up and it's making me go crazy.   Come on military, give us a house NOW
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was at the grocery store, buying Mason some jar food. I got a little more than I really needed, but I just wanted to stock up on it.  Anyways, at check-out, the lady behind me gave me her opinion. "Ya know, it's cheaper to make that yourself" So I replied. And than she asked me how old Mason was and I told her. She gave me the meanest look and said.."Can he even sit up by himself"  So I told her that I follow my instincts, he's doing well with his sweet potatoes, he's digesting it great and all.  She just shook her head. I was so mad at her.  This lady was a very overweight lady, wearing something way to small for her. I could have said.. " You know, being very obese likeyourelf, it isn't good for your health" Or I could have said.."You're burning my retinas, with what you're wearing" Some ppl, they just don't know how to keep their mouths shut!  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>