<Blog>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I'm going down in flames, I'm falling into this, again.     &nbsp;  So, a lot has happened! Which is cool though because I have all the time to write this post since the net won't be accessible for another 5 or so hours. I haven't called Mo yet to see how the homestudy went but I plan on doing so around 4 or 5. I want to give her all the time in the world with the lady since I can't remember if the time was going to be around 9 or 3. I'm hung up on those two times though, so it has to be one of the two. I'm dying to know how it is,...     &nbsp;  By the end of this post you guys will know, but for me its another two hours!! You guys can just skip on down, whereas I can't push a forward. Damn you people, damn you!I guess I should start off with talking about Justin since hes on my head right now. I know I should so be sleeping (didn't get to sleep until 6 am this morning...) but I woke up at 11 cause Luke, the fluffy mini panther cat, was on his back with his feet in the air sleeping at my feet. For some reason that reminded me of Justin and I couldn't go back to sleep. We talked for ages last night... not on the phone though. I was dying to ask him if I could talk on the phone with him but I know how much of a nag I must be to him. He says I'm not, but the last few times I've asked him if I could call him (Damn his addictive northern accent!) he said no cause of something or another. I always bitching in Witches for the longest, just about random things. Giving my very opinionated view on abortion, murder, sex before marriage, teen pregnancy, bullying others, and drugs today. Also had a big hissy fit cause people were saying shit against basic instinct. You know, the instinct to live. The instinct to eat. The instinct to produce. Shit like that.     &nbsp;  I know, I'm trying to lose weight but I'm trying to get healthy is the main thing. I want to look good and have a nice firm tummy but I'll be so much happier just to be healthy again and have my tits at a good C. But anyways, he came in and he joined in on some stuff. I disagreed on what he said a few times, and once I think I agreed on something and he says, "Exactly". We said a few other things like, "Wb, ty, yw," but thats it.     &nbsp;  The main thing that got me out of the Justin-You-Bastard mode was when I thought Kyou, Matt, a hella good friend of Justins, was kicking him out of the room. I bitched at him though and he explained Justin is my bestfriend why the hell would I kick him. So, I was in the wrong (Omfg, did I just admit that?) and I said, well good because even if me and justin dont get along right now I wouldn't want him being kicked from rooms and shit. And he said, don't worry worry justin adores you, hun. BAH!!So of course, I had to harass him for a good hour trying to get more out of him. He said he talked to him around the whole part where I was back, which means about two or so weeks ago now. So it was recent. He refused to tell me exactly what he said because Justin confides in him for a reason, ect ect.     &nbsp;  He did give me a lot of good advice though. I know him and Heather had a hella serious relationship going on... and shes the reason he wants no more from us net chicks. She fucked him over bad from what everyone tells me. Said if I cared about him enough I could probably get him, but it would take a lot of work and shit. He also told me that out of every girlfriend Justin has ever had I was the only one he thinks will treat Justin the way he should be treated. Course, I dated Justin before when I was drunk half the time and didn't appreciate him half as much as I do now that I'm sober and clean. He told me a lot of flattering stuff on my character, how not everyone can do that and stuff and it takes a lot to be able to do it. And that he really hopes me and justin get back together, blah blah.     &nbsp;  *sighs* I told him that the main thing I want is for Justin to be happy. If its with some other girl then okay. Justin has been through a lot of shit in his life and hes always treated me a hella lot better then I deserved at times (except for the other night but we were both bitchy, and i failed to note that.). I mean, he is seriously the only guy that has treated me so good. Even IRL guys didn't treat me the way he did. Misha would fucking make me feel stupid all the time and like I was less then him. I hated that shit. Justin doesn't. Justin is always making me laugh, and hes a hella big goof ass so we're normally acting pyscho. I'm happy where we are at now. If I can still talk to Justin, and still somehow be in his life,... well I'm happy. Yeah, I care for him. Yeah, I want him. But I'd much rather him be with someone IRL and fall in love and have a happily ever after then be with me and that not turning into a happily ever after. I know I'm always talking about wanting one though. A happily ever after, that is. And for awhile I was caught up in my dream of it. I just think I've matured a lot and I realize,... some people are better off without you. No matter how bad it hurts.     &nbsp;  Christ, see how awful I'am. I'm listening to a poppy emo song. Although, it is an amazing song... I just don't like the dude that sings it. Okay, so yeah I wanna screw him but thats different lol. Most chicks wanna screw Justin Timberlake. Those sexy muscles and lips... Anyways "Gone" kicks ass. And now another depression pop emo song comes on. "Emotions" by Destiny Child.     &nbsp;  I confuse people so often. I'm just so versatile when it comes to music... Like there is this one song the Backstreet Boys sing that just tears me apart on one of there CDs. When I was with Adam I would listen to that over and over again. It's about bestfriends who fall in love and it fucks everything up... and I used to sing "Dear Diary" and some other song by Britney Spears to Adam all the time. He used to make me sing it over and over again, trying to see the difference cause I can flip my voice around a lot. Making sure I wasn't using a tape lol.Oh yeah, Kim, the chick who used to be my bestfriend and who dated Adam while I was with him as well, came on yesterday for the first time in years. We started talking about Adam and I told her about his kid and she goes, "That could have been my kid!!!"     &nbsp;  Kinda pissed me off. Oh well, I'm over that. I still think about him but he was my first love, so yeah. I don't think you ever stop thinking about your first love. I really don't think about him except when I start writing about him in my story. Otherwise I'm either wistfully thinking of Justin or feeling bad for all the people Misha must be flipping out on. Guy wise,... life wise... *sighs*. One day I will be a very happy chickadee. I will have a killer home, awesome healthy figure, good grades, and lots of kickass friends. One day I'll even fall in love although I highly doubt that'll be anytime soon. There is only one guy I'd be willing to give up singleton for and he doesn't want me. Ugh, I hate my self esteem. My mind gets all twisted about everything and the conclusion is always, "Because I'm fat." I know that isn't the case here, but thats what keeps fucking popping up in my head.     &nbsp;  My feet are yet again screaming at me for a day on the treadmill. I really should start wearing shoes on that thing. I guess going 4 and 5 mphs without a shoes isn't exactly smart... but I fucking hate shoes. They are pretty to look at in my closet but besides that? Psh. Forget it.I'm going to go see a doctor soon about this thing on my foot. It's on my heel and I don't know wtf it is. Before it was so tiny if I wasn't always massaging my feet there is no way I'd of noticed it. It's like this little bubble inside my foot where a bubble shouldn't be. It was like hella small and kinda stung if I pushed it in too much. Like a sharp stabbing sensation. Well, that was about a month ago that I first noticed it and it's gotten much bigger. You can see it now. My heel is always this reddish color cause of the treadmill nowadays but theres a small bubble sized white circle with a greyish circle in the middle of that. I don't have to push down to feel it either, I can just run my finger over it and feel it protruding a little bit. It still aches but its a bigger ache, not as sharp since it's bigger and covers more ground. We were gonna try to make an appointment today but my social worker never called. It fucking hurts walking on it sometimes and it's irking me. She better call tomorrow.The poor white bulldog was being talked about this morning. She will try to sell it for atleast 200 hundred since its not walking that well. I also heard her saying over the phone," Well Crystal wants it too. And so does this one girl at Faith's work, so who knows what I'll do." I don't think Mo would let me have her though. She is the prettiest bulldog I've ever seen,... and I would hate for her to go to a home where they wouldn't know how to take care of her or not know how to do therapy with her. If your not willing to get a little shit on your hands while you exercise her in the bath tub, that you don't understand.     &nbsp;  Well, I guess Mo is working night shift tonight so you guys won't hear what the outcome was. Oh well! I'll just call her tomorrow first thing in the morning since she goes to work at like 2 pm. Well,... thanks for listening to my rambling. MWAH!!  
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ever since i was little i knew i wasnt going to live a very long life. i still know it at the age of 16. of course, i have ambitions and i plan to go to college. i want to become a vet and start a really big business for unwanted animals. the pretty ones ill send to humane societys because those are taken quickly. the ones without a home. well, those will come with me. animals just like me.  i know that im meant to LIVE though. its hard to explain though. i mean.. life is so... amazing. the pain. the suffering. what an adventure. most people dont know half the #### ive been through. most people never will. but then again millions know that and much worse. foster care is a scary as #### thing. especially the group homes. those are awful. but ive been in it since november when my father tried to strangle me and DHR saved me. i lost all of my clothes, my belongings. and here i am. here. my grandmother is trying to get custody of me but she lives in georgia and it was alabama that i was living in before.   ive lived with grams for years though. its just that when pa pa got sick i moved in with my uncle cause mo couldnt take care of me since she was always in jacksonville with pa. bo was nice and all  but he couldnt keep me forever. so i moved in with my mother. my mother's husband hates me and my mother cant live without a husband so a few months later i was #### kicked to rickys, my fathers.  he once told me he got a few people pregnant in texas. i honestly think those kids are lucky. they dont have to know how awful a man he truly is.  and then there is misha. he was a good friend of mine when i lived in kingsland and he wrote me a letter after my gramps died saying how when he saw me again he realized he truly loved me, yaddah yaddah. i was thrilled. he had been my bestfriend for years.  big mistake. never date your bestfriend.  i do think this is such a great adventure though. i mean yeah it hurts a lot. i hate that i cant be home for another month, maybe even two. now its all up to paperwork. on the 13th the homestudy will be done and then we go to court. of course the paperwork has to go back through before court.  then i will be crystal e. helton.  in my head though, i already am.  im changing my middle name. i hated it. i want ella because ella is such a pretty name and Ella Enchanted was one of my favorite books and still is.  but misha though. he has continued calling me, writing me, ect. since he first told me he loved me on october 31st 2003 he has wrote me a letter ATLEAST once a week and often twice. throughout all the homes he was there. supporting me.  and now im breaking up with him. now im ruining the best relationship ive ever had.  why??  because of me. there is something wrong with me. i dont think i was meant to have relationships. i mean it. i mean i love him but as a bestfriend. i HATE it when he touches me. i hate it even more when he kisses me. he makes me want to vomit.  vomit, vomit, vomit.  and hes so great. hes going to grow up to be rich as hell. hes going to get a full tuition to some fancy new york college for filming and become the new peter jackson.  and i will be a hermit with 100 cats living in a broken down house with no plumbing and primitive lighting.  no kidding.  no. ill be a vet. an amazing vet. ill have exotic animals in my very own house. ill start my business. ill continue photography and do some small films. i dont want to be a director. but i do enjoy filming things. im really good, actually.  actually, im pretty much really good at everything i do.  which makes my life all the more awful.  maybe im just a baby. because i have the most amazing grandmother in the world and i cant get over the fact that i have her. it scares me sometimes to think i might lose her. i cant see life without her. oh #### im gonna cry.  i. will. be. more. then. that.  ill be amazing. beautiful. intelligent.  oh wait, i already am.  i just have to keep thinking that.  this diet pill is amazing though. i came here for a visit but i have to go back to alabama on the 6th. maybe ill be okay.  im going to miss home. and my cats. and my dog.  *sighs*.  but you know what else.  i have to quote  "to die would be an awfully big adventure."  i wont think of that though even though it eats at me all the time. i wont think of that.  i wont think of that.  i wont.  ill keep my head up and ill be okay.  i will.  i  have  to be okay.  crys.
      
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i just decided to take a chance on this blog... you know. since laurell k hamilton has one too.   i dont have much to say yet. ill post in a few minutes when im done glancing around this site. just wanted to see how it looked in a post.  i hope this is better then livejournal.  crys
      
</post>


</Blog>