<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My little laptop has decided it doesn't like me, and has stopped working.  After a complicated phonecall with Dixon's customer service youth training scum (sample dialogue: "Hi, my laptop has stopped working." "What's wrong with it?" "It... doesn't work." "Oh, right.  Why's that, then?"), I arranged for the lovely people of DHL (or was it DHSS?) to come and pick it up.  So, they posted me a little brown box a day or two before collection, and I packed it away nicely.  Delivery day came, and now my laptop has been taken to wherebouts unknown by a burly man with a fake-looking moustache called Kevin (the man, not his moustache... I don't think it had a name and, if it did, I was too busy keeping an eye on the scary owner).  Problem is, I have no idea when it is coming back... various calls to Dixon's have resulted in the conclusion that it may turn up sometime this year.  Helpful fellows, customer service people.  I MISS MY LAPTOP!  Well, I miss being able to scour the net for obscure things at 2am. Right now, I am relying on the internet cafe (and the lovely ladies that run it) next door to work for my web fix. Thankfully, due to some expert flirting on my part, said internet cafe ladies don't charge me for my time online. I hope they don't want some free books... 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bored.  It's my day off work today, and here is a run-down of what I have done.  Woke up at 11:30am (after finally falling asleep at 5am). Went to bathroom, and answered the call of nature. Put TV on, realised that I'd have to watch "This Morning" or some other lame-ass morning magazine show, and wept silently. Turned TV off. Bumbled about the flat, avoiding eye-contact with my washing up. Text some people; got no response (except an invite to go feed the ducks, which I declined due to the effort on my part that would have involved). Went online. Went offline, utterley bored. Looked at my Dvd collection. Went back to bed. Got up. Got dressed, and went to Tesco. Bought things that I don't need and that are bad for me anyway- to wit, a chocolate fudge cake and a "meat" pie.&nbsp; I don't know what "meat" it is, but it has 20% less fat.&nbsp; Less fat than what, I don't actually know since it didn't specify. Went home. Went online.  So, here I am. Still bored.  I need&nbsp; a hobby.&nbsp; Maybe I'll take up archery. I think I'd be a good twanger. "TWANG!"   I wonder what this "meat" is? 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Every so often, my limbs seem really heavy.  I can be at work, and it feels as if my legs and arms have weights hanging from them.  I never do any physical activity to warrant this, so I can only put it down to one of three things:  1) I am dying &nbsp; 2) My diet is so poor that it affects my health and stamina and, therefore, makes me feel drained all the time &nbsp; 3) There is a faction of invisible gremlins who tie heavy invisible things to my limbs.   I think we all know which I'll go for... those pesky gremlins! What would Murray Futterman say? &nbsp; "Hey, Billy..." 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The sky is, if you hadn't noticed, kinda big. &nbsp; So why&nbsp;do metal machines crash into each other every so often?  "Captain, that cloud out there looks awfully like a pla....argh!" CRASH! BURN!  Etc. 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am getting more and more concerned with the growing hatred I have for all human life... other than my family/friends.   Maybe it comes from working in shops, bars and customer service environments. I just have no patience for people anymore. Or should that be, I have no patience for customers?   People with stupid questions ("I saw this book on telly, it was blue, do you sell it?"), smelly old people, bad mothers with screaming kids, tramps sleeping in our comfy chairs, thieves, thieving tramps, annoying teenagers, snogging couples, middle-aged fake-tan too-much-cheap-bling women, office girls, middle aged men trying to talk to me about naval history, skanky sci-fi fans, BEARDED MEN WHO FAKE DISABILITY AND RIDE AROUND IN THOSE LITTLE MOBILITY BUGGY THINGS SMELLING OF WEE, bearded women, people asking to "borrow" a carrier bag, people demanding to know why we don't stock some obscure book they want ("I can't believe you don't stock this author; he is a bestseller in the field of bee-keeping!"), people putitng books back in random places (often upside down or, even worse, ontop of the shelf so it then sliiiiiiiiiiiiides behind the entire bookshelf and sits on the floor where it gathers dust until I -and only I because nobody else gives a toss- go around on my hands and knees digging them out), people who go to Mcdonalds and then come to our shop to fucking eat it and then leave their wrappers and foul-stench all over the place, people who wander up to the till with a book that is "a gift" for someone and then want a discount ("I got you this book for your birthday.... don't care if you like it 'coz I got it cheap!"),  people who spend an evening on Amazon.com and come in with a list of books they want... and then say "They are American so you probably can't get them"...THEN ORDER THEM ONLINE, FUCKO!, people who say "I want this book, but it's out of print, can YOU get it?" (Erm, what do they think 'out of print' means?), the shopping centre (yeah, that is "centre", Americans!) secuirty people who do NOTHING AT ALL except poke their fat heads around the door at 9am on a wednesday morning and ask "Any trouble?"...................   I love my job.   
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hula Hoops are great. But not weird mutant ones. They are evil. EVIL! EEEEEVIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIILLLLL!  And I know I shouldn't start a sentance with "But", but hell.&nbsp; Bollocks to it. 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should go to bed.   
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If I hear the phrase "lady garden" ONE MORE TIME... I will kick said person, whoever says it, in their poxy "lady garden"! &nbsp; I mean, come on! If you don't like saying what it is called, why talk about it at all? *sigh* &nbsp; This is all because of someone on a current reality tv show... I HATE THEM!  I get addicted, and lose weeks of my life. &nbsp; I am so weak... 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I HATE SATURDAYS!  Well, working in a shop on Saturday, anyway..... bloody teenagers stomping about reading the sex books and startling the old ladies looking at "Reader's Digest" cookbooks, and then even more bloody teenagers shouting off of our balcony (yeah, SUCH a high-class shopping centre I work in... ) and then wondering why we kick them out.  I will rant about this time and time again. *sigh*  Am I allowed to hit them? 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is it me, or are they all fuckers? Slap 'em all, that's what I say. 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just saw "shrek 2". Was highly entertaining, and had far more in it for us jaded, cynical adults to enjoy than there was for the kids.... which is a good thing, lets be honest.  When I was a kid, I very quickly went from watching things like the Animal Olympics cartoon, and Pete's Dragon, onto Star Wars and Indy Jones, and then tthings like Terminator and Alien....  I wonder if that has something to do with me being a bit of a weirdo, now I come to think of it. I mean, I watched John Carpenter's "The Thing" when I was about seven years old.....  Hmm. Don't report my mum to social services, thanks!  :)  
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've become more and more concerned of late with my constant habit of having chewing gum and swallowing it when it loses it's taste, as opposed to spitting it out like some unruly yob.  Now, I do wonder if I've a HUGE backlog of about 20 years worth of gum wedged in my belly or - horror of horros - my bowls somewhere.  Anyone know a good proctologist?
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After months, I finally got my bed fixed. HURRAH!  Y'see, I'd moved into my flat in November, and the bed was broken. It is one of those "up-into-the-wall" beds, since I live in a studio (flat, that is). The bed itself was sleepable-on, but the mechanism to put it into the wall was faulty, so I had a bed in the middle of the room all day.  Being me, a lazy so and so, I thought "Stuff it" and left it down. For seven months.  Now, thanks to Brian the Builder (he has a brother called Bob, I swear), I can put the bed into the wall again.  Of course, I won't do any such thing because I am a lazy so and so.  Just thought I'd share....  Was my day off today. Spent it arguing with women, which is nice. 
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I work in a shop (yeah, yeah, I'm 27... so what!?!).  We have more than one till point and, at the end of the day, close them off one at a time. They then get a sign on them, saying that the till is closed and that the customers need to pay downstairs.  We understand that people may not expect a till to be closed but, most of the time, they see the sign and wander off to the correct place. Sometimes, someone will stand there hopefully for thirty seconds or so before heading to another till.  Now today, beating all previous dumb customers by some margin, we had a bloke come up to one of the closed tills and lean AROUND the "Till Closed" sign. He put his books down on our side of th esign, and looked at whoever it was serving at the time expectantly.  I see stupid people... 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A long time ago, I first put my own little website on the net using the my SEGA DREAMCAST (which had net access, obviously).  I have since forgotten EVERYTHING to do with HTML... I'm now going through a steep learning curve to get my site looking lovely.  So, for those of you who've had a look at it, I'm sorry it looks lame!  *grin*
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy, I figured I'd take this first "blog" post to briefly explain the "Norton" part.  That is just a never-used nickname, courtesy of Los Chimpos.  So there!  Anyway, it's late and I'm tired... today has mostly been spent trying to remember HTML codes so I can start my web pages. *sigh*  Off to work tomorrow.... Books Etc (plug plug). God bless the old ladies and their romance books, and the theives who take everything but romance books!  X
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, home at last after five days away at me mum's.  This means that, in about 12 hours, I'll be thoroughly sick of work and chavs and thieving scum. *sigh*  I spent abpout three hours riding around on my step-dads ride-on lawn mower, and got thoroughly sunburnt shoulders for my efforts. At least the fields were cropped short! I kept catching myself singing "I've got a brand new combined oarvester" though.  Ooh ah, and all that!  Gonna go to sleep now, and get myself into chav-defense bookseller mode... wish me luck! 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY! I'm sitting in my step-dad's pc room, with my little brother and sister runnign around, a horse in the background, some dogs, a duck or two, a couple of bats, an owl, and a mooing cow somewhere.  I am safe in the knowledge that I am pretty much safe from chaviness by a clear ten miles at least -the nearest town, Peterborough, is very chav-friendly, but I think I'm safe out here in the sticks! HEH  Annoyed today. Was supposed to get an email from someone at work, about an internal post that has come up. No word as of yet, and deadline is sunday. If I wasn't lazy, I'd pick up the phone. But, I am, so stuff it.  I'm off to ride a horse. LATERS! 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm off to see my mum and family in their HUGE house, out in the countryside this week.  I'll be riding a horsey, and a quad bike, all for the benefit of my little brother and sister, who seem to find it funny when I get injured. Hmm...  Heh. Looking forward to it, and I will post a pic or two if I can. I'll be all manly with a throbbing beast between my legs!   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a bitch of a day at work. It was a good day, in the sense that it passed quickly. Unfortunatley, most of that passing involved OLD PEOPLE! I swear to whoever you swear to in such circumstances that all I did today was either serve, offer fantastic customer service to, or roll my eyes at old people.  Why do the women all have TERRIBLE make-up, and even worse frizzy hair? I hate them! They all smell of Parma Violets, or Oil of Ulay (or however it was re-branded).  Trust me, the smell of too much moisturiser on piss-stained skin isn't pleasant.  At least the blue-rinse seems to have died a death. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the week has got itself off to its usual wonderful start. *sigh*  Woke up, and the sunshine has left us - still warm, but raining and over-cast. Which was nice.  Got into work, and it started. Miserabl rep, trying to sell me some veyr dull "literary" fiction.   "This is Chav Town, madam, are you aware that the only thing people around here read are their giros and z-list celebrity biographies?"  "But this got a fantastic review in the Hamburg Reader... many Germans said they would think about buying a copy!"  "NEXT!"   After sending the rep on her merry way,  I had many dumb customers asking dumb things. "Is this book here, on the counter, that says "FREE SAMPLE" free?" "Where is upstairs?"  My reply, as always; "Erm, upstairs."  I went to lunch, and had the pleasure of missing the thieving chavs that came in to steal our DVDs and threaten one of my managers. Scum. They left empty handed, with many "evils" in the staff's direction.  Finally, ignoring more dumb customers, at the end of the day as I was up a ladder putting books away, a charming-odoured trampy man was looking around the staff-side of the till! As I approached, and asked what he was doing, he hurried to the customer side, saying he was looking at our leaflets for Theatre Tokens. THEATRE TOKENS! THIS DRUNK WANNABE THIEF COULDNT EVEN SPELL THEATRE, LET ALONE BELIEVABLY BE A THEATRE GOER!  *Sigh* He left, and minutes later we closed the shop and went home, as that was the time and all that.  To top things off, on the bus home I had to put up with some teenage wannabe Eminem types performing various "human beatbox" noises all the way home.  Joy.  
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, you net monkeys, coming soon to a DVD store near you, THE GOONIES! Yes, the best "kids" film of the 80's s being finally released on DVD in October (2004).  If you haven't yet seen it, you deserve a slap! I'm so happy that this is coming to DVD, I'm gonna go have a bath and go to bed.  Hey, what do you expect me to do? *grin* 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Can somebody please tell me the point of Jean Claude Van Damme?  Have you ever WATCHED his films, and his so-called "acting"? It worries me that a high-kicking gimp like him can get a film made, when there MUST be better actors and film-makers out there?  Thankfully, it seems as if he has started to vanish into the world of "Where Are They Now" celebrity. Thank God!  The reason for this is a boring Sunday afternoon, and one of his "films" on tv.  
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We at work have come to a startling conclusion, following months of study.  In a few short weeks, our customers should be looking fit and healthy. They should be at the peak of physical fitness, infact, and should have skin that glows. They should also be dressed to impress, with not a hair out of place or a mis-matched colour to be seen. Finally, they should all be eloquently spoken.  The reason for this? The stupidly-high sales figures for the following books:  YOU ARE WHAT YOU EAT   WHAT NOT TO WEAR EATS SHOOTS AND LEAVES   God, if only the chavs and chavettes would actualy bother READING some of the books that they steal to sell and pay for thier burberry addiction, the youth of today might have something resembling intelligence!  I am aware my spelling is bad, but it's gone two in the morning. So stuff ya! 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I'm sick of them.  *sigh*  Just wanted to share.  
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just spoke to someone who I thought hated me.  To say it's made the sunshine break through the clouds that hover above me would be an understatement. 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, a Big Brother is over for another year. I WILL ENTER NEXT YEAR! Mark my words!   On "Big Bro", after everyone had left the house, they had one of those oh-so-wonderful montages where they show clips from the previous 10 weeks. Now, that's cool. BUT THEY USED ONE OF THE SONGS I WANT AT MY FUNERAL! Bastards!  "Good Riddance (Time Of Your Life)" by Greenday... it's such a perfect song for a funeral, and I will have it played at mine. I've often wondered what music I would have played. It seems the "in" thing to play three songs; one as people enter and get seated, one half-way through, and one at the end as the coffin is burnt and the body is incinerated and the bones crushed by huge metal pins because the flames aren't hot enough to actually turn a human body to ash.  Anyway, onto my three songs. As mentioned before, I want the Greenday song played. Maybe "Outside" by Stained.... I KNOW, I KNOW, everybody hates that band, with their lead singer always going on about his depression, but that song sums me up.  And, being honest, it is one of the few songs that I can listen to and cry to when I am feeling the need to let go and sob for a bit. What?  Am I the only one who bawls like that? Shit.  Anyway...songs. Well, I always liked the flying theme from ET, but my Nan had that at her funeral and I wouldn't want to infringe on her memory in the minds of my family, so not that.  The Smashing Pumpkins had a cool instrumental at the beginning of the double-cd they released. Can't remember the name of it, though.    So, there you go. Three songs that won't be played at my funeral, since I'll be dead and will have no say in the matter. And will have no doubt ostracized (spelling?) entire family by then, so balls to it!  
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got back from bowling. I went with four other people (three girls and a guy), all of whom are aged between 17 and 20. Me, being 27, felt very old and, infact, almost fatherley. Which was odd... but I'm getting more and more used to that.  Anyway, it was kinda fun, and I won one of the two games we played.  Now, the problem with any form of outdoor activity these days is the increasing number of CHAV SCUM ( urlLink http://www.chavscum.co.uk ) that you find out and about. Bowling, naturally the home of the chav, was a test of my patience.  Next to us (on lane 30 of the Heathrow Bowl, fact fans) was a gaggle of lady chavs, or chavettes. Aged between 14 and about 18, they were dressed in regulation Chav uniform of sports wear and Burbury. All of them were smoking (actually smoking AS THEY BOWLED, which was quite impressive to see!), swearing, and giving us "evils".  Actually, that was quite amusing; everytime one of the girls I went with moved to pick up a ball, one of the chavettes would jump up and reach for the ball, flapping about, or they would all just sit there and stare.  I mean, I'm 27 years old, and all I could think about was "Oh, fuck off." I feel soliled by their chavness.  And when they "pulled" some chav lads who were bowling somewhere further along, it got worse. The overdose of gold chains hanging on the outside of their shirts, and their irritatingly white trainers... it made me have to go and play "House of the Dead 3" in the manky chav-lite arcade just to release the tension.  *sigh*  So, that was the fun I had bowling. I can't wait to go again!  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't bother going to see Hellboy, as I knew would be the case. Too much effort involved, to be honest.  Anyway, various people (well, two- the evil Sarah, who is leaving work for pastures new and is enjoying the depression this is causing me, and Tony the gay-looking comic book geek that we all know and love (more on him later)) have seen the movie on pirate dvd and have told me that it isn't very good. So, I probably did the right thing.  I realise I used double brackets up there. Do I care? No.  I hate pirate movies. Not movies with pirates in, but pirated copies of films. I just like watching big movies on the big screen, not on a semi-clear dvd copy. Maybe I'm a movie snob?  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, hurrah and huzzah. My laptop came back today. No more need for unneccesary flirting with the internet cafe ladies...  DHL man came and we had a ten-minute one-sided conversation about his wife and his hard drive (was he coming onto me?), and then he thankfully left me alone to open the box and whip it out (erm...).  It was a little dusty and scuffed for some reason, with what looked suspiciously like biscuit crumbs over it... if you can remember the fat computer nerd Dennis from Jurrasic Park, I imagine someone similar working and drooling and stuffing their face over my little laptop at Packard Bell HQ  Anyway... I have it back, so praise the lord and all that.  Off bowling now... something I havent done since about 1999. Oh well. I guess somebody has to lose; it may as well be me!  Remember people: Worship those monkeys! 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This really bugs me: How many times, in the course of one transaction, do you think the average book-buyer will say "Thank you", or a variation thereof?  On average, and I have worryingly worked this out on a dull afternoon, my average sale consists of one of us (seller or buyer) saying a grand total of six "Thank you" 's!  One charming, if slightly odd-smelling, old lady bought some romance books and said the magic words a total of nine times. NINE TIMES!  Jesus, just say "thanks" once, will you!  Hand me the books, they say thanks. I scan them and say the amount, and they say thanks. I take their money/card, and they say thanks. I bag their stuff, they say thanks. I hand them their change and receipt(s), and they say thanks. I hand them their books, and they say thanks.  It is possible not to say anything to people except the words "Thank you", and "That will be (insert amount), please".  Which I have also done on a VERY dull afternoon, just to amuse myself.  So, what do we learn from this? Use the words "Thank you" sparringly, or they lose all meaning.  Okay, it isn't a great moral, but it'll do! 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have the invite to go and see "Hellboy" tonight, at a vaguley private showing by 'Titan', the publisher of semi-decent quality graphic novels and such like.  I really, really can't be arsed.  This is worrying me... all I am going to do after work is go home and watch the new "Adam and Joe" dvd that has just came out. I really need to get a life, don't I?  *sigh*  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sitting in a net cafe, on my lunch, and the charming young lady next to me, dressed in black and thoroughly goth, is looking at a Stephen Gately website.  Now, fact-fans, as we all know, he was the rabbit-loving one from Boyzone.  I don't know... these wannabe goths everywhere.  Tsk. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, sometimes, all I can think about is burying an exe into the heads of my so called friends.  Wonder if I'd get away with it, saying that the axe carried no warning label against chopping people in the face with it?  Hell, I could sue the axe-making company......  Hmm. I may have stumbled on a new get-rich-quick scheme..... 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to feed the ducks today...  In Stockley Park, a bizarre business-cum-leisure complex, they have a bar, a lake, a gym and so on... many upper-class Uxbridge types go there to get fit, drink heartily, play golf and so on.  Being a lower-class Uxbridge type, I just go to feed the ducks in the nicest place in the area.... not one shopping trolley or drunken tramp to be seen.  Hurrah!  Anyway, I started happily feeding the ducks, and then the fish that came up for some food, and then, OH JOY OF JOY, a little turtle appeared! So, I fed him some pizza and off he went.  Okay, he didnt get pizza because he wasn't a ninja turtle. He got a bit of soggy bread instead which, now I think about it, probably doesnt compare to a nice deep pan but there you go!  Also, being a hot day, I wore some breezy cool trousers and a sleevless top.... "Top up the tan", I thought.  Now, I have a white body and red shoulders, and vaguley brown arms. *sigh* I need a hanky for my head. 
    
</post>


</Blog>