<Blog>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            Go to the link to see more of my photos. 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                 Well since the last entry, not much has happened, well nothing has happened really. I went fenceing on Wednesday, can't wait to go again, save one thing they're are campers there! There are two of them who just happen to take the junior class, the class which is before mine, argah! Luckily this is there first time fenceing so they are not in my class.... *few*.              This week I did one of my annual ufology searches. I turned up a few good hits, but I am starting to think that I have found most of the good ones. Here are some of my finds so far: http://ufos.about.com/ http://www.ufology.org.uk/   (to bad its perely british and the despise anyone else....) http://www.scifi.com/ufo/     (a surprisingly good site) http://www.x-ppac.org/main.htm     (they scare me at times, very secret society like, even though they are against them...?)  http://www.cufos.org/ http://ufoinfo.com/roundup/  (page looks dumb, is one of the best, to bad it looks dumb) http://www.conspiracyarchive.com/    (not souly by any means Ufology, but an okay page)                  And just cause I have started nameing links, here are a few others which I enjoy, and/or participate in: http://www.adiumx.com/ http://www.scifi.com/ http://www.nationstates.net/ http://www.nationstates.net/cgi-bin/index.cgi/target=display_nation/nation=the_vi_melon     (my country, or actually Nation-state in the above)  http://sasroleplay.proboards33.com/   (this is one that I participate in, and do NOT enjoy yet, cause well, nothing has happened, at all, but meh, I feel obligated I am friends with one of the admins and I mean there are only like four people there right now.) http://www.wicca.com/celtic/cc002.htm  http://wicca.com/celtic/forums/     ( a great, no the best, forum out there!)          Today my pop and I ran thousands upon thousands of errands, like we do EVERY sunday, One of the places we stopped was the Harly Davidson store, to get his brother, my uncle, a girft for his birthday. Well I am getting the feeling that my father wants to join my uncle in Hoggness, and get a bike....... Eeew. That would crush me, well not really but it would mean I could not go auto-crossing with my dad, and thats fun. So, yeah, as other people wine about how horible their lives are on there boards, I am winning about how conflicting my good life is.....  geee, I better stop before I hurt my self, eew.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I worked today, I worked from about 8 am till 5:45ish pm, THANK GOODNESS THEY LEFT EARLY! I am, well DEAD tired, sorta over did it at the end of the day i guess, running about, holding children, ugah, pain. Need advil... well not really since I would rather be in pain then take that stuff, but meh. Today I also, well  did nothing but work and watch an hour of TV....  grrr, another boreing day in the day of the life of. Haha. Well tomorrow, I go fencing after work, YEAH! Hmm, I guess I should not post on this EVERY day, its pretty lame when I do, meh.   Note: from now on post only about things which are remotely interesting.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, today was very uneventful, I did chores and fiddled with the sensor I installed in my dads car yesterday. I also went through my dads entire CD collection, who knew the pops had good taste in music! WOW!? Well, save the peter paul and marry, ergah... * shivers *. But so from his collection I took two Led Zeppelin albums, all four Woodstock Albums, Tommy, by the Who, Queens greatest hits... why did I take that one? A Crosby Stills, Nash and Young CD, Hell Freezes Over by the Eagles and a Billy joel CD. I also lifted weights today, out of boredom, I really do strange things when I am .  O, I also made a fool of my self on the Celtic Connection Forum.  *sigh* I am very hapy that I did not have to go to work today, but tomorrow I go back to chaseing the little menases of our society from 8:00am till 6:00pm,  Yee Haa! 
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well Happy fourth of July! I just decided to start this blog this evening, after watching fireworks... mmm, explosives. I do not know how offten I will post on it, but I hope to make a habit of it. 
    
</post>


</Blog>