<Blog>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey... is this thing on???  Dude, the ability to update The Red Zone via telephone is amazingly clutch.  And amazingly dangerous.    Oh, faithful readers... if I start replacing my typical drunk dials or drunk text messages with phone calls to this page, it could get ugly.  So sit back, turn up your speakers and enjoy!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome to my new spot on the internet.  As some of you know, I used to have a nice place over at JayLowe.com called The Red Zone.  Let's just pretend that was a pilot for this column.  I'm going to try to do a better job with Inside the Red Zone, or "ITRZ".  By the way, if anyone can come up with a better name, please feel free to send it my way.  Anyway... in the words of Scott D., now we go!    When people talk about hot actresses, why isn't Rene Russo ever brought into the discussion?   Is it any wonder that Harris, the old pitcher from Major League, uses Vaseline, KY Jelly and a little "jal-uh-pee-no" to fool hitters and eventually gets rocked by the Yankees?  He's not throwing harder than 50 mph.   Normally, I cheer for the underdog.  That's part of the reason I cheer for whoever is playing the Yankees, the Lakers, the Raiders, the Cowboys, etc.  But with Lance Armstrong gunning for his 6th straight Tour de France victory, I'm pulling for him big-time.  Call it a little American patriotism shining through on the 4th of July.     When Cerrano hits the ball out to tie the game against the Yankees, why does he carry the bat with him?  This has always bothered me.  I realize he's got a relationship with his bats ("hats for bats") but still.  Only an idiot would carry their bat around the bases like that.   I'd like everyone know that I cooked chicken in a skillet this weekend.  Twice! I used olive oil, a lemon paper marinade.  I even cooked rotini pasta, a long time Big Red speciality, at the same time.  This is pretty revolutionary for me.   I've been getting a lot of crap lately from Bertsch and Heather who have been hammering me for not seeing some "classic" movies.  So I've never seen Rocky, so I've never seen Sixteen Candles, so I've never seen Pretty in Pink.  Why is this a big surprise?  These movies were made before I was 10.  Secondly, so what if I haven't seen them?  I've never heard anyone say these were some of the best movies ever made.  I realize Rocky won the Oscar for Best Picture.  So did Titanic.  What's the big deal?    I've got a bone to pick...   ESPN has been doing their best and worst lists of the last 25 years.  First of all, didn't they just do this?  Secondly, are they on crack?  They did their top 25 sports movies of all-time and Rudy came in at #24.  24???? Are you kidding?  So here are my top five sports movies of all-time:  Honorable mention:  Bull Durham, Jerry Maguire, Tin Cup.  5.  Miracle.    This movie overcomes a major personal obstacle. I saw this movie while on easily the worst blind date of my life. This girl will remain nameless, but let's call her Amy.  Amy, who was a big hockey fan, wouldn't shut the hell up during the whole movie. She kept asking when Gordon Bombay was going to show up, asking when the guys were going to do the Flying V.  Listen, if she didn't want to see the movie in the first place, she should have said so.  But that's neither here, nor there.  Very good movie. It goes to show that no matter where I am, what I'm doing, the U-S-A chant is pretty powerful.  4.  Major League.    So many great lines.  Very hard to put this movie as low as four.  Rick Vaughn, Jake Taylor, and the most under-rated character in the movie, manager Lou Brown ("there's two or three all-stars on this team").  It's an all-star cast with a young Wesley Snipes, Rene Russo in her first feature film, Charlie Sheen at his best, Bob Uecker doing his thing.  Well done from start to finish.  3.   Rudy.    I can't believe ESPN had this at 24.  It's a movie about true friendship and having your dreams come true.  You get a fat Jon Favreau, an angry Charles Dutton and a role so perfectly fitted for Sean Astin that he could never do anything else without having everyone say, "look, it's Rudy!".  When Rudy runs out onto the field for the kickoff, I get a lump in my throat.  Everytime.  I can't help it.  2.  Field of Dreams.    I was talking to my friend Sara a few weeks ago and she couldn't believed I liked this movie.  Couldn't understand why I'd ever want to watch it, much less watch dozens of times.  So I hung up on her.  I questioned whether our friendship was over.  To me, "You wanna have a catch?" still ranks as the most tear-jerking line in the history of American cinema.    1.  Hoosiers.    Obviously, this is a no-brainer.  I don't have to explain this.  Everyone knows how the story is going to end and yet, you're captivated.  The only downside is that Norman Dale is a bad game coach (how are you NOT going to give the last shot to Jimmy?!?).  Even so, Hoosiers sits atop this list, without a doubt.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink   
</post>


</Blog>