<Blog>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey there.   This evening I went to a Welcome Orientation for the RNC '04 in NYC.  I'm from across the hudson so I went to the event in Hackensack NJ at the BCRO on Main St.   The turnout seemed kind of small, but it was one of the earlier of the seminars scheduled for the day. My only real problem with it was the presentation was only 15 minutes long and they told us nothing.  Basically all they told us was to show up with the same IDs we came with for training and that the website will be updated later in the month, so go home and we'll see you soon. I for one hoped they would have discussed what we as volunteers would be doing other than working 6-8 hour shifts doing something "volunteer-like".     I created this Blog for everyone who's volunteered their time for either the re-election of our President, George W. Bush, or for the Republican National Convention.  I'm not affiliated with either organization, and this blog is not affiliated with their respective websites.  I'll post any relevant news about the RNC that I come aware of between now and the convention.  -
    
</post>


<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two years ago on this day I found out that my father was dead.&nbsp; I wasn't overly surprised by this news.&nbsp; He had had a few heart attacks in his day, so I assumed that was the cause.&nbsp; I was not particularly close to the man, so I wasn't all that upset.&nbsp; You see, my parents had been separated since shortly before my birth, and the divorce was finalized a year or two later.&nbsp; My mom had sole custody of me, he did of course have visitation rights which he seldom used.&nbsp; I can distinctly remember the half dozen or so times that I actually spent time with him.&nbsp;  My first impression of him was back in 82, or 83, I can never be sure since I was so young at the time.&nbsp; He came by to visit and he brought me a gift, a toy.&nbsp; As you well know, all small boys and most girls love toys and presents of all sorts.&nbsp;&nbsp; Well, dear old dad got me a doll.&nbsp; A Ken Doll with some weird shaving accessory (put his head under cold water and he has a five o'clock shadow, use the shaving accessories along with warm water to shave him).&nbsp; My initial reaction was "Gee thanks Dad..."&nbsp; or something to the effect.&nbsp; I was a rather intuitive child, so I made him feel better about himself by bringing a crappy toy.&nbsp; For chrissakes, I'm a boy!&nbsp; I don't play with Ken &amp; Barbie!!&nbsp;&nbsp; Enough about that sore episode.&nbsp; We'll flash-forward a few years and skip a visit or two, and go straight to the last few. In the summer of 1986 I spent several weeks down in Toms River with my aunt Sheila.&nbsp; She was my favorite aunt growing up as a child, and I would spend a few weeks with her every summer till I was around 10 or so.&nbsp; This particular summer I remember clearly.&nbsp; Aunt Sheila and I were going on a "special" trip.&nbsp; None of the other kiddies who were ever-present at the house were going on this trip.&nbsp; We told everyone we were going to Seaside, for a nice little jaunt on the boardwalk.&nbsp; To me, Sheila told me we were going to see my dad, and no-one really knows that he's in prison right now, except for her and a few others. You see, the reason for my parents breakup was that my dad was an alcoholic, and a very good one at that.&nbsp; The reason his whereabouts were a secret was that he was in jail.&nbsp; Apparently Dear Old Dad was on a bender, ran out of cash, and decided to hold up a liquor store.&nbsp; The only problem with his plan was a) he had a fake gun, b) he tried to rob a liquor store that he frequented regularly, and c) he wore no disguise.&nbsp;&nbsp; Definitly not a smart idea, but he went through with it anyway and wound up in the clink.&nbsp;  So here I am, seven years old, and about to enter a prison for the very first time to visit my incarcerated father.&nbsp; Can't you just see the mental scars forming?&nbsp; I don't remember much detail other than white linoleum flooring, beige painted prison bars, and lots of scary sounds.&nbsp; Dad promised to keep in touch with me, and write me letters regularly.&nbsp; I was apithetic, bored, and scared.&nbsp; I couldn't wait to get home.&nbsp;  That night I spoke to my mom about it, she asked me how I felt, I didn't know.&nbsp; I still don't know.&nbsp; It's an odd thing to come to terms with.&nbsp;&nbsp; Following the visit, i patiently awaited the promised letters from Dad.&nbsp; They never came.&nbsp; I was a bit disappointed.&nbsp; Not too much, for I learned at an early age, expect nothing from him.&nbsp;&nbsp; After a year or two, I mentioned the letters to my mom, and she let me know that he did in fact write me letters, but she did not want me to be exposed to a father in jail and have a constant reminder of it with the letters a-flowing.&nbsp; She wrote him and asked him to stop the letter writing, he complied.&nbsp; It wasn't until I was fourteen that I saw him again.&nbsp; This time at my uncle Kevin's funeral.&nbsp; He too was an alcoholic (alcoholism seems to be the family trade) and died of cirrosis of the liver.&nbsp; At the funeral Dad showed up once again, we spoke breifly.&nbsp; I noted how short the man seemed, he couldn't be an inch over 4'10" and I was already through puberty, so I had at least six inches on him.&nbsp; Once again did he say he'd stay in touch, he told me that I should come down to visit him.&nbsp; I said sure, why not?&nbsp; Though at the time I was in the midst of the hellish years of high school, only months away from my first real drug experience, so the visit thing never happened.&nbsp;&nbsp; Several months later on christmas morning I got a call, not from him, but from his companion (a woman I'd known growing up, though then she was married to another man) at first, telling me that my dad wanted to talk to me.&nbsp; That made me feel a bit uncomfortable, nonetheless I complied.&nbsp; We spoke again of "visits" and happy holidays and all the other small talk.&nbsp; That was it for my relationship with my father.&nbsp;&nbsp;  The next time I saw him was two years ago, in his coffin.&nbsp;  I hadn't seen the man in eight years, and I was starting to feel a lack for a dad.&nbsp; I made attempts at finding him, but without asking Mom, I didn't know how she'd react to it, so I thought it best to avoid the subject.&nbsp;&nbsp; I did some searches for him on the internet and such, but had no real luck.&nbsp; It's hard to find someone that you know so little about.&nbsp; I knew his name, but not his full name.&nbsp; I had the feeling that he was still in New Jersey, but that's about it.&nbsp; There are 8 Thomas McGoverns in new jersey, and about 89 T. McGoverns.&nbsp;&nbsp; That makes finding him hard.&nbsp; I thought about calling each listing and asking them if they had a son named Daniel, but that idea bothered me.&nbsp; So I kept to a passive search.&nbsp; I narrowed it down to a half dozen Thomas' and T's in southern New Jersey, and thats where I remained.&nbsp; I didn't know how to go any further, and so I gave up the search. My aunt Gail was the one who contacted us.&nbsp; She lived close by, and offered to drive me down to the funeral.&nbsp; Sure, I really wasn't up for a drive down there by myself, so I happily accepted.&nbsp; The drive down was long and tedious since we hit alot of shore-traffic on the parkway.  When we got there, I spent a lot of time wandering around, being introduced to people who I had met in my early childhood, or who knew my dad.&nbsp; It was a very surreal experience.&nbsp; All of these people knew him so well, and here I was, knowing very little of the man.&nbsp; I hadn't even found out how he died, and here these people were telling me more about the man than I had found out in my 23 years of existance.&nbsp; I felt angry and depressed, and I really wanted to leave, but I didn't.&nbsp; I kept my cool and listened to their stories, knowing that this was the only way I'd ever come to know the man who was partially responsible for my birth. The picture I had in my head matched rather closely to what everyone told me.&nbsp; He was a loser and he was good at it.&nbsp; They made it seem a lot better than that, but it was the underlying truth of it all, and I had accepted that much sooner than they had.&nbsp;  I learned the circumstances of his death eventually, my cousin took me on a ride, we got high, and she told me the details as best she could.&nbsp; I could only stare in disbelief.&nbsp; Dear Old Dad had wound himself up in jail again (i'm still not sure what exactly for, but I'm going to assume it was drug related after my cousin enlightened me about his last profession of drug-runner).&nbsp; After smoking cigarettes for so many years, he wound up with emphysema like his mom.&nbsp; Also like his mom, he tried smoking while hooked up to an oxygen tank.&nbsp; Oxygen &amp; fire mix quite well, the result is bigger badder flames.&nbsp; He inhaled fire, singed his lungs, and died of an infection, in jail.&nbsp; The best part of it all, I found out, was that he was soon to be released, but because of his accident, he was found to be in violation of the state-wide ban on smoking in prisons.&nbsp; Guilty of having contraband, no get out of jail card for you, Tommy.&nbsp; What was only a 6 month extension of his sentence turned out to be Life Without Parole.&nbsp;&nbsp;  Was he a bad father?&nbsp; Without a doubt.&nbsp; Did he try?&nbsp; Not hard enough.&nbsp; Will I forgive him?&nbsp; Forgiven and forgotten.&nbsp;&nbsp; This is my final goodbye to you&nbsp;Dad.&nbsp; I hope you rest in peace. &nbsp; &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Somehow this passed by everyone who doesn't read print media, but Edwards is no match against Cheney in any regard other than youth and looks. Edwards has little governmental experience and his only contributions to society have been as a tort lawyer who made millions. His political background is this: get elected as senator so I can make a bid on the presidency.  Cheney spent years in the House of Representatives, served as White House Cheif of Staff, Secretary of Defense, and currently the Vice Presidency. He'll eat Edwards alive at any debate the two hold.  Why would anyone think that George Bush is the type of person that'd drop his running mate just to gain some points in the polls? Has he ever done anything remotely like that? Unless you can find something that I haven't, the answer is no. There is a reason the Bush campaign is called Bush-Cheney '04, because they've been together since 2000, and they'll be together til 2008."  The other night I posted this reply on one of the forums I frequent.  urlLink ABSForums.com  It was in response to a thread on if/why Cheney should be dropped from the Bush ticket this November.  The idea has been floated around by many prominant (yet also fringe) politicians, most recently former Senator Alphonse D'Amato.  In hopes of either damaging or strengthening the ticket.    I've come to the conclusion that this has all come from John Kerry finally selecting his running mate, John Edwards of North Carolina.  Edwards you may remember from the Democratic Primaries as the fiery young Carolinian Senator running for President.  Not only was that his first attempt at running for a national office, it was his second attempt at ANY office. Edwards' lack of experience isn't just an attack on his record, it's a statement there of.    Does anyone remember Steve Forbes?  He ran for president against Clinton.  His only qualifications were that he was rich.  He had never won an election for anything except maybe Chairman of the Board on one of his many companies.   Somehow this unknown scion of the Forbes family became a serious candidate, if for just a few months.    Ross Perot was another one without public office experience, and he was mostly taken seriously throughout the whole election, even though he came in a very very very distant third back in 1992.    My questions to you are these:  Does the running mate matter?  Is experience such a big deal? My answers: yes and yes. The running mate is important and does matter, but the running mate is not an issue.  They're not the ones we're putting into the highest office, they're just a backup plan.  Experience is a necessary in all jobs.  Is it required in a VP?  Sure, they may just have to takeover as President.  
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just to let everyone know, my girlfriend went through her surgical procedure yesterday without a problem.  The precancerous cells are gone, she's not in much pain, and I feel a million pounds lighter now that we know everything will be fine.    Tonight, I was at the Welcome Orientation for volunteers of the Republican National Convention to be held later this year (August 30 - September 2  urlLink  )  I cannot wait till the convention. I'll tell more about this later.  I just felt the need to update again.  Tomorrow sometime I'll send a better update via email.  g'night.
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Maybe it's me, but I really don't get the whole blogging thing.  How do you sit there and share your life with everyone with a PC and internet access?  Are you interesting enough that we need to hear about your latest colonoscopy?  Unless you're doing it live on national television like Katie Couric, I don't think so.        Which leads me to my next question.  Are we that bored with the internet that we have to find people who are more boring than ourselves, or maybe more fucked up.  Do we like to read about people who are dying of cancer?  Do you like to hear about a girl's brutal upbringing of rape and drug abuse?  A young man's journey into schizophrenia?   These things are all Blogs of one sort or the other.   Why do we do it?      I am a very boring individual.  I work retail.  I have a girlfriend of 4 years.  I still live with mom.  I have no ambitions, yet my interests are all-encompassing.         Now, did I mention that my girlfriend is going into surgery in two days to have a cancerous growth cut from her cervix?   Or that my mother is a month shy of 50, has had one big heart attack, several minor strokes, survived cervical cancer, and has been HIV positive since 1987?        Not so boring, but it's still nothing major.  No one's dead yet, no one's been bedridden and hooked up to a ventilator. My life is very good.  I love my girlfriend, I love my mom.   I survive by helping others survive.  I'm there for them when they need me.  I am mostly helpless on my own.  I can't do laundry, pay my bills, or groom myself properly without one or the other telling me what to do.   But I can fix anything mechanical (at least until a real mechanic can get involved), an outstanding cook, and I also have extensive first aid & medical training (almost all of it self taught, but I've diagnosed things quicker than an MD and been correct!)      So, are the trials and tribulations of a pussy-whipped professional slacker momma's boy all that interesting?   You'll be the judge.  I'll get around to telling you all the horrid details of my life.  But first, things I've done that've been greatly appreciated by mom & girlfriend.          Took out old busted A/C in girlfriend's bedroom & replaced with new one.       Got dinner for girlfriend       Sex with girlfriend (several screaming orgasms for her, one nice blowjob for me, and a nice sexy shower together)       Mom's under the weather (summertime colds, they suck more than most)  Picked her up some Vic's vaporub cream and picked up some other comfort items.       Got the morning paper for mom, also lent her my laptop (which is why i'm just now getting to use it)  These are the little things you do to show others that you love them.  You do things for them without asking, and you do it with humility.  When they thank you, blush and bow your head.  Don't gloat over the fact that you helped them.    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome Friends!   This is my first venture into the world of Blogging.  I don't know what I'll do with this.  Maybe I'll use this to push my politics, or express my feelings, or maybe sell myself to the world.  Maybe it'll be all of them.    I'm not your everyday Republican in an italian wool suit.  I'm your average every day Long-Haired Pot Smoking Metalhead Republican.  I love america and all that she stands for.  I love our political sytem.  I love our freedoms.  Most of all, I love our Metal.  You may think of metal as music perpetrated by Aqua-net enhanced rejects like Poison and Ratt and Warrant.  It's more than the hair-bands of the 80's.  I also love Johnny Cash.  His music speaks to my soul and gently caresses it like a mother does her babe.   Give me Slayer and Johnny Cash and I'll be happy.  It's the simple things in life.  Enough for now since this is my first.   
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          THERE   &nbsp;are people who are out to  get us.&nbsp; They do exist, no matter how hard we try to ignore them because  they're from third-world nations in mud huts.&nbsp;      We  &nbsp;  went to  Afghanistan, everyone said "YAY!! Kill them Taliban F**ckers!!"&nbsp; I still  don't see the point of Afghanistan other than removing the Taliban.&nbsp;&nbsp;  Sure Osama and his merry band of Mad Bombers were there, but we still haven't  gotten them.&nbsp; We did make them less effective, but they're still alive and  3,000 americans are still dead.&nbsp;    Iraq became the next target on our list of Terrorist States.&nbsp; We spent  12 years trying to ensure that Saddam was disarmed, and we failed.&nbsp; We  threatened force over &amp; over again, but never did anything more than a  bombing raid or lob a few cruise missiles.&nbsp; GWBush went to the UN and said  "Enough already, we've been attacked by one group already, and Iraq's been  threatening us for over a decade.&nbsp; Resolution after resolution, we tried to  get him to disarm and agree to inspectors and Saddam refused to comply, even  though he lost the war back in 1992.&nbsp; It's time for us to pay back our  promises in full.&nbsp; Are you with us?"&nbsp; The UN said No.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp;  Why not.&nbsp; No one in the UN really ever liked us except the Brits, and only  because we've saved their asses so many times it ain't funny.&nbsp; The French  are in the same boat, but they'd been turning more and more Anti-US since  Charles DeGalle.&nbsp;&nbsp; The Germans we'd beaten into submission 50 years  ago, and I don't think they've forgotten it, so they obviously don't want us  exerting any more power.&nbsp;&nbsp; And the Russians, well, c'mon&nbsp;you can  take away the Soviet titles, but they're the same old commies, only now they're  broke.&nbsp;&nbsp;    So we went to war with Iraq in hopes of finally ending the Greek Tragedy  that it has become over the years.&nbsp; The Iraqi government fell within weeks,  Saddam was caught a few months later.&nbsp; We've been rebuilding their  nation.&nbsp; Oh but what about all those soldiers that have died??&nbsp; What  about them???&nbsp;&nbsp; I knew you'd ask that, so here's my answer:&nbsp;  These brave soldiers, airmen, sailors, and Marines all joined up knowing that  there would be a possibility of laying down their lives in the service of their  Nation.&nbsp; Every recruiter tells you to go home and think about that before  you sign anything.&nbsp; Remember, this is their job.&nbsp; They've spent weeks,  months, and/or years of training to go to war for a reason: war  happens.&nbsp;&nbsp;    Another thing you lefties start talking about is all those innocent  civilians that George Bush, Dick Cheney, and Haliburton have killed.&nbsp; 20,  30, 40 thousand innocent people killed for oil.&nbsp; Bullshit.&nbsp; More than  half of the civilians who've died in Iraq&nbsp;are killed by their fellow  Iraqis.&nbsp; Suicide attacks, truck bombs, roadside bombs, mines, mortar fire,  all of these things are aimed at the US, but hit civilians as well.&nbsp; If you  read the reports of US soldiers dying or wounded, they go something like this:  "2 US servicemen killed, 14 wounded in action near Najaf, 34 civilians killed,  over 200 wounded in same truck bombing"&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I guess you can blame  GWBush for those deaths, because if it werent for him, the Iraqi "freedom  fighters" wouldn't be fighting against the US Oppressors and Occupiers.   &nbsp; 
    
</post>


</Blog>