<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I've come to terms with myself. This whole situation is stupid. I say if me and Kellie never got into this fight, then we would still be together... but it did happen, and I can't change that. Right now I have a second chance to get a great friendship back. I'm going to take it. Everything else will just happen. Sorry about the last entry, I was very confused and frustrated that night. So, take care everyone.  That is all.  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't know how I feel right now.&nbsp; Tonight my life got turned upside down when I got an IM from... Kellie.  She apologized for some of the stuff she said, and that was awesome.&nbsp; We started talking just like old friends.&nbsp; The problem is, I can't seem to remember her as a friend . . .&nbsp; I remember her as my g/f I called and had a great time talking to.&nbsp; Or the g/f I went to Brusters and made a fool out of myself in front of.&nbsp; Why can't I just move on?&nbsp; WHY!? Gah...  I guess we started talking and basically someone (no names) told her something happened between me and Melissa that didn't.&nbsp; I'm like wtf?&nbsp; Nothing more happened.&nbsp; But at the same time Kellie trusts this person with all her heart.&nbsp; Who am I to go against that?&nbsp; This whole event has really pissed me off.  I'm happy we talked.&nbsp; I'm sad that we got into that event again.&nbsp; I'm mad lies were told.&nbsp; How am I suppose to feel?!&nbsp; Then all I get is frustration when I talk to her, and that's not what I want!!&nbsp; I just want to sit down and be able to let this shit handle itself.&nbsp; I am almost positive that if me and Kellie talked like this never happened she would not only learn to trust me again, but I'm almost DAMN sure she'd like me again.&nbsp; But should I even like her still?&nbsp; What the hell is this?  Gah... I don't know what to do.&nbsp; I need to get my thoughts straight...  Why can't I just fall in love with the girl next door, take her to prom, get married too early, eat spagetti suppers for a year, and keep falling for her day in and out while we raise a family?&nbsp; I mean yeh I'm too young to be thinkin' about kids, but damn.&nbsp; I was raised in a house where love was some beautiful thing that will find you and hit you so hard you'll be on your ass.&nbsp; Have I felt love?&nbsp; Can I understand love?&nbsp; Should I even say the word at this level of comprehension?!  Sigh... I just wish I could focus on one thing like I used to.&nbsp; Back in the day I'd focus all my efforts towards one thing, one person... and my efforts would pay off.&nbsp; Now I put efforts in to get nothing back.&nbsp; Why can't I just get back SOME of what I put in?&nbsp; Gah... I'm going to sleep off this hell I've created in my mind.  If this is Kellie or Julia reading this... just don't... the thoughts in my head are so confused right now.... so... until tomorrow...  That is all.  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, haven't posted much recently so here it goes...   I'm currently at my dad's house for the weekend.&nbsp; I won't be back until Monday/Tuesday.&nbsp; It's alright here, but meh... I dunno.&nbsp; That's a long story, I suppose.&nbsp; He'll always be my father, but at the same time it's not really 'my life' here.   Other news, more Kellie drama.&nbsp; I was reading her journal the other day and saw she's having a rough time with her parents and shit.&nbsp; So I got on and talked with her step-sister to make sure that she was alright, then I said it seemed like she needed a friend.&nbsp; I was trying to be nice or whatever, but then the next day I read an entry flaming me.&nbsp; It said: "If I needed a friend I would've come knocking on your door, asshole."&nbsp; =/ &nbsp; I guess nice guys finish last.&nbsp; Although, I dunno, I can't blame her for hating me because of how shit went down.&nbsp; Whatever, I guess it's in the past.&nbsp; Just worries me that we'll be at the same school next year.&nbsp; I don't want anymore drama.&nbsp; Hell, I went shopping at Kohl's today and saw someone that looked like her.&nbsp; It was gut wrenching.&nbsp; I don't wanna see her there, cause that'll just start more shit.   Anyhow, I've decided that the state of Virginia hates me.&nbsp; They make me wait until I'm almost 16 even to get my learner's permit, then they throw stupid questions at me.&nbsp; I don't wanna get into all the details, but I was one question short of my learner's permit.&nbsp; No fun.&nbsp; =/ I've been talking to the people at GameStop.&nbsp; Namely Jimmy and the dude with the Midnight Club II hat (I forget his name >.  Oh, and my dad's birthday is July 31st, that's why I'm down here.&nbsp; I went to Kohl's (where I think I saw Kellie... I didn't wanna confirm) and got him a shirt then over to B&N to get him a book he wanted.&nbsp; Good stuff.   And my computer news... I'm working on a proramming project over the summer.&nbsp; It's going to be a fully-functional game once I'm completed (I hope).&nbsp; Right now I'm just trying to stream-line the graphics and do buffers and all that jargon.&nbsp; FFXI (Final Fantasy 11, a game I play often) is going good, too.&nbsp; BioWare finally emailed me back... said they'll take a look at my game once it's done.&nbsp; I can't wait until I'm working for a big-time gaming company!   Well, that's about it.&nbsp; Got most bases covered.&nbsp; Friends and me chillin' often, got my games set for the next few months, school supplies are bought.&nbsp; Now all I gotta do is sit back and relax.&nbsp; Hopefully the rest of the summer won't have too much more drama.&nbsp; Until next time...   That is all.    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sigh, tons of drama has transpired over the last few days.  It feels like Drama is my shadow.  First off, there is this chick named Anna.  This entry is mainly towards her.  Tuesday night she gets on and starts IMing me like mad while I'm at my friend's house.  She wants to talk to me or something.  So I get home and check my messages.  She's still on so I send her an IM.  We start talking, but something is different.  She's in a completely bad mood.  I realize this and ask her about it.  She doesn't want to talk about it.  That's fine, so I ask if she's alright.  She says:  "Sure."  I'm like ok... so then I tell her that I'mma go cause she asked me to stop swearing.  I mean I respect her trying to quit but I've listened to her swear up and down, dude... that's BS.  So anyways I'm about to go and she gets all sarcastic and says "Oh thanks for caring."  So then that totally sends me off the edge.  I've cared about this girl since the day I met her.  She's always been a friend to me and I've always been there to listen.  That's BS that I don't care.  It's just she gets all pissy and expects me to take it.  I dunno, I'll talk with her about it sometime.  Really pissed off right now.  In other news, no job yet.  Still just looking around.  Also, we're prolly moving to a house and outta this apartment.  Trade off, I guess.  No grass to mow up here, lol.  I liked that part of it >.  That is all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Man my wallet is full of nothin' but moths.  I need some serious cash.  I'm gonna start looking for a job today, so don't expect me to write too often.  Summer has been flying by and I've got alot of goals and dreams I'd like to accomplish during it.  I'll fill you in when I'm not busy >.  That is all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last night I couldn't sleep well.  Alot was on my mind, as it usually is every night.  Regret.  What does this word mean to most?  To some it means to dislike, or have a wish to change, a past event.  To me it is that, and much more.  It is also a lifestyle for me.  Some that know me well might call me a perfectionist.  This is so true.  All of my life I've been 'go big or go home.'  Every night I think about the mistakes of the past.  A better comparison to me would be a werewolf.  Every full-moon a beast is summoned from within me.  Then it feels like it feeds upon my mind.  There are too many past stories to share in this one entry, but I'll share what last night, particularly, was about . . .  Well, I guess I should begin with me coming to Virginia.  I moved here and met a very nice girl named Andi.  She's fun and kool to hang out with.  I mean, yes I liked her at first, but we've been good friends for about a year now.  Anyhow, as the year went by she had a birthday come up.  I, of course, was invited.  So when I show up I meet this frined of hers named Kellie.  Wow.  Kellie is so down to earth and her sense of humor is exactly like mine.  We clicked right off the bat.  So then after the party, about 2 weeks after, to be exact, we start talking more and we eventually start going out.  It's amazing.  She's awesome to talk to and is a very caring person.  Then, we take a break.  Kellie had some family-issues to deal with.  I'm perfectly fine with that.  My family is jerry-springerish, so I know all about that, haha.  For the next 2 months me and Kellie talk on and off.  Sparatically I guess you could say.  Then SHE has a birthday coming up.  I was invited months ago, so I called her up and asked if I was still welcome.  She told me that she'd love for me to some, so I did.  I show up at her party and it's me and 7 girl . . . yeh, you heard me SEVEN, lol.  Anyhow, me and Kellie just say our hellos and I plant myself on her couch.  Now, I know I'm not the best looking guy, so I don't quite understand the next series of events...  After about 10 minutes of my presence at the party I'm being hung over by atleast 2 women at a time.  It was a very wonderful feeling, but it's not what I wanted.  I would've prefered a nice, quiet dinner with just Kellie and me.  Anyhow, later on that night we go for a walk at 11PM . . . and there is a full-moon :D, lol.  There are 8 of us, so we split into groups of 4's.  Kellie isn't in my group.  Then my group of 4 breaks down further into a group of 2.  That leaves me and one girl, named Melissa.  Me and Melissa had been talking some during the party.  She's a very level-headed girl and very fun to talk to, but at the time I still liked Kellie.  Hell, I was talking about her non-stop to Melissa.  Anyways, we keep walking and one thing leads to another.  The next moment she turns to kiss me.  I am a tad surprised by this.  Then what goes thru my mind is:  "I'm at my ex-gf's birthday party and I don't even think Kellie likes me anymore.  Why not?"  So then me and Melissa start making out.  But then about half-way thru I pull away.  That's not who I wanted to be kissing.  Later on Kellie finds out.  I don't exactly tell her right off the bat, but I come clean by the end of the night.  I find out that she still does like me, and that she's very upset about all of this.  Well then I felt like an ass because if I knew that, I would've told the other 6 girls to fuck off.  Kellie didn't know how much I actually just wanted to be with her.  Anyhow, after the party me and Kellie talk some and try to start up again.  I ask her out and we schedule a time, but she doesn't show.  So then for the next 2 weeks after that I can't get in touch with her.  Later I talk to Andi, her friend, and find out that Kellie thinks I lied to her, which I didn't.  To this day I still don't exactly know what Kellie was told, but I am certain that it is false, or that it can be cleared up.  Kellie won't accept my calls or ANYTHING.  I think she's being very immature and should atleast talk to me about it.  Regardless, that is not what I regret . . .  What I regret is the fact that me and Kellie couldn't have found out what we could've had together.  I mean, we weren't exactly in love or attached, so I'm not tore up about losing her.  Also, I regret that if I knew that night at her party was the last night I'd see her as my friend, then I never would've left.  I actually hope she sees this.  Hopefully it'll clear some of her misconceptions up.  Regardless, this is just another scar to add the my arm of regret.  That is all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here I am on a Monday afternoon with nothing to do, so I decided to write about my 4th of July weekend.  To start off with, it was pretty kick-ass.  My mother and I went to the lake with her boyfriend.  The first night there, which was Friday, was pretty lame.  We got in late and had to work work work.  We crashed at about 2AM or so.  Next moring at about 10 we got up and ate, then spent about all day on the boat, swimming, and chillin'.  That was pretty fun.  Went skiing, tubin', and all that fun stuff.  We then came home and had a classic smoores feast before playing Phase 10 for about 2 hours.  Very relaxing.  The next day was July 4th.  We did the Boat thing again and went and got some ice cream.  After the day died down we watched soem fireworks and went back to camp for some R$R (Rest and Relaxation).  Then Monday was spent packing and driving.  Not a long haul from Lake Gaston.  It's just about a 1 and 1/2 hour drive, or there abouts.  Got in here at about 1PM, unpacked.  Then I've just been chillin' since then.  Hopefully I'll get unlazy and post more about my past and the events that've made up who I am.  That is all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, not much to say.  Just started this blog in hopes of sorting out some thoughts.  I figure everyone else is doing it, so, hell, why not, eh?  Perhaps actually hearing myself talk/write will help me to be more aware and patient in my words and actual thought process.  No more news right now, gonna tweak the settings and what not.  More posts to come, I hope... 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       First off I'd like to thank whoever left the ever-so-kind note last entry.  Made my day. ;-)  (And you reminded me to write in this thing... but no one needs to know that haha).  Please leave me another and maybe a name/contact this time?  Thanks in advance.  Anyhow, we're moving over there to Deer Run.  Good stuff.  I like the house, although it's not the best.  It's good for our income and shit.  So yeh, anyways... That's about it.  Nothing is really going on.  Just enjoying the summer.  Going to reclaim my learners Monday !! lol  And I think...  That is all.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, let me get the good out of the way first, since that's the shortest part of recent events.  Today went well.  I got a lot done.  Read a few chapers in a book I'm reading called 'Angels and Demons'.  Then me and my mom rented some movies.  Namely Matchstick Men and Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring.  Great movies.  Both had 'w-t-f mate? ^^' endings to say the least.  I had fun chillin' with her most of the day.  Good times.  Now, the bad news, I guess.  I don't really think it's all 'bad' news, just confusing news (in my mind).  I have referred to the past events as 'Kellie drama'.  I've talked about how she judged me, how she has done so much wrong to me, and all of that stuff.  But really, is it Kellie's drama?  She didn't create this.  Perhaps the answers to my 'drama' problems don't lie in talking with her, but within myself?  I've noticed I get frustrated whenever I see some of her entries (She has an online Journal).  Such as the recent one about her.  She has a cast on her wrist, and I have no idea why.  She told a good friend a secret.  Why do I get frustrated by all of this?  I guess it's because I used to believe I was a trust-worthy friend.  Not just to her, but everyone in my life.  It's not just me and her who haven't been talking as much as I'd like, either.  I feel like I'm helpless to help any of my friends.  Isn't that what we're suppose to do?  Help each other?  Then again, I'm never one to take kindly to help.  Perhaps I should take my own advice... I dunno.  All I know is that Kellie, Holly, Brian, Anna, and all of my other good friends are goin' thru a lot of shit they don't deserve, and I can't do a damn thing about it.  That tears me up...  I guess it's out of my control tho.  Anyways, I can't wait for school to start.  Been dull around here over the past few weeks.  Also, I think we found a house.  My next entry will contain final moving details and all that mess.  So I guess...  That is all.  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well I've been pretty lazy over these past few days, what else is new?  Last night I played FFXI until the we hours of the morning after I got home.  Got Rank 6, which is good, I guess? O.o  Anyhow, today I woke up at about 1:00PM.  Good stuff.  I downloaded some stuff, mostly just Tupac and Linkin Park.  More good stuff.  Then I talked to a special someone.  GREAT stuff.  =)  I can't tell you her name, because then I'd have to kill you?  Not really, just don't wanna cause anymore drama in my life.  After I got off the phone I went out with my mother to dinner then to the movies.  It's her vacation week, so she asked me to hang out with her.  It's kool tho.  Good family time, I suppose.  She wants to do a daytrip thing somewhere on Friday.  I guess Virginia Beach, I dunno.  Well nothing else to say really.  Just been being a guy, I suppose.  Cars, girls, video games, and food, lol.  I'll post once some drama starts up.  It's bound to happen soon.  That is all.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>