<Blog>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well championships were friday night and yesterday morning. our older kiddos kicked butt and our little kids werent so hot. anthony cut his hand open and still swam. hes a total beast. and alexander almost did the bend and snap for me and mags but it didnt happen. and my butt was soakin wet cause i sat in thomas's chair and it was wet. yes leanna im that dumb thanks. then yesterday me ben and amy went to mags house for a while and watched win a date with tad hamilton. amy left early and me mags ben and wizzle crashed on the couch. then ben took me to my house so i could change and went to pick up mags and wizzle then came back and picked me up and took us to the pool. then he had to go check on olivia cause shes sick :( but shell get better if ben gives her the medication properly. the pool was so cold and boring. it was like overcast and we were freezing. then we watched the awards ceremony and sheryl came. mags and ben went back to mags house and me and sheryl and thomas and alexander were gonna go to the movies but it was too late. so thomas and alexander went to see king arthur.  today i got up, ate 2 doughnuts and a bowl of cereal, and then my day went downhill from there. carrie busted the window ((idk how. i was upstairs cleanin my room)) and i got a piece of glass stuck in my foot. i thought i was gonna have to go to the hospital cause my foot would not stop bleeding and there was still a piece of glass in it so i just put on a band aid and got over it. i had to clean it up cause carrie was basically in shock. she was crying and couldnt breathe and it was freakin me out. she grounded for a looooooong time but if shes nice and her attitude doesnt get outta hand itll graually decrease. then i did yard work. fun. then alexander called and asked if i wanted to come over cause thomas him and kevin were playin cards. i would have but kevin and i dont really get along. so were just gonna get together tomorrow and go to dinner and come back here and watch cabin fever or go see anchorman.   well im gonna go... rat race is about to come on :O)
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yesterday was good...  i went to drivers ed woo? then came back here and went to the pool. megan was there and she made some bracelets and all. we played keep away with anthony andy and about 50 other people. i talked to jen for a while. she goin to forsyth tech for a semester then goin to app. shes cool as mess. megan left around 5 and me carrie patrick travis and brock were in the shelter ridin patricks motor scooter. travis was tryin to go uphill on the steepest part of it and he broke it so josh had to come out there with the toolkit and fix it. then he started ridin it. it was hilarious. then jordan came to get his bike and all and said hey and thats when i met sara. she walked up to me and was like is that your brother? i said no and then we talked about stuff. we went and played volleyball and tried to go across the monkey bars but neither of us had enough coordination. then we started playin sharks and minnows. i hate that game.  then leanna came to the pool. i introduced her and sara then we talked to leanna. well she called jordan and he said that he was gettin ready to come to the pool. so we were like cool. well like 1 minute later him and thomas show up. fun stuff. jordan thomas and josh were jumpin off the divin board and me sara and leanna were watchin. then we were playin with the ball and jordan and thomas stole it and we were tryin to get it away from them and it just wasnt workin cause i dont swim and neither does sara and leanna was sittin in the chair watchin. i accidentally stepped on thomas when he was underwater but thats ok cause i told him sorry rite sara? but it was fun. then the kid who has the cute brother came. i dont know their names or anything but the oldest one is 15 ((cause i saw him drivin the other day)) and the little one is 6. hes so cute. then when we were leavin josh comes up and acts like hes gonna kick the ball and carrie starts screamin and me and sara busted out laughin. i dunno why it was hilarious but she started laughin and her laugh makes me laugh cause its funny haha. and one thing i learned last night is that guys either dont listen or their really really slow.  me: i lost my contact  thomas: did you lose it?  me: yeah  jordan: oh  sara: yall are stuuuupid yeah sara that was nooooooooice ;) some of that kentuckyness comin out haha.  and i talked to mags last night. i havent talked to her in a while. elizabeth got her tonsils taken out. mr bill told me. and i saw wizzle yesterday. gotta love that kid haha.  and leanna is gonna love me cause im gonna do a good thing for her because im a great friend and i love her :)  well i gotta go get in the shower. i got practice tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok lets go back to yesterday...  leanna and i went to a dca show to cheer on william the man and alexanderwander. we end up doin somethin for garmon then we go sit down. well here comes jason. so we watch 2 of the performances and then jason and fuzz and alexander leave during intermission. well they never came back. so leanna and i said screw em. so we see a LOT of gay guys yadda yadda yadda. and we saw tyler and harrison and andrew. tyler looked very nice ((and no im not just saying that sweetie haha)) and harrison smelled like a pig so he wiped his sweat all over leanna. it was hilarious. so then the last group comes to perform. this guy on the colorguard pops out of the middle of nowhere and hes big and black ((no im not being racist cale)) and funny hair and pierced nipples and NO underwear whatsoever. he was flappin in the wind. i swear that was the nastiest thing ive ever seen in my entire life. hes got pink flags and wavin them around and jumpin and dancin and screamin into the crowd and blowin kisses and me and leanna and kim and her bf ((he looks like nick carter)) were bustin out laughin and the woman in front of us turnes around and was like is it my imagination or is this really happening? hes bigger than my husband! it was so disturbing.  so then since my parentals were working concessions we got food for free. so we go to the stands after the thing is over and this guy is shoving piles of fries in my face. now, being irish, i accepted them. but about 200 fries later i was about to give them all back. so i ran outta pepsi and i had to go get some more. well i go to the door and will baucom is standing there bent over gettin some ice. so i took the door and kinda nuged him with it and he still didnt move. i called his name and he didnt move either. so i just opened the door right on his butt and he turns around, and in his mexican voice, goes OH CAIT YOU TOUCH MY BUTT! and ms dana and wills mom and williams mom and my parents and some other kids parents turn around and look at me and will and he goes NO RUN RUN FOR YOUR LIVE CAIT! and wills dad goes honey if you wanna touch wills butt just tell him im sure he wont mind. haha i love mr jim. we went sleddin together last time it snowed and it was fun. but anyways last night was great. i didnt go to bed till like 3 and i had to get up at like 730 to go to drivers ed. loserface leanna kept me up all night.  leanna slept in while i went to drivers ed. i came home and kicked her butt in some vodeo games then my mom left around 1145 to go get stuff for the party tonight. it stopped raining and the suns out so were havin it at the pool thank god. but we ((me leanna and carrie)) were in the living room and carrie goes to get somethin to eat and goes OH MAN CAIT COME HERE so i go into the kitchen and theres soap bubbles ALL over the kitchen floor by the dishwasher. i start freakin out and leanna comes in there and weve got buckets and bowls and towels and plastic spoons tryin to get all the soap up before mom comes home. we were on our hands and knees gettin that ish up... it was crazy. well the bubbles started comin out faster and were slidin and fallin all over the floor so i decide to call jordan stepansky. i mean this kinds strong, smart when he wants to be, and we figured that he could help us. well he goes just keep soakin it up itll be ok i gotta go im starvin. well leanna and i are mad at jordan right now. but we ended up gettin the wet towels in the dryer and the bowls and spoons washed and the bubbles up. it took us about 2 hours but im just glad mom didnt see. she woulda been pissed.  well we gotta go set up for carries party now. fun stuff.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well this is what happened after i came home to eat...  so leannas phone rings and it sounded like the ice cream truck so i jumped up and grabbed a dollar and was lookin for the ice cream man and i mean im screamin cause i really wanted some ice cream so claire leanna and mom start laughing at me and all and well i wasnt very happy because i really wanted some ice cream.  so we went back to the pool and we were playing movies and anthony was in the big chair and he was just like josh... hed say every movie righ after someone said the initials and it was funny but it got annoying after a while. but thats ok because i asked anthony to see if someone would guard monday night for the party and he said that he would make him so if anthony comes thru for me hell be my new favorite person. but if mr barbour comes thru hell be my new favoritest person.  i was talking to leanna about some things that were on my mind and she didnt really help me and all. but i still love her tho. geez i wish someone could tell me how this is gonna end because i dont wanna get hurt again.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow today has been superb!  ok so leanna comes over and we went to the pool. guess who was there? i cant tell you because its a secret. but leanna knows. so anyways yesterday i burnt my finger cuttin the grass and the water was hurting it. so i went up to him and i was like do you have a bandaid? and he was like sure and we went back to the snack shack and he got me a bandaid. he got it and started opening it and i stuck my hand in the window and he put the bandaid on my thumb and was carassing my hand and oh it was wonderful. and leanna told mr barbour that i liked him and now hes gonna tell him tonight at his baseball game. ah lordy i want him to but i dunno. he was playing movies with us today. it was really cool. hes so hot. well i gotta go back to the pool i got people gettin bored over here.  ahh hes so wonderful...
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the day has gone by so slow...  i went to drivers ed ((fun stuff)) and watched videos about crashes and dangerous stuff and all. these peoples daughters and sisters and brothers and stuff all died because of drunk drivers and careless people then when they get to court and all they start crying saying it was an accident. well i cant promise that i wont get drunk when im older but i sure wont drink and drive. ill get a DD ((designated driver for all you dumbasses out there)) to drive me home.  today is carries birthday. shes the big 11. she got a real nice present from my aunt and somebody just sent her a bouquet of flowers and like 20 balloons. its real nice. shes in the shower so i dunno who sent it cause i dont open other peoples mail. but its just hard to think that my sister is 11. i remember when she was like 4 and 5 and she ran around the house screaming 'i pooped in my pants!' yes silly i know but i used to run around the house screaming 'im a good girl!' the sillyness runs in my family.  well when i got back from drivers ed carrie and i went to the pool. guess who was there... brock. yes, my favorite person in the whole wide world. so i was sitting at the table reading a book ((yes... i have to read a book every summer. moms rule)) and its actually quite good. its by julie andrews, you know the chick that played the grandma in the princess diaries... but anyways i was just sitting there then my phone rings. my uncle called because he just did. so i walked out to the shelter and megan and her brother and her cousin april walked up. we all went back to my table and we were sittin on the edge of the pool. april and megan jumped in and i didnt wanna get in cause i got my nails done the other day and any girl knows that manicured nails and swimming doesnt go together. so brock comes up and pushes me in. now my nails are chipped like crazy and i cant find my white polish to repair them. no, im not crazy about my nails but they were $20... MY $20. but its all good because we played movies and sharks and minnows and categories and jumped off the diving board. i totally did my can opener and totally screwed up. my contacts kept falling out so i couldnt do much of anything. so when we were gettin ready to leave brock comes out from the creek and was like COME HERE! so i followed him and carrie was like what are we doing and he was like i gotta show you something. i start freakin out because i know theres snakes in the creek and i dont like snakes. so i turn around and brocks like no come back it wont hurt you its just a lil crawdad. brock was riding his bike across the creek and saw it and decided he needed a new pet. we were there for about 30 minutes trying to catch it. and he said i just needed to dye my hair back blonde. yes i was born blonde but when i was about 3 it turned brown. he thinks i dyed it. if your mom dyed your hair blonde when you were 3, you need to find a new mom.  tonight were goin out to eat and to the movies for carries birthday. she wants to go to applebees and see harry potter 3 for the 4th time since it came out. me and daddy said were gonna go to mi pueblo and see spiderman 2 instead. well i gotta go shower... if i dont wash out the chlorine itll turn my hair blonde again. i went two days last summer without washing my hair and it took my hair a month to turn brown again.  brock i wanna know who it was. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yeah happy birthday nate.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      geez im so tired... i havent slept at all since last saturday. ambers been over all week and we partied hard at the pool all day then came back here and ate then went back to the pool till closing then came back here and watched movies and fell asleep in the sunroom. but she left today so i might be able to get some much needed sleep this week.  jordan called me last night from wrestling camp. i saw him at the pool tuesday and he left yesterday for camp. we were gonna try to get together with leanna saturday night but he wont be back till sunday. i havent told leanna that yet.  today i woke up, got ready, got in the car, went to gens house to pick her up, went to drivers ed, slept, came home, fell asleep in my big chair, and ate. tonight i have practice. im really looking forward to it if you cant tell.  today is nathaniel ryan hargroves 18th birthday. he was spossed to get me some subway for his birthday but i guess he forgot. oh well. i had subway the other day anyways. and the girl that made it didnt take a bite out of it.  well im gonna go. general hospital is about to come on.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i woke up around 9 to let the dogs out because everybody else in my family is too lazy to then i went back to bed till 1145.  i woke up, got ready, and went school supply shopping. fun stuff man. i got everything i needed at target and only had to stand in like for like 15 minutes. after that i went to staples then to like 4 other places. then i went home and took a shower.  around 6 alexander amy and jason came over and we went to lowes and the dollar store to get stuff for the party. i felt like i was about to die. i was extremely hot and my knees were killing me and i had a major headache. then we got to alexanders and i forgot the cds so jason and i had to come back to my house to get them. then we had to go back to my house again so i could get the plates and napkins and all. then we stopped by james's house to invite him. then we got to alexanders around 645. i fell asleep on the couch and james came and tried to throw a pillow on me but he kinda missed. we blew up balloons and listened to cooool music. mags ben stacey dbo derek carrie kris alan kevin and some other person came later. they played mafia and basketball and it was hilarious. me and stace decided that alexander should play volleyball. me mags and ben stood at the end of alexanders street flagging down the pizza guy cause someone stole the st leonards court street sign. william drove his rx7 to alexanders and his stick thing lights up and flashes and its hot. and i found out that rick james died. its real sad.  me and mags had a long conversation about something that has recently come up. i just want her and krissy to know that i dont think i will because i didnt realize how good ive got it until tonight. i dont think i could ask for better friends than the ones ive got now.  well im out... i have to wake up in 7 hours to go to stone mountain where its gonna suck because i cant climb stairs or walk trails or fun stuff like that. bad knees suck major. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today was bad then good :)  i went to physical therapy. knees got iced for 10 minutes and they had to carry me out to the car cause i couldnt feel my knees.  got home and got ready and went to mi pueblo and to the movies with katie. food was great, movie was great, everything was great. oh we saw i, robot by the way.  then i got home and mom was asleep and i had to kick carrie off. daddys taking me to open house tonight so that means ill probably end up going to sonic and movie gallery afterwards :)  i 'met' someone today. his name is maurice and hes cool because he told me what time open house starts. thanks maurice :)  well im outie... i gotta go do something to my hair and eat some more. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so today was long then it got good.  i got up at 1230, took a shower, then went shoe shopping. i found the PERFECT prom shoes. their so adorable but the price wasnt. id so buy them if i had like $400 more. then i went to the mall. i spent $100 and found the PERFECT prom dress to go with the PERFECT prom shoes. and i got a hat, more shoes, shirts, pants, and lots and lots of sour candy. then i had to go to the wake store to git joshs birthday present and lets just say that the guy that works there thinks im a weirdo. krissy knows. so then we try to go to eckerds so we can git some hersheys kisses and they got shut down. so then we see an at&t little hut thing so we walk over to it and start looking at the cell phones. the guy that worked there ((we didnt know him)) came up to us and we carried on like a 30 minute conversation about our phones. so after all that is done krissy had to go to a meeting at the pool.   then i go to alexanders and me and him and william sat there and watched i love the 80s and we watched andy roddick. it was nice. then james came and us 4 played halo. i shot james. then like in an elapsed time of 20 minutes jason, thomas, fayth, anthony, tj, lindsey, krissy, zeke, lane, kevin, alan, james, christine, amanda, and like 10 other people came and it was 8 against 8. then outta nowhere the guy from the at&t store pops up and was like yall are the girls who want new cells! it freaked me out. i mean when i say 'popped outta nowhere' i mean he literally popped outta nowhere. so by the end of the night i learned that thomas is good, alexander and anthony are ok, and james sucks because i shot him.   and even tho jason sent me that horrible picture that really hurt me, he is still the man II and i love him... even if he is a dumbass georgia guy :)
     

    
</post>


</Blog>