<Blog>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's my first time blogging, yes, I'm a blogger virgin. So be gentle on me!  I guess I'm just going to be using this as a diary/journal, so feel free to read & comment (guess it'll be one of those diaries where when you ask a question, you actually get an answer back, huh? LOL)  I'm in a wierd stage of my life, I'm 24, hispanic, and work at one of Houston's longest running nightclubs.  I have 57 hours of college credit, no kids, and just recently left the nest and moved in an apartment close to my job.  My boyfriend of 4 years moved in with me, and it just doesn't seem to be working out.  See, I'm the youngest of 4 girls (no brothers), so you can only imagine how spoiled I am.  On the otherhand, Ken, my boyfriend, is an only child, so you know we have to do a lot of compromising to make this thing work.  That's just it, I do all the compromising, or shall I say all the sacraficing.  Before we got together, I used to travel a lot, would go out of town at least 2x a month, and loved every minute of it.  I've met a whole lot of interesting people, and have partied with the best of them (example: Cypress Hill).  Ken doesn't do diddley squat.  Out of the four years we've been together, we went to gamble for 4hours in Louisiana for our 1 year anniv, and spent 3days in San Antonio for 4th of July in 2003, that's it.  I have went to Vegas twice, and he got after me both times, saying that I shouldn't be gambeling money that I saved (although I did come back with more than I took), and to a few other places (colorado, Del Rio, Austin, Florida, Mexico, Grand Canyon).  He doesn't want to go on vaca, and when he does, he's a total scrooge, making me feel guilty for buying a souvienere shot glass and stuff like that.  BEFORE we got together, I never gave guys second chances.  I was like, "what did you say? C-ya!" and never thought twice about it.  Ken was an unexpected love, I told him when I met him, that I wasn't going to do anything with him, and he better not expect to get anything, because it wasn't happening.  Well, it happend (although it did take quite a few months).  The more I got to know him, the more I saw the good in him.  Well, about 6 mos. into the relationship, he kissed another girl. Obviously I took him back.  Two months after that, he slept with someone else, again, I took him back.  He tells me only what he knows won't bother me, but he isn't a good concealer because I've always caught him because he doesn't know how to lie.  I've always been the one to pamper the one that I'm with, but I always get pampered back.  Not in this case.  For instance, the apartment is in my name, when I moved in, he moved in with me, although he didn't want his name on the lease.  So I told him, what do you wanna do, split all the bills straight down the middle, or did you just wanna split rent, and we each take on certain bills?  He said we'll each take a certain bill, so we split rent, I take electric, he takes cable/internet, and we split groceries.  Being the second month, I paid the frist months rent, we split the second month's rent, and I have paid electricity (both months) and we got our first cable bill.  He went out and spent 600 at a benefit one of our friend's was having for her son, so when it came time to pay the cable, he said that I should not go shopping, and should return the Dolce & Gabana sunglasses I just bought because I have to pay the cable bill, he can't afford it!  OMG!  What kind of shit is that?  I really don't need cable, I have over 150 DVD's, and don't really care for reruns.  That pisses me off.  Okay, last week, we went grocery shopping, bought 225 worth of groceries, and he ended up paying only 65, I paid the rest.  Cleaning the dishes:  I don't mind washing dishes, I cook, I eat, therefore I can clean.  But Ken takes his lunch to work everyday, so that's tons of tupperware.  He leaves the tupperware (sometimes with food still in it) in his bag, and when he's packing his lunch the next day for work, that's when he empties his bag, so just imagine the stinch that comes from that tupperware.  He doesn't clean the tupperware.  I basically feed him and clean up after him.  I work at a night club, the other day I got home from work at 3am.  We were sitting on the couch watching tv, and he asked me if I could make him a grilled cheese sandwhich.  I gave in and finally made it for him.  Well, when I was going to bed, he wanted to stay up and continue to watch MARTIN.  I was in bed, the bedroom door wide open, he had the TV on loud, and he was laughing out loud to every funny part.  So I asked him if he could shut the bedroom door, he said no, said i needed to get up and shut it if i'm the one who wants it closed!  That pissed me off, I said, "I just got off work, made you 2 grilled cheese sandwhiches, and now i'm trying to get some rest. will you please do ME a favor and shut the door?!? He said No, i need to get off my ass and shut the door (keep in mind by this time was 4:30am) I said fine, if I get up to shut the door, i'm locking it, and you're sleeping on the couch!  2minutes later, i get up, told him i was getting up and locking the door, threw his pillow on the couch, and shut/locked the door. This mister badass had the audacity to get up and KICK IN THE DOOR!  Yes, this bastard did! Messed up the frame around it, so now the frame around the whole door needs to be replaced.  I told him, you better pay for it to get fixed.  He said, I ain't paying for shit.  This moochin postal worker (he gets paid more than i do!) is costing me more money to live with.  Isn't that fucked up?  What's so funny is that today this itiot was looking at the frame, and actually tried to use super glue to put the broken/cracked wood back together!  Poor humpty dumpty.  LOL.  Now i'm trying figure out a way to kick him out, but I'm bitting my tongue until I know I can pay all my bills and still afford to shop like I want to. I mean i'm not at all broke, I have enough for 3months rent, but I don't wanna be penny pinching.  I wanna know what the hell his problem is.  I mean, he's cute, but he ain't the cutest guy i've ever been with.  He's just the only one that i've given billions and billions of second chances to.  go figure.  Gotta go 2 bed now.  Till then.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>