<Blog>


<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink http://www.stickdeath.com   urlLink http://www.miniclip.com   urlLink http://www.newgrounds.com   urlLink http://www.gotlaughs.com   urlLink http://www.dayudie.com   urlLink http://www.ihateyour.com   urlLink http://www.jippii.com   THESE ARE JUST A FEW OF MY FAV WEBSITES OF ONLINE GAMES AND VIDEOCLIPS AND FUNNY STUFF. ON THE STICK DEATH HOMEPAGE, CHECK OUT MEET THE TALIBANS.  

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    3 guys with leprosy are playing poker. one throws his hand in and the other 2 laugh their heads off.
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   LISTEN CONTAINS THE SAME LETTERS AS SILENT. WHEN YOU RE-ARRANGE MOTHER-IN-LAW YOU GET WOMAN HITLER. WHEN YOU RE-ARRANGE ELEVEN PLUS TWO YOU GET TWELVE PLUS ONE.  

						
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yo Mamma is so fat that when she runs, the CD skips...at the radio station Yo Mamma is so fat that when she goes to the beach, Greenpeace come and try to tow her out to sea Yo Mamma is so fat that when i tried to drive around her, i ran out of petrol Yo Mamma is so fat her picture fell off the wall Yo Mamma is so fat Bill Gates could not afford her liposuction Yo Mamma is so fat her clothes and car have stretch marks Yo Mamma is so fat her baby photoes were taken by satellite Yo Mamma is so fat her picture has 2 frames Yo Mamma is so fat that when she lies down and stands up, there is no change in height Yo Mamma is so fat she has her own area code Yo Mamma is so fat she makes big bird look like a rubber duck Yo Mamma is so fat she makes free willy look like a tic tac Yo Mamma is so fat she makes sumo wrestlers look anorexic Yo Mamma is so fat she sets off car alarms when she runs Yo Mamma is so fat she needs 2 watches. One for each timezone Yo Mamma is so fat that when she goes to the movies, she sits next to everyone Yo Mamma is so fat she is on both sides of your family Yo Mamma is so fat when she bungee jumps, she pulls down whatever the other end of the cord is attatched to Yo Mamma is so fat that when she gets into an elevator, it has to go down Yo Mamma is so fat that when she tip toes, everyone yells "stampede" Yo Mamma is so fat that when she walked in front of the TV i missed three commercial breaks 

						
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I like to think of myself as a humerous person. I like any joke (that i dont know) as much as the next person. If people out there know any good jokes, why not email them to me?  thegamer999@hotmail.com 

						
</post>


</Blog>