<Blog>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Crap Crap and more Crap.      Now that I have that off my chest I guess I can get on with todays blog.    I finally learned how to change the windows explorer text size (after being a coputer tech for ten years), so now I can actually read the pages I go to on the web.  Too bad there isn't anything worth reading out there.  Friends of ours from Alberta are comming to stay with us for a while.  Their ACTUAL vacation plans got screwed up beyond repair so their final desperation choice was our place.    My dick hurts.  Took my son and his friend to the community pool today.  This was the first time I had been there.  Nice place.  The tits on one of the lifeguards were pretty nice also.  I wasn't allowed to smoke near the outside pool so I had to travel through the main building and out the front doors to get my nic fix.  I just ate two pizza pockets but I'm still hungry.  that's it  go away now.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       AAAAAAARRRRRGGGGGGHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!  This pretty much sums up my life.   I'm not really unhappy, just frustrated and fucked. (hence the Paxil)  Since this is my first blog ever I guess I will tell you the story of Ogrgiss from the planet of Xlplik.. Or maybe not.  Perhaps you would rather I stick to the theme and describe my daily life etc...   ON WITH THE SLAUGHTER   I was born at a very early age  ha ha  ha ha I love that one.  My wife says then I turrnneedd (sp) into a gorilla.  Not quite sure what she means by that but she is sitting right beside me so I will humor her.  she is getting abdomon pains right now but she says it isn't period cramps just dull aches that won't come out.  Probobly farts.     OH I SEE.   She said the gorilla thing as I am hairy.  wow she comes up with some good ones doesn't she.  Today I did squat.  Same as yesterday.  And the day before that.  You see I am on Paxil.  A drug that is given to people (and lab rats) that stops you from going deeper into depression.  That depresses me.  The side effects include sleepiness, a sense of lazyness, and the inability to CUM !  This is why my wife is a very happy person.  I can go for a long time without cumming but that presents other problems such as a raw penis, wife falling asleep during sex,  AND SEVERE RAINBOW BALLS   Rainbow balls are like blue balls but even worse.  To see a picture of my wife's dildo collection click here urlLink    Sorry boys that link thing didn't work.  Lets try that again here urlLink    I'll have to work on that link.    I guess I'll go for now as I am feeling horney and need to jerk off.  Sorry if I offended you but if you can't take a joke   FUCK YOU!    In the next episode you will hear about the time I rescued all the one legged taranchulas from a KFC slaughterhouse.........
     

    
</post>


</Blog>