<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MAN I was tired today! I still am....I stayed up late the previous night playing super smash bros (the first and best) trying to beat this one match. I was given the task to beat this specific match by my older sisters bf because he was a GOD at the game and I was always second best. It's my favorite game and the one I'm best at so......finally......after around three years......I did it.....it was glorious......:-).....most girls hate guys who play videogames even a little but this was so much more! So I have to wake up early to get a haircut, which I wanted, but I just crashed on the waiting couch at Don Carlos. Considering the fact that I just pulled on shorts, running shoes, and a BIG german army jacket....I looked like a homeless 20 year old dead on a couch. That didn't stop the extremely attractive hair dresser from talking to me! I don't consider myself that handsome, but I'm not one of the guys that doesn't expect everyone to talk to him. I believe it's the people skills that draw people of all ages.....I really dislike (H-A-T-E) american society, but I do enjoy great conversations. My people skills though, do not get me dates :-(.....so we talked about home school and the asswipes who decide to share their opinion on how we're stupid freaks and how home ed doesn't work....also about how sleep is great. Hey guys...do you want to know how to start a great conversation with a beautiful woman?...here ya go......pay attention.....DON'T STARE AT HER BREASTS! I swear....every day I went to my old high school....I came close to vomitting while watching my fellow males....they would stare OPEN MOUTHED at anything with breasts! Oh and never her face...always the ass and face. The worst days were when they conjured up the balls (god knows they fondled themselves until whatever genitalia was left was withered or covered in a rash) to flirt with them...hey bebbuh...you got a real perty face....hows about you and I go to a movie?.....Then this girl will proceed to let out the most HIGH PITCHED and primal AW BOY YEAH in agreement....I think that during our primal years as slightly hairy apes, the women would let out screeching howls in agreement of fuck dates...maybe to deafen the male....cuz god knows women want one thing but do little things to delay it from happening...like a guy listening....anyway.....my hair was cut but not the way I wanted so I guess I'll get a picture next time. So we go home so I can work which can't  be done because dinner is on its way, meaning no ritalin, meaning no work. So I play some more supersmash bros. My shirt didn't come...but I stood outside and glared at the UPS guy. Not his fault...?........well....as soon as I sit down to work.....Ian and I have to go pick up caitlin because she couldn't drive herself to cosmetology school.....because she now has vertigo.....?.......I know what the problem is....caitlin I have diagnosed you with freeloaderitis...eating an entire box of cheezits without moving more than half a mile a day is NOT good for you. When we get there, it was like picking an oreo cookie out of a sea of melted black and white crayons....for some reason every girl had the same haircut, shirt and shorts.....?.......stupid kids....trying to be different.....people are constantly trying to define differentiality or searching for a way to be individual by changing the way they think.....the key is not to involve yourself in such circles. Not giving a fuck will get you in the same circle AND you look like a careless hippy idiot.....just forget about it. It's easy kids! Well now I'm home and working (kind of). Dr. Perring, the entomologist, hasn't emailed me back but I don't expect him to ever reply. Ian just came to say hi and I had to get him to leave. No one knows how hard that is to do but he's such a time burglar :-D.....sorry about the first I did this and then and then and then of this entry...at least I got that out of my suster so I can entertain you more later tonight...
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Latrodectus bishop! Native to florida though....supposed to be a rare member of the latrodectus family. I haven't ever seen this one...online OR in the books! It only puts up about six images on google image search. Very venomous (duh) and stuff. I can believe the spider hitching a ride here from florida easier than australia....but maybe it's still something to call the entomology department about....just goes to show you kids....don't fuck with spiders unless you know what you're doing!
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This widow is SO an L. hasselti! It has the hourglass, physiology, resting position and web pattern to be a latrodectus, a widow spider. There are latrodectus in the states and california, but none with DORSAL markings!!! This spider has a thunderbolt shaped stripe going down its abdomen and similar stripes pointing down and outward on the sides of its abdomen.....I know what you're thinking.....fag....why is he so worried about a spider? Well asshole, this spider is in the top ten/five most venomous spiders. It's more deadly than our black widow...so how many are there? Can they create a hybrid widow with our native? Hey the more spiders the better but introduced species are BAD. I'm not an expert in toxicology...so I donno if all widow venom is the same or similar. That fact could mean that we don't have the proper antivenin to treat such a spider bite. The two males I caught were less than twenty feet from a mature female native widow. I've been taking care of my friends house while he's on vacation and yesterday I noticed an ASTONISHING amount of widows in such a small area. It might be breeding season but I couldn't see the spiders themselves. Widows are fairly common but what if they're redbacks? I'm probably just being paranoid....I'm calm.....just confused.....
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a dream last night…..I dreamt that I had found the love of my life….and we were already six months or so into our relationship! She had purple and black hair like the kind I want, wore tight black pants, a sleeveless hoody and was short. When I describe my dream girl…which is…a short girl with BIG brown or blue eyes, strawberry blonde hair (I lose all self control and smoothness when I see this hair), she’s short, hits when I make fun of her, kicks when I make fun of her, pushes when I make fun of her, has a strong strong strong love for sarcasm, uses sarcasm on a regular basis, doesn’t have to be interested in my hobbies but asks a lot of questions even if she knows the answer cuz she knows how much I love to get into the animals, likes to play with my snake (jim the cornsnake) :-D, watches a lot of cartoons, protests a lot of things I do just for fun and other stuff…….of course I know hardly any girls with three of these qualities but yeah….girls are the devil…..anyways the girl in my dream….I never quite saw her face but it was pale. I L-O-V-E pale girls. Tan is bad!!! So the dream consisted of her coming to my house and watching me feed the creatures. We walked outside and she pushed me for fun and then the dream ended. Not only is life cruel, but your dreams mess with you too. I usually dream about things that I fall asleep thinking about, which is usually some sort of animal. One of my favorites was a dream about keeping a pair of green tree monitors in my droors, which would come out of the walls in random places and heights. Dreams are great…..I think that the reason people can’t find a pattern or reason for dreams when looking at the context of the dream itself is because everyone has different perceptions. Every dream will change due to perception…then again…I’ve had dreams where I love something I hate or vice versa. Maybe I’m in denial about certain things I love? The wisteria through the sliding glass door of the study looks great this morning. I can’t imagine what types of spiders and little creatures are running through there. Does anyone know where Joseph Mobutu  was a leader? It’s either Turkey, Zimbabwe, Rhodesia, Israel, Zaire, Egypt or Iran…..I’ll go with chucky cheese. I guess I’ll be posting in another five minutes. Guilt is what makes me stop posting and then bitch goddess of boredom gets me back online…..or maybe it’s the terrible triviam?
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ian and I are watching videos on ogrish.com....I particularly enjoy the ones with animal attacks. Whoa! This leopard just.....wow.....what a time for your windows to fail......I bet that asswipe wishes that he listened to the guy about power windows at the dealership! :-D.......I'd just rip off my clothes, assume the fighting position and go chromag style! I could take a leopard.....hhmm.....I think I just discovered a great job!
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok the widows aren't what I thought they were! *smacks head*.......the problem is I thinkt they're an australian spider! The redback spider, latrodectus hasselti, is like the australian version of our widow but more toxic (I think). Well the dorsal stripe is identical to the red back! Red, thunder bolt, outlined with silver and dashes on the side of the abdomen......it's just......here......?...........I'm fairly experienced in all arachnids but it seems like there's something wrong with one of the top five most venomous spiders residing in a pickle jar next to my t.v..........
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey.....haven't done much today besides work....I found two male widow spiders in my backyard BOTH under the arms of chairs. I figured they were in a bad spot for a spider besides the fact that they're harmless so I've moved one and am going to move the other later. I might keep the bigger one cuz I don't have any spiders in the home. I usually just go out in the backyard to check out funnel web spiders, orb weavers and lynx. Widows are often killed on the spot so it might be a good idea to just snatch one up. Phoebe is still the same. I'm awaiting an email response from my fencing instructor for some answers and hopefully a new exercise. I really love fencing. One of the few things that bothers me is the fact there's always someone better than me....close by. I'm not one of those guys who freaks out when he sees someone is better at his new deal and either freaks or becomes a primal beast. I just get uncomfortable and either try hard or continue learning in solitude. Everyone is just so friggin' friendly though! Sept for this one kid.....little orange haired bastard.....he's so cocky. For the first time we fenced, he was (and still is) much more experienced than I am so I was prepared to loose. This guy was waiting for me to come in so he could explode in a lunge or other violent move. He did this about three times and so I stopped coming. After about five minutes of waiting, he dropped his arm and was egging me on for a free shot...I didn't move.....another five minutes later.....he comes in and I switch the tip of my blade around his and before he knew it I had earned a point. Next two points were quick and all his. At the end of the match we shake hands and he leeeeeeens in and says.....you need to attack more......I know I don't take critiscism well but HEY...FUCK YOU PAL. :-D.....I did the attacking more than half of that match! Anyways....the girl who kind of lives in my house and was born of my mother and father (I REFUSE to call her my sister) stopped by just a little while ago. She and her simian bf crashed in front of the tv and tuned it up to share with everyone. Thanks a lot.....now I can read about Eva Peron and listen to the Worlds Most EXTREME Cowtipping on Fox! I swear.....she goes to cosmetology school and then whenever she comes home she either rapes the poor fridge or sits on the couch and accumulates mass. The best part is she gets fatter and fatter every day! Caitlin used to have the worlds best metabolism, even better than mine, and she would dance for hours on end so she was fit. She also has an odd amount of natural muscle.....anyways.....just a year or so after she got out of high school.....her body gave out.....glorious times....g-l-o-r-i-o-u-s.....t-i-m-e-s......I'll give a background on her later since there's so much to say. I can honestly say that I do not love her and regret every sign of affection I ever showed her. Well I have more history to do, fencing to practice, a widow to catch, a room to clean, animals to feed and clothes to wash so I guess I'll see you later you non-existent readers!
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah....we ordered from outback.....man....just a few bites and I was out....maybe it was because I was drinking chocolate milk and just finished fencing practice. I love garlic mashed potatoes though...well I'm watching the tour with mom dad and the brother. Fenn montgomery just crashed and couldn't go on...apparently that's the fourth time he couldn't finish the tour. Poor guy....I really don't know what I'm talking about though...it's Ian and dad who are into the cycling. Well phoebe, my female uromastyx geyri, is still sick but she behaves normally throughout the day. Lots of basking and running from me. Ian started a blog just yesterday....I told him blogs are for girls....then I told him I had one.....well....jesus who reads these things? 
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Does this work? .......
    
</post>


</Blog>