<Blog>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have decided to soon commence forth in swimming.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      everyone is in the pool at this point. should i go into the pool? should i stay on the computer... choices choices..
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i went to neonteen (its finally working again) talked to stacia, posted on the boards took a shower and nobody is really on chat so im going to get something to eat.. don't fret.. i shall return.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate fucking n00bies.. i was going 2 go 2 chat, but chat is no longer working again.. why? too many n00bies overloading the servers.. my gawd i despise and loathe n00bies.. as for religious subject... hmmm i don't feel up 2 it at the moment.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the stiffmeister is a canadian. if you want to piss him off say something about canadians. not that i have anything against canadians.. a lot of my relatives actually live in canada, but it's ever so fun to see him spaz out.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am a self proclaimed atheist, i'd very much appreciate if people would stop shoving their religious belifs in my face. i don't do it to others so why the fuck should u fuck with me? hmmm more on this subject later, but nana is making me clean up.. bullshit.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      don't ever buy a swimming cap from wal-mart. they are cheap peices of shit and they don't work worth a damn.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i think i'll go swimming.. indeed i will.. YES.. i shall go swimming.. i shall return later.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my fucking finger really fucking hurts ... god this is bullshit i suppose i'll go swimming soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just figured i could change the settings so anyone can post.. feel free... or don't.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       For some reason people continously ask me if i'm cuban. i continuously say i'm not cuban... they ask again. wtf is that? my father is from trinidad and tobago, which makes me half black.. my mother is from osaka, which makes me have japanese. please take notice... i am not cuban. thankies.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my nana is here trying to get my baby sister (spirit) to shut up with her crying, but the problem is nana is singing to her. her singing is gut wrenching and the baby continues to cry. when will this pain ever stop?
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If sleep is for losers i suppose im the absolute epitome of loser. i slept until 2:30... nobody told me they were going swimming so my sister, brother, and cousin are swimming in the back yard. i would go swimming except for my sister borrowed my swimming cap and i don't want to be a party pooper.. ah its life. hmmmm i'm eating pop tarts for breakfast.. its been so long i almost forgot what they taste like. i have decided to devote my life to spreading the word of how pop tarts a delicious..not.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the title of that last post should've been 'SLEEP IS FOR LOSERS'
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SLEEP IS FOR LOSERS.. i suppose i'm a loser.. good night.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i forgot 2 put the address...  http://www.rwdmag.com/
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i listened to some uk garage rap stuff yesterday and today... its alright.. this cat named wiley is pretty good with his song 'wot do you call it'.... i recommend everyone listen 2 it.. just go 2: urlLink  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is really no need for this post, but i'd just like to make it known that i'm going to leave the message boards and chat and yes i am an avid masturbator.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well i'm back i have just realized something is wrong with ash (aka my best friend in the entire world). it's either :  1) He failed  2) He's moving to louisiana with his mother  3) He's not being accepted by his mother for being gay.  if it is number 1 my life is going to be hell because he won't be with me next year in the 10th grade... omfg i couldn't live without him.. my life will be over.  if it is number 2 i should just kill myself. as simple as that..  if it is number 3 at least we'll still be together so i can help him work through it.. dear god please let it be number 3 or none of the above.. anywho i know somethimg is wrong.. i just can feel it.. my spidey sense is tingling.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've known about all of these fucking AP projects i have to do over the summer for these god damn classes... im no where near finished with any of them... this fucking sux.. i really need to get started, but it's soooooooo hard... ehhhhh, this is shit... so much fucking work.. so little fucking time.. i use the word fuck too much. as i thought the terrible twosome (Sunny and Kassey) have fallen asleep and it is only i who is awake.. like i said before SLEEP IS FOR LOSERS. they were watching this movie called Honey and there's is a remake of the song "everybody wants to rule the world" by tears for fears... i rate it a four. the original song is much better.. i'll probably post back soon on account of the fact my life sux and there is nothing more to do.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On the 4th of july i dyed my hair pink. i was going to dye it blue but my cousin (anthony) suggested i do it pink since i was wearing mostly pink. my sister (lavender the slut) dyed her hair platinum (my god she makes a slutty blonde). anywho my mom didn't have any problem with it then... when she found out i was going to see my father's mother (whom i haven't seen in 4 years) she turned into a complete bitch and made me fucking wash it out. i spent my fucking $7.52 on it and im fucking pissed. everyone liked the way it looked but she's all bitchysome about it. she didn't give a fuck about my sisters hair.. sometimes i really loathe and despise. i probably shouldn't say that b/c no matter how much she pisses me off i still wouldn't want anything 'bad' to happen to her. i used to think i could live without her until she had a car accident a few weeks ago. although i promised to cherish her after that i find myself back at square one.. hating and loathing and despising her. she's my mother so of course i love her but still... she can be a pain in the vagina sometimes.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i should probably be asleep right now. my dad normally doesn't let me stay up past 3 (even thought its fuckings summer).. there are the pros and cons of my parents. my dad is nicer and has more of the green stuff, but my mom lets us have more freedom, yets she's the bitchiest bitch of them all. hmmm ... its life i suppose.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      please do notice i have posted 5 times already today.. this being my 6th.. yes.. i have nothing to do. look at my profile and read my boondocks comic. the boondocks.. now that's real class.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      a friend of mine checked out my blog for me, but as it turns out u can't post a comment unless ur registered.. oh well.. i guess u'll all just have 2 listen without commenting.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i always thought these blog things were kinda stupid.. ive made several,but could never continuously write in them.. i suppose this one might be different.. btw... is it just me or is britney spears's ass getting bigger?
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my brother and cousin are being little lesbians and they're tired now. they're watching some movie although i know they are going to fall asleep in the next teen minutes.. fuck that.. i say SLEE IS FOR LOSERS. i plan on staying up for a while longer myself. hmmm since you all love hearing about my life so much im going to let u in on a little secret. the j in my last names stands for jenkins.. yes... sunshine jenkins.. that's me. doesn't really matter however.. its impossible to find me. if you look me up on dogpile.com u'll actually find one other sunshine jenkins but she lives in texas.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just looked at my previous post and realized the time there is wrong... i tried 2 fix it, but it didn't fucking work.. wtf... who cares?
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          my first time posting on this blog... what a mile stone.. yeah right. its 3:33 here... fucking triple digits and im at my dads house. my cousin Kassey is here from new york along with my grandmother.. nana. everyone is asleep except for my brother, kassey and me. Nothing much.. i really don't have a thing to do so i'll probably post back again tonight.. doesn't the life of a sun goddess rule?
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I HAVE A THROBBING FUCKING HEADACHE, I THINK ITS A SINUS HEADACHE, BUT IM NOT SNEEZING OR ANYTHING... hmmm... im sure i had something else to say but i forgot. oh well. this is shit shitty shit.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I HAVE A THROBBING FUCKING HEADACHE, I THINK ITS A SINUS HEADACHE, BUT IM NOT SNEEZING OR ANYTHING... hmmm... im sure i had something else to say but i forgot. oh well. this is shit shitty shit.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      GUOD ROCKS MY FUCKING SOX TO ANDROMEDA AND BACK.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is the post of stacia. stacia lives in texas. stacia kewl. this is the thread i told you i'd make about you stacia.   Stuff Tomatoe Aphrodesiac *feel free to correct me stacia* Corn chips Isaac Hayes Alabama.  tis my post of stacia. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am hungry and im thinking about going to Krystals. I am also horny.. they left already, but im still not sure i should masturbate yet. I am happy b/c i finally got my package in the mail.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mom still isn't home, we're still waiting and i'm horny. i would masturbate but there's too many people coming in and out... god im horny. oh well.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just can't seem to concentrate on these damn summer assingments... maybe i'm just not AP material... god if i don't get it done my parents will be so disappointed... beezlebub save me.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm at home now. daddy is in the car waiting for jiro to go get mom so sunny and kassey can see her... its kinda weird...well it feels weird to me anywho. hmmmmmm. There's a lot of people next door at the sexy neighbor boy's house.. i would go see what they're up to.. but i won't. ciao for now i guess..
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmmm i sometimes find myself underpressure by my peers.. i doubt its normal peer pressure, but the pressure of not being anything.. race wise i mean. I either get labeled as black or asian.. but i'm neither. It seems all of the asian kids except me to be one of them and do the things i do, and all of the african-american kids expect me to do the stuff they do... if i hang out with asian kids i get critisized by the black kids and vice versa.. ah.. its shit. Maybe i should start hanging out with the other asian/african american kids.. oh wait.. there is none. hmmmmm oh well... i'll figure something out.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ummmm. i woke up. got on the computer. ate pop tarts (they are soo fucking tasty) and did stuff. hmmm i for some reason don't have a lot to talk about at the moment like i usually do.... feeling melancholy.. as always. I sorta kinda fucked up my dad's computer for a while, but i fixed it. i had 2 find him some riddles for his newsletter. when i get home im going to ask my mom to take me to the store so i can buy the sims. i'm also supposed to send stacia a copy of Donnie Dark-o.. she says its a great movie but i've never watched it although its been in my living room forever.. maybe i'll give a try. i really need to get started on my summer assignments.... beezlebub give me strength.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i once again change my mind.. only registerd users can send me messages.. although i doubt i'll be getting any.. but wth.. im the lord emporess and i do as i please.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so its 3:42.. i am not tired, yet i want to go to sleep. there is simply nothing further to do. will i however go to sleep? probably not.. hmmm oh here's something interesting for my lovely audience. BLONDES ARE NOT THE ONLY DUMB ONES.. i am a brunette/red head and today i proved blondes aren't the only stupid ones. My dad's friends came over. One friend brought his two daughters, another brought his son. One of the girls, the boy and i decided to go swimming. Everyone left to buy food. EVERYONE. we stayed and talked and finally decided to go skinny dipping. They dared me to go first. me being the person that i am, i went first. After about 45 minutes the cars started pulling up and we got dressed. The nosy neigbor children happened to be spying on us over the fence and saw only me take my top off. They called my father... he was very pissed, but thankfully he's not one for discussing things about my 'body'.. yes it is embarrassing, but hey.. its life.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me on marvin gaye. marvin gaye was the greatest fucking male singer of all time. he fucking rules. i listen to his stuff all of them time.. when u listen to let's get it on or sexual healing you can't help but to get horny.yes.. that's me on marvin gaye. oh yeah. i've had a hell of a hard time finding a shirt for females with his picture on it. not only him but bob marley and che guevara are hard to find. i did however find an intriguing purse with Malcom X on it the other day.. cost me $35 but it was fucking worth it. hmmm sometimes i think my thoughts are uselss. sometimes i think i think too much. sometimes i just think.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i started a thread on neonteen messages boards.. everyone should read it.  http://www.neonteen.com/boards/showthread.php?s=&threadid=39903
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i found an imperfection of this site. you cannot upload pictures from your computer.. therefore i can't upload my picture. wanna see it? go 2 http://www.mzSunshine58.4t.com/ or just check my profile.. doesn't matter to moi. o.O
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have decided i don't want anyone commenting on my thoughts.. from this point forth u can't post. nobody can reply to my thoughts. yes.. this is wonderful.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wal mart fucking sux i used a brand new one for my hair it didn't fucking work, my hair is fucking soaked, im going home tomorrow, nana gave me $30.. yeah ME! hmmm i'll post back later if there's anything worth it.. or perhaps i'll post back simply because there is nothing else to do. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      we shall not go to the movies today.. we shall go to the movies tomorrow.. hmmmm im not hungry, but im sure i will be soon... krystals sounds good right about now..
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ah, shit pooey i didn't mean to post that twice... of fuck it.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My daddy... the one in the middle with the cap on.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    1st class sergeant major jenkins.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      trying to decide whether to go 2 the movies or buy a mic... mic last longer than the movie.. this or that.. hmmm masturbation rox my sox. i suppose i'll go ask for opinions now.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i dyed my pubes pink last night.. don't know how i forgot to mention it earlier. lavender wants me to go to the movies with her and i said yes, but now i realize i may have to turn her down so i can afford to buy a mic. hmmmm the-n fucking sux. mom made me do the disehs. of course there was no dish washing liquid for the dishwasher since there is never and dish washing liquid for the dishwasher on  my turn. old sauerkraut stinx. tis all for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      if there was a jesus he wasn't white, he was middle eastern.. yes... like people from jeruselem, iraq, afgahnistan etc... bob marley is my jeezus however and my jeezus was sexy.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    bob marley aka jesus.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    tiz moi.. yes.. looking spaztic as ever and pale.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i posted the pictures but they didn't show up.. dirty fucking bullshit. fuck i need a bigger fucking vocabulary. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i woke up, cleaned up dog shit, went back to sleep woke up around 3pm and ate the rest of my chinese food from last night. never by chinese food from a restuaruant not owned by chinese people. Hmmm im posting 2 pictures.. one of moi, and one of jesus.         
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's probably been less than a minute yet i have decided to take my sorry ass to bed.. i am retiring at 4:22 am.. night night all.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tired am i. i am tired. im thinking of staying up just because... however chances look very slim.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just looked at my picture and realized i have a huge fucking nose.. fucking huge.. ah the better to smell with.. can't believe i never noticed it before. i also look rather pale in the picture. i suppose i look spaztic.. its life sue me. oh yeah, guod has the prettiest hair. hmmm i wonder if the size of my nose has anything to do with my headache. did i already mention the orgasm helped with headache, but the headache is slowly starting to return.. ehhh.. oh well.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have a headache and stacia said orgamsms will make it go away. im going to masturbate now. not only for that reason, but becuase i've wanted to do it all day... ciao.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the sexiliciousness markiliciousness himself&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      TIS THE POST OF THE FABULOUS MARKILICIOUSNESS _____________________________________________  In June of 1988 a SEX GOD was born. His name... MARKILICIOUSNESSLESS.Markiliciousness is the sexiest Gemini ever. Markiliciousess has pretty blonde hair AND a sexilicious stomach AND hes fucking smart AND he can play guitar.. he fucking rox doesn't he? Hmm let me recall when markilicious first met.. Me thinks it was in September last year.. lol the first thing i ever said to him was 'Do you want to be my S.S.S.M'? lol i still don't think he remembers what it means. Anywho markilicious and i have been friends ever since.. even through all of the turmoil of a certain Cabamalan Pussy Boy. Hmmm from what i know of markian he really likes Queen and Nirvana. As a matter of factness markian is the reason i like queen today. Markilicious does not only have all of the qualities listeded before but he is also fucking hilarious... he can really brighten up a shittyful day... Hmmm now that i think of it markiliciousness is the only person i call a liciousness (so feel speshul you). Other things i have learned of markian is that he has a sister who is jealous of his ginger pubes. He also has a cat. He also has older brothers and his father faked a leg injury. Markiliciousness lives in Trent of Stoke in England (me think). If that is true i shall go to england and hunt him down. Hmmm this is only pt:I of the ode to markilicousness.. look forwards to others ____________ aliases of markian ____________ freakboy Mark Markian Marklaar Mark Meakin Meakin1 |Mark| Speshul ``` ```` ````` PaPa_sMuRF Mr_Tinkertrain hmmm im sure there's a lot more, but there's too many so i shall stop now. ______________________ 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the saga of Emporess Stacia pt. III... why? because i felt like it. Here is a list of reason i shall not let Emporess Stacia call: _______________________________________  10)Don't talk sex to me  9)I've got something in my front pocket for you Why don't you reach down my from pocket and see what is If you squeeze him, he'll get happy Come on kids, don't be sappy I've got something in my front pocket for you  8)The Fat Fuck Formely Fucking Know As Lavender Wont Get Her Fat Fucking Face Unglued From The Fucking Phone.   7) I (seriously.. no lie) just learned my phone number.  6) I'm not good at masturbating and talking on the phone( i can't multi-task).  5)Ain't no thang, but a chicken wang.  4)I am forever waiting for my Ashley to call so i can bitch him out for not calling in nearly 4 days  3) Ummm... haven't you heard my voice yet? It could make you grow herpes at uncontrolable speeds.  2) If i call stacia she will look at the caller I.D. and then call karl and tell karl to come to america and karl will fly to america nad stacia will meet him at the airport and they'll go to Ramada Inn and make sweet love and they'll walk to georgia on foot and find me and abuduct me and sell me in a third world country for baskets.  1)Stacia only wants to talk to me for my hot stick body.  _________________________________________________________ And that was the Saga of Emporess Stacia Pt:III ..... or was that 4??? hmmmm oh well let's just call it 3 1/2... yeah.. 3 1/2.   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    the lead singer of black bud.. as a i said b4 go 2 http://www.blackbud.co.uk and listen to sitting by the river... WHAT ARE U WAITING FOR? GO NOW!&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, call me a spaz if u want, but god damn i hate my voice. I mean i alway knew i sound horrible, but not that fucking bad. errr. is there like anyway you get your voice surgically change or sumthing? Fuck i hate my voice.. this is fucking awful. Damn you beezlebub... keep testing me bitch.. keep testing me.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The more i listen to my voice message the more i hate my voice.. oi, beezlebub why hath thou damned me with such a voice? Doth thou hate me? god... my voice sux.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some pizza stealing cock sucking bitch was in my room as i slept. whoever it was stole some of my fucking pizza and im fucking mad. everyone is fucking gone so when they all get back im going to fucking go on a fucking rampage. i told them to fucking give me some fucking money if they wanted a fucking slice, but no... the fucking refused. stupid bitch.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dude, this morning i woke up a lot earlier than i thought so i decided to call and leave a voice message, and as u all probably know i like hate my voice so i did it about 3 times and then i realized it wasn't toll free, so i left the worse message possible... i mean u can hardly hear what i was saying (which is kewl b/c my voice sux), but anywho when my parents get the phone bill my ass is going 2 be grass but.. oh well.. enjoy the message i suppose.. not that there's anything enjoyable about my voice and had just waken up about 7 minutes before... so.. ciao.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sometimes everyone wishes they could crawl in a hole and die... im going to sleep.. and i didn't even masturbate.. and im not even tired. ciao  *the cat dog them song rox my fucking sox*
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Before i rant on about my 2 most cherished family members i'd like to say, i am not tired, it shall be 7am in 3 minutes, the street lights have gone off and i probably won't wake up until around 3 or 4 pm. Okay, now that ive gotten that out of the will talk about my dog, missy, and then my little sister, spirit.      MISSY. I love missy. Sometimes i talk badly about missy, but i love her.. hmmm i suppose, it's because she can't talk back or maybe because she doesn't critisize me. Anywho we bought missy last year at the petshop 'Feather's and Friends'. She was in a cage all alone and there was on cage on either side of her with 2 puppies in each cage. I actually didn't want her b/c i thought she was ugly. I wanted one of the peek-a-poos (i'd had one in the past named scooter), but then all of a sudden missy one of the dogs in a cage beside missy licked her and missy bit it and wouldn't let go. The pet shop owner had to unlock the cage to make missy let go and since we saw that he lowered the price on her from $250 to $150.. needless to say i got stuck with missy. My mom picked her up after she'd gotten her shots and such the next day and i was the first person home 2 see her. After that she followed me around continously for about 2 months until i became rude to her and i'd yell at her to make her leave me alone. She stopped following me and started following lavender who does not care. Still, i love missy (she grew on me)although she pees in the bed once in a while.. she's a lot better than my mom or sunny anywho.      Spirit Spirit was born August 18, 2003.... 3 days after Lavender turned 17. She is 15 years younger than me. I love spirit and spirit loves me. we're as happy as can be. wow that rhymed. lol j/k. Anywho, i find when spirit is not being dumped off on the nanny, im constantly taking care of her. I don't really mind though, i like watching her grow up and do new things such as talk and crawl (she did learn how to walk, but she forgot). Hmm i really take pride in the fact that she calls me SuSu, but she doesn't call my mom anything (HA IN HER FACE). Spirit's birthday is coming up and i plan on getting her something special, but i wonder what exactly... I can imagine 10 years from now having spirit coming to live with me b/c she won't be able to stand living with my mother. Hmm.. spirit is the most adorable baby isn't she? I think she is anywho. Someone asked me was she a boy once. I nearly had to kick her fucking ass. NO... I DIDNT CARE IF SHE WAS 11...hmmm spirit is kewl. she's a lot better company than lavender could ever be. I only hope we get along as we get older since they say scorpio's and leo's don't get along (this has been proven between my ex bf vs me and lavender vs me). Anywho, i love them both.. missy and spirit.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow that whole post came out wrong.. i tried to make two columns, and failed horribly. Oh well.. you figure it out for yourselves.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm i have that feeling that you get, but can never explain. It'd be useless for me to explain the feeling since, you never can truthfully express it when you get it. I guess i'd say im feeling ____________. I was looking at signatures on neonteen when i came to Ethposikal's ( i think that was his name) i went to the site in his signature and i found a wondeful new band.. Black Bud. i reccomend everyone go check them out at http://wwww.blackbud.co.uk dude... they fucking rock, especially the song 'Sitting by the river'... i thought the problem with my crappy computer was gone.. apparently that's not the case. FUCK i hope it gets fucking fixed.. shit im trying anything i can possibly think of. Hmmmm the time is now 6:37am. The sun is shining bright. Am i tired? Ish. There is nothing much left to do, except write this and wait for the virus scan to stop. Hmmm maybe i should make sum lists. Yes.. that shall surely pass the time.  5 things i love the most:                               5 favorite baby names: My Dog                                                  Julian My little sister                                        Julia My Ash                                                  Julius Other family members and friends                        Julio                       My computer                                             Juliet  5 favorite foods                                        5 favorite movies: Cheese and Mushroom pizza                               What's Eating Gilbert Grape Tortellini                                              The Fisher King Goat Roti                                               The Breakfast Club Yakitori                                                The Butterfly Effect Mr. Rogers Ice Cream                                    Good Will Hunting  5 favorite historical people                            5 favorite possesions: Che Guevara                                             My laptop Bob Marley                                              All of my shoes Joni Mitchell                                           My pussy Pol Pot                                                 My pussy rubbing hand Marvin Gaye                                             My Malcom X Purse  Hmmm that tis all. I suppose i'll post again before i decide to go to sleep.. or maybe i won't who knows? It depends. Oh yes. Remember.. everyone is a potential enemy.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tis funny how one's mood can change such quickly. I went from horny, to distraught, to crying in the span of a few minutes. Hmmm. I suppose talking about Ash will at least make me feel better about ash now on account of i have nobody to talk to at the moment. Hmmm i remember when we first met in November of 2000. It was like 2 or 3 weeks after my birthday and we had just moved back to Columbus from Meridian, MS. Anywho i was in the 6th grade and Lavender and Sunny were gone somewhere when his dad and him came over. It was like a little while before mom met jiro so, they came in and talked for like 2hours straight. While that was happening we sat in the den playing video games and didn't say anything for like 30 minutes lol.. i guess we're both really shy. I don't really remember what we talked about and i don't even think i told him my name, but i do remember seeing him in most of my classes when i started school. Hmmm i actually remember hanging out with him and people saying stuff about him being gay... anywho, we're still friends now. God i miss him even more now. I must seem spaztic going on and on about him, but i don't care.. hmmm more stuff about Ash  Full name: Ashley  Simon Swartout (his initials are A.S.S.) Birthday: December 15, 1988 Sign: Sagittarius i think Color: Yellow (just as me) Favorite TV Show: Real World Favorite Movie: Almost Famous (i've really got to watch that) Best Friend: Me of Course First Kiss: Shockingly me... that's really a different story Favorite Band: 3 doors down (i could never really get into them) Favorite Video Game: The Sims  Hair Color: Black Eye Color:Brown (lol he always said he wishes he had eyes like mine) Pets: Hunter and Nina the greyhounds (they are soo ugly) Turn ons: Blonde Hair, Blue eyes, intelligence Turn offs: Back hair, Knuckle Hair, cockiness Favorite article of clothing: Quick silver tabagon.  hmm... i feel a lot better now. i suppose that was a good idea. i guess i'll try to call him again tomorrow/today ish. Hmmm.. i still miss him, but i feel better. God im a spaz. Beezlebub save me.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is my Ashley.. god i miss him. ='(&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes... i am crying right now. He didn't answer i caMlled like 10 times. I miss him sooo much and i know he's there. God i wish i had answered the phone. I hate this summer. this is the worse summer of my life. God i hope he comes home soon. I feel really shitty right now. My headache is coming back, im going to go take some medicine and cry into my pillow. ciao.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well lookie here. My best friend of 3 years (Ashely Simon Swartout) has finally decided to call me. I have been waiting for like 3 days.. its so uncommon for him not to call. I mean.. what if something were to happen to him. So he just called and im trying to decide whether i should call him back or not. Here are reasons i shouldn't call him back:  1) I want him to suffer just as i have  2) long distance calls cost a shitload  3) I might seem needy  reasons to call back:  1) I miss him ever so much  2) Maybe something really is wrong  3) I have nothing else to do.  Beezlebub why must you taunt me? Why must you pull my ASH thousands of miles away from me.. damn you beezlebub. I shall call him.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    There is no other definition of socialism valid for us than that of the abolition of the exploitation of man by man. - Ernesto Che Guevara  smart and sexy.. what a package.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm.. just as i said as soon as stacia left everyone started to leave and in under 5 minutes 3 ppl were left in the room. DouGo is gone now but he helped get a worm off of my computer.. i suppose i'll go post whoring and then masturbate and such... ta ta.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tis the thread of the continuation of the stacia saga!!!!!!!!! Oh stacia, how we cherish stacia. Stacia oh STACIA. As i said b4 stacia is really kewl, the room gets fucking boring everytime we leave so then everyone gets quiet and leaves to message boards (except me cuz i have no life).Tis why we cherish thou so much. she makes things interesting. Where do u go when u want to ask someone how to scan your pussy? Stacia. Where do you go to ask someone how ear sex feels? STACIA of course. hmmmm what does stacia mean, what does stacia mean? Ah, here it is. Stacia means ressurection.. hmmm that has to fit her in some way i suppose. Maybe it has to do with her being wise beyond her years and such. Hmmm in japanese she's be named Chikako i suppose. Anywho stacia completly makes the world go round therefore i had to make this post... please do look out for future ODES TO STACIA. ta ta 4 now.  WE CHERISH YOU STACIA... (yet we cherishe me a little more).
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I fucking vote we fucking declare june 1st national stacia day. stacia fucking owns (besides me of course). This is why stacia fucking owns (besdies me):  1) when stacia and karl have their 7 children they shall be named Sunshine 2 Sunshine II Sunshine Jr. Lil' Sunshine Little Sunshine Sun Shine Sunshine the continuation  2) She masturbates and  all ppl who masturbate are fucking kewl (except men and women over 45 cuz then its creepy unless ur the play boy guy)  3) her first name is Empress... that has to say something..  So as i said before.. EVERY JUNE 1ST SHOULD BE KNOWN AS NATIONAL EMPRESS STACIA DAY aka NESD.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hmmm.. nothing really of significance has happened today. I just realized i still haven't eaten anything, but when i woke up (around 1:30) i got on the computer, vacuumed the floor in the hallway, and talked to stacia. Q called too... dumb ass. Iunno, maybe i'll call him back.. maybe i won't. I have yet to hear from Ashley.... i don't know wheter to be angry or worried. Uhhhh i have to go get some shots (its going to be fucking horrible) and when i tried to unplug the speakers from my old computer i hit my head hard. I have this big ass mosquito bite on my ankle.. i mean its fucking HUGE and it itches like hell. I might make another recording... iunno.. who knows. My dad's birthday is on Thursday (he'll be 42) but luckily i already bought his birthday stuff... SUNNY CAME HOME WHICH IS GOOD CUZ I MISSED HIM, BUT BACK B/C NOW LAVENDER IS GOING TO HAVE TO SLEEP IN HERE AGAIN AND I CANT STAND HER... most of the time anywho. Uhhhh, i played with missy today... tomorrow spirit has a check up at the doctor ( i still can't believe she forgot how to walk) and ummmm.. oh yeah i took a shower and masturbated until i drooled (god it felt good). Thats all.. ciao.  I walk with a limp cuz my nuts heavey I like to hit from the back so keep ur butt steady... heh.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, you probably don't know who you are... i mean i guess you haven't figured it out yet. I don't know what else to say or do for that matter. If you don't get it by now i guess you'll never get it. I just wanted to say that i wish things could go back to the way they were ..... yeah, this is out of character for me, but i love you and and i miss you and really wish we could be together again... and after i write this you probably still won't figure it out.. how obvious can i make things? And if you do know, but u don't feel the same anymore you could at least say so. I mean really, yeah i'll be sad, but i'll just be worse off if you keep on forever. *sigh*... i can't think of any more words to say at this point.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      そうこれは日本語の私の最初記入項目である。。ようである多分私のお母さんによってが私により素晴らしい私が日本語に書く方法を実際に知っていたら彼女は彼女が日本語に書くことができるのでラベンダーを多く好む。それは。私が私が決して日本語に書くことを学んだあらないことは事実を意味するそれについて考えればちょっとおかしい。時々私は私が頼むべき不精にあることを私ができたが、私が仮定することを望む。私が私を教えるそれのための刺激を有してもか。それらが前に停止した学校2 年で持っていた日本プログラム。私は私が大学の日本の調査を取らなければ私がねじで締まることを推測する。だれが、知っているか。多分私は意志、多分私... BYE 今のところ私が推測する。 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tis the picture of Emporess Stacia which i should have posted some time ago.. shes a gemini too, but i have to point out Gemini's rule the arms and legs of the human body... Scorpios such as myself rule the sex organs.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I HAD A GRAPE. IT TASTE REALLY GOOD. IT WAS A GREEN GRAPE AND IT WAS KINDA SOUR AND SWEET AT THE SAME TIME. I think i'll try chocolate tomorrow although i'm a little worried about my throat itching as it is at the moment. My mom has gone to the store. I asked her to pick me up a calling card. She reluctanley agreed so i can call my ASHELY. Hmmmmm.... i tried calling Amber, but no body answered her cell phone or home phone number... tis all for now.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    i know i posted this once already, but since che guevara was so fucking sexy i'll post it again.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I woke up around 1. For the first time in forever i went downstairs adn ate cereal. I realized i didn't want it so i gave it to the dog. I went back upstairs and let Sunny on the computer. I turned off the cookies un purpose so he couldn't do anything therefore he got off the computer quickly. I went in the bathroom and tried to pop this zit. It started to bleed. You can hardly tell it's there though so i may be able to leave the house soon. I suppose i'll call ashley today. Yes I SHALL. And i'll call amber too. Uhhh.... found a post about this racist ranting about women dating black/hispanic/middle eastern and asian guys saying the mix races. #1 women in general are not only white.. they're black/hispanic/middle eastern and asian too. #2 who gives a fuck? Ummmm.. tiz all for now i suppose.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not tired, i am simply bored. I think i will go in the bathroom and look at my naked body and get horny over my looks. Then i will come back and masturbate until i fall asleep. Yes... i suppose i might go back to chat real quick and see whats happening.. nothing most likely. Here is the thought of the day:  Some people are like slinkies… not much good for anything, but you can’t help but smile, when one falls down the stairs.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Errrr.. i know im supposed to hate country muzik.. me being the person i am and such, but there is this one country..ish song that i've been hearing lately.. its by Mandy Smith and its called "Come To Jesus" . Its actually very eerie, if yew ask me.. Maybe its because its like 4 in the morning and im sitting her watching it in the dark, but it reminds me of 'Oh Brother Where Art Thou' in the KKK scene. Hmmm i suppose its a fairly good song with me not being a country fan and all. Anywho.. that's all i had to say.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to the bathroom to piss and look at my breasties in the mirror when i noticed i had a HUGE ass zit on my chin. I shall not leave this house until it is fully popped and gone. Its fucking ugly and gross and i fucking loathe it and want it to die. My dog missy is sleeping beside me now. She has her 4 paws in the air and her mouth is wide open. She is snoring loudly. Her PUSSY smells like sea water and HOT garbage. She fucking needs a douche. Did i mention i have an ugly zit??? Hmmmm.. i like Finger Eleven.... i've liked them for a while now.. maybe i should add them to my muzik list in my profile... maybe i'm to lazy to do that. Hmmmm what else , what else? BITCHES LISTEN UP I TOLD YEW BITCHES TO GO TO HTTP://WWW.BLACKBUD.CO.UK/ YET IM SURE THERE IS SOME OF YEW WHO HAVEN'TBEEN LISTENING. IF YEW ARE ONE OF THOSE BITCHES WHO HAVEN'T GONE I SUGGEST YEW TAKE YOUR SORRY ASS THERE AND LISTEN TO 'SITTING BY THE RIVER' ... thank yew. Uhhhhhhhh.. im answering message boards and watching VH1's Insomniac Music Theatre as alway. o0o0o0o my song just came on (Heaven- Los Lonely Boys)... hmmm tis all for now. I suppose i'll go answer sum more stuff.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was just watching George Michaels new video "Amazing" and then i went to thinking of his old song " I Want Your Sex" and i just wanted to say that if he were straight i'd want his sex. I'd Steal his sex. I'd own his sex. Hell... who gives a fuck if he's gay or not? I don't... i steal would steal his sex even if he's gay... doesn't bother me one bit.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "What else did sunshine do today?" That is the question you may be pondering at this moment. My dear friend, ponder no more, for i shall tell you what i did. I masturbated just a few minutes ago. I signed up for this thing which sends me free pictures of gay guys having sex every day. OH YEAH. I looked up Jennifer's number on dogpile.com and so i called her and we talked for like.. FOREVER. I was so happy to talk to her again. She said she just got back from taiwan and was telling me about how the wheather was nice there for the first time and how her relatives live in taipig (or whatever the fuck the capital is). We did a lot of politic discussing and she was happy to hear the news about the bush administration considering the new voting laws. We might go see farenheit 9/11 next weekend after her parents get paid. She also said her and her brother are going to start taking Tennis lessons soon. I also talked to Q and Keisha today. Keshia is going to have to retake Algebra 101 next year (HAAAAAA) and Q said the usual perveted shit. I still haven't gotten my fucking schedule either. God i still have to get started on that AP shit. I have yet to hear from my beloved Ashley.. i don't know what is up with him, but if he doesn't call tonight im going to buy a calling card and call his skinny ass tomorrow/todayish. Everyone is already asleep as usual. Even missy, she's lying right behind my ass.. im thinking about blowing spit in her face so she wakes up. Maybe i will.. maybe i won't... i will. Lmao, she turned jumped up and ran under lavender's bed. Lavender is sleeping in the guest room tonight since she apparently can't stand me. Hmmm... i finally had a HOME COOKED meal. It was fucking awsome... no french fries or anything. I'll probably post back again soon... iunno.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It has just occured to me that i am relationship disabled. I am incommensurating some relationship gene because every relationship i've ever been has gone horribly wrong... on my behalf. I suppose i really am going to die all alone and old, and yeah i know im only 15 but come on... Take robert for instance... dated for five months and then just dumped him because 'he was too depressing' for me. God im an idiot. And then he begged me to work it out and we got back together like twice, and each time i was such a bitch to him.... god i have a problem. As i re-examine everything i realized i really fucked things up.. yelling at him, cursing at him, not talking to him for days... dude.. i suck. Maybe i jump into relationships too fast.. yeah... that could be it. Maybe i date guys too old for me (last boyfriend 19).... i suppose i really need to re-evaluate the way ive been going about these things... hmmmmmm i suck.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lavender woke me up at like... 8 this morning. I didn't know it was 8.. i thought it was like 12 cuz i asked her to wake me up in time to see Maury.. i suppose this means she can't tell time. I went down stairs and ate pizza... oh yeah went to take a piss at like... 5am today and i got on the scale and i lost like 10 pounds... so i can eat whatever i want for the next few days i suppose. Uhhh i couldn't fall asleep after i ate the pizza so i called Amber and bothered her for about 20 minutes until she almost fell asleep on the phone. I tried out that mic Sunny gave me.. it was a dud... he stole it from skewl anywho (it has the skewls name taped on it). Certain boys suck as usual. I went back to sleep. Woke up about 4 or 5 hours later. Someone at my last slice of pizza.. most likely that fat ass jiro. OH YEAH. STACIA SENT ME " LET'S GET IT ON" aka THE BEST SONG OF ALL TIME. I guess that's all for right now... oh yeah.. i shall never eat another grape again... they taste good, but it'll fuck ur throat up. Hmmmm i am now on page 46 of Eidolon... another masterpeice by myself... ciao.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Marvin Gaye at Carnagy Hall.. or however you spell it.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been really tryin', baby Tryin' to hold back this feelin' for so long And if you feel like I feel, baby Then come on, oh, come on Whoo, let's get it on Ah, babe, let's get it on Let's love, baby Let's get it on, sugar Let's get it on Whoo-ooh-ooh  We're all sensitive people With so much to give Understand me, sugar Since we got to be Let's live I love you  There's nothin' wrong With me lovin' you Baby, no, no And givin' yourself to me can never be wrong If the love is true Oh, babe, ooh, ooh  Don't you know How sweet and wonderful life can be? Whoo-ooh I'm askin' you, baby To get it on with me Ooh, ooh, ooh  I ain't gonna worry, I ain't gonna push Won't push you, baby So come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, baby Stop beatin' 'round the bush, hey  Let's get it on, ooh, ooh Let's get it on You know what I'm talkin' 'bout Come on, baby, hey, hey Let your love come out If you believe in love Let's get it on, ooh, ooh Let's get it on, baby This minute, oh yeah Let's get it on Please, please, get it on Hey, hey  I know you know What I've been dreamin' of Don't you, baby? My whole body is in love Whoo  I ain't gonna worry, no, I ain't gonna push I won't push you, baby, whoo Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, darlin' Stop beatin' 'round the bush, hey  Gonna get it on Beggin' you, baby, I want to get it on You don't have to worry that it's wrong If the spirit moves you, let me groove you good Let your love come down Oh, get it on, come on, baby  Do you know I mean it? I've been sanctified Hey, hey Girl, you give me good feelings, so good  Nothin' wrong with love If you want to love me Just let yourself go Oh, baby Let's get it on 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      love is pointless.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing is going right... suppose i'll just go back to sleep.... that always works.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    You Wish.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HAPPY 42nd BIRTHDAY DADDY!!! (even though u can't read this).  clears her throat  Derric N. Jenkins was born July 15, 1962 in Port of Spain, Trinidad. Uhhh... he got married once then got divorced. He got married again and got divorced. He got Married again and got divorced. He's on his 4th marriage now. I love my dad. He's fucking #1 and he's fucking loaded. I hate his wife. She's a bitch. If my dad took his dad's last name my name wouldn't be Sunshine Jenkins.. it'd have been Sunshine Hastique.Uhh.... My dad joined the Army when he was 17 years old. He retired as a Sergeant Major aka 1st Seregeant last year after 23 years i think. He has 3 kids. Uhhh.. yeah.. that's my dad.  ***********************************************  I didn't post yeseterday cuz i didn't want to turn my cookies on. MY ASH WHORE CALLED!! I MISSED HIM SOOOOO MUCH. He said he went to see his mother's family in Arizona and couldn't call. He'll be home on Saturday, Sunday, or Monday. I can't wait. I miss him soooooooooo fucking much. We're supposed to have a porn party (gay porn only) when he gets home. I'm soooo happy. I was sooo happy when he called i didn't even bitch him out. Tomorrow i have to go to my dad's house and do stuff. On saturday my mom wants me to go see my grandmother again but fuck i don't want to. Urrr... my hair is no longer a big friz ball.. took me like 2 hours to get it straight again. My mom thinks im Anorexic now so i've got to gain some weight (which will be no problem). Still haven't gotten my schedule, but i finally got started on AP assignments.. other news later.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay... this is the 2nd best song ever written...... ex - factory, by the one and only Lauryn Hill....  It could all be so simple But you'd rather make it hard Lovin' you is like a battle And we both end up with scars Tell me who i have to be To get some reciprocity See no one loves you more than me And no one ever will  Is this just a silly game That forces you, to act this way Force you to scream my name Then pretend, that you can't stay Tell me who i have to be To get some reciprocity See no one loves you more than me And no one ever will  *Chorus* _________________________ No matter how i think we grow You always seem to let me know It ain't workin' (it ain't workin) And when i try, to walk away You'd hurt yourself to make me stay This is crazy (This is crazy) ____________________________  I keep letting you back in How can I, explain myself As painful as this thing has been I just can't be , with no one else See i know what, we've got to do You let go, and i'll let go too Cause no one's hurt me more than you And no one ever will  *repeat chorus*  there's more after this... but just a bunch of libs and shit.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah i haven't posted in a while eh.... nothing important has happened...... i doubt it will *cry*..... ashely is home. I missed him so much. We went out for lunch today he *gasp* got a phone number. Provino's has excellent fetuccini. My brother has gone to the movies... or so he says. Uhh..... i haven't been horny in forever. I just feel kind of blah.... like nothing matters all of a sudden. I think im going to drop that AP History course..... too hard. I suppose i'll post back if there's something worth it.... but i doubt there will be......  i love no one.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>