<Blog>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's finally the day I leave and I'm very excited!&nbsp; Of course, I've got tons to do and little time to get it done.&nbsp; Why do I always do that?...&nbsp;&nbsp;   I'm sure glad to go home and I don't think I'll miss much about Indiana right now while I'm gone (well except one certain somebody).  Off to have some fun...leaving all my crap behind...  later 
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am wide awake...too much coffee tonight.&nbsp; I had a migraine earlier and took a nap before work too.&nbsp; I should be doing other things because I have tons to do before vacation, but alas, I am not.&nbsp; Playing on the computer, obviously.&nbsp; I also bought 2 new phones, business &amp; personal...the ones I had were a pain.&nbsp; I hate to spend the money, but whatever.&nbsp; Walmart shopping at 2 AM...it's the best time to go. &nbsp; I can't wait for vacation!!!&nbsp; I am just thoroughly excited.&nbsp; I need to go home very badly, my life has been crazy the past few years and finally I can go home and just relax for vacation...though I do have lots planned.&nbsp; I can't wait...I said that already. &nbsp; I have lots to do tomorrow and Wednesday to make sure stuff is done before I go...just things need taken care of.&nbsp; Of course, my usual self has procrastinated and saved stuff for last minute...I work well under pressure.&nbsp; I do wish it were already done though.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I bought a journal to write in (a long train ride awaits me)...and am also bringing some books, my Bible, and I also bought a portable CD player w/headphones...there goes more of my money I shouldn't be spending.&nbsp; I couldn't stand the thought of going on that long of a trip without music, I'd go nuts.&nbsp; I bought&nbsp;a cheap little CD holder too that holds 12 CDs.&nbsp; I'm ready. &nbsp; My attitude is better than this weekend, I'm not sure what the heck was up with that.&nbsp; Too much buried inside that just decided to rear it's ugly head...it's good to get it out...whatever it was.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Well, I better get to bed...not much time left to sleep...darn it. &nbsp; &nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, so the sensitive mood already struck.&nbsp; I am trying to keep my head high and keep a good attitude...don't want to get too down.&nbsp; I'm crying again though, how annoying, I already did enough of that earlier.&nbsp; I'm not even sure why I'm crying, which only leaves me more annoyed.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Still have stuff to do so I'll keep myself busy.&nbsp; Busy at home doing 'stuff' on a Saturday night when I have no kids, how pathetic.&nbsp; Whatever!&nbsp; I miss home and can't wait to go on vacation.&nbsp; I was stupid to ever leave there.&nbsp; Indiana is not exactly my wonderful dream of a place and if it wasn't for my son I would've been gone 2 years ago.&nbsp; There goes the bad attitude creeping in again...I better go put on some music and find something constructive to do...if I keep this up, I'm sure I can find a bunch to be mad about right now.&nbsp; Or cry about, though again, I'm not sure why I am. &nbsp; I guess I've just gotta get through something that's really bugging me.&nbsp; Seeing that I usually bury stuff pretty deep, I'm sure there's lots inside that's wanting to get out...probably why I'm crying. *sigh* 
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, attitude check.&nbsp; It's better.&nbsp; I took a bath, tried to pray...though I fell asleep during it, I hate when I do that.&nbsp; I guess I was relaxed which is good after feeling pretty angry today.&nbsp; I had no ambition before my bath, but now I have to get with it, I have things to do...work and stuff around the house.&nbsp; Vacation is just around the corner and I have to have everything in order. &nbsp; Plus, I'm going to get a coffee on my way to go work.&nbsp; Coffee can cure many a bad mood with me.&nbsp; I thought about drinking tonight when I was in my bad mood earlier, but knew that would be a bad thing.&nbsp; Drinking and overly emotional and angry do not mix well with me...I'm not much of a drinker anyway...which is a good thing.&nbsp; I just wanted to drink to hide from my problems but they would just be there in the morning along with a crappy headache...it's just not worth it.&nbsp; I'll just do the Dew...lol...just kidding...I really mean caffeine through intravenous coffee fluid.&nbsp; Okay, now I'm getting weird...gotta go. &nbsp; I do know this, I have to be cautious because I have a sensitive mood lurking real close by...and I don't want it to reappear.&nbsp; Attitude, it's the key!&nbsp; And church, well, I'll let God let me know later.&nbsp; For now, I'm not gonna think about it.&nbsp;  
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My previous post just kept reminding me of a poem/lyric I wrote last year.&nbsp; All day today, this particular one came to mind.&nbsp; It was&nbsp;one I wrote about my husband on April 3, 2003.&nbsp; I was pretty angry then...imagine that. &nbsp;  You’ve Won  April, 3, 2003  &nbsp;  There’s too much anger  Built up inside  All the hurt you caused  All that you’ve done  You’ve won &nbsp; You’ve pushed me away  You want it all  All to be your way  Is it too late  You made the mistakes  Live to face the day  You pushed me  Now I’ve walked away  My heart no longer yours  Guarded by these chains  Don’t try to break them  There’s no way you can  You’ve won   You’ve pushed me away  You want it all  All to be your way  Is it too late  You made the mistakes  Live to face the day  You pushed me  Now I’ve walked away   Don’t cry to me you’re sorry  It’s too late for that  When did you ever listen  You walked all over me  Don’t think my heart is yours  There’s nothing left to give  You tore it all to pieces  Live with what you give  You’ve won   You’ve pushed me away  You want it all  All to be your way  Is it too late  You made the mistakes  Live to face the day  You pushed me  Now I’ve walked away   What else did you expect  Someone to kiss your a$$  My heart locked inside  Guarded by it’s scars  You’ve won &nbsp; Copyright 2003, all rights reserved. &nbsp; &nbsp; I just kill myself when I read stuff like that.&nbsp; That was almost a year before our divorce was filed.&nbsp; Heck, the marriage was over before this was ever written.&nbsp; I guess I just thought I had to try to make it work, for the kids or it was the right thing to do.&nbsp; It only made things worse and better yet, he found wonderful ways in which to blame me...because of course, he couldn't be any bit to blame for the collapse of our marriage.&nbsp; Now I'm being sarcastic...again, attitude (and a bad one). 
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last week, I posted about attitude...and here I am with a bad one.&nbsp; Luckily, I've been away from the computer most of the day so I had some time to process some of what's bugging me.&nbsp; But, the bad attitude has lingered. &nbsp; Last week I was thanking God for him being so amazing after I went to church and this week I'm feeling like screaming 'why'&nbsp;and I didn't go to church.&nbsp; I wanted to go to church and had every plan to, but things changed.&nbsp; If you read this and don't know me, then you won't understand why this would sway me from going to church.&nbsp; If you&nbsp;do know me, then you know my soon to be ex-husband has tried to manipulate me in any way possible, including through other people.&nbsp; Right now I want nothing to do with anything that he is associated with which is why I had decided to try a different church than we were going to...and I love the church he currently is at. &nbsp; This morning he informed me that he knows the pastors wife of the church I have recently attended, and made it a point to say he knows her very well because he knows her through work.&nbsp; He said it nicely, but please...&nbsp; Like I said, if you know me...then you know him.&nbsp; I had absolutely no desire to go to church after that.&nbsp; I had a horrible afternoon because it brought up all kinds of crap that bothers me about my stupid marriage.&nbsp; I wanted a divorce 2 1/2 years ago, but his threats and everything else still controlled me and I stayed.&nbsp; Now that I'm in the middle of it, he has still succeeded in making my life more miserable than it should be.&nbsp;  &nbsp; My thought is why did he even tell me.&nbsp; I know he knows it would bother me because I'm trying to get away from him altogether and anything associated with him.&nbsp; So my one conclusion is he did it on purpose (or maybe without even realizing it), but he knows deep down it would ruin things for me.&nbsp; He never wanted me to be my own person.&nbsp; Now here I am secluding myself from people which is so unlike me...all because of things he did during the seperation and beginning of the divorce.&nbsp; I was already secluding myself at this church and have made it a point to NOT talk to people...again, so unlike me. &nbsp; I'm not perfect and I've done wrong, of course, we all do...but for once in the past 7 years, I would just like to feel like I can be my own person without him hovering around.&nbsp; I can't make a choice without feeling like he has to meddle in it somehow.&nbsp; Not like I think he is going to talk to her about me, but rather when he was in psycho stalking mode, I'm sure he said many, many bad things about me at work.&nbsp; He is very, extremely persuasive with people and very good at it...so I'm sure the people at work are totally convinced of his version of our divorce story.&nbsp; My six year old is convinced of his version. &nbsp; I'm just angry and I'm sure God knows it.&nbsp; I'm not afraid to tell Him, heck he knows what I'm thinking anyway...I can't pretend it's not there.&nbsp; I don't get it.&nbsp; I know things happen for a reason and we are led elsewhere sometimes...so am I not supposed to go to this church or is it just me being paranoid and I should just keep going.&nbsp; I've dealt with too many judgmental Christians lately and I'm pretty much not in the mood for it anymore. &nbsp; I have faith, so much faith in God.&nbsp; It's these times I think I am led elsewhere or may discover something if I could just listen to Him...but I don't think I'm hearing very well lately.&nbsp; I feel disconnected from that close relationship to Him.&nbsp; I was hoping vacation and the Christian music festival would revive that, but that's my hope.&nbsp; I'm not in control,&nbsp;He is.&nbsp; I don't know what He has in store for me right now, I'm just frustrated, confused and angry.&nbsp; I've got so many things buried inside.&nbsp; Again, it comes back to my attitude today...I am not having the faith that there is something in the plans...instead, I'm angry about it.&nbsp; Where is my faith today...I only see anger. 
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today my son told me that he hates me (just in conversation as we discussed life right now, not all up in my face). Luckily, I'm not the only one, he hates his dad too. And my 'boyfriend' and his dad's 'girlfriend.' I guess I can't blame him right now, because at six years old, his whole life as he knew it was shattered. Divorce is an ugly thing but I know in the long run, every one of us will be better off.   First he used the word mad, but then as we got talking,...hate came up. We were talking things through, so at least he is expressing himself. For awhile, his behavior was very aggressive and angry...now he's talking about what's bugging him. He does blame me for the divorce since I'm the one who wanted it. Hopefully, with time, the wounds will heal.   I wanted to go with him to the church picnic on Sunday but I've decided not to. Since this is a new church I've been going to and I've been keeping to myself, noone knows about my situation or about me. That's thanks to Christians I know from my old church. Some people have been so judgemental and I thought that's what 'Christians' were NOT supposed to be (I guess I shouldn't be judging them either, should I?). I've been very discouraged by the behavior of some people and don't want to be disappointed at the new church if I face the same type of people. So very unlike myself, I've been kind of a loner at church so far and just keep completely to myself.   I guess I used to be a 'Christian' like some people I know...they are on a different walk or path than I. Now I consider myself a 'Christ follower' thanks to the contemporary churches I've gone to, I like that term much better. When I was a Christian, I was the kind that said I am, but I didn't truly have Christ as my personal Savior then. I said it but you couldn't tell by my actions.   Now that I do, it is so different. When I accepted Jesus as my personal Lord and Savior, my life changed. That was only 2 1/2 years ago. I know I'm forgiven, but I also know I will continue to sin. I can only try my best to follow Christ and what I read in the Bible. With the strength of the Holy Spirit, I've become a better person. People know I'm a Christian (Christ follower), not because I say it, but because I try to live it...even with all the mistakes I make. I fall over and over again, but He is always at my side.   Nothing else in this world can lift me up as high as my relationship with God, absolutely nothing else.   So hate may be a harsh word, but the love of God can overpower anything. 
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, yes I'm very happy about vacation...but...I really wish I had the ambition to go on a diet. Like I have enough shorts to take on vacation, yah right (because they don't fit...how depressing). Anyway, I gave in and went shopping today (like I have the money...not) and bought me a new pair of shorts. Of course, I couldn't stop there and bought this really cute outfit...it just was perfect...not what I would typically even try on, but I love it.   I have told myself when I get home and the kids start school, I have to get serious about being healthier...eat better, exercise. I am very down about my body right now. Yah, yah...I know God accepts me and has created me as I am...but I would like to take what He created and treat it a little better. Plus it would be nice to have a little confidence. My confidence has been in the toilet lately.   Food is a comfort thing...I hate that. I just have to be determined enough to do it...I've been there before and done it. I do hate going on vacation feeling fat. There's something about going home where everyone that knows me there, knows the skinnier version of me. 
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm getting rather excited...vacation is almost here...only 1 week away. In the past many years, my vacations have been somewhat stressful...but this one will be different. I'm FREE! Free to make decisions, free to have some fun, free to say and do whatever, free to be myself, free to go out DANCING, free to go to places I love without hearing crap about it, just free to have a vacation like I want...where I grew up...with my family and friends that I miss so much!   I look over the past years and see how much I missed, how much I didn't do because it wasn't worth the fight. It's so crazy. How could I change so much of me...though I know the answer to that one...it was survival. To survive in the relationship I was in, I had to change to make it tolerable. I lost myself, who I really I am, the person that makes me, ME...and that wasn't good at all.   I'm trying to get that person back, and figure out again just who that person is. I am so much happier though. Thank you God. Though maybe I'm being a little selfish and wanting happiness for me...living in a self-gratification mode right now...but I'll come back. I'm trying to redefine myself. I know it's not all about me and what I want, it's what God wants. I just have a process to go through because I've been lost so long...not lost without Jesus, because I've had Him by my side helping me to get here...but rather, lost in life circumstances that made me someone I didn't like to be.   I have a long train ride to reach my vacation destination and I plan to bring my Bible, some writing paper, and my creative imagination. Not only that, but a 4-day Christian music festival during vacation will light another fire to get me back on track with my faith. It's there, I've just lost sight of it at times lately. 
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Seeking refuge while in this place A place we call home it's only temporary just as God created it to be Just a place for now til we fade away our souls leave in flight and sail to the heavens where our Lord awaits us We stand to face him I'm thankful He forgives for I'm a sinner as we all are and when I ask Him He forgives and forgets still by my side day by day even when my heart and mind are far, so far away from all I know he gives I just can't seem to be everything he wants me to I struggle to achieve but I know He accepts me for me
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      God is so amazing!  If you seek Him, if you listen, He will be there and provide.  I needed something to get me out of my mood I was in the past few days...and alas, there it is.  Church was really good last night.    One small portion of the sermon just spoke out loud and clear in regards to how I've been feeling.  I just felt messed up this past week and was unclear to exactly why.  The sermon was on accepting responsibility and the part that hit home was the part about Choosing my Attitudes.  "Be made new in the attitude of your minds." (Ephesians 4:23).  I was so caught up in emotions that I forgot to keep my attitude in check and it brought me down.  My last post said I felt I was the glass half-empty type this week, but Jesus helps me be the glass half-full type...optimistic and positive throughout any circumstances.  "I can do everything with the help of Christ who gives me the strength I need." (Philippians 4:13).  I just needed to hear that stuff again and be reminded that I can do all things through Him.  That portion of the sermon also talked about Thankfulness...and praising God no matter what the circumstance.  I do that and continue to try to do that even though my life has had some bad circumstances lately.  It helps me to see the good in my life when surrounded by the bad.  There is always lots to praise God for if you just seek it.  When I praise God continually, I see Him working in my life...again, He is so amazing.  When I left church, my spirits were so lifted...it didn't take much...it just took the help of God and my ability to open up to Him.  He's always there, just sometimes I get caught up in my own world and don't turn to Him.  The ride home (or actually to Jerime's) was awesome because I felt a load had been lifted that had been weighing me down all week.    I don't know how I lived my life before I found Jesus...lost, I guess...because life is so much easier to bear with my Lord always by my side.  God bless!
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate feeling vulnerable...  It sucks in a big way!  I also hate having too much crap on my mind.  But, I'm off to church to feed my weary soul.  It needs it.  I wonder what the message is today...hmmmm...  I look too dressed up for church though, I'm used to wearing jeans...but I'm going out tonight so I'm already ready.  It just feels weird after dressing down in church for so long.  Well, gotta get going.  Out to my hot, no air-conditioning, stupid car that the radio doesn't come in decent (boy, that sounded optimistic...lol...so unlike me...I think the glass has been half-empty the past few days!)
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I woke up this morning to your gentle eyes looking into mine.  I feel so lucky to have you.  I never imagined that this would have happened, but it did.  There wasn't any effort or trying to make things happen, it just happened and here we are.  It's not some magical, heart-pounding, butterflies in my stomach type thing (even though you do make me feel that way at times).  Instead, it's a peaceful, open, take all of me type thing.  I don't have to pretend to be something for you, I can just be me...and you can accept that.  I'm not afraid.  I don't worry about doing something wrong, or that you won't like me when I'm myself.  I just do what I do, act the way I act, feel the way I feel, say the things I say, and you accept that.  I feel comfort in your arms and an openness that I couldn't experience in the past.  I love to give to you because I want to, not because it's expected of me.   And you give back because you want to and I don't expect it.  It's a two-way street with us, and neither one is in control.  We are able to share and care for the other person.  I love being there for you and I love knowing that you are there for me when I need you.  You are so gentle and kind, but yet passionate.  I love the way you look at me now, I can see how much has changed between us.  I feel that way too.  Again, it surprises me because I never expected this to happen with you.  I'm so glad it did because I cannot imagine not having you right now.    Remember the first time we hung out.  I had prayed many times, asking God why?  Why was I supposed to reach out to you...I couldn't understand, but I felt it was what I was supposed to do.  So that is what I did even though I felt foolish at the time.  I felt really weird talking to you that first time, but I'm so glad I followed God's will for me.  He led me to you.  I don't know why for sure (I have my thoughts about it), but I'm glad He did.  You've been here for me during a tough time and I leaned on you so much and I needed you.  Out of all that, I've found so much more.  I found someone and something that I never thought was possible in my past.  Someone that respects me, accepts me for me, is giving, kind, passionate, fun, honest, comforting, responsible, accepting, not angered easily, takes life day by day, willing to do new things, and very, very cute.  I am incredibly attracted to you, not just because you're cute, but because of who you are...the whole package.  You don't ever pressure me and you allow me to make decisions for myself.  Then when I do, you respect them.  Like I said, I am so lucky.  I thank God for you, Jerime.  And I thank you for being you, you are so amazing.
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      If I could describe my life in a nutshell, what kind of nut would I be?  That's it, it's time for bed...lol!  I can do tomorrow what I didn't get done today because it will still be there waiting for me.  I'm also sleeping in...I need it.
      
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's late and I should be going to bed (or doing some computer work) but instead I'm playing around on the computer, again.  Actually, I'm waiting also.  Waiting for what, you ask? :)  I wanted to write tonight on a christian website www.faithwriters.com where they host a writing challenge weekly, but again, I am playing on the computer instead.  I feel this incredible sense to avoid responsibility over the past few days.  It's been awhile since I had personal time to myself to accomplish things that need done.  Now here it is, I have a little time, and I have a huge list...a list too long to be accomplished in the time I have to do these things.  So far, I've avoided getting started.  But that ends tomorrow because tomorrow I'm going to start.  Or will I?  :)  Or maybe I should just start RIGHT NOW...that makes sense even though it is almost 3:00 AM.   
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, ever since I spilled coffee on my mouse (imagine that, coffee), my scroll bar goes crazy...sometimes I am trying to work and the scroll bar is scrolling up and down when I'm not even touching the mouse...freaky!  Anyway, I had a good cry today...which I'm sure I needed.  Now if I could just stop eating because of stress.  I should pray about it but I feel my eating habits are something  I should be able to control...obviously not.  I just feel quite selfish if I pray about something that would improve my looks.  Okay, forget this, my scroll bar is now bouncing up and down and I can't even read what I am typing...wait...it stopped...okay, wishful thinking.  Anyway, stress level is high but I'm making it okay, yeah right...eating my way to comfort myself...how self-destructive.  Yes, I do need to pray for help there because I cannot do it on my own.  I have a new place I am going to submit some stories to for possible publication.  I think I'm gonna work on submitting more than one...true life prayer story type of stuff.  gotta go because my computer is driving me nuts! 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Where are you Why am I lost Where have I gone To feel I've turned away again  Refreshing as life seems Recently I felt you near But I still face struggles And cry my tears  I want to feel you Know you're close by Here by my side Guiding my path  But instead deep inside I find myself guided By my own thoughts And losing my way  I felt inspired again And then reality hit I want to hide away And ignore what's ahead  So help me right now I really need you I need your voice To help me face these days   Copyright 2004, all rights reserved. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, here I am...back from vacation.  Vacation was AWESOME!!!  This vacation was the best trip back home since I moved away 7 years ago.  I loved it.  I had so much fun and felt so free to make my own choices and do what I wanted to do.  On the other hand, I definitely did not look forward to getting back to reality...and reality is hitting me hard.  I had 2 days of turmoil and stress and I'm trying to not let it get to me...taking one thing at a time.  I hate regret!  There are things I regret and I can't take them back...they are the things that have landed me in my current crappy position.  Getting a divorce sucks (and costs way too much money!), and living in Indiana totally sucks.  But alas, that is my predicament and I must face it because of bad choices I made.  On the brighter side, there are many positives that have come from the past 3 years and living here; one is that I accepted Jesus as my Lord and Savior...that coming from facing a very distressing marriage that sent me into depression and thoughts of suicide...in the darkness I found the light of my Lord who saved me from the bottomless pit of life I had fallen into; two, I found a fantastic friend (who lived in this sucky state at the time) that helped me learn so much about myself that I never had realized before; and three, I now with God's guidance found someone that I share a relationship with that I never thought possible for me.  Even in my stressful state of mind today, I know God is amazing.  I sincerely praise him for the amazing things he does give to me.  If I just get the crap out of my head that's wearing me down and look at what is so wonderful in my life, how can I go wrong.  I am truly blessed. 
      
</post>


</Blog>