<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   writing..mmm... i love to write, it..uh..releases me,. the only other time i feel free and closest to myself is when i run on the ring road. the funny thing about running is that tho' i was good and won a coupla medals, yet it was only when i quit competing and ran 'cos it was what i wanted to do that i started having fun. same with writing i guess,&nbsp;the moment i'm aware that people will read 'me' i stiffen up and start to add frills and stuff and&nbsp; in the end just seem silly. facing that great dilema that every writer faces. who should i write for? be true to myself? entertain the sheep?[no offence intended]. have a mondo writer's block.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; it's cloudy right now. man i wish i could have a mug of coffee. hoping that laura will get the hint and actually brew me some. this capuccino, frapuccino, al-pacino stuff is ok, but give me south-indian filter kapi anyday.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   

						
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     &nbsp; yeah yeah i know thats a silly pic. hey i wanted try what kan told me and at that moment i could'nt find any pics,just one of joey's cartoons.&nbsp; &nbsp;so cool huh? i can post a pic,i can post a pic!! bring out out the wine and dancing girls.&nbsp; &nbsp; urlLink     

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   last night i was in  urlLink laura 's house and i tried to post a pic, tried being the operative word here.i was at it for more than two hours and i just gave up.man it's easier to build a thermo-nuclear device than to get a pic to appear.either that or the 'pulao and chicken curry' did a number on me.&nbsp;  it was also joannes birthday ,i had gone there to wish her and ended up celebrating for her, cos she was too busy eating 'italian' pizzas and savouring malyalee cooking.&nbsp;  Laura, urlLink kan  and i&nbsp;had gone shopping for her and during that time i had an ephiphany,actually i was tired and in all the "euphoria" that shopping induces in me i realised a few things.&nbsp;  i am known to do things in a hurry and more than what is required  urlLink jej  calls it impulsive i prefer to be addressed as the "extra mile man".[ i know,i know...i gotta change.]she also says marrying may cure me a bit...hmmm, there's a constructive idea.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; so everything is ready and the stage is set,i even know the florist. all i need to do is find a girl who is willing to marry me and&nbsp;&nbsp;i am cured, of my impulsiveness.ta da!!  [forgive the sarcasm,had a long day]  anyways, i'll have dreams tonight of lakes and memories. good night.      

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i got this mail from a friend, she says that&nbsp;my e-&nbsp;mails are&nbsp;like haiku poetry. short and precise. yeah right! check out this one   "Tsuki no ku wo haite herasan gama no hara"  this translated means is .&nbsp; a moon verse - belching will reduce the toads belly.  what does that mean?? and my writing is like that hmmm.   

						
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						       July 15th    &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; The Internet operators are on a strike. I’m forced to type on a note pad hoping that I can post when I do get online...in all this I forgot my post.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I went with a friend to pick up his kids from their school. I don’t have to talk about Bangalore’s wonderfully unpredictable weather, add this our previous chief minister's plan to employ a special team from somewhere to do "cloud seeding" [or at least that’s what I think it is.] And we get the "fox's wedding"  &nbsp;&nbsp; Anyways we were delayed by 45 minutes. When we got to the school the youngest who is 5 had been crying for sometime. My friend looked at her and said something that was very touching. He picked her up held her up to his face and said "sweetheart your mother and your father have never forgotten you and will never forget you. Even if it gets dark just know that we will come to get you, just play and enjoy yourself till we come"  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; It was amazing, when I heard that, I realized that the same conversation happens between the Father and me. Sometimes I wait for Him to show up and make everything all right and there is no sign of Him, I usually have one of the two responses. Either I get angry with Him or I begin to cry. Both reactions not complimenting my supposed confession of whom I understand Him to be, or what relationship I share with Him. I read in Isaiah 49:15,16 that even if my parents forget me, He will no, because He has tattooed me on His hand!!  &nbsp;    July 16th    &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Last night I walked in the rain with Laura, talking about wisdom and God's free gift. I realize that I miss that...I miss not caring and not being worried about what will happen if I get wet.  [I love the Bangalore rain, it feels nice on the skin, just a bit warm. when I was in Nagaland the rain there was cold...i mean freezing cold!! the air in Nagaland is purer though'.]  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    July 17th    &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Today was the launch of  urlLink Worship2004 Professional . It did not go as we expected. Crowds did not swamp us. There was no need for our well-rehearsed moves to manage the crowds and prevent them from destroying our kiosk. We sold two demos.  &nbsp;&nbsp; In all this I still know that God is in control.  &nbsp;    July 18th    &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; For the past three days i have been baby-sitting three kids. They are really very cute. The oldest is 8 and the youngest is 1. Saturday night I went crazy, Joshua wants to experiment with the effect of steel on marble floors, Nadine wants to sit on my lap, nevermind that I am 'standing' near the microwave. Nicole quizzes me on what the aftermath of a microwave 'accident' would be like and what would they do if I died before their mom came back. Took me the better of an hour to get my food from the microwave onto the plate and into my stomach.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Now I am free. This morning at 4:30 I picked up their parents and when Nadine woke up she saw her father and walked up to him and asked him "why you didn’t come to my house?”. He just grabbed her and she slept on his shoulder. Nothing like a fathers shoulder to sleep on.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;      

						
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Well where do I start there...... I was hanging of a rope that's supposed to be made to handle 150 kgs. And I have this flash of brilliance... "Start a blog" me mind says, well the rest like they say is history and so I sit at this computer tapping away at the keyboard as fast as I can with my perfected two finger technique.&nbsp;    &nbsp;  i started window cleaning because it was something different, something people don't generally think of as a smart career choice.&nbsp;i just love the fact that i can rappell down glass surfaces. the rush is amazing. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; the nice thing about window cleaning is that I get time alone with myself to observe and analyze&nbsp; of-course Roland says that I micro analyze, this helps me with my focus,but more importantly it helps me appreciate life.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; "..Life in fullness..!!" [John 10:10]that's what I want  I guess I write for myself as anybody because that's what this is - a reminder that I have a great life.       

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   day 8 of the training...i guess i'll stop with that. last night J-man, granma, fox and i went to see a movie. we went for 'scream', also called spiderman2. i'm bored and  sleepy...and bored and sleepy...sleepy.  

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   sitting in the training room waiting for the persecution to begin. i just saw  urlLink j-man  create his own blog. aww man the trainer walked in i gotta go 

						
</post>


</Blog>