<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i really don felt any love from any of my caregroup members... i  talk to sharlene about it and i am still trying very hard to get  along with them but i STILL don felt any care that had shown  (if they have)it's a really bad test from God, but i really wan to pass this testand take up a new test from Him, but how am i going to another test when i have not even pass one... i can give up my friendship's love but i can't give up my sister's and brother's love as we are also still in this family ... but today while we are  having our caregroup meeting, their love is what i wan, the  laughter, jokes, and the love that i have sense ... but i know that this won't last long, only during meeting... and now my sheep is not growing in the Word of God, her mature in Spirit and  everything that show to me, i don really allow what she had done, i wan her listen more to leader, don complain...ang God help me to grow ... i wan to grow big time for the Lord i really desire a lot  ....in Jesus' name i will GROW!!!      
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      oh... yes, school reopen liao, i must chiong on all my stuff, like the SOW,evax, shepherding, study and the commitment. i cannot be  scare to share but really chiong all the way. today is my 1st day  and of course there is a big change in my timetable and in church, i no longer a care leader anymore, but a core team of east c 2 but  it's ok to me cos i am actual quite stress lead st. hilda and now  ... thanks to God, he answer my prayer, st.hilda is under "jolene" and now she is also my shepherd, ya is no longer sharlene but is  back to jolene. can said than the change really hurt me a lot but  i don really mind becos the changes is good for God's kingdom, so  it's ok to me...but the changes in my class is better now... they start talking to me again, and i also don really mind of what they  did to me last term of school ... and from am i can't slack anymore if not i won't grow spiritually.... and my goal is to be very mature in christ...    
      
</post>


</Blog>