<Blog>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jared Cordes, another Wisconsin Runner in the steeple, made it through to the steeple final, also.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Wisconsin Runner's own Isaiah Festa made it through to the steeple final.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Jearl Miles-Clark, 800m victor, on her victory lap.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A happy Hurd with the new American Triple Jump Record.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night Marion dominated in the long jump by a foot, and then broke down during her post-win interview.&nbsp; I can't imagine the pressure she was under.&nbsp; And yesterday we found out that Torri Edwards had tested positive for a stimulant back in April, I believe.&nbsp; Of course, she blamed it on some glucose supplement she was taking.&nbsp; I'm so sick and tired of athletes blaming supplements for their positive tests.&nbsp; What these athletes need to start doing is acting like professionals.&nbsp; If you don't know what your ingesting into your system, then don't ingest it.&nbsp; Seriously, are these people idiots?&nbsp; You're going to get tested so know what your taking.&nbsp; I have no sympathy or patience anymore. &nbsp; As long as I'm talking about drugs, what was up with LeMond?&nbsp; If has proof of Armstrong and drugs, then show it.&nbsp; If he doesn't, then he needs to shut up.&nbsp; I lost all respect for him.&nbsp; I'm just going to keep believing that Lance is legal.&nbsp; He hasn't failed a test, and nobody has credible proof as to his guilt.&nbsp; Maybe Le Mond has some that he's hiding from all the rest of us, and when Lance crosses the line in Paris he's going to show us everything.&nbsp; What an idiot!&nbsp; It's certainly interesting to note the comments about the French press not wanting to see an American with six Tour wins.&nbsp; Le Mond.&nbsp; If I had never heard of him before, he would sound like a French reporter. &nbsp; It's too bad Groose didn't make it in the 1500m.&nbsp; The quarterfinals were last night, and I believe he could have advanced through to the semifinals.&nbsp; He missed the Trials by .6 seconds.&nbsp; That has to be tough.&nbsp; Woodworth flew in last night, and she'll run tonight.&nbsp; Good luck, Liz! &nbsp; The men's steeple final was great.&nbsp; No screwing around.&nbsp; They went after it.&nbsp; The top five hit the Olympic A standard.&nbsp; They were through the fourth lap at 4:22.&nbsp; Yowser!&nbsp; Lincoln's kick was spectacular.&nbsp; Fam was pumped after his race--the only one that did a post race lap.&nbsp; And Gary, at 31, looked great too.&nbsp; He's staying at our Extended Stay.&nbsp; Now I just need to print off a picture I have of him so he can sign it. &nbsp; Festa ran well.&nbsp; He missed third by about a second.&nbsp; Cordes, I can only imagine, didn't have the race he wanted.&nbsp; It was till cool to see the two Wisconsin Runner team members in the final.&nbsp; Sandu Rebenciuc, the former DIII runner at Augustana, DNFed.&nbsp; I never saw what happened, and I never saw him leave the track. &nbsp; Another DIII guy, Andrew Rock, had a rough final.&nbsp; Don't get me wrong, he ran fast.&nbsp; Really fast.&nbsp; 44.96 fast.&nbsp; Unfortunately, most of the other guys ran faster.&nbsp; Rock didn't look like his normal self in the race.&nbsp; He looked tight, and he didn't seem to get a great first 200m.&nbsp; He kept himself in it though, and his time was awesome. &nbsp; Finally, the women's steeple.&nbsp; I have no idea what is being shown on TV, but if you had a chance to see this race you could have laughed, cried, and just generally been amazed.&nbsp; Briana Shook led the whole way.&nbsp; She ran 9:31.&nbsp; It could have been an American record.&nbsp; But in the end she was DQed.&nbsp;  &nbsp; It all happened on the start of the second lap where the runners are supposed to take the first water jump.&nbsp; Well, Briana forgot to do that.&nbsp; The replay of her mistake went up on the board shortly after the yellow flag went up.&nbsp; I was in total disbelief.&nbsp; How does that happen?&nbsp; As a runner, you should&nbsp;know&nbsp;your race.&nbsp; It's that&nbsp;simple.&nbsp; On the other hand, aren't there supposed to be officals kind of herding them into the water pit.&nbsp; Don't get me wrong, the&nbsp;blame is still&nbsp;on&nbsp;Ms. Shook, but I still found it odd.&nbsp; The&nbsp;sad part was that she ran the next six laps leading and winning.&nbsp; I don't know&nbsp;when she figured out that she missed it.&nbsp; She still ran.&nbsp; She still won, and she still did a post race lap as if she had won.&nbsp; Whether she knew&nbsp;by then, I haven't heard.&nbsp; All she&nbsp;said about missing the water was that she was looking down, not really paying attention, while&nbsp;she was running.&nbsp; It's&nbsp;so terribly comic; sad and funny at the same time. &nbsp; Oops, it's time to go.&nbsp; This evening session should be another good one.&nbsp;&nbsp;There's going to be some fun distance stuff.&nbsp;&nbsp;More&nbsp;photos soon.&nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This vacation requires more work than I thought.&nbsp; Marion had a tougher time than I thought she would with the 100m.&nbsp; I expected her to make it--even if she was going to have a rough time.&nbsp; I never expected her to be eliminated.&nbsp; She certainly dominated the long jump, though.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  How about Montgomery?&nbsp; He hadn't looked good in any of the heats.&nbsp; How he got through to the final is what amazed me the most.  &nbsp;  As for the vaulters, I have mixed feelings.&nbsp; It was fun to watch, but then some of them started with the celebrating that just became annoying and over the top.&nbsp; I felt like the only reason they wanted to make the height was so that they could dance on the mats.&nbsp; Maybe some of y'all like that, but I just found it stupid.&nbsp; Not even the sprinters were as bad.  &nbsp;  Monday's session was easily the best so far.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; Because I love the distance races.&nbsp; Steeples, 5Ks, 800s:&nbsp; all good stuff.&nbsp; The women's 5K final an awesome race.&nbsp; I'm so happy that Shalane Flanagan made it.&nbsp; She deserved it.&nbsp; She led from about 150m until she was out kicked at the finish.&nbsp; She was the only one that had the courage to lead the race.&nbsp; At about 100m into the race the field slowed to a walking pace (the fans didn't like that) and nobody would take the lead.&nbsp; That is until our heroine Shalane went to the front and forced a good race.&nbsp; People willing to take that risk deserve to make it.&nbsp; It was a happy ending.  &nbsp;  Tuesday and Wednesday there were no events, obviously.&nbsp; We toured the Jelly Belly factory with other swarms of kids.&nbsp; We bought some jelly beans and other stupid souvenirs.&nbsp; I shouldn't say stupid.&nbsp; I did get a long sleeve t-shirt; good for running.  &nbsp;  On Wednesday we took a drive to Lake Tahoe.&nbsp; It's a beautiful drive through the mountains and the water in Tahoe is gorgeous.&nbsp; We timed our trip just right.&nbsp; Wildfires broke out that morning near Carson City and we could see the smoke rising from the other side of the ridge on the east side of Tahoe.&nbsp; I didn't actually see any flames when we were driving down into the valley the lake was in, so we went about checking out the beaches, hiking a few trails, and driving around the lake. &nbsp; It was last night that the action resumed.  
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Meb and Abdi catching Ritz for the first time.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Abdi on the victory lap&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Davis and Shay before they stopped.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The beautiful track on the first day.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      10:30 (Sac Time)  Well, I'm sure you've all seen that Marion didn't make it through.  I mentioned that I thought she would have a rough time getting through, but I really didn't expect her not to make it.  Obviously, Devers didn't make it either.  I was somewhat surprised.  Also, in the men's shot put, Cantwell was the odd man out.  It didn't help his cause that he had one throw for a mark.  Ahhh, and now to the important stuff.  The men's 800m saw Robinson and Peterson in the first heat--they both advanced.  In the other heat, Burley pulled off an awesome run at the finish.  He went from fifth to first in the last 150 meters.  Granted, this was only a semifinal, but it was still fun to watch.  The final should be great.  The women's 800m was a great one, too.  The clarks ran fast.  That was to be expected.  Teter was to be expected, too, and she looked impressive.  She led her heat the whole way.  She never looked challenged--complete control of the race.  There's not much happening today.  Not on the distance side anyway.  The men's 100m final should be fun.  I'm actually kind of glad it's a short day today because it's going to be hot!  Tomorrow will be one of my dream days.  Lot's of distance and mid-distance.  Oops, I almost forgot.  The 400m today with Rock.  That is something I'm looking forward to.  On a less track related area, security around here is tight.  Metal detectors, bag checks before you can get in.  Explosive sniffing dogs running around with their ATF handlers.  If there's one thing I miss about the 2000 Trials, it is the freedom.  I guess it really is a small inconvenience when I consider what some of the possible alternatives to be.  But it's damn hot waiting in line.  We'll just get there earlier.  
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Abdi, Meb, Kennedy, and Browne lead the 10K early on.&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The only final today was the 10K.  What a race!  Meb, Abdi, Browne, and Kennedy broke away early.  And then Kennedy dropped out early with a strained achillies.  I was rooting for Kennedy, but it was not to be.  Browne eventually fell off the back leaving Meb and Abdi to run together.  And then Meb just pulled away.  The most interesting part of the race happened late.  Both Shay and Davis stopped a lap early.  I'm seated on the backstretch so I saw Davis start to pick it up at about 300, and I figured he was going to make a long surge to the finish.  (Meb finished in a 61)  I watched Davis go buy, and then people started yelling that Shay had stopped like he was done.  When he realized he had stopped too early, it was too late.  He struggled home.  While Shay was struggling to get going again, Davis ran through the finish line like he was done.  And then he realized he wasn't done.  In the end Davis caught Shay and passed him.  The two "early finishers" struggled mightily, and they might have cost themselves a chance at the Olympic 10K.  I'm not sure how they got the idea that they were done.  Meb and Abdi hadn't finished yet, and Meb and Abdi had led the whole way.  In fact Davis was battling Meb to prevent himself from getting lapped by Meb.  Then again, I would never run the 10K--it's way too long and it takes too much concentration for my small brain, and I think that was evident here.  Ritz finished, but it was obviously a tough night for him.  I'm not sure why he was running in the first place.  I guess it's a tough call, but if you know you're hurt, why would you take away a spot from somebody that is healthy?  That actually happened a couple of times today.  And, of course, they always get the sympathy clap.  I won't give it to them because I'd rather see somebody healthy running.  Buttry ran really well.  Toshner probably did as well as he could.  It was cool to see some DIII athletes out there.  It looks like Groose won't get in.  I believe Woodworth will.  Marion Jones got suprised today.  The 100m could be tough for her this time around.  On a differnet note, I was disappointed in the t-shirt designs.  They need someone that can design a good t-shirt.  That didn't stop me from blowing $60 on a t-shirt and sweatshirt.  So maybe they don't need a better designer.  The weather has been beautiful out here, but it's suppposed to start getting warmer--mid 80s and low 90s.  I haven't even looked at the schedule yet, but I know the 800 rounds are up today.  At least I hope they are.   I'll try posting again tonight or tomorrow morning.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      12:40 (Sac Time)  We're here!  Unfortunately, the place we're staying doesn't have any high speed access.  They only have a 56k data port on the side of their phone.  Ugh.  So, I'll be posting from the Kinkos down the street from our hotel.  And I was too tired to post last night when I found out we didn't have any access.  The meet starts in about three hours.  The weather is perfect.  It's not as hot as last year...yet.  Other than that, there is not much to report until the action gets started.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A test&nbsp; urlLink     Photo posting test.  This bodes well for the future.  The photo is faithful to the original and it was so easy to post.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is my first post.  Despite the name of the blog this will most likely have nothing to do with baseball.  Although, the Brewers might get a couple of comments.  Who would have thought?  I can thank Cukes for the name of this blog.  Cukes and I ran track (and Cross Country) at UW-Oshkosh together--mostly the steeplechase.  Anyway, he was Mr. Statistic.  It didn't matter the sport, he was always trying to memorize averages, draft picks, number of Gatorade showers, etc.  Sometimes our team used to waste away the time on the way to far away meets by quizzing each other from a sports almanac.  If Cukes wasn't quizzing us, he was firing off correct answers before I even could comprehend the question.    So he introduced me to the Mendoza Line.  It is a batting average. .200 or .250, I'm not real sure.  And honestly, I really don't care because baseball is not one of my favorite sports.  It was just a fun little nickname, and it reminds me of some good running times.  Beth (my wife for those of you that don't know me) and I leave for Sacramento tomorrow morning at five.  It's Olympic Trials time!  I plan to add a post each night, and I might even add some photos if I can.  The last trials, also in Sacramento, were a blast.  It's impossible (if you're a track and field fan) not to be excited.  This is the cream of America's crop battling it out for three spots on the Olympic team.  Every race means something.  I was lucky enough to run in a few Division III National Meets, and I thought I was nervous then.  I can't even begin to imagine how big the butterflies are in the stomachs of the athletes when they walk to the starting line.
    
</post>


</Blog>