<Blog>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Word of the Day: crocker sack; See gunnysack   Random Words of Wisdom: if you ever shoot a gun, don't forget about your foot. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      word of the day: enthalpy; A thermodynamic function of a system, equivalent to the sum of the internal energy of the system plus the product of its volume multiplied by the pressure exerted on it by its surroundings.   random words of wisdom: T.N.T. stands for, Tri Nitro Toluene
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "i like pie" then "I do. With berries "
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "pop goes the weasel and XOXOXO" was exactly wut the thermometer said to the cat as he killed him with a cup filled with bannana berry kool-aid and tropicana orange juice.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The Eye Of Truthfulness is Ever Watchful&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Most people do not know that Pseudo-pod means "false foot" they also dont know about fizzy ring tailed-lizards.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      an ostridge and a 3 legged turtle are walking along the beach. then the ostridge turns to the turtle and says: "how do u lay eggs?". the turle looks at his tail and says: "eggs?". so the ostridge sits on the turtle and farts right b4 running off into the water and sticking it's head in the sand under the water. then the turtle, after being gas poisened by the deadly ostridge fart, lays some eggs in the sand and poops on them. then he runs up into the ostridge's butt. after passing out from suffacation becuz it's head was under water, the ostridge wakes up on the beach. 2 weeks later the ostridge dies from fecal matter build up (couldn't poo) do to blockage in its rear end. when the zoo keeper buried the ostridge he dropped a chicken egg (the kind u get in the store in styrafoam thingys) on the grave knowing the ostridge never had kids. just then built up gas from the butt caused the carcaus to explode, but due to it being buried under ground only the gas seeped through the dirt and up out of the grave. becuz the fart gas was deadly it killed the zoo keeper with its toxin. then the sky hailed chocolate flashlights and lucky rabbits feet.   true story
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The alligator is the only known animal in the world that can and does fart out of its mouth.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      as the personal administarter of this site i apoligize for the lack of content. it is so new the new site smell hasn't even been installed yet. so we hope u will be patient with us and bountiful with your comments.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hallo und wilkommen.  word of the day: didle ;to jerk up and down or back and forth  random words of wisdom: skunks are nocternal animals, so if u see one in the day, do not aprroach it. it is most likely rabid.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey, we need help. things are getting slow, bad slow, nothing hopping anymore. so, give us help. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Word of the Week: "picaroon" ; a pirate, a pirate ship, to act as a pirate     Random Words of Wisdom: learn to throw a fit before leanring to throw a knife, that way we're both in the fox hole. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>