<Blog>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Anyway, it's been ages, so let's get up to date.  What have I done:  ...uh...I won a giant fish at one of those games in the arcade, we were only there because the pool was shut though, but the fish kinda rocks...  ..wow!&nbsp;&nbsp;Haven't I been busy!?  Oh yeah, CAMP TOMOROW!&nbsp; Well, technically the day after because we leave early in the morning, but we have to get to the place at 8pm tomorow, (if I'm awake...) so yeah, it starts tomorow I guess.&nbsp; I'm pretty damn excited, especially since it's in Spain.&nbsp;   I will miss you all dearly,  I won't post for two weeks, but will tell all when I return, Yours sincerely, Jonny  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, So, what's up with me?&nbsp;  &nbsp; Well... So, two nights ago I slept at Alex's, ...or didn't sleep at alex's rather, kind of stayed up, hehe, t'was fun.&nbsp; Were five of us, including Alex, the day was fun to. &nbsp; Ok, so I go to my main man Sax's at like half two, and danny's there, who later leaves, and then me and Sax hang for a bit, then head off to Aarons, where we hang for a bit, and see Sam!&nbsp; (Who I haven't seen in literally years, he went to live in Wales),&nbsp; so that rocked.&nbsp; Then we went to mine, and the delivery chinese place was shut, as it is on tuesday's, so we ordered one and took the tube to west finchley to get it, we ate and then headed off for Alex's.&nbsp; The tube was fine, despite haven't to have just missed two trains in a row, and having to wait 7 minutes (yes, I know, seven minutes, I'm so hard done by..), we get to Golders Green, where we have to wait around half an hour for a f'n bus to come, one came just as we arrived, but just as we were going to get on, the 'out of service' sign came down, damn! &nbsp; Anyway, so me and Sax eventually arrive at Alex's palace at about half ten (weird, considering Sax had to leave at 11...meh..), and we're on the trampoline, as per usual.&nbsp; Danny, Re, and Fran were there, which I knew about, but Julian was to, hardcore!&nbsp; We talked on the trampoline for a few...hours, before going in to watch Terminator 2: Judgement Day.&nbsp; What a film!&nbsp; Seriously, one of the most rockin' sequels ever, and the best out of all three terminator films, Arnie is the man!&nbsp; We then chill for a bit, before watching Scary Movie 3, now that was just hilarious, I love that film, I have to watch it again sometime, simply brilliant, the second one was a bit of a let down, but this one really made up for it. &nbsp; Anyway, talking, blah blah, and Danny falls asleep, so we draw whiskers on his face, hehe, how childish are we?&nbsp; Julian and Fran are making out on the floor, yet I'm the only one who notices this, except Julian..and well, probably Fran as well.&nbsp; Danny wakes up and is pissed at the pen, but oh well. &nbsp; This was classic, you know how when you wake up in the night, you're kind of half asleep, and have no idea what's going on, well, anyway, we drew a beard on Re's face, and Julian woke up, and was like 'what the hell is on Re's face?', but we cleverly convinced him there was nothing there and he was hallucinating, and he fell for it, hehe... &nbsp; Anyway, it gets to about 5am, and we go on the trampoline again, it's already been fully light for at least an hour now, so no chance of sleep, Alex's attempt to get on the trampoline without getting his feet wet by using a method of laying down wood, the treading on it worked, but didn't seem like it was worth the trouble, meh.&nbsp; We woke his parents up, shit, but we went in.&nbsp; We then talked for a bit, except Fran was now with Alex, but I don't think they were doing anything, except like looking in each others eyes, and stroking each other (no, not like that..), but that was really cute and stuff.&nbsp; Anyway, we just chilled from then, and drew&nbsp;on Danny.... again, and Julian, and everyone, except me, because I am that hardcore!&nbsp;  &nbsp; The next day me, Julian and Re were discussing how Julian was practically having sex on the floor, (well, not quite), yet nobody but me noticed.&nbsp; Anyway, Julian/Danny/Re went out for a walk, while me and Alex slept, (I went to sleep at about 11am), and poor Fran was feeling sick, so she stayed.&nbsp; Anyway, I left about 1, and phoned my mummy, but she said they'd be nobody home, so I made a stop off at Aaron's for a bit, then went home, where I ate left over chinese, was good.&nbsp;  &nbsp; I then stayed in and played guitar/chilled, went to bed, woke up at like 4:30 the next day, played guitar/chilled, and here I am now, at almost half one, about to watch the DVD of 'Anger Management', whooo! &nbsp; Anyway, that was a long post that you probably didn't read, Keep on Sleepin', Jonny  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, Woke up this morning...uh...afternoon at like two, despite my mum's many attempts to get me out of bed, yeah..right.  Went downstairs, to see a piano on the hall, not bad, I should learn how to play that.    I played football for the first time in ageees today, my friend who's been in America for a few years moved back across the road, I'm not -that- bad, just pretty awful, considering his 10 year old sister totally owned me... but in my defence she's pretty good you know...  My parents went to some concert, and my sister went out, so I've been here on my own for the past 6/7 hours, and I've realised that I've done nothing, except do a bit of excercise, play guitar, and surf the net, but it felt like that time went quick, hmm...  I think I might actually leave the house tomorow, to see a friend...wow...  Anyway, if I do leave the house, something exciting might happen, like the time I saw a cloud, and it was an exact cuboid, with completely straight edges, and 90 degree corners, weird...  Keep on Truckin', Jonny 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       'Lo, So...*huff*...anyway..*huff*..I've...just..*wheeze* been..on...the ...ex..cercise machine...  Ok, so it's not that bad, but anyway, 500 calories in 40 minutes ain't bad...(..well, maybe it is considering I usually put on 500 in 4 minutes, but that's not important).  As for the goldeneye, we got to the jail thing, I think it's called bunker, on secret agent and got bored, so we did some multiplayer (where I lost 12-3! - oh yeah!) and then watched some of Wrestlemania XVI, -brings back memories.  Probably going to do more excercise/guitar playing tomorow...not too exciting.    Oh yeah, bowling last night was cool, and we met this Vai/Zappa fan, who saw them 7 times, what a dude, it also turns out the barman was a Vai fan, as well as an AC/DC fan, nice, small world, eh?  And I'd like to dedicate this paragraph to the man, who first decided to get a pizza, and fill the crust with Cheese, what a man, what a genius.  Anyway, you never know, something exciting might happen tomorow...or not.  ..Jonny 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ...So maybe the title was a bit over-dramatic, but none the less, the dreaded end of year school report has arrived.  My parents aren't the happiest of people about it, agh!  The comments from one of the staff, my deme warden (No idea how he got this name, he doesn't really have anything to do with me) said 'Doors are being shut', which my parents got very hung up about, not that I even understand what it means. *shrugs*  Anyway, Music/IT/Business Studies/Chemistry weren't to bad, where as german/english/maths/physics were quite appauling.  Over-all - not impressive.  I also have to see this deme warden fellow at 10am on the tuesday before school starts again, meh, I don't get up before 1 in the holidays, but I don't think asking to re-schedule this 'til about 4 is a good idea, I think they might interperet that as pushing it, and well... being rude.    Anyway, in other news, I've just got off the phone to my friend and partner in rock (how cheesy?) Zi, and it seems we're spending the whole of tomorow night going through golden-eye on the N64, from scratch.  We're hoping to finish it...should be fun.  I'll report tomorow with hopefully some good news, Jonny. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Blogs....they're cool...right?  I mean, it doesn't make me a geek because I post on an internet diary, does it?  It's fun.  And cool.    Is anyone going to re-assure me of this?  I mean, at least I don't claim I am t3h 1337 h4x0r or anything.  Besides, I came across some forum earlier, for various reasons, which was a programming one (agh, this isn't helping my case for not being a geek!) and there was the usual 'chat-up lines' thread that comes up on any forum, except these were like 'You want to get beneath the cascading style sheets?' - See, they are geeks! Not me!  Anyway, this post is pointless, and it's ten to one, agh, I'll post something worth reading tomorow..I promise..  Jonny. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Guitar, excercise, films, friends...pizza, the holidays aren't doing too badly so far, however the real fun starts in 17 days.  Camp! Whoooo! And you know what's even better? It's in Barcelona, I mean, not that I don't like London, but considering I was up last night at about half twelve, and it just randomly started raining, I mean, honestly, that's not how summer should be, should it?    I'm trying to lose some weight before I go, but ..meh, you know...anybody who has tried to lose weight will know how I'm feeling.  In other news, I'm addicted to frosties. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, turns out I do actually have a blog, as I went to set up, it turns out the name 'buddyfuzz' was already taken? Well, there is clearly only one buddyfuzz, so I tried to log in, and it worked!  Anyway, what's going on?  Well, school has officially finished for the summer, which is a relief, what with the awful exam results.  But I'll do better next year...yeah right.    I have camp in a couple of weeks, but apart from that it's two months of guitar playing/excercise...and seeing friends...and party's...and fun.. yay!  Anyway, I'll keep you updated, Jonny. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>