<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hedonism has begun!  Woke up oddly earlier than expected this morning, so laid in bed reading for a while. Finally couldn't ignore the bladder anymore, so shuffled my way towards watching cartoons for a bit. Wound up spending a good part of the day with my mum. She wanted to go hunt for a proper rain barrel, instead of the hacked up chunk of plastic she currently uses. So I mentioned I had seen a nice one at Golden Acres, and off we went. While there I fell in love with this tree/flower thing called a Pink Flower Maple. I've never seen a tree that looks like a bouquet before. It's more of an outdoor plant, so maybe someday I will have a place for it. Basement suites aren't conducive to plants. Also found out why a succulent plant is called that (the leaves are fat and filled with liquid). I love wandering around Golden Acres, and there weren't many people there either this time, which was nice. Since she had me captive, my mom decided that I could help her with some other labour intensive tasks, so we went to Totem to get some more lawn bark (I smelled like cedar chips the rest of the day), and then to Costco for a mound of food. It's impossible to spend under a hundred dollars there. They must have some sort of cross-dimensional monetary decoupler or something at the front door. "Your card? Thanks. [ZAP!] Have a good day." *smile*smile*.  Later, I wrecked havoc among the good citizens of Vice City. The FBI doesn't like me much, but I like their tricked out Ford Explorers. Ah needs me one! It would go nicely next to the SWAT truck I stole earlier. While making supper I tried to find some decent TV to eat by, but as usual it all sucks. I really need to cut my cable. I'd save a grand a year by doing it. Opted instead for the wonderfully campy movie, Johnny Mnemonic. William Gibson is my most favourite cyberpunk author, but it's a shame his work has never really been decently translated to movies. The Matrix drew, in part, a lot from his work, but even that wasn't spectacular (they really should have stopped after the first one). Keanu Reeves gave his expected stone-faced performance, and Ice-T was at the height of his confusion between being a rapper and an actor. Still, it was fun. Not as good as the book, but movies rarely are.     Song of the Day:  Hot Fun in the Summertime  by  Sly and The Family Stone   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thought it was going to rain today, so wore my hat. Got oogled by various women, coming and going, as a result. Cover up my greying, receding hair, and suddenly I'm interesting. One girl on the train in the morning kept casting subvertive glances my way. Her eyes said she was interested, but her body language was shouting that she didn't think she was good enough. I thought she was cute, but whatever. I'm not going to be drawn into the ridiculous peacock prance, and I don't talk to women on the street anyway.  Spent all day at work doing IT stuff. Which isn't really work, as far as I'm concerned. There's nothing physical to show for it when you're done. The people actually doing the work are the ones who use the computers to do other things. I think the only reason IT people make so much right now is because they're riding on a wave of ignorance. In another two generations, when everyone alive can configure a printer, and all the technically illiterate are dead, the idea of having an IT department will be quaintly outdated for all but the most intensive areas.   Today was definitely a metalhead day. Stayed with me all day too, which was cool. Went to work in a good mood, came home in a great mood, ready to start the long weekend. Rented two movies, and chatted with the nice clerk at the video store. She usually has a ton of hardware on her face, but it was all gone today, making it less distracting for me to talk to her. I wonder if she got in trouble for it. Hope not, because I think body art is interesting. Not that I would intentionally put holes in myself. I do that well enough by accident. I enjoyed Hell Boy, but it was obvious the transition from comic to movie script was tough. There were big character development holes, and scene transitions didn't always come off very smoothly. But it was still great; one more comic hero in a market extremely short on them. And Selma Blair is always a babe. Something about dark haired sulkers that makes me feel all cuddly. I wasn't expecting a lot out of Starsky and Hutch, and boy was I surprised. Ben Stiller kept his over-the-top performances to a minimum, and Owen Wilson was fun as always. I absolutely  loved  the car sequences. It made me want to fire up GTA:VC, but it was too late after the movie was over. Good thing it's the long weekend. I smell some virtual shit disturbing on the wind.    Song of the Day:  Du Hast  by  Rammstein   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been drug free for six days now in an attempt to get the crap out of my system. I can't stand taking anything, and I could smell that antihistamine crap whenever I was sweating. So now, in a tribute to my occasional deep breaths, I present a list of all the smells I encountered this morning, from the time I left my house, to the time I arrived at work...  1. Weather. Stepped outside and encountered the last vestiges of a storm, slowly disappearing on the wind.  2. Noticed that my near-butterscotch smelling lip balm was a lot more noticeable outside.  3. Walked past a lawn reeking of weedkiller.  4. The first bus I got on had the wonderful hint of dying orange. Some kid probably forgot their lunch behind a seat.   5. Getting off the bus I got a snootfull of some guy's cologne. I don't understand why people insist on making themselves a nasal exclamation point. I tend to breath out whenever passing people, to avoid that nasty burst of smelly air after they pass.  6. Woman on the train and her bad perfume.  7. Leather-bound stud standing next to me was sloughing off cow ions.  8. Leather-bound woman going through a mid-life fashion crisis.   9. The second train I got on had a strange biscuity smell to it. Like someone had just eaten animal crackers and was breathing up the place.  10. Got off second train and walked into cloud of strawberry gum and cheap perfume emanating from another over-the-hiller.  11. The second bus smelled like a dusty legume. Worrying.  12. Young woman getting off bus smelled like shampoo. The only pleasant smell I had encountered yet.  13. Industrial smog. You couldn't pay me to live in the southeast.  14. And finally, old, wet coffee grounds assailed me at work. I don't like coffee, and the smell doesn't do for me what it seems to do for others in commercials.   There you have it, my morning through the eyes of my nose. Usually, when my allergies aren't acting up, this stuff just glances off my awareness, but right now it's all very annoying. I feel sorry for people who are constantly overcome by all the unnatural smells they have to deal with in everyday life. I can see how it would destroy your quality of life, like having a really bad cold all the time. Thank Allah for majestic trees being turned into snot paper...        Song of the Day:  Duvet  by  BOA   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Down-right chilly this morning. I'm trying not to get my hopes up, but we may be in for  some  urlLink seasonal disturbances  if this continues. Had a fabulously productive day filled with much re-animation of abused technology. On the way home I was treated with a train stuffed full of interesting people. It was almost disconcerting, and they all got off at my stop. Fans, no doubt. The city continues to bleed populace, due to the slack-assed working conditions caused by the Stampede, and the upcoming long weekend. Somebody should just give in and declare July the non-productive month. I again got home very early (that's twice this month now. wow!), and caught my favourite toons in full.  Stepping through my front door (well, more like the rear, basement entrance), I'm often greeted by my number one devotee, my cat. She is the most intelligent animal I've ever known, most likely because I raised her, natch.    urlLink     Full of attitude, bursts of speed, a big mouth and a bigger stomach, she's a smaller version of me, with a little less hair. Here she's caught in the action of trying to take a playful chunk out of my finger.  My second cat, however, is a little less wealthy in the commodity of brains. She can get lost in a closet, and the sound of her litter being kicked around behind her will scare her out of the box, but she's really soft to hold. Witness her show off her ability to hold her leg in the air for an extended period:   urlLink      I love them both, and they keep me company. Horrible conversationalists until you get some tequila in them though. Then they won't shut up.      Song of the Day:  Josie  by  Blink 182   
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last night I dreamt that I tossed a cat into a near-empty mayonnaise jar. But he had it coming to him! He was chasing me and some other guy around a kitchen with a panel saw attached to his paw, and when that didn't get us, he started using the laser on the end of his tail! After I made him take a time-out in the jar for a bit, I let him out, and all was kosher. He even had a beautiful, healthy coat.  No more late-night peanut buttery snacks for me.   I work with a guy who emigrated from Fiji. In many ways it's cool, because I get to hear stories about growing up in a tropical paradise, and the history of British rule and how Indians came to be on the island. In other ways, it's not so great. Because of his youth, sheltered from all things American, a lot of stuff that I grew up with and subsequently discarded is very much new to him. Right now he's going through an adult contemporary music stage, and the radio is stuck on a station that plays the same twenty songs over and over all day. But wait, you say, be more specific. They all do that. I nod, thankful for my earphones. If it wasn't for the greatness that is ABBA, I'd go nuts. Oh Fernando, can you hear the drums?...  Arriving home tonight, I glanced at the new Maclean's cover right when the song of the day started. Oh universe, how you tease me with your flippant synchronicity. It would seem the millionaires of the world just don't have enough, and we should now call them "upper middle-class". About 600,000 Canadians are worth at least one million dollars, if you count family homes. Which you can't, of course, says the article, because of the crazy nature of real estate recently. So about half that are worth over a million, 2000 of those have over $25M, 60 have $500M, and only 30 poor Canadians are able to reach the heights of the billionaire's club. Tsk tsk.  Meanwhile the rest of humanity slowly separates from this group due to rising inflation and job outsourcing, thanks to the entire group's fanatic desire to pay less than the other guy. Watching society slowly destroy it's economy due to everyone's constant drive for  more  is hilarious. Fools.      Song of the Day:  Lifestyles of the Rich and Famous  by  Good Charlotte   
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last night would have been a great night to curl up next to someone. The wind turned chill, and blew through my room with much snobbery. Gave up waiting for anyone after a few hours, and put on a shirt. Thus did I wake up a tad grumpy, due to some missing REMs. Despite the best efforts of Grandpa Jed, my first-leg bus driver, I managed to catch the fourth-leg bus right before it drove off in a cloud of diesel. Work wasn't so great, with many broken things adamantly staying broken. This of course put me in a grumboly grump mood for much of the day, on top of the growing heat outside, and I was sooo ready to share the joy upon my fellow transit riders come hometime. Then I stepped outside. Praise be to Moses! It was downright brisk outside! I'm not a warm-weather person. Nordic genes and a healthy dose of fur make that possible. The cool air wrapped itself around me like an ice-queen's thong, and all my complaints ate my dust. The wimpy white-collar lot downtown must've run home to their fireplaces and cardigan sweaters early, because the trains were delightfully empty. I be-bopped my way home to some enjoyable tunage, noting the difference in attraction between my fellow passengers and the people just on the other side of the glass, in their cars. With the odd exceptions on both sides, of course. The lack of passengers ensured that I was early for my bus home, and I made it in time to catch some toonage. Note: tunage != toonage. Know your homonyms. Surfed for a bit, read for a bit; the usual.  A few hours after supper I realized I wasn't sufficiently sated, and went looking for a snack. Lo and behold, I found a tub of peanut butter hiding in the back of a cupboard. Half gone, with marks in it that looked like some Zombie Gerbil had forsaken cutlery. Then I remembered - I used to make peanut butter squares! Which reminded me of when I bought my casserole dishes...  The time, Xmas, 2003. The place, your typical Zellers. I had been wandering around in that male-induced last minute frenzy of buying family members such endearing gifts as tissue box warmers and pet hair rollers, when I found myself in the kitchen aisle at Zellers. There was a big mark-down on casserole dishes, four for something like ten dollars. Score! I added them to my pile, and made my way to the electronics checkout, where there weren't any lines, cause I'm crafty like that. Standing behind the counter was the usual Xmas Zellers employee, a dumpy, middle-aged woman, with giant glasses vying for space on her face currently taken by a big scowl, and enough back fat to keep  urlLink Jack  busy for a month. I gently laid the dishes on the counter, so as to not smash the glass display, and waited. She scowled at the dishes, and then scowled at me.    "You're certainly giving someone a lot of work."    I looked at her and gave her my cheeriest "It's Xmas shopping season and I love the chaos" smile, and said:  "These are for me."  Her scowl retreated a few steps, and she did the mercantile magic that produced my receipt and emptied my wallet. I thanked her and walked happily out of the store with my cookery full of potential. Lasagnas and buttery squares, oh my! Who knew you could actually make yourself sick after eating a pound of peanut butter, a pound of butter, a bag of icing sugar, and ohmygodweneedmore marshmallows all in two days.  WHO KNEW!?!?!   I certainly do now.     Song of the Day:  Graduate  by  Third Eye Blind   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today was chore day! Hooray! Hooray! Bleh. Dutifully did I tromp through all the little things I deem necessary of keeping my hovel livable. I even did the thankless job of washing one of the cat litter boxes. My sister's computer was acting up, plus she wanted to borrow the lawn mower, so I went over there for a few hours. One of the memory slots on her aging motherboard (P233) had died, so after I played around with the ram a little, I got it running again. Got some leftover ice cream birthday cake for my troubles. Yummy. Came back and finished up cleaning. Unfortunately missed Antique Road Show, but oh well. Hopped in a car and cruised around town for a bit. I love driving, but have the bad habit of passing on all sides of the road, riding the middle line to squeeze between cars, and tend to glance off just about everything. Speeding up going over a bridge is exciting, because I'll usually catch air on the other side. The cops don't like it though, and chased me all over for a bit. Luckily by that time I had jacked a fast car, and lost them. Decided almost an hour later that I had had enough of  urlLink GTA:VC , so went in search of other entertainment. Hah! Did you forget I can't drive? *grin* Decided it was time to crack open another book in my most favourite series of all time,  urlLink Discworld . I own almost all the books, but they are so divine that I limit my enjoyment to about two per year. It's fantasy set in a fantastical world, and Terry Pratchett is amazingly skilled at the art of extended metaphor. Unfortunately, the hot day, my recent late nights, a massive tasty supper (mmm spaghetti), and the general good feeling I get with a good book all provided to overcome my consciousness. Within twenty minutes I had passed out, and didn't wake up for a good two hours, wild-haired and groggy-eyed. Rolled off the clean laundry and slowly picked my wits up off the floor, dragging my way toward bedtime.      Song of the Day:  Broken Wings  by  Mr Mister   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I woke up with grand plans this morning. I was going to put on my coolest clothes, and head out to the mall. I needed some sealant for my new shoes mainly, and window shopping is always fun. The conversation with myself went thusly:   "So you're heading out to the mall, huh?"   "Yup! Gotta get some spray for my shoes, and then I'll probably go to Chapters to say hello to all my future purchases. Plus, there's a good chance I'll see some cute women, and maybe I'll hit it off with one of them!"   "You're going to the mall to cruise for chicks?"   "Thought I would. The best ones hang out at Chinook."    "So, explain to me how this is going to work. You're going to be walking down the mall, and some woman is going to fall in your lap?"   "More like, I'll be walking along, and she'll be coming from the other way, we'll lock eyes, she'll be stunned by my boyish good looks and kind eye twinkle, make her way over, say hi, and BAM!"    "Bam, huh? Allowing for the moment that all this comes to pass; a cute woman in the mall you happen to be in who happens to be confident enough to introduce herself to a stranger she just saw for the first time, and somehow finds you desirable enough to do so, then what?"    "Huh?"   "Then what. What will you do?"   "Say hi back."   "And then?"   "And then, um... We'll live happily ever after."   "You skipped a few chapters."   "Fuck it. I'm staying home."   So I talked myself out of going anywhere. Watched cartoons and played video games all day. Responded to a woman I met on a dating website. Ya, I use them. Where else will I find computer geeks? At least, that was the initial idea. I think I've seen maybe ten in the four years I've been actively looking on there. This one had similar personality quirks, but a tad too extreme for me. It was nice talking to her though. My problem is I'm two completely different people at home, and outside.  At home, I'm the stereotypical computer geek. I want to sit for hours in front of the computer, exploring the net or slogging through RPG's, hunting down good anime and music, sitting around half-naked and talking to the cats. I hate people, I want to be alone, I don't want to go anywhere. Once outside, I'm suddenly Social Boy, defender of all things fun. I want to hang out in restaurants, go for walks, hop in a car and go to the mountains, hell, I even want to take up sports like rollerblading or martial arts. I love nature, people are interesting, and god damn I could pick up a cute chick if I tried. It's that threshold I can't cross. In out in out in out. If it wasn't for my loyalty to my work, I'd never leave my house. Once I'm out, I don't want to go home. I need a woman with a good-sized boot, to get me over that first step.   And kind enough to not mind having to do it all the time.      Song of the Day:  Stand Up  by  Ludacris ft Shawnna   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       One of these days, hopefully later than sooner, that little voice in the back of my head that says "This would not be a socially acceptable action in public." is going to be asleep at the wheel, and I am going to do what I constantly fight not to do almost all the time.   Yes, I feel the need to sing.  I don't know how people go through their daily lives not singing. Happy, sad, horny, whatever emotion is floating beneath the carefully controlled surface of their face, it can and often is expressed so well with a melody set to meaningful words. Especially on public transit, where if you aren't being distracted by something of your choosing, you're staring at another peon making their way home and determinedly ignoring you. Why don't these people carry music??  In a short separation from logic one day, I created a grand fantasy where Calgary Transit piped music into the train cars; something to lull the crowd away from the dreary realization that they are stuffed into a small box with 200 other people. Soft announcements would break in from time to time to announce stations, rather than that annoying current voice that ranges from a sultry middle-aged porn star to a chipmunk. One Saturday, long long ago, I was heading downtown in the morning, and the driver had hijacked the tape, inserting cartoon voices like Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck in front of the station names. It was great, and every time someone got on at a station, they were confused as to why everyone was laughing.  But back to me.   It's getting hard to hold back in public. At home, I sing all the time, usually just humming with force, since I rarely bother to learn lyrics. I love harmony. In public, when a favourite song comes on, I break out the air drums, bopping along to the beat. If I get really caught up, I'll softly start forming some notes in my throat, but that's as far as I get. Maybe I should take up kareoke...  Not so long, long ago, I used to travel home from work really late, about 11pm, on the trains from the University to the northeast. There was this guy on the train now and then, who almost looked like Zman from CJAY, if you remember him. Short blond hair, yellow shades, leather coat and jeans. He'd sit there in the crowd, listening to his music, and suddenly break out in full voice, singing whatever he was listening to. Everyone around him usually pretended he didn't exist, although a few would stare. I don't know if he did it because he was feeling the vibe, or if he was testing group reactions to unexpected events, or if he was just plain crazy. I loved it. He didn't look like the type that would appreciate applause, so I just quietly watched and smiled. I probably saw him a total of five times in a two year span. Maybe some day we'll bump into each other again on the train, and can have a musical face-off, West Side Story style. Biatch.    Song of the Day:  Point to Prove  by  Theory of a Deadman   
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Over the past few years, in the interest of ever-more moola, the company I work for has gradually been reducing our work force, passing on the estranged duties to whoever is  urlLink lucky  enough to stay behind. My original designation, electronics technician, has now expanded to include the parts manager and information technologies manager duties. All three of my hats are extremely fun to wear, and I love doing any one of them. Two together can be done with skilled juggling, which I'm good at. All three together, however, is winding up with everything getting done half-assed. This is mostly because it's summer and people keep disappearing for vacations, leaving things unfinished for whoever just got back, so nothing is flowing right. It's making me a tad frustrated, since I'm a bit of a perfectionist in my work. Do it, and do it right, is my mantra. I'm hopeful that once summer is over, and once I get caught up on the backlog of work, and once things are organized properly, and  just as soon as  pigs fly, everything will be peachy-keen.   But in the meantime, I'm a big growly geek with a grudge.   Heading home today, I took extreme pleasure when a ditzy girl standing beside me on the train started doing those flirty motions  right  when the song of the day began playing at high volume on my earphones. Sometimes the universe's timing is impeccable.     Song of the Day:  Girls and Boys  by  Good Charlotte   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My preferable state of being is set to 'brood'. I get up in the morning, usually grumpy, propelled by my alarm clock and my over-active work ethic. I can't start the day without a shower. If I wake up super late, the one thing I will not sacrifice is my five-minute vertical sluice. Heading out, I try and match my music to the type of day I see forming around me: punk for the sharp heat, ambient for rain, trip hop for fog, classical for snowstorms, metal for bad traffic, industrial for bad hair days. The music must match the mood, or I get annoyed. Sometimes the tunage I start with in the morning doesn't match my mood in the afternoon, but because it's what I started with, I'll be listening to it, and wonder why I'm feeling so stuffy and irritable. A shift in genre and AHhhhh.... much better. As long as the music works, I'm feeling good, even if it's a broody good.  It probably started when I was a kid, as most personality-affecting disorders do. Having ample time to sit on the sidelines due to whatever propels kids to discriminate against each other left me with a lasting enjoyment of being there. I like being out of the way, having an objective vantage point to note the proceedings from. Even if it's just mental detachment; sometimes the best place to observe is when you're in the middle of the chaos. This constant state of ponder fits me like a well-broken-in shoe, a feeling I'm lacking at the moment with my new footwear. I don't pull off the brood look very well though. Those Goth kids are enviable, with their dark, greasy hair, the fashionable trenchcoat, and the so-artful-its-trendy tattoos. I don't have the complexion to dye my hair black, and the long coat and chains just doesn't go with yuppee wear. I'm often mistaken for appearing smirkish or bemused. I'll just have to take whatever label I can get, I suppose. Goth probably wouldn't go over well with my boss, who's a member of the British upper crust in decorum. Not to worry, Goth sticks out too much anyway. Can't observe when you're being watched. I need to invest in some shades.    Song of the Day:  Generation Trance 2000  by  Kimball Collins   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I was so enraptured by the rain yesterday, I forgot all about how Stampede was over. Empty trains, that oh so fresh city smell again (yak), fewer annoying tourists... Truly a reason to celebrate.   On one of the buses I take during the day, there's a group of autistic young people I ride with. They are amazing. It's like being on a elementary school bus all over again. For the most part they're friendly folk, and I'm always grateful for their companionship. They make me smile even in the grumpiest of morning moods, with their simple view on life that everyone 'normal' could learn from. They get after each other for swearing, one guy is constantly being reprimanded for picking his nose, they jump on a seat together vying for space, and have no problems laughing at the top of their lungs. One guy in particular I really like. In the winter, he proudly wears his Flames jacket, whenever he isn't proudly wearing his Bow Valley Community College jacket. He almost always has a smile on his face, but even when he's serious, it's hard to take him overly so. Not in an unbelievable way, it's more like Elmo on a bad day. You're sure he has a reason to be serious or upset, but you know the raincloud will pass soon. He loves his beard, he has an unusually high voice, and when he laughs (which is often), he could make a good cartoon character. Whenever one of his group is feeling down he's there with a consoling hand, but it's so innocently done that one could never be creeped out by him. He's just an all-around good guy, who got dealt a poor hand in the game of life.  It's odd that we've never actually been introduced to each other, although he greets me by name every day, and I try to return the pleasantry when I hear it (I'm usually lost in music). A long time ago, a beautiful woman worked at my company, and would ride the same bus. One of the other autistic guys wasn't so polite, and was in love with this woman. He'd harass her every time he saw her, sitting next to her and putting his arm around her, trying to throw out a player's lines that freaked her out. So she started sitting with me to keep him away, and I guess this guy picked up my name that way and passed it on to the rest. I don't see the annoying one much anymore. Maybe he got fired from where they all work. But I can always count on the nice one to cheer me up. I wish I was more confident in taking stranger's pictures, because I think I could really capture his personality well in a photo. Somebody in his past did a great job at molding a fine human being, and sometimes I wish I could be more like him. Which is funny, cause I think maybe he reveres me a little too.  Crazy humans.     Song of the Day:  Funny Break  by  Orbital   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hoooweee, did I get pissed on today. Left work to find a fantastically brooding cloud circling to the west. It was eerily calm though, with no rain, so I wasn't worried about getting wet. Takes me ten minutes to get to Macleod Trail, and I got to a shelter about a minute ahead of an unbelievable wall of water. It was dry one minute, the next, solid wet. I loved it. Slow walkers were coming into the shelters totally soaked, but I was still dry. Hopping trains downtown changed that really quick. In the twenty seconds or so it took me to cross the street, I was bathed. I didn't mind; I love the rain.  While waiting for my next train, I was introduced to a guy who had an unfortunate run-in with a car, and it looked like the car won. I'm often approached by drunks or Natives looking for change, probably because I appear innocent and friendly. Haha. I'm polite to them, and treat them like humans, which seems to surprise them, but I never ever give them money. Usually I just get them to tell me about themselves. This guy had steel rods up his leg, and a steel plate in his hip, as well as numerous healed scars on his face. Fascinating. Often in the past, when I see some innocent, typically timid person being harassed by such folk, I'll step in and get them to talk to me, but it scares me every time. Keep the conversation interesting and upbeat. I once made the mistake of suggesting to a guy a thrift store, and had to smooth a sore temper fast. But usually such people just like to be treated like humans, and walk off in a good mood. Today was such a time.  On the ride home, I rescued a door in distress. Yes, a door. I think I annoyed the woman who had just tried a rescue attempt before me. Yes, I'm a big, strong male. Accept it, and get over it. Walked half the length of the train to do it, past rows of cow-faced riders unsure what to do. Nyah. Just as I was almost home, the rain clouds passed, and the sun shone down upon we. Heated up the roads, so there was this cool evaporating mist everywhere. Walking home, towards the east the dark blue storm cloud moved on, disappearing behind the rows of townhomes, while in the foreground a flock of land gulls that had rode out the storm in a field took flight, their white bodies standing out in sharp contrast above the deep green of the field.   Pure beauty.    *Mental note: Don't stick your head in the window to talk crazy talk to the cat while beautiful women are walking past the house.      Song of the Day:  Assorted Trance Vol 3  by  DJ Nyman   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        As far as I know, I created that truthism, so no linky. Feel free to use it whenever you want to grump about the corruption of culture. Every time I watch TV I'm offered more evidence for it, and it makes me laugh. Such powerful music of the sixties, that were the aural banners of groups fighting corporate, social, and federal oppression, are now luring these same people into buying that new car, or that  fabulous  new diet plan. Ads to watch for in the next twenty years:  Linkin Park - 'In the End' for hemorrhoid cream (It starts with ooone) System of a Down - 'Aerials' for a world-covering bluetooth ISP etc.   I used to absolutely love Rage Against the Machine - fight the power, death to the corporate oppressor, ya baby! until someone pointed out that they worked for Sony, one of the biggest multi-nationals in the world. Hah...  I was watching MuchMusic for a time today (surprise) and for some reason was really enjoying a music video by Maestro - God Bless Da Child. I don't particularly like the song, with that fake, high-pitched backup singer, so I couldn't understand why I was enjoying it. Then I realized it wasn't the song at all, it was the time that the video was shot in. Fall! It was windy, chilly, yellow leaves everywhere and people wearing jackets or double-layered shirts. Absolute escapism heaven. Fall is my second-most favourite season, next to winter.   ----------  One of my favourite TV programs was on today, The Antique Roadshow, where the saying 'One man's garbage is another's treasure.' is most evident. The British series is much better than the American one though. The American stuff is usually civil war items, or odd early 20th century cultural items. The British one has the good junk. I love seeing people bring in pieces that were lying around their house, and leave trying to fathom how to insure a priceless artifact. Even more amusing is the type of people that think they're an amateur aficionado of antiques, and bring in stuff that they just paid a ton of money for, looking for a free appraisal. The conversation often goes thusly:  "Well, madam, what you have here is a  wonderful  replica of a  fabulous  work of art." *shock and dismay* "How can you be sure?" "Well, I've been doing this for thirty years. You develop an eye for such things." "But surely this, this, and this here point to an original piece??" "Nope."  And then I cackle in the background.     Song of the Day:  Hard Knock  [off]   Life  by  Jay-Z   
    
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I decided it was time to finally take in some old books I'd been wanting to trade. I have a ton of books I have yet to read, but a few I had duplicates of, so I headed out to my favourite  urlLink used book store . My first thought when I stepped outside was "Holy fuck it's hot out", immediately followed by my second thought "I'm going to regret these boxer briefs later on...". But I soldiered on anyway, and wound up at the bus stop. While I was sitting on the bench waiting, this old guy on a bike trundles past, and decides to toss some chitchat my way. Okay, buddy. Did you not see the big black ovals stuck in my ears, connected by a long black wire? I can't hear you, and you don't look interesting enough for me to remove them. But I smiled at him anyway, just in case he was trying to tell me I had bird crap on my hat or something. (I checked after he left. I didn't). From bus to train I made my way downtown. Along the 7th ave strip, these two women with giant backpacks got on and sat next to me on the bench, obviously heading from the hostel to the greyhound station. I thought about talking to them, curious as I was to where they were going, and even offering one of my good books for reading, but that would've involved drawing their attention, which just isn't done. So I said nothing and stared out the window. Got off at 10th st and made my way to the store. Passed a cute redhead hiding in an alley enjoying lunch. Startled her for some reason, but all I did was look at her. Oh well. It was the first time I had seen the new Riverwest condos, and they reminded me exactly of the futuristic apartment buildings in SimCity 3. Got to the store and handed over my books. I've always liked the bookkeep for some reason. He's a little odd, and at first he was hard to talk to because he has a lazy eye, but he's a nice guy, and knows his stuff. Picked up these sweet graphic novels as trade. The series is  urlLink Priest .   I often feel as some sort of anti-geek. I love geek things, I do geek stuff, but I just don't fit in with geeks. On Thursday there were these two guys on the train home who were so blatantly geeky, I felt ashamed to portray myself as belonging to their clique. Faces poorly shaved, jaws jutting out under thick glasses, old T-shirts with odd logos on them, and worst of all their horrible conversational skills. Listening to them was torture; they could barely get their ideas across to each other in stilted English. But I knew that if I were to ask them DnD stats, they could rattle off a ton of knowledge. So here I was in a used book store buying fantasy comics from Japan, standing in front of a nice guy who looks like he stepped out of Revenge of the Nerds, me wearing jeans, skate shoes, a skater hat, and some sports T-shirt. He seemed surprised that I was polite to him. Maybe pre-conceptions were shattered on both sides of the counter...  Off I go again, back to the train station. By now the heat is getting really bad, and my internal temperature is starting to rise. I get on a surprisingly empty south train, and settle in to wait for Chinook station. One thing I forget when I don't go outside much is my ability to catch the eye of fourteen-year-olds. Normally, with my diminishing hairline and my more work-oriented clothes, I don't make an interesting target. But with my hat on, suddenly I'm 22. I realized that again today. Two silly little girls kept glancing at me from their seat. I usually stand to let more needy people sit, and so I stare out a side window, my peripheral vision scanning the crowd. I suppose I should be flattered, but it would be nice if a  legal  woman would take note of me once in a while. Maybe when I'm thirty-ish I can find one of those confused young women that want to skip their generation in dating. Ugh. The two got off at Stampede, releasing me from further discomfort.   Got to Chinook, and went browsing. I always stop in at Chapters when I'm there, even though I don't need any more books. And, happy days, I found some shoes! After finally catching a clerk's attention at SportChek, I asked if they had any size 15 hikers. Glory be, the guy came back with a box. I bought them. Not the first colour I would have chosen, but when you're this mutated, you can't be picky. Decided it was getting way too hot, and while I was getting hungry, I didn't want to spend any more money on food, so I made my way back home.   While waiting for the bus of the last leg of my trip, this girl and her mom were standing behind me and off to the side. At one point, a bus pulls up, and the girl walks out in front of me to check the number. A foot-high number I, with my bad eyesight, could see half a block away. She decides it's not hers, and turns back, pointedly making eye contact with me. She smiles, I smile back, but turn away before she gets it into her head to talk to me. She was cute, but I'm not going to hit on a  woman while her mom is within smacking distance. Then, when my bus pulls up, and I'm waiting to get on, this girl gets off at the back doors and walks past me, and gives me the skunk eye! You know, '0.o'. What the hell?? There's got to be a booger on my face somewhere, but no amount of subtle finger searching can find it. I am so ready to crawl back into my cave and hide from these people. Rented a couple movies (Bruce Almighty, which sucked, and Drunken Master, which I wasn't in the mood for), got some pizza, and retired to my soothing aloneness.      Song of the Day:  some streaming stuff  by  Digitally Imported    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't believe it. Today, I honest-to-god made it home in time to watch BOTH episodes of  urlLink Fairly Odd Parents . On a Friday. On a Stampede Friday, no less. AND, I even got a seat on the way home. I think somebody is doing some PR fandangalry, to hide the fact that everyone is avoiding Stampede. Sadly, no rare, near-mythical creatures today. But then they wouldn't be rare and near-mythical, would they?    ----------    I'm facing a courting conundrum. Being ill-experienced in such things, I don't know if I should be looking for someone that matches my personality, or counteracts it, like baking soda on acid. I like women that are cheery and friendly, willing to please and relaxed with life. But at the same time this archetype drives me nuts. Ignorance is bliss, and blissy are they. I'm a pretty patient guy, but around someone who's totally unaware of the world in exchange for happiness, I'd get frustrated fairly fast. So on the other side of the bagel, is the woman who's deep, critical, firmly aware of herself and her world, and ohmygod get out of her way she's wearing heels and your ass is the welcome mat. I also like how the thinkers tend to be slightly off-center, 'eccentric' as some like to say, but how far does one let one allow one to go before one can no longer handle one's circle? I ask myself that all the time. For you see, diary, there's this girl...    (" Ahh ", says Diary,  " it always starts with 'There's this girl...' ")    Shut up and listen. Now then, this girl , you see, is one I've had an eye on for a long time. I used to see her all the time, passing by on my daily commute. Tall, slim, luxurious long dark hair, the most riveting eyes you ever did see... you get the picture. The second thing that drew my eye towards her was that she was decidedly  eccentric . She dressed quite well, walked fine, no outwardly oddisms. But while she waited for the train, she turned into this peculiar nymph. Holding her hands above her head for no apparent reason, but making her belly button bask in daylight glory, squatting down on her heels to curl up into a little ball, tracing squares on the concrete with her footsteps... All this I witnessed with my fantastic peripheral vision. I excel at making other people think I'm ignoring them. Part of the observer's creed. Anyway, I've long longed to go over and introduce myself to this strange woman, but I balk over one simple fact.    I don't know how deep the rabbit hole goes.    I love a surreal mind, but I'll be damned if I wind up with a crazy old woman to tend to in my later years. My menopausal mother freaks me out with her continual visual aids, revealing why I should find that boring, cheerful, ditzy woman who will never broaden her mental horizons.    Yeesh. I imagine if I ponder long enough, it will become a moot point.               Song of the Day:  Release the Silence Volume 4  by  DJ Celica    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today I got to poke around inside a Dell PowerEdge server.     *pauses to wipe off drool    Dell makes the sweetest mass-produced cases this side of Apple. Easy to get into, everything laid out with performance and flow in mind, no sharp edges to remove pieces of knuckle... My chunky Inwin pales in comparison. If I didn't already have dreams of building my next computer inside an  urlLink antique , I'd get a Dell case and custom build a rig inside it. mmm    ----------    I always get a kick out of people who are experiencing the wonder of public transit for the first time. Today on my way home I crowded onto the train as usual, the doors closing shut right behind me. I turn to stare out the window, so I don't have to look at the people around me, and see this guy walking along the platform toward the train. Squat, tubulous, man-made fabrics stretched oh-so alluringly around his midriff, the slack, open-jawed composure of a redneck scholar, and a giant soft drink in hand. He decides my door is the choice entrance, and heads over to it, to push on the door opener button. By now though, all the train's doors are closed, the signs saying the doors are unlocked are unlit, and the arms of the crossing lights are dropping into position. Our hero is still trying to push the button, then looks at me, extending his arms in the universal gesture for 'wtf?'. I shake my head at him, and he stumps off to try the next door. The train leaves, with me wondering how obvious life has to become before everyone 'gets it'.     ----------   Getting off the train at my stop, I catch sight of that rare creature, the beautiful transit rider. Tall, slim, luxurious long dark hair... I cast a wistful glance at her back, heading out to my bus stop. Lo and behold, she shows up at my stop! This is fate! This is meant to be! I can hear the wedding bells already. I'm sure I dreamed of this moment last night. Trying to catch her eye is difficult, since I'm blocked by her shades, but I'm persistant. The bus pulls up, we queue. I think she's looking at me! I lazily reach into my back pocket to pull out my bus pass, tilting my head forward for god only knows what reason. Just then my sinuses decide it would be a  spectacular  time to flush out the ol' system. You know, get rid of all that nasty pollen buildup, for the good of the host. My leisurely bus pass grab switches into a high speed, desperate dig for a kleenex in my front pocket. 'Studly' has flown out the window, 'boyishly cute' hot on his heels. I'm lucky if I get an honorable mention for 'so pitiful I could hug him'. Oh well. I've never approached a woman on the street before, and I guess today wasn't the day to break the record.       Song of the Day:  Pocket Cowboy  by  Denki Groove      
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        We're in the middle of the big cowpie commonly known as the Calgary Stampede, and I'm wondering where these record-breaking crowds are hiding. Sure the trains are late, often adding an extra thirty minutes to my already long commute, but they aren't nearly as full as I remember them last year. I can manage to get from Macleod Trail to downtown without even leaving impacted skin on the windows. I know the crowds are out there, somewhere. I can smell them. That unique blend of fried food, creatively whipped sugar, horseshit, and smoke is hard to miss. Especially for one such as I, lucky to be afflicted with an overactive histamine surplus. The ride home just happens to coincide with my twelve-hour drugs running out, so my time is spent desperately trying to keep myself from sneezing. It's hard to make friends when your spit beats your handshake. My secret strategy is pinching my nose right below the hard cartilage when I feel that oh so familiar tickle. Instant anti-sneeze mechanism. Cause if I get started, I go for a  long  time. Ten minutes is a good estimate. When I'm done my neck and my diaphram are limp meat, to say nothing of the poor souls in the blast radius. I suspect I've antagonized a few with what looks like a subtle comment on ambient B.O., but it's much better than the alternative. A pox on my redneck neighbors, who feel they have some inalienable right to burn open firepits in their backyards at night.  This is one of the reasons why I hate camping. I love the outdoors, the mountains, etc., but sitting around a neanderthalic oven trying to cook garbage while choking on carcinogens is an exercise in stupidity to me. Growing up on the farm, I've had to go years without running water, medieval sewage systems, and overly-friendly forest critters. A hotel is the closest I get to sleeping outdoors. Long live the Outdoor Life network!     Song of the Day:  Aldebaran  by  Shiva in Exile   
    
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Today my niece is one year old! She is the greatest little kid I have ever known, and I love her dearly. She finds my eyebrows absolutely fascinating, and will often shove her face in mine until her eyes cross, cackling with glee. She was born a month early, thanks to my sister's worrying over other stuff at the time, but has caught up in size wonderfully, and is now just starting to get her walking perfected. I believe she's bumped into every sharp corner she can find at her house, and finds exceptional joy in eating lost cheerios. My cat, the terror of my household, flees when she comes around. My best wishes to you, little cutie, and may you have many more happy years to come.      ----------   The cover of this week's Maclean's begs the question "Can Science Give You A Better Sex Life?". I took one look at it and shouted HELL YA! As soon as my mail-order holodeck arrives, I'll never leave my house again. Funny how you never see lowly 24th century janitors sponging spooge off the holodeck walls while trading stories with each other about which superior officers prefer which raunchy simulations. As we all should know, the porn industry drives everything that the war industry doesn't get around to, and I highly doubt this will be different in the technologically advanced 2300's. Just for the record, I prefer my future in the  urlLink Firefly  style, which, incidently, was a direct rip of the  urlLink Cowboy Bebop  style. Remember what I said back in my first post?     Song of the Day:  Dissolved Girl  by  Massive Attack   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Beautiful people don't ride public transit. It's one of those inescapable truths I've learned in the 13 years I've been riding transit in this city. Unless it's transit causing everyone to look bad, perhaps a special clear coating on the windows that casts a nasty glow on everyone inside, rendering them undesirable.  Or , maybe it's simply because I'm always traveling to the northeast, and that's where they keep all the ugly people. (Yes yes, save any comments with the word  mirror  in them for later). I once came up with a wonderful riddle: which is worse, people who  live  in the northeast, or people who  work  in the northeast? I haven't decided myself, yet. In other news, the most beautiful, charming woman I have ever known just moved into the northeast. Such a cruel twist of irony. She's even started taking the bus.   Being The Computer Guy at work can lead to anxious moments from time to time. Case in point: Today a lady walks into my workroom to announce that the printer up front is no longer working. I get up to go check, with possible scenarios suddenly leaping to mind. It was just working so... Did they mess up a setting? Did they knock loose a cable? Turn it off? Is it a major hardware failure? Such thoughts trundle through my mind as I make my way to the printer, wondering how long I'm going to have to spend digging through their computer to decipher what they were doing and what happened right before it went kaput. Just as I get to the affected computer, the woman goes "OH! It's working now! I was just trying to print from the wrong screen." I nod knowingly, on the outside appearing to be the wise Computer Guy, who would have simply taken one look and declared the same solution. On the inside, I'm breathing a huge sigh of relief, glad that I now won't have to spend half an hour to discover that they didn't know what they were doing. I turn to go back to my work, when I hear an unbelievable "Thank-you!" called out after me. I was stunned. All I could do was reply 'No Problem'. Because it really wasn't.   Today was most certainly a Sock Doffing day. I enthusiastically did doff my socks upon arrival at home, only to have to don them with haste mere hours later. Sadness. A friend of my mom's was being given an old bed in storage, and it was my duty to load it up and put it together upon arrival. No Problem. Futons are made for assembling enjoyment. Did the deed, and headed home. But what trip with mother would be complete without the expected "For fuck's sake. If you'd pay attention to the car in front of you instead of gawking out of the side window, you wouldn't have to jam on the brakes until the tires squealed all the time!" type conversations? Luckily, this trip did not disappoint.  I'm finding that writing without the pressure of trying to convince someone on the other end that they, yes they, must date and/or/prettyplease copulate with me, is a lot more enjoyable. But (much) more on that some other day...     Song of the Day:  Scatterbrain  by  Emiliana Torrini   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        It's been almost a week since my mom nearly killed herself. Again. I swear she has some sort of subconscious death wish. On Monday, I came home from work like usual, had supper, and settled in for a long night of surfing and all around slacking in general. I had plugged in my phone, which was the only reason I heard it to answer, since when it's not plugged in it's set to vibrate, and I never hear it. So I answered it, to find one of mom's friends on the other end. She told me that mom had a bad accident, falling down a flight of basement steps, and was now at Peter Lougheed hospital. She wasn't very coherent, and mumbled something about a bad gash on mom's forehead. She was leaving the hospital now, having been there since about 7pm. It was about 7:45. I thanked her for the call and immediately called my sister, who came and picked me up. We got to the hospital a little after 8pm, and went to stand in line at the emergency desk. When we got to the window, my sister told the nurse we were here to see our mother, so they let us through, telling us which bed to find her in. I hate hospitals, but I've been at the emergency room there enough times to find my way around, and we went directly to her spot. Except she wasn't there. Her clothes and various accessories were unceremoniously piled in a heap beside a table full of first aid items. It was a creepy feeling, looking at those typically innocuous items that had suddenly formed the only bond we had with someone everyone else there would regard as just one more victim. A bra, her pants looking like she had just stepped out of them, her purse. Things that could very possibly be the last connection we had with her. My sister turned to find a nurse, and asked where the woman that was assigned to that berth had gone, and the nurse said she had been taken to X-ray. So we went back to the waiting room to do the expected. This was about 8:15.  You never really know how much pain and anguish goes on every day until you hang out in an emergency room. Everywhere were people who if you had seen them on the street, would look like any other average person. But here, their pride had been stripped away and they NEEDED someone else to help them with something they couldn't overcome themselves. In one spot, a young pregnant woman was being forced to sit awkwardly in an uncomfortable plastic wheelchair, across from me was a small Chinese girl who kept moving from doubled over in pain to curling up sideways on her chair with her head on her arms. She was dressed to enjoy the nice day.  Not knowing how long an X-ray was supposed to take, and with the parking meter ever ticking, we got back in line about 8:30, and again went back to check. Still no mom. I was starting to get annoyed. I hate being left in the dark, and my sister was starting to worry. In the background there were two nurses quietly conversing, and my acute hearing picked up one telling the other that a woman had just died. I looked at them, and you could tell they were having a rough day. I wonder if they make all the new recruits start in emergency, to see if they have the ability to handle hospital life. I could never do it, and I have even avoided dating women in related fields in the past. My sister asked what we should do. I don't think she heard the nurses. I crossed my arms and said, "We find a nurse and find out what's going on". So she walked over to the two standing there and asked again, and they said there was probably just a lineup at X-ray. So we went back to the waiting room. I didn't tell my sister what I had heard, not wanting to worry her. We waited for a longer period this time. People kept coming in, and the ones that were there before were still there. At 8:55 we decided to check one last time before going out to the parking meter. When we got back, the berth had the curtain closed, and a quick peek inside found my mom, alive and joking through an adrenaline high. She had a nasty gash on her forehead, which the young doctor there was getting set up to sew shut, as well her upper lip looked like her teeth had gone through it, and she was badly bruised down both sides of her body. But she was alive. We asked her where her vehicle had ended up, and she said it was in the parkade. It was quickly decided that my sister would go and get my dad so he could drive her car while she drove mom's. I can't drive, a fact that the young doctor made note of but was polite enough not to say anything about. So my sister left, and I got to stand and watch my mom get 20 stitches in her face. It's something I'd never thought I would ever see, since I'm always cutting myself but have never had them. Parents are supposed to slowly sink into idle activities as they get older, not perform stunts that I wouldn't risk at half their age. Once my mom was patched up, she got dressed and we headed back out, through the waiting room. She looked pretty bad, with a bloody bandage around her head, and bruises all over. If I hadn't known, I would have sworn she was in a car accident, something she's also really good at doing. That night was long, since I had to wake her up every few hours to make sure she didn't have a concussion. It turned out ok though. She decided four days later that she didn't want to go back to have her stitches taken out, so took them out herself. I just shook my head. Mulish would be a good adjective for my mother. At least the experience has convinced her to update her will. The one in force now still has my uncle from back east coming out to be my guardian. Hah.       Song of the Day:  The Rewt  by   urlLink Mantrakid    
    
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Happy Cartoon Day! I paid homage to the weekly holiday by sleeping in late, then getting up and watching my favourite cartoons all morning. Finally my mom dragged me over to her rental condo to do some work. I told her when she bought the place that I wouldn't do any maintenance on it (the idea being that if she's making a profit, she can bloody well pay for a professional to fix it), but her falling down the stairs recently works great as fuel for guilt trips. After we finished there, I came back home, mowed the mini jungle forming in front of my house, and then headed back out to rent a movie.  Came back with Return of the King. I had promised myself way back last Octoberish that I wouldn't watch the movie alone, since I went by myself to the theater for the second one, but nobody ever stepped forward, so I decided it was time I saw it. I really enjoyed it too, even though I still hold to the truth that the books were better. There's so much more that happens in the books. Of course, the book doesn't have nearly as much bass, even if you drop it really hard. I was thinking of going out today to try and find some new shoes, but such a task is so disappointing with my skis, that I don't like to make special trips just for that. Maybe one day moccasins will come back into fashion. And chest hair, while I'm dreaming.     Song of the Day:  The Walking Song  by  Bilbo Baggins (sung by Peregrin Took)   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Ugh. Stampede is upon us once again. I'd avoid it entirely, but unfortunately I have to commute directly through it every day. Thanks to the parade this morning, the train was packed to bursting with anxious parents and strollers. yeehaw. I grew up on a farm. Real cowboys wear rubber boots, and herd cattle with the truck. Less likely to get trampled that way. Stampede is like an extended Halloween to me, with everyone wearing the same absurd costume. My boss does it the right way, and leaves town for the week. So I get to work today to discover that Accpac pooched itself. Couldn't have picked a better day to do it actually, with everyone working on death by sausage and pancakes. So while they chowed down, I rebuilt the database. Spent the rest of the day sifting through old hardware, which is just how I like my Fridays: low stress. The commute home was more of the same agony, with the trains all late. I waited 25 minutes for a bus that never came, until I walked the 20 blocks home. Did it in 20 minutes too, which is a record for that stretch, considering I had to go up and down Whitehorn's big-ass hill. I hate the northeast.   growlgrowl...     Song of the Day:  Bleed in Silence  by  Wumpscut   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         *cough* Well, at least  my  part of the universe. Yes, you have stumbled across my blog, where I hope to entertain, rant, practice my writing skills, and add just a little more vain pollution to the wonderful toy called the internet. As this is my first blog, please be patient.  You may notice that my titles will tend to quote other's creative works. I'm doing it on purpose, in a forced attempt to limit where I copy others, as well as to show that nothing is truly new under the sun, and all creative works are derivative of works before them. Humans don't live in isolated bubbles. Yet. Something the RIAA needs to realize. Feel free to try and guess the quote; I'll always try and link to something that gives an answer.  I also happen to love music, and am trying out something at the bottom of the post that will show the song I enjoyed the most that day. Do seek out the artists, all things creative are wonderful, and should be enjoyed by everyone.  Now then, on to me...    Song of the Day:  Big Black Cloud, Little White Lie  by  Goldfrapp   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Woke up this morning and slowly made my way towards consciousness. Decided it would be best to get on with things, so didn't spend a lot of time slacking off. Started chores, headed to the store for food, and came back. As I was poking around in the yard, I fell into a murderous rampage. My front lawn is covered with ant hills trying to make something of themselves. I had a few bottles of poison, so I went around kicking hills and dumping poison and water on them. I bet I killed at least a thousand outright, and there were abandoned eggs everywhere. I felt good about it.  Later I tried to catch something good on TV while having lunch. Could not be done. I'm sick of paying for this crap, so I moved all my online registration stuff to web email addresses. I had wanted to use GMail, but never got an invite, and it's still beta, so I went with Yahoo. Hotmail is garbage. Months after the features war, Hotmail still only offers 2Mb of storage, and all the spam you can eat. GMail has a gig, and yahoo offers 100Mb. I'm ready to cut my cable now, and mooch off the roommate's DSL line. It's not easy giving it up though. I've had cable since my first computer in 1998. Sigh. It's one of the many sacrifices I'm going to have to make in order to save money though. I had a chat with my financial advisor (takes pipe out of mouth to gesticulate for a moment), and we decided it would be in my best interest to move one of my RRSP's from TransAmerica, which is doing nothing with their customers (I earned maybe $30 last quarter on it), into another RRSP from Maritime, which is earning 28%. I'll take a little penalty for moving it, but will make much more back on it at the new company.  Tonight I had a chat with my mom, and explained my desire to buy my own place. She listened, which I was grateful for. She said she was intending to help me buy a place, since I had helped her buy her house a year ago (I have perfect credit, I'm just poor). So that's nice to know too. I'd really really like to be able to put down at least 20% on a new house though, so I may have to suck it up and get a second job. I'm going to have a chat with the boss too, and see if maybe my efforts at work are worth a raise. And I'm putting matters of the heart on the back burner. I'm not happy with my life at the moment, and that's not a great frame of mind to meet people in. Plus, for a long time I've been thinking that I could find someone and we could succeed together. But I did that once, and it turned into a couple roommates living together, rather than a relationship. I want to do it all on my own, and maybe someday if I still feel like I want someone around, I'll go see if anything out there is worth my time.  Back to work tomorrow. I can't remember what I was working on, on Friday, with all my plans bouncing around in my head. The rain outside is soothing, and I'm looking forward to falling asleep to it.   zzz  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Woke up this morning and slowly made my way towards consciousness. Decided it would be best to get on with things, so didn't spend a lot of time slacking off. Started chores, headed to the store for food, and came back. As I was poking around in the yard, I fell into a murderous rampage. My front lawn is covered with ant hills trying to make something of themselves. I had a few bottles of poison, so I went around kicking hills and dumping poison and water on them. I bet I killed at least a thousand outright, and there were abandoned eggs everywhere. I felt good about it.  Later I tried to catch something good on TV while having lunch. Could not be done. I'm sick of paying for this crap, so I moved all my online registration stuff to web email addresses. I had wanted to use GMail, but never got an invite, and it's still beta, so I went with Yahoo. Hotmail is garbage. Months after the features war, Hotmail still only offers 2Mb of storage, and all the spam you can eat. GMail has a gig, and yahoo offers 100Mb. I'm ready to cut my cable now, and mooch off the roommate's DSL line. It's not easy giving it up though. I've had cable since my first computer in 1998. Sigh. It's one of the many sacrifices I'm going to have to make in order to save money though. I had a chat with my financial advisor (takes pipe out of mouth to gesticulate for a moment), and we decided it would be in my best interest to move one of my RRSP's from TransAmerica, which is doing nothing with their customers (I earned maybe $30 last quarter on it), into another RRSP from Maritime, which is earning 28%. I'll take a little penalty for moving it, but will make much more back on it at the new company.  Tonight I had a chat with my mom, and explained my desire to buy my own place. She listened, which I was grateful for. She said she was intending to help me buy a place, since I had helped her buy her house a year ago (I have perfect credit, I'm just poor). So that's nice to know too. I'd really really like to be able to put down at least 20% on a new house though, so I may have to suck it up and get a second job. I'm going to have a chat with the boss too, and see if maybe my efforts at work are worth a raise. And I'm putting matters of the heart on the back burner. I'm not happy with my life at the moment, and that's not a great frame of mind to meet people in. Plus, for a long time I've been thinking that I could find someone and we could succeed together. But I did that once, and it turned into a couple roommates living together, rather than a relationship. I want to do it all on my own, and maybe someday if I still feel like I want someone around, I'll go see if anything out there is worth my time.  Back to work tomorrow. I can't remember what I was working on, on Friday, with all my plans bouncing around in my head. The rain outside is soothing, and I'm looking forward to falling asleep to it.   zzz  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       More odd dreams. I wonder if it's because I've changed my diet. I never used to sleep deep enough. Maybe fresher room air aids in proper sleep... hmmm. Got up, watched some 'toons, and then my sister called saying she was on her way over. So I got to hang out with her and the babe for a bit. Mom bought a sofa bed, so I had to go help her move that in and set it up. New sofa beds are wonderfully light. I once had one that weighed easily 300 pounds. I think I left it in a basement somewhere.  Spent much of the day dreaming about moving. When I took back the movies, I picked up a condo guide and took a look at what they had listed. There wasn't much in my price range, which had me worried for a bit, until I checked out the MLS listings, and found more than enough interesting prospects. I'm far from being ready to buy anyway, but it's good to know what's out there. I opened a new savings/chequing account today too. It's from the Manulife Bank, and is online, like ING's. But because they see that as competition, they have a better interest rate. You can only get it through a Manulife insurance broker though. I'm also seriously considering canceling my cable, to save money. I only watch about thirty minutes most days anyway, less if the bus is late coming home. I plan to focus all my energy on saving. I want to be away from roommates, separated from family members by a security entrance, and able to walk around nekkid in my house if I should feel the need.  Finished up the evening by watching the new Battlestar Galactica series premiere. Now  that  is a well-told sci-fi story. I had never heard of the original series, and only vaguely remember a video game that never materialized, so the entire story was new to me. And I love it. I hope the series stays as entertaining.  
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I dreamt last night that me and this cute girl were cat burglars, and broke into a mansion via the attic. While there, the owners came home, so while we waited for them to leave, we scoped out the storage space. Found a fake wall, and what was stashed behind it? Why, chocolate bars, of course! One in particular I remember, Cadbury's ButterCreme (like Caramilk only yummier). Since I've never seen that in real life, maybe I had a chocolately glimpse of the future! Time will tell. I headed off to work with what I  thought  was my grumpy commuter mask, but turned out instead to be my tourist guide mask. I got asked for directions twice downtown. I crawled out of my shell to be nice to them, and couldn't get the damn thing on again, so I was pretty perky the rest of the day. Fired up the music at work at one point, happily crooning along to my ...moderately... volumed tunes. My boss loves to sneak up on people from behind and stare at them till they notice him. I finally noticed him and asked how long he'd been there. He said long enough. So I turned it down a little, but kept crooning. haha! I think part of the reason I was all giddy was because people kept feeding me chocolate all day. First a wagon wheel, and then this vanilla KitKat. Evil sugar.  Rented some movies on the way home, because there's no way I'm hanging outside in this heat. I'm already red like a radish. The young woman at the movie store tried to tell me something under her breath as the other one walked over, but with my music in one ear and my mind on the door, I wasn't ready for conspiratory whispers. So I grunted politely, which seemed to be a sufficient answer, and headed home. The Big Bounce was fun, but left me wondering where the story went. The Perfect Score was absolutely hilarious. Some guardian angel slipped me a Caesar sometime during the evening, which no doubt raised the haha level of the movies.  And finally, one of my cats decided to play the family-fun game, Puke in the Dark. So now, somewhere in my house, is a prize waiting for me to discover. I can hardly wait!     Song of the Day:  Dreams Come True  by  S.E.S   
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Aarrrgh... I trumpeted the return of fall a bit too soon, it seems. It got up to almost 30C here today, and I was dripping all the way home. Had to change all my clothes, they were so soaked. Nothing I could do, other than growl and accept it. My basement suite is heavenly in times like this.  Managed to smack my head not once but twice today, both on buses. The first time, I somehow hit my head on the roof of the bus. I knew I was close to the ceiling, but it surprised me. The bus turned too sharply going around a corner, right as I was getting up, and I raised up on my toes to balance. Instant bonking noise. I think the only person that noticed was the guy getting up behind me. Second time was getting off another bus, I hit my head on the rear door jam. I do that one a lot. One would think I'd have learned to duck properly by now. The loft at work has a cement beam that's 6'1" off the ground, and from time to time I re-introduce myself to that one too. One day when I wasn't wearing my hat I actually took skin off. Stupid midget world... Finished up my double-issue Maclean's mag. The article that stood out the most in the second half was about urban golfers; people who are fed up with the snobbery of the golf course, and instead buy a cheap club and some tennis balls, and chase them down city streets and parks. That sounds like a grand idea to me. The closest I've come is pounding real golf balls across a park, trying to make it over the road on the other side. Golf balls bounce really good on pavement... My sister is tearing her hair out over recent problems with her husband's work. They're going on strike, which is no fun when you just bought a house and had a kid. I can't help them much other than offer emotional support, since I'm trying to save for my own house, and I have problems with some of their house rules, which means I'd never move in to help out. I think she'll be fine, but with the added stress of my mom's birthday coming up, the ongoing family feud, and relatives and strangers both from back east planning to head out here, we both are contemplating our own cozy spots under our beds. It seems obvious to me that the more people you have in your life, the more complicated (read, aggravating) life is.     Song of the Day:  Pretty Fly (for a white guy)  by  The Offspring   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       From the beginning of this week, summer has slowly started to slip into fall, with cold mornings and hot afternoons. I love the mornings like this, when the air is easy to breathe and exertion doesn't result in soaked clothing. The heat is bearable for the short amount I'm in it, but I don't make plans for extended outdoor stuff. I followed yesterday's shadow through the day, and felt pretty good about it once it was over. Enjoyed some anime - Gundam is getting very exciting -, and settled down to finally try and get through my double issue of Maclean's.  Learned about Acadians in Canada, to start. I always wondered why New Brunswick had bilingual licence plates. I had never heard of Acadians, other than vague references of a French nation running the length of the eastern seaboard, and some odd hints that much of southern USA had French-speaking communities. The French of the Maritimes are a completely different lot from the French of Quebec. A wonderful quote by Premier Bernard Lord talking about Acadians vs Quebecers: "It is important to know our history, but it is equally important not to be prisoners of history.". Quebec seems to be coming around to the idea of staying in Canada though, under the leadership of Jean Charest.  Moved on to read about the rising AIDs epidemic in Canada's Native communities. I've always felt they are a neglected group in Canada, and this article pointed out a consequence of that neglect; the ease at which disease can burn through their demographic.  Read about upcoming economic woes, and the surprising hint that the 'investor class', a group in America who can afford to own more than $50K in stocks, favour the Bush administration. So once again you can blame the rich for the politics that ignore the poor. Laughed at the demise of Molson Breweries. Oh no, Canada's losing a cultural icon. Gosh, how horrible. A family's childish in-fighting destroys a once-profitable company. Can you say Eaton's? An impassioned writer complains about continual Judenhass, the hatred of Jews. Every western religion teaches hate. I don't know why people continue to be surprised at this. Children grow up in those groups learning that others are inferior, and to blame for their ills, and the cycle continues. The wall that Israel is building around itself will be curious to study, in how it will affect relations with the countries around it. The Berlin wall drove Eastern Germany into poverty, and earned people living there the disgust of their western brothers.   And that's only half the magazine! Gah. This week's issue is waiting for me to dig into, not that I care about the Olympics, which is featured on the cover.   ----------  Found out indirectly from a third party that a woman my mom met in Ottawa is coming to stay here at the end of the month. My mom has glorious ideas about hooking me up with women she deems worthy, and then tries to force me to hang out with them. Her deeply-researched criteria? The woman must be tall. That's it. Who cares about personality or common goals and morals. Find some chick with stretched legs, and she's good. My mom sees it as a travesty, those tall men who shack up with short women. I personally like a woman I can pick up, and most women my height have the poundage to match. I was planning on taking the end of the month off, but can't because I have to work on year-end IT stuff. I really wish I had been able to. I could stand an impromptu visit to Vancouver.     Song of the Day:  Believe  by  Nami Tamaki   
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My early morning joy over the weather was slowly destroyed as it grew warmer and warmer throughout the day. Once in a while I wake up slightly anxious, and it tends to follow me around all day. Going to and from work today, I felt that way. I have no idea why. I've eaten healthy foods almost constantly for almost ten years, and the slightest amount of bad food really affects me. Pop and coffee freak my system out. Excessive fat causes stuff to go haywire. I didn't eat anything out of the ordinary, but my body was reacting similar to that. Maybe there was excessive crud in the air. Maybe I'm ovulating. Hyuck.  Got a great amount of work done today, both real, and IT-related. Bought a hard drive from a guy at work, and installed it as soon as I got home, so now I have twice as much room. Mmmmm.  On the way home there was a group of Japanese kids on the train. I'm always tempted to talk to such groups, but the only reason I can come up with is to hear myself speak Japanese, and to enjoy the typical surprise they have when a gaijin is speaking their language. So I don't bother. I'm not so shallow that I could honestly enjoy that kind of ego stroking. I'd have listened to their conversation, except I already had my music in, and taking it out for no reason would look suspicious.  When I was young I participated in some student exchange stuff, teaming up with a group of girls from an all-girls school in Fukuoka while they were here. That was tons of fun. They have the same varied personalities as school girls here, from the frilly bimbos to the mouthy tom-boys. Just walking around with them and experiencing them interacting with each other and the city was fantastic. Talking with older Japanese people tends to be a struggle. Partly because I'm not fluent, and they don't know how well I speak at first so once they discover that, they feel embarrassed. Partly also because regardless of what language they speak, I don't like talking to humans much. I think what really drew me to learning Japanese is it's combination of being extremely logical in design, with specific rules that are adhered to 99% of the time, yet it's also a beautifully artistic language, both in the way it's written, and in the way thoughts are composed. I hated French, because it was so abstract. If I hadn't grown up knowing English, I would've hated it as well. I'm not big on any of the Romance languages actually, except Latin. Latin interests me because I can see how English and others break down into their Latin roots. The guy from Fiji at work speaks Hindi. I'm curious about how that language is built too. Maybe I should learn that next, so I can eavesdrop on his phone conversations... hehe  My dear anorexic cat decided to show her opinion of the carpet tonight. Damn thing sounded like a plunger in reverse. At least she did it after I was done eating. Why can't they ever aim for the linoleum, fer cryin out loud...    Song of the Day:  After Landing  by  Bowery Electric   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm loving this cold weather. I like to be bundled, which is something I can't do in the heat. Today I had on my hoody and a long-sleeved shirt, and it was just right. I'm looking forward to the fall. I wish I could live somewhere that the weather stayed fall-like year round. I imagine a mountain near the equator would have something like that.  Stopped in at the store on the way home to pick up some salad dressing, and headed over to the express lane. Wound up between two women who apparently didn't know how to count, but it didn't really bother me. Spent my time in line trying to tactfully avoid looking at all the feminine hygiene products. Thank god I never had a girlfriend that expected me to go buy that stuff for her. I can't even make it through with condoms without blushing. Curse my innocence!   ----------  I really wish I had a channel that was broadcast from Japan. There's only one available on Shaw, but you have to buy a huge package first, and then you get the privilege of paying extra for that channel. Plus, it's one of the sucky ones in Japan, like Access is here. Suitable, but hardly entertaining. Watching so much anime lately, I'm falling back into the groove I was in at the height of my Japanese studies. I used to spend eight hours a day pouring over textbooks, interspersed with some movie rentals from Rogers. It was absolute heaven. I've started creating conversations in my head again, just to practice Japanese. I may have to re-read my Dragonball manga soon. Or even better, run away to Vancouver for a day or two, to visit that excellent manga-ya in Richmond.  With my latent passions surfacing again, I find myself wondering why I bother trying to find a girlfriend. I only do it when I'm bored, because when I have stuff to do, I really don't want to be around other people. I've never met anyone that I'd want to share the stuff I'm interested in with. She'd have to be extremely unique. Having a warm body around just to satisfy my body's desires, and to stave off that cliche of growing old alone, just doesn't seem worth it to me. I simply don't care about being friends with other people. They're never on my wavelength, and talking to them is such a chore in any way other than professional. Bleh. I'm certainly keeping my eyes open for that specific mind I'd admire, but I've yet to see one in my lifetime. Until then, I can find lots of things to occupy myself with.   Sour grapes? hehehe... Oh, probably. :)    Song of the Day:  Crescent Suns  by  Shpongle   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Sunday dawned much the same way Saturday had, except I got up soon after waking. I have lots to do on Sundays, and don't like putting it off. Started my chores, and then headed off to the grocery store to collect items for my new dinner experiment. It was cold out, but nicely brisk. I laugh at the campers of the world. For the amount of vegetables I bought, I was surprised that I spent less than I would had I bought ingredients for spaghetti. When I got back, I did some yard stuff, and then my sister and niece arrived, so I hung out with them for a bit. My niece fell asleep while my sister went to do some errands, so I didn't get to play with her much, but it gave me time to finish up the housework.  After they left, I wasted a few hours watching cartoons, then dove into my experiment. After having a second cherry tomato explode on me, I decided my knife was too dull, and hunted down my steel. When I was a cook, I used to have the sharpest knife at work, allowing me to zoom through prep, and sometimes, myself. Guess I got lazy with my home utensils. After a few swipes with the steel, I tried again. OMG! It was glorious! I had forgotten how good a sharp knife is. It sliced through the tomato like it wasn't there, and bit into the cutting board too. Such perfection! I even went through the seeds, instead of pushing them aside. I was overwhelmed. I nearly wept. *snicker* Finished up dinner, and dug in. A big mixing bowl of salad filled me up about the same as a giant plate of spaghetti would, so hopefully it will be my new diet. I certainly feel better after dinner, although I forgot one of the benefits of eating pasta: dependable bathroom schedules. With pasta, I could set my watch to the 12 hours it took to digest. With this salad, I barely made one hour. That could take some getting used to...  Later I went browsing for condos for sale on the net. I really want to move, and I was curious to see what I could afford. Surprisingly, there is stuff out there, and in areas I wouldn't mind living in. So my spirits were raised a bit. I still need to save a lot for a downpayment, since I don't believe in 5% or less down. The more you put down when you buy, the cheaper your payments will be. I'm all for low payments. Did some phone tech support for a friend too. It's not easy when they have no idea about computers, and are using a program I've never used. But we managed. I hope this weather stays like this until fall. I love cozy weather...    Song of the Day:  Anna ni issho datta noni  by  See-Saw   
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Woke up this morning to the constant dripping sound of rain. I had my window open too, and it was cold, so got up just long enough to turn on the cartoons, and then darted back under the covers. YTV doesn't seem to be running Jackie Chan Adventures anymore, so I had to make do with Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles. Finally officially got up a couple hours later. The rain kept up until the early afternoon, and then it got pretty sunny out. I spent most of my time bumming around the house. Watched some Gundam, and fixed a laptop for a friend of my mom's. I like to make stuff work again. My cat kept me company much of the day. She has some sort of lap sixth-sense, always knowing when I just made one. If I'm laying on my stomach on my bed, she'll curl up on my legs right below my bum. Dangerous place to be. Watched Tombraider later in the day, on TV.  I think it's time to change my diet again. I'm a really lazy cook, and will make a huge batch of one thing to last me the whole week, always on a Sunday. For the past two years it's been either spaghetti or lasagna, but I'm getting sick of pasta. I love tomato sauce, which is what has kept me going this long. I'm hankerin towards some sort of Chef's salad now. I eat a lot of vegetables and grains during the day, it's more just because I don't like how heavy I feel after a giant plate of pasta. I'll have to see how it goes. Maybe I'll put cold pasta in the salad, if it winds up not filling.  Finished up the evening with a program on A&E called The First 48 Hours. It's a crime investigation show. Most of the time I don't watch such shows, because my mind wanders off, contemplating all the people affected by that particular crime, instead of paying attention to where the director wants to take the camera. I started watching it, and kept putting off changing the channel. It turned out to be pretty interesting.  So much for Saturday.    Song of the Day:  Hands  by  Jewel   
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Friday dawned with little of the brooding cloud cover of late, so I headed off to work minus my hat. I've been in a melancholish mood lately, and chose some melodic ambient to match my stride through the day. It takes me a good while to greet the day with enthusiasm, something that I slowly find while I commute. So during my commute, I'm often withdrawn, and I don't enjoy being interrupted until I've come around, usually once I arrive at work. Terse responses to co-workers I meet on the way, a small nod and smile to  urlLink Andrew . Today was typical, and of course, I had to run into  her . A beautiful, sweet woman, who I avoid like the plague to keep from falling in love with her again. We'd kill each other within a month if we ever had a relationship, but trying to stay away from her is like pulling a rare earth magnet off my dense metallic skull. I saw her coming, and made to pretend like she wasn't there, because I knew she'd say something. She did, of course, and it was too obvious for me to ignore.   "Good morning, arashiken." (names have been changed to protect the stupid. namely, me.)  "Good morning ..." I said, and then froze. I had a giant brain fart, and couldn't remember her name! I watched the expression on her face change from cheerfulness to defensive ponderment, seemingly wondering how cruel I was going to wind up being this time. Finally her name popped into my head, and I said it. Her expression didn't change, so I laughed it off like I was joking, and kept on my way. I felt like an absolute ass the rest of the day. I've known her for over two years, and looking at her always makes me sad and annoyed at my feelings for her. The last thing I want to do is cause her trouble though, so I try to avoid her as much as possible. It's easier that way.  The rest of the day was pretty productive. Got a lot of real work done, and that made me feel a little better. On the way home I walked passed a really bad, recent car wreck. That's always a downer, and I wondered how I would have reacted if it had happened when I was walking past. My big heroic gesture would probably amount to using my phone. Spent the ride home staring out the window and listening to music. Home life is aggravating, as I get constant updates about my bickering family. They're a bunch of uncivilized children, and I wish I could walk away from them all.   The rain is comforting, at least, and my cat always seems to know when I need a hug.     Song of the Day:  Maresias  by  Robert Miles   
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm constantly dismayed by prevailing ideologies I see in North American society. It seems common knowledge that ambition and the constant desire for more is a good thing. There's no such thing as being happy with what you have, and 'content' is a homonym for 'sloth'. Unfortunately, in an economy governed by supply and demand, there is no room for everyone to be happy. It's a capitalist mantra to keep the economy going. If you are happy with what you have, you won't buy more. If you don't buy, you're a bad little consumerdroid, because somebody's wages depend on you spending instead of saving. What really bugs me is when people wrap themselves in this false belief that obtaining ever more will make you happy, and then staring down their noses at people who accept what they have, and find more personal reasons to be happy with life.  As I tend to avoid most people, I rarely encounter this elitist attitude on the street. The guy in his beamer giving me the finger and spraying angry spittle on his window, while I watched in quiet amusement from the sidewalk corner, was one. Walking into Holt Renfrew one day in skater clothes just to look around, and being given the cold shoulder by everyone was another. More, I run into this conflict on the net. Internet dating to be precise. I once thought that I could find a lot of geeks like myself on online dating sites, since that's who uses computers, the logic went. The sites tend to cater more to the busy professional though. I don't know if it scares away the blue-collar peruser, or if that demographic doesn't buy or can't afford computers, or if I just don't know how to look properly, because I can't find the personality I'm looking for. Someone who knows they have the intelligence and power to do whatever they desired to do, but are happy with what they have. Someone who believes honest work usually means getting dirty, and they are okay with that. Most especially, somebody who could lose their every material possession, and still be happy with their life. The women I see are often looking for the guy with the career, the car, the house, and 2.5 kids in the future. (I laugh to think how women complain about men not rising above their hormonal urges of wanting sex, yet they never rise above their hormonal urge to have babies.) They have a shopping list of perfection, and while their personalities look like they may enjoy the same things you do, because you don't match what's on the list, they ignore you. My ex had a great term for these women, "Business Whores". They'll sell themselves to the highest bidder, and step on the unwashed masses. My ex became one of them though, which is another story. Driven through life by their own selfish goals, they never stop to look around and consider the consequences of their actions. As a result, society slowly decays, even as it feeds this rot. I go through life wondering which will happen first; the collapse of the system, or an uprising of the unhappy majority.     Song of the Day:  Polomerria  by  Cocco   
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There is no greater tragedy, to me, than the destruction of a world. A vast amount of life and the biosphere it survives in, all gone within a moment. Not only is the dominant race's history and potential future gone, there's also no chance for any further evolving of other life forms to take their place. Humans have always had, and always will have conflict, usually resulting in wars. It's hard for me to feel sorry for people who die in them, because each one of us has a choice, through action or inaction, to control the future. Which is why I'm typically unfazed by Remembrance Day observances. Humans are a foolish race who make foolish choices, and we pay for those choices in turn. But to have an entire planet lost, through accident or massive war machines of the future, puts a knot even in my throat. It's an idea that has had much deliberation in science fiction. The  urlLink wallpaper  (Inevitable) on the computer screen in my profile picture references that idea. Movies like Titan AE and Armageddon kept me glued to the screen with the horror they depict. Once a planet is gone, it's gone for good. Terraforming is still an idea best left in fantasy, whereas cataclysmic destruction could happen at any time. Even if we did have enough warning, and had the technology to get a large amount of the population off the planet before such an event, we'd have few choices. Power systems on spacecraft right now are archaic. Leaving the solar system would be out of the question, because the time it would take to get to the next one, even if we knew which one had a planet that could support life, would take lifetimes to reach. Supplies would give out before we got there. Building a colony on Mars or one of the moons of Jupiter or Saturn would probably be the best bet. If we ever lost this planet, life would turn cold and brutal. Which all boils down to my desire to be part of an Earth defense force, puttering around in a ship and shooting asteroids.   Weeeeeeee!!!!!!  Dammit, freeze-dried spaghetti  again???  Ugh.    Song of the Day:  Psychotrance Vol 1  by  Mr C   
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       UUuuoooooo......  Back to work after a long weekend. Not liking that one bit. Went through the motions like an automaton, and with the help of some ambient music, found myself at work ready for action. Did a whole lotta nuthin again, since I had some IT stuff left over from Friday. I'm finally getting caught up on it though, so hopefully I can do some real work tomorrow. The weather's been annoying lately, promising gloom and dhoom, but not coming through with it. Same story today. The west side of the city gets all the fun stuff, and by the time it gets over here, there's nothing. I need to move over there.  Headed home in an odd mood. I play the part of the moody dreamer very well. I think in part the blame can fall on the shoulders of a great anime I found last night, Mobile Suit Gundam Seed. Finally, a serious sci-fi, full of the tragedy and duty found in any war, and properly told. I've known of the Gundam franchise for a long time now. I think it's at least ten years old, and probably closer to twenty. There's so much to see though, and not every series follows the same plot lines, so I was always intimidated by it. I'm glad I finally tried it. I wish there was just ONE decent station in Canada that played adult anime. No, not the porn stuff, I'm not really into that. I mean shows with intelligent plot lines, characters you care about, and adult humour. Pokemon and Yuugi-Oh can be entertaining for a little while, but the entire concept is so...  infantile ... Kidnapping animals and stuffing them into capsules so you can fight with them later? Oh ya, animals would love that. And any series bases on "dueling cards" makes me dumbfounded. I tried Magic: The Gathering for about a week, and it was sooo boring. The whole trick of the game is to buy more packs, hoping you get a powerful card. Who would play a magic card game with monsters when you can play a video game full of realized sprites? Such card games are about twenty years behind their time. It would have been great for the DnD crowd. Give me Neverwinter Nights or give me... anything but a pretty deck.   urlLink        Song of the Day:  Cosmic Ambient Garden  by  Akasha Project   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, maybe long weekends aren't so bad. So far today I've helped someone move, repaired a computer remotely (XP's remote desktop is fabulous, competing neck 'n neck with Linux's xvncviewer), discovered a new delicacy (mix French Vanilla yogurt with Fruit Loops. mmmmm), and best of all, discovered a part of my personality I had lost. I tend to do that a lot, getting stuck in the grind of daily life, I forget about things I like to do. This latest exhumation was my love for anime. Living way too far away from video stores that carry it, and cable not being any help at all, I used to collect lots from the internet. But I forgot about doing that almost a year ago, back when I was interested with Linux. Most software in Windows doesn't have a nice, easy to use Linux equivalent, so I just stopped using such things. Which is one of the reasons why I eventually gave up Linux. I spent more time tweaking the OS, than actually using it to do stuff. Anyway, my latest anime is Furi Kuri, which is downright weird. Perfect for a lazy Monday afternoon.      Song of the Day:  Ride on Shooting Star  by  The Pillows   
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't know if it was because I went to bed late last night, or the dark weather, but I did  NOT  want to get out of bed this morning. I just laid there for a good 90 minutes, reading. Finally decided the longer I put it off, the longer the day would be, so I pushed off the cat and got up. Dragged myself through my chores, proving to myself that I actually could be a productive member of society by doing yardwork for two hours. When I was done, I was exhausted because I hadn't eaten lunch yet, so did that, and then read for a good while. I'm almost done my Discworld novel, and am ready for something more involved. Maybe I'll dig into that cyberpunk murder mystery I bought a while ago. Found myself in a creative mood, so wasted some time in my art programs. Later on I sunk into a video game. Long weekends always sound like a good idea, but once I'm in the middle of one, I find myself wishing to head back to work. At least there's something to do there. People to talk to, stuff to accomplish. Sitting at home is so boring, but hanging out by yourself outdoors is equally unsatisfying. I always feel like I'm in the middle of an  adventure that never happened. Get on the bus, go downtown, wander around with a purposeful stride for a bit. And then...? I used to do it a lot, swinging from one side of the city to the other. Walking everywhere, just looking at stuff. Maybe I'm bored of this city. I'd move to Vancouver if I had a job set up there, but I worry that the same thing would happen. A part of me always feels like I should be a homeless adventurer, not worrying about money or politics, finding love infrequently wherever I wound up for the night. I certainly have nothing holding me to one spot, other than that fear of stepping over the doorstep. I do hope that I can find relief in writing about such things though. I'm going to buy a notepad soon, so I can jot down all the ideas that pop into my head throughout the day, but I forget by the time I get home. One of my biggest fantasies I've come up with is having what I call a Jump Ship. It's a two-person Solar class ship, capable of obtaining orbit from startup within a minute. The Jump name comes from it's ability to launch from landing position, without having to tilt so the rear thrusters can face the ground. God I need some good sci-fi.    Song of the Day:  In The Meantime  by  Space Hog   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>