<Blog>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been taken by a girl that i am falling for vary fast if it ment to be than i meet her soon and i intend to be hers untill the end what ever that might be.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bla bla bla bitch bitch bitch rant rant rant this is what i want to do im in a bad mood and im tierd
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Me standing next to my computer&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every day the same thing... NOTHING!!! I have few friends to start with and they don't bother much with me so forget them. But I am SO board I want to cry =(. Any way this day wasn't too bad I got to help at the local festival setting up a both and bought a set of swords that I have wanted for a long time.  
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have been thinking about things and i am realy lonely of late and i have found im realy loenly and i want some one to be with but i dont know of any... IT REALY SUCKS!!!! im not horrny i just want to curl up with some that i care about and just wisper sweet nothings into her ear! but no one wants to be with me =(
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have self injured for ten years now I have thousands of scars and marks on my skin. The last year has been the worst year of my life... I tried to commit suicide 6 times in 5 month how in the hell did I get this way? Why do I have the addiction that I do? Why do I cut so deeply that I bleed for long periods of time? What do I have to live for? 
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my heart is lossing its ability to love and I hate it so! 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i had to break up with my girlfriend today becuse im too unstable to even care for my self!!! why cant i have a normal life with out this pain? im tierd of living in a hell! 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am being torn apart by so many things right now I don't know how long I can survive... I want to die and I want to live I don't know how to do either and the gods aren't paying attention to my crys of pain... Disgrace to my life for the past I hide!   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have fought the demons of my mind for so long I fear that I have lost all my strength. I have little keeping me from dying, my GF, computer, car and so on but anyway the demons of the heart are now comings of age and the mind is fighting on fronts and I don't know how long I will be able to survive another night 
    
</post>


</Blog>