<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my corner  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kasumigaseki  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      rhumba frapucino any1?   urlLink      
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kasumigaseki bldg  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oops, took me some minutes after gulping my Starbuck café au lait to come up with the name, quite satisfied and blissfully funny…, but don’t know why reflecting on that 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, it's only 10 p.m in Tokyo, but I'm listening to that 'sugar' song, 2 a.m. and the rain's falling... used to be touched so much by that song. Back to reality now, I have load of work to do and get to come to  urlLink adbi  tomorrow, will bring my laptop there, need to work with this 1-year partner tomorrow, what's this weekend got to offer? just thinking about that Starbuck&nbsp; hmmm, the&nbsp;&nbsp;Matcha Cream Frappuccino again, yummy   ah hah, some food for thought .. got it sent over by somebody:   The Blunders of the world:  1. Wealth without work  2. Pleasure without conscience  3. Knowledge without character  4. Commerce without morality  5. Science without humanity  6. Worship without sacrifice  7. Politics without principles  8. Rights without Responsibilities   for more see for yourself, the link is here:  urlLink http://www.gandhiinstitute.org/8blunders.html    have to put some rice for lady V, she wont be home till midnite, god, cant imagine taking medical-related major...   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Twintower Shinjuku  urlLink    try to post some photos...  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two movies and two clubs on the same nite... by no means meant that we are either cinema or clubbing maniac; maybe the best reason I can think of is that we are 'victim of circumstances'. At first, it seemed to me that none of us thought about an overnite in Tokyo, well, I guess somehow, nite life in  urlLink ROPPONGI  is really new and tempting that we can't resist exploring,&nbsp;okay, everyone, &nbsp;let's take the plunge...  Intended to see SPIDER MAN 2 on the first show day in ROPPONGI's virgin cinema,we came to find that the 5.45 pm show of  urlLink of the film  was sold out and decided to try  urlLink THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW . My only complaint was that we had to be seated on the front and to me the film sometimes has unnecessary emotional-raising scenes. And the idea of seeing the SPIDER MAN 2 was kinda persistent that we tried the 27:10 show. An overnite was also wise in the sense that until the end of the show do train operated and we wanted to go another clubbing. All of us, The Monk seemed to be the most advocating to the ideas of overnite, Lady Van and me may share an equal same enthusiasim to make it, the 183 boy was also curiuos about his first visit to ROPPONGI and Lady Phuong and Lady Thu is too nice to be with us. If only one of us wanted to left early, the overnite would collapse, I guess.   Is there anything I miss out in this messy post? ah, I tried the  urlLink Tequila Sunrise  while other orders were common stuff like  urlLink Sex on the beach ,  urlLink Margarita    The clubs are only Japanese in the sense that they are funnily small as a club and somtimes we couldn't find room to swing our hips... hehehe.   surpise,surprise, we all felt it when we got out of the comfortable cinema, it had been sunny and bright ... Someone regreted getting up so late and made a resolution to make an earlier day.   got home at 7 and slept like a log after coming home till noon... still tired and the legs hurt..   well, sleepness in Tokyo...    
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is damn hot and you got sticky. and guess, I walked in Ueno under the high noon sun without my favourite arm gloves -)), that's what I remember about the summer in Hanoi when all the girls are covered to the teeth to avoid the sun attack... 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just testing my new blog
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here I am in Hanoi, to the surprise of everyone of the change they see in me, physicallym, grmm, grmm, really have to plot a weight killing plan.. All I can say is I'm happy to be home. will travel in next few days before going around for the thesis material... home sweet home... 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>