<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Did I mention that this blog would be rude? Possibly offensive, and decidedly unappealing to probably most but a certain set? If you think you are part of the certain set (I leave it up to you to decide. We function on an honor system here), you might enjoy this next bit.  Yesterday I came down with a very annoying case of diarrhea. Now, once upon a time, I was VERY disturbed by such things. However, after driving over many rocky roads and coming out laughing, I've decided that the trots are, indeed, rather funny. To a point. It was funny when I was sitting at my desk and realized it would not be safe to fart, even with the relative privacy my office offers. It was funny when I got to the restroom and made the walls rattle. It was funny when this cycle repeated itself roughly six times. However, on the seventh round, the humor started to evaporate.   Now, I believe I have lived to wittness a certain social revolution. I don't know if it's the popular acceptance of television shows like SOUTH PARK, CRANK YANKERS and MOST EXTREME ELIMINATION CHALLENGE, or if it's the evolution of internet accessibility that makes any and all information accessible, nothing secret, and therefore fewer things to be embarassed about, but I can tell you that 10 years ago I NEVER would have plopped down in my supervisor's office and asked her if she wanted to run over to the store with me to get some Immodium because "I've got flaming diarrhea and I just can't work like this." Nor would I have announced this fact to the receptionist and HR manager in the front office and laughed my head off all the way out the door. Nor would I have plopped down the box of Immodium pills in front of the hot young (male) cashier with all the humility of a prize fighter on his tenth undefeated round.&nbsp; But I can safely say, it was just another day at the office.  I've also come to realize that this annoying little affliction even has some advantages. My post-partum tummy looks flatter than it has since my pre-pregnancy days, and my weigh-in at Weight Watchers last evening revealed a 2.4 pound weight loss, despite the fact that I'd ignored every WW principle and ate like a pregnant elephant for the past week. It was rather a proud moment, though I couldn't help feeling like I had cheated, just a bit.  But apparently I didn't feel to strong of a need to justify myself, and it's a good thing the WW facilitator didn't choose that meeting to ask me "what made me succcessful this week." Because I don't think I could have resisted standing up and telling all present that I owe my svelte success to a most fortuitious bout of flaming trots. 
      
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I tried to get to my lovely blog from my work computer today and apparently my access has been blocked! This usually only happens when one tries to visit pornographic or recreational drug-related sites, so who woulda thunk? I don't FEEL naughty, or, uh hmmm.  &nbsp; I guess it's time to end this post as my lovely toddler is having a tantrum downstairs and I feel the heat of my husband's blood boiling from this distance. I bid good evening to everyone and no one. 
      
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Watch your step. It's a long drop to the bottom!
      
</post>


</Blog>