<Blog>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SO today was good....it's weird when you're in such a positive headspace and as a result don't feel much like writing.   Busy week ahead, tonight is din-din with parents then off to a gig at the dog, and thurs is drinks after work and sketching in the park....   Mike is coming in on Friday, looking forward to seeing him. Part of me really wants Brent to meet him, and part of me...I don't know would rather just skip the whole stupidity of important people in your life meeting other important people...why can't there be some sort of osmosis growth for that relationship....I just hate the "hello, nice to meet you"....urg, I know them both and it makes me uncomfortable. And I know Mike...he's so judgy judgy....I know there's no way his opinion would make a difference but I want him to like him and see all those beautiful things I do...I guess that's not what matters.   What's really interesting this week is the sudden abundance of friends...I should explain. Do you ever notice that a week or two may go by and you seem to lack a life? People aren't calling as much, not that you care too much, you've got you're own shit going on...but it suddenly dawns on you that you might never have a social life outside of your relationship again...   But this week, I'm getting emails from people I haven't spoken to in awhile, friends and people are writing and calling....It's like fate put a beacon on top of your house and said..."THIS WEEK IT'S BECCA!".  awww, i wish that would happen with money...nah   I love the Shins...seriously and Metric. YA!   COMBAT BABY!!!    
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://hokev.brinkster.net/quiz/default.asp?quiz=Better+Personality&page=1 20 Questions to a Better Personality  Wackiness: 72/100 Rationality: 50/100 Constructiveness: 56/100 Leadership: 68/100    You are a WECL--Wacky Emotional Constructive Leader. This makes you a people's advocate. You are passionate about your causes, with a good heart and good endeavors. Your personal fire is contagious, and others wish they could be as dedicated to their beliefs as you are.  Your dedication may cause you to miss the boat on life's more slight and trivial activities. You will feel no loss when skipping some inane mixer, but it can be frustrating to others to whom such things are important. While you find it difficult to see other points of view, it may be useful to act as if you do, and play along once in a while.  In any event, you have buckets of charisma and a natural skill for making people open up. Your greatest asset is an ability to make progress while keeping the peace.    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate my brain.  I wish sometimes it would stop reliving and creating the moments in life.  And most of the time it's not the good stuff.  I hate Angel.  I can't believe how much of a bitch she is, I can't believe how selfish...and just fucking stupid.  I would love to just write it out, but it's SO FUCKING RETARDED that I'm surprised...not i'm not, that this is going to be the breaking point.  Basically, there was a job posting that we both wanted to apply for but she REAAALLLLYYY wanted the job, so it really "bothered" her that I was going to apply too...I DOUBT SHE'LL EVEN GET AN INTERVIEW!!  Is this what friendships go for?  So did I apply?  Nope.  Do I want to speak to her anytime soon? Fuck no.  And I think what gets me the most, is that in her head I'm the one in the "wrong" and she's SO good at justifying any fucking position that relieves her of responsibility....  right...maybe the rest of the day will be a little more positive.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just heard about a possible job opening as something that would be SO cool, as a career advisor...  I WOULD LOVE TO, the only thing I really don't have is the solid experience...informally...but formally. Non.  Going to apply anyway, but to have a job that I wouldn't mind going to!!  There's also an opening in another city...think I'll still apply.  An opportunity is an opportunity, not sure if I should even mention it to Brent.  Maybe just wait to see if I get an interview first.  Not sure what his reaction/feelings would be...  Moving to the Cameroon yes...in awhile...but another city in the near future.  I'm not sure he's ready to go yet.  hmmmm, right, wait for the interview first.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A good friend of my love's is in from the Cameroon.  He's a really neat guy, funny, introspective and full of ideas.  Hard to read at times, but I think that becomes easier the more you know him.  He teaches there with his wife, and it sounds like such an amazing adventure.  He's trying to convince Brent and I to go...I would love to...  I mean sure, there's some trepidation.  Look what happened last time.  Brent and I aren't even engaged, let alone married...But fuck that would be amazing!!  I've never wanted to teach in Canada, for some reason it hasn't really appealed to me...but the Cameroon...wow.  I'm interested to hear how the whole thing turns out there.  I wonder if Brent can handle it...  Everytime I think about it...I just can't wait for him to be my husband.  I love just being with him.  He's so amazing and I can't wait for us to just grow and grow as a couple...  I'm not as afraid of it all as I used to be...I was so afraid it was going to end.  Now, I know I just need to be myself (not that I wasn't before) and just accept that, that will just have to be enough.  ...  Last night was a LOT of fun.  Brent and I had dinner with his family for his brother's birthday.  I love his family, they're so sincere and down to earth.  So much fun ( i know, it's family) but they're so lovely and funny.  Neurotic, at times but that's what makes it interesting.  Then back to Brent's to meet up with Pete for a little trivial pursuit and smokes.  SO funny.    I miss Lisa.  Wish we had more time together, and more in common.  Hopefully that will change.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess that probably sounds like a fairly morbid title for any blog entry.  But I don't mean for it to come off as depressive, or suicidal.  In fact, it's to indicate my anonymity.  You see, I made the mistake last time of telling several friends about a previous blog thinking that they could be updated on the day to day...but then i found myself editing and censoring my thoughts on entries....I mean, the whole point is to vent right?  Or at least, to let a little of the craziness out?  And since I sit at this fucking computer for a better part of the day....why not...let a little out.  There's a song by a Jem called "Save Me"...the lyrics, unfortunately or fortunately describe a common thought pattern that I have...overthinking, overanalyzing, overdreaming...is there such a thing?  Or is the rest of the world crazy?  A little info about me...I'm 24...I love books, creating art, politics, humanist debate, unfortunately reality television, knitting, writing and editing, crying and laughing.  I want the world to be a great place, for me and my children but find my motivation and ambition to do so....wane and lack focus.  Anyone understand this thought?   I'm absolutely in love with a boy, and I try everyday not to be afraid that it's all going to end.  I love my parents, particularly my mom who I strive to be like everyday.  I have a best friend, one that I can talk to about dick size, both Cheney and the physical.  Doesn't sound too bad hey?  Nope, and I'm not complaining.  But I still have a voice inside my head that wants expression.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>