<Blog>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK.... so yesterday was Warped Tour and it rocked my socks. WOW! IT was so great.. The best part was seeing Taking Back Sunday for the first time AND ::drum roll:: CROWD SURFING for the first time. It was great! A wonderful experience. The adrenalin rush when you are surfing is so great, because two seconds before it looks like they are going to drop you... they catch you and hurl you back in up in the air. Its so awesome. I love it.... too bad Ashlie and I are DAMN sore today. Thats the only bad thing. As much as I hate to say it... New Found Glory was pretty good. I honestly thought they were going to suck but they didnt. Yellowcard was good, Story of the Year was good. Coheed and Cambria really let me down.... I expected a lot more from them. Oh well....! But The highlight of my time there was definatly Taking Back Sunday. Its great... but yeah, I've ranted enough about this so Im going to go. Hey Ashlie- BEND OVER AND TAKE IT LIKE A BITCH! HAHA!
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok... so Summer school, The 4 of us (Ryan, Ashlie, Mark and I) all sat on seperate walls. How gay is that bitchy teacher?! Wow Im not even going to start on that beyatch. So after School I drove with Ashlie for awhile to meet Ty... which he never showed so I left to McDonalds and got a crap load o' food. I got: 10 Piece Chicken Nugget, A Double Cheese Burger, and Fries. I ate most of it. Ashlie got a salad that was WAAAAAAAAAAY raunch. It smelled horrible and just looking at it made me want to toss my cookies. Then we got bored so I went to Marks house and rang his doorbell for awhile lol. He was sitting right in front of the door with it open and he was about to answer it. Silly boy! Then I had to come home because I got in a fight with my mommma. So I came home then this Bomb ass guy named Kody IMD me and goes "Guess what!! IM IN TOWN!" So I was freaking out and I just HAD to go hang out with him because Kody rocks. He's coming back next weekend.. hopefully Ill hang with him for awhile because he makes me laugh. Him and his peanuts. ::giggles and shakes head:: And we took random pictures of each other and of us with our cams. You should check em out with I get them posted on Myspace.com (which that link is in my profile but if you don't view my profile here it is http://profile.myspace.com/users/4321823 ) And then I came home and chilled... Called Deryck (Cali) and talked to him while he packed because he's leaving this weekend and I wont be able to talk to him for awhile. :-( Anyways... I don't know what else to talk about and this is really long. So bye bye!!!! :-D
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh yay... lookie what Rachel has!
    
</post>


</Blog>