<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "The test of a first-rate intelligence is the ability to hold two opposed ideas in the mind at the same time, and still retain the ability to function."  ~ F. Scott Fitzgerald 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Beatles Eleanor Rigby  (Lennon/McCartney)   Ah, look at all the lonely people  Ah, look at all the lonely people   Eleanor Rigby picks up the rice in the church where a wedding has been  Lives in a dream  Waits at the window, wearing the face that she keeps in a jar by the door  Who is it for?   All the lonely people  Where do they all come from?  All the lonely people  Where do they all belong?   Father McKenzie writing the words of a sermon that no one will hear  No one comes near  Look at him working, darning his socks in the night when there's nobody there  What does he care?   All the lonely people  Where do they all come from?  All the lonely people  Where do they all belong?   Ah, look at all the lonely people  Ah, look at all the lonely people   Eleanor Rigby died in the church and was buried along with her name  Nobody came  Father McKenzie wiping the dirt from his hands as he walks from the grave  No one was saved   All the lonely people (Ah, look at all the lonely people)  Where do they all come from?  All the lonely people (Ah, look at all the lonely people)  Where do they all belong?    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Desiderata   Go placidly amid the noise and haste, and remember what peace there may be in silence. As far as possible without surrender be on good terms with all persons. Speak your truth quietly and clearly; and listen to others, even the dull and the ignorant; they too have their story.   Avoid loud and aggressive persons, they are vexations to the spirit. If you compare yourself with others, you may become vain and bitter; for always there will be greater and lesser persons than yourself. Enjoy your achievements as well as your plans.    Keep interested in your own career, however humble; it is a real possession in the changing fortunes of time. Exercise caution in your business affairs; for the world is full of trickery. But let this not blind you to what virtue there is; many persons strive for high ideals; and everywhere life is full of heroism.    Be yourself. Especially, do not feign affection. Neither be cynical about love; for in the face of all aridity and disenchantment it is as perennial as the grass.    Take kindly the counsel of the years, gracefully surrendering the things of youth. Nurture strength of spirit to shield you in sudden misfortune. But do not distress yourself with dark imaginings. Many fears are born of fatigue and loneliness. Beyond a wholesome discipline, be gentle with yourself.    You are a child of the universe, no less than the trees and the stars; you have a right to be here. And whether or not it is clear to you, no doubt the universe is unfolding as it should.    Therefore be at peace with God, whatever you conceive Him to be, and whatever your labors and aspirations, in the noisy confusion of life keep peace with your soul.    With all its sham, drudgery, and broken dreams, it is still a beautiful world. Be cheerful. Strive to be happy.    Max Ehrmann, Desiderata, Copyright 1952.      
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Such truths should arrive loudly  with clanging cymbals and crashing thunder. Or as seeping, creeping cold with icy tongues licking to numb my core.  Then I could cover my ears or with flint and steel strike a hopeful spark. What can I do in a room so full of Empty the echoes have flown?     jcr2004  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have never smoked, but I have lived with smokers for most of my life. Several times, I have held a lit cigarette in my hand and considered taking up the habit, but I have never taken two consecutive drags. It's not that I immediately began coughing or felt I was going to be sick, it is more a matter of it not feeling like something I would do. When I look at my hand holding a cigarette, it seems like someone else's hand.   There is much I envy about smoking, though.   For one thing, the camaraderie. There is an automatic sense of something in common when two smokers come together, even if they share nothing else. Simply offering a light is a form of communication, an expression of some basic acceptance and understanding. A group of strangers can stand around outside and smoke together, saying very little and still feel as if they have shared an experience with one another. We non-smokers stand there feeling separate from the group. And when I see my partner lean over to light another woman's cigarette, I feel such an intense, unreasonable jealousy that I hardly recognize myself -- it catches me off guard every time. I feel like asking why he can't just hand her the book of matches. But I know that's not how it's done.   Smoking seems a big conversational aid, too. An elaborate lighting up ritual can buy a person a lot of time. Naturally he cannot be expected to respond until that first drag has been completely inhaled, savored and contemplatively exhaled. Meanwhile, we non-smokers run the risk of being considered evasive if we don't reply immediately to another's query or suggestion. Taking a drink of coffee just does not consume a fairly proportionate amount of time, no matter how much I try, and it doesn't help that I drink it black. I have no sugar packets to open or spoon to stir 'round and 'round as I gaze contemplatively into the swirling liquid.   Stress reduction is another apparent benefit to smoking. Some attribute the peacefulness they feel to the chemicals included in tobacco, while others say it is the rhythm of it, the physical comfort of it. Either way, sometimes when I come to the end of a work day with a person who has taken multiple cigarette breaks and is still complaining about stress, I feel like saying, "What about me? I dealt with this whole mess without benefit of any such stress-reducing tool. Imagine what  I  feel like!"   I have often felt separated from my partner by his smoking. While smoking and staring off into space, he seems complete, needing nothing from me. Sometimes I wish I was the cigarette, cradled so effortessly in his hand.   In her novel,  Now Is the Time to Open Your Heart , Alice Walker writes:   "The habit of smoking (terrible, dumber than stupid, he knew) had taught him about emptiness, the need to fill internal space, the huge internal space within all of us with Something. He was grateful he could smoke. Though he knew there were women who dismissed him the instant they saw him light up, because they could not imagine kissing him."   So I read those words to my partner last night to see if he would consider them an apt description of the way it is to smoke. He said yes, and more than yes. He told me that often that he smokes instead of talking to me and that it is easier to smoke than to talk. In other words, smoking requires less of him.   Looking back over the relationships I've had with smokers -- all of them long and important ones, associations that have shaped me as a person -- I found both her words and his extremely interesting. Why do I seem to gravitate toward men who smoke? And why has my response to their smoking never been to take it up myself? Why haven't I chosen to fill my huge internal space with the same thing? God knows I've a lifetime of examples to emulate. Is it possible I've filled it with nothing? Is it possible I am just all emptiness inside?   None of the smokers in my life has ever suggested that I join him in his habit. I have always thought they were concerned for my health, or maybe that they didn't like the way it looked on someone else. But lately I've been thinking something new.   What if they don't want me to smoke because they don't want me to be filled up the way they are? What if they understand on some level that if I were to smoke I would be less emotionally available to them?   I have never nagged a person about smoking. And I have never been the type to refuse to buy cigarettes on the theory that to do so is to aid and abet another's destruction. I allow people to smoke in my home and in my car. My attitude has always been that I value the person and want that person to comfortable when in my company. I have never disqualified a person as a potential friend because of smoking. Being around a smoker doesn't bother me.   But now, in light of this new perspective, I find myself thinking about it somewhat differently. What if the emotional distance I feel from my partner is caused because he smokes? Will he ever be able to (or choose to) make more internal space for me? If smoking fills him up inside, will there ever be room for me?       
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The spell lingers and every mundane touch evokes comparison, whispers of you.  Resting by the street, I settle myself into the wooden contours of a sagging bench and feel it waken, forsaking decades of jaded indifference. Its arms and legs are yours and so I sit a while, savoring the embrace, public in its privacy.  Sunlight finds the shoulder still dusted with your breath and my skin quivers, alive in reverie.    jcr/8/7/04 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I want no more things to bind me! All this stuff much too narrowly defining me!  Wife. Mother. Child. One day soon I will just go wild from knowing I cannot get free.  I want to listen to the sea... to catch my thoughts in poetry and vent my fury when its riled. I want no more things.  I want to wander endlessly, marvelling at eternity. I want to lose myself, beguiled by that which was before reviled. Dancing through the stars, joyously... I want no more things.   jcr2003 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Strength to Share  Hope flies all around and through me. It's magic in the air: more real than wishes made for free, or even pious prayer.  Hope shows us how we long to be: dancing the way we dare, our souls as open as the sea, released from needless care.  No way to prove what you can't see, believing makes it there, flying all around and through me, giving me strength to share.   jcr2003 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "When a trout rising to a fly gets hooked on a line and finds himself unable to swim about freely, he begins with a fight which results in struggles and splashes and sometimes an escape.  Often, of course, the situation is too tough for him.  In the same way the human struggles with his environment and with the hooks that catch him.  Sometimes he masters his difficulties; sometimes they are too mcuh for him.  His struggles are all that the world sees and it naturally misunderstands them.  It is hard for a free fish to understand what is happening to a hooked one."  ~ Karl A. Menninger
     

    
</post>


</Blog>