<Blog>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        For those who are going to Singapore Sports School next friday...remember to meet at 2.30 or maybe earlier to board the bus..joel would be taking attendance.&nbsp; For next week training, there would be no gym by instead more of technical skills and footwork. For those who did not go for training todae (23/7/04), pls contact any one who went for training to find out from them whether are u goin for the friendly matches against the sss retar... aiyah nvm i would post the names of those going lar.. just check here if u r not  sure....      Those going but not confirmed yet:      Joel kuan      Marcus Ng      Gabriel Wu      Justin Kong      Richard Teo       Tang Xin Quan      Ye Yu Zhi      Chen Chen Jia (nai nai de di ku)      Jonathan Chow      Nigger Wong      Eduard lee luo han      David Wong      Jeremy Loh Blur King      Alex Lim      Shi Xian      Nicholas Ng      Edrick Yap     nnnn i tink one more but i forgot....   But for max and garry ...dont be sad.. continue to train harder.  &nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Bring your skipping ropes for trainin this week...&nbsp;and also dont be late for trainin..if u cant come for any of the trainins..tell mun hoe as he would be taking down your attendance.&nbsp; train hard oso...and dont slack...      
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey if u ppl wan to say something or post something, like ur comments on ho w u find the trngs, the coaching methods or trng dates and everything else, tell ur level head be it sec 2 or sec 1 and then he will post if for u.the level head had better post it or u'll die i tell u first.ur identity will be kept anonymous yar.so dont worry.this is ur chance to say what you want, of cos constructive criticism.
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      after this blog has been completed, the username and password would be only given to certain number of ppl per level as in the badminton team. For the sec 1 level, Ivan would be given the username and password, for sec 2 level, benjamin and jon chou would be given...n for the sec3s joel and kenneth seet and i (jinyi) would have it...for those who hav the username and password pls do not give it to anyone else...if found out u wwill be dead... for ppl viewing this blog, u can comment on the blog or express your views and suggestions of how to improve this blog... 
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      alright alright..the tag board would be up as soon as possible so dont be impatient la.actually come to think of it, il give everyone the user name and password to this blogger account.then after that, if u pple want to post anything, change the template or whaatever u want to do wiht, please ask me and inform me that u are doing so.u can inform jinyi also.
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey people, trng on monday as usual, and wed also, pls note dont be late like yushee otherwise we will all punished k.anyway im joel here and if u want to post any entry then let me know alright.this is for u to comment on trng schedules, u can remain anon also, and il try my best to solve ur problem along with jinyi. on the tag board is where you all will share your problems and all, and any changes in trng schedule will be notified to u via this as well.if u cannot make it for trng, u can try to let us know through here.but make sure u sms sir first.96924176.let him know in advance,thank u.my number is 96787589 if u all dont know.lastly, train hard and hopefullly the title will be ours next yr.if the the username n password to this account will only be diclosed to a few sec 3s.sec 2s and sec 1s are kindly requested to use the tag board.ahahhaha.not my idea ah.jinheng's idea
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this blog is created as a "meeting or chattin place" for those who were once or now in the badminton team...posts would be put up in the future like training time or anything that is related to badminton, so do check here in the future if u need to noe anything that is goin on in badminton... 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      congratulations to david, garry, nicholas, max,gabriel, ivan, kkenneth seet for performing well in the cross country.if i never include ur name here,paiseh ah.anyway for those that didn get anything, try harder next year.dont get angry la, or even jealous.u siao ah.train ur badminton not running la.so fit but if u suck then u will lose on court.hello.u cant always outrun ur opponent.u need skills too ok.wake up ur bloody idea la! 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      there would be no training this national day holidays... so go and spend time with your friends and family members.. however, training would resume on this coming friday.. so don't forget... and also stop spammin g... 
    
</post>


</Blog>