<Blog>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Good morning, well, it's 14:30 then it must be good afternoon! I woke up an hour ago and my eyes are burning, I was studying till 04:30 AM last night, chatting and studying.. I have a job interview next week in a Hi Tech company in Haifa. I so want this job.. The position I'm applying to is R&D Engineering Support. It has to do with System/Information analysis, JDBC, ASP & .NET. So I had to lie a little in my resume, I add few good spicy thing and deleted others. Since I have been studying so damn hard for this - I have no idea what JDBC is - so  I had to find out what the hell is it...I hope I'll get the job. Wish me luck, I'm optimistic.   anyway, this is the first time that I write in a blog and I think I like it. I hope could meet people in here who share the same interests with me, and I'm looking forward for any comments/replies by the readers. Truly yours;  Joker. 

						
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Just for the fun of this... I woke up feeling gooood, and i rushed to my computer to write this down. Ruba will be back tonight some where around 7-8 o'clock. I wonder what she have for me?! heh    Last night was terrible! I wanted to go out so bad, and so i checked with my friends, i made some phone calls,&nbsp;but none of them wanted to go anywhere... Maroon (M.F) was not in the mood! Roni (M.F) claimed that he has some arrangements... I wonder what arrangements... Isam (M.F), this guy is a  phenomenon , he bought a car some years ago, and since then i've never seen him driving it! He always have  argument s, a  crybaby... sometimes it's the test, the insurance, the  mechanics! son of bitch.   I had to spend my time by the computer, chatting or whatever.. Maisam is cool.. But It was  FRIDAY NIGHT  for god sake!!   p.s: M.F stands for Mother Fucker! 
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    I've got 21 questions and they are all about love, life and  beyond.   
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm shocked! I was watching TV and on the I-TECH show (what's new in Hi-Tech) they presented a new device, an electronic meter, recently developed by some company.. An ease to use device, compact , and more precise than the old tool!  &nbsp; Wondering what does it have to do with me? Why am i shocked? Well.. I thought of the idea some time ago.. I was wondering back then what device could a person invent and gain serious amount of money out of it? And i got the same idea.. What did i do with it?  Nothing!  Asking why?  &nbsp; Well.. I would have jumped on the idea right way.. But.. There is a  BIG BUT  here, meaning, what if the is not 100% straight vertical? This would cause a calculation error. What if a person wants to calculate a flat surface, a 2X2 table for instance?  &nbsp; Anyway, I think that if i can come up with such ideas i can, eventually, fix it's defects.   

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I wonder what Ruba is doing right now? We haven't spoken for two days now and i miss her so much. I could use some good jokes right now.. She is a funny joker, the way she describes incident or tell me the news is so funny, hilarious. I miss her, I miss her a lot. What is more to say about her? I'm in love with her, I think.   Love is complicated, freaky, frightening,.. And in my age it's not a joke anymore, there are more responsibilities than before. I just hope, for my sake and hers, that i'm on the right path in this junction.  I think i made more complicated choices and decision before in my life, most of them were wrong of course and i've failed many times to succeed?! But now, for the first time in my life, i have a good feeling about a choice that i made (i.e: us, me and Ruba), I uhh.. It.. I.. It feels good.  Doubts, Uncertainty, insecurity, Fears,..    Is that what love is all about?!  

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is one hell of a speech by Al Pacino taken from the "Any Given Sunday" movie. It's called  urlLink "Inch By Inch speech" . I just can't help myself not to shiver every time i  listen to it.. I got the audio and the text file of it. The text is  brilliantly outstanding , the background music (a classic guitar) is from heaven..  lucidly silence ... And Al Pacino is one mother fucking genius actor.    Al Pacino's Inch By Inch speech from Any Given Sunday     "I don't know what to say really. Three minutes to the biggest battle of our professional lives all comes down to today. Either we heal as a team or we are going to crumble. Inch by inch play by play till we're finished. We are in hell right now, gentlemen believe me and we can stay here and get the shit kicked out of us or we can fight our way back into the light. We can climb out of hell. One inch, at a time.  Now I can't do it for you. I'm too old. I look around and I see these young faces and I think I mean I made every wrong choice a middle age man could make. I uh.... I pissed away all my money believe it or not. I chased off anyone who has ever loved me. And lately, I can't even stand the face I see in the mirror.  You know when you get old in life things get taken from you. That's, that's part of life. But, you only learn that when you start losing stuff. You find out that life is just a game of inches. So is football. Because in either game life or football the margin for error is so small. I mean one half step too late or to early you don't quite make it. One half second too slow or too fast and you don't quite catch it. The inches we need are everywhere around us. They are in ever break of the game every minute, every second.  On this team, we fight for that inch On this team, we tear ourselves, and everyone around us to pieces for that inch. We CLAW with our finger nails for that inch. Cause we know when we add up all those inches that's going to make the fucking difference between WINNING and LOSING between LIVING and DYING.  I'll tell you this in any fight it is the guy who is willing to die who is going to win that inch. And I know if I am going to have any life anymore it is because, I am still willing to fight, and die for that inch because that is what LIVING is. The six inches in front of your face.  Now I can't make you do it. You gotta look at the guy next to you. Look into his eyes. Now I think you are going to see a guy who will go that inch with you. You are going to see a guy who will sacrifice himself for this team because he knows when it comes down to it, you are gonna do the same thing for him.  That's a team, gentlemen and either we heal now, as a team, or we will die as individuals. That's football guys. That's all it is. Now, whattaya gonna do?"   

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   All the things one has forgotten scream for help in dreams.   urlLink   ~Elias Canetti     I dream a lot, specially if i eat before going to sleep. Last night i had this weird dream... My friend Souhel and his wife Fayze, they got married a week or two ago, but since my aunt passed away a week before their weeding i was not able to be present there. I think i should call and congratulate them. Another dream was about Zohar from Eilat.. She was my neighbor the time when i was there... The weird thing about this one is that she was disgustingly fat! It has been a month or two since the last time we had a conversation.  When i woke up i had to search for a quote the matches with my dream and i've found the one above. I've found many  urlLink interesting quotes here.   

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have no title for this one cause i aint got nothing to write. Ohh... By the way.. I got my hair cut..Good job lazy ass. 

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today I've dld the following albums:   - George Michael - GNR - Nirvana - Alanis Morissette - Eric Clapton - Pearl Jam - Sting - Lauryn Hill and Lenny Kravitz (still in dld process).  All these albums are from the MTV Unplugged concerts show , probably the best show ever. TO be honest, I enjoyed them all. George Michael was great, Eric Clapton was very emotional but Alanis's concert was the best! I enjoy it very much... Relaxing. 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was planning to go out today and by me a T-Shirt or maybe a pair of jeans, get my hair cut maybe, but here i am home..  Again !  

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ruba is going tomorrow to Jordan to get her degree. She is going to stay there for 4 days, and i already miss her. We had a long conversation on the phone some minutes ago, and i could feel her sorrow.. She was melancholic. She is a joyful full of life person, she makes me laugh every time i'm sad. She loves me immensely. It's hard for me too, i care a lot for her, she is an amazing person. Oh shut up.. i'm talking as if she is gone forever. She'll be back on Saturday night. 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Being on a diet is not easy. I have to eat low calories, fat and healthy food. In order to ease this i have to come up with fine tasty recipes.. So i cooked Chinese food, and it was so damn delicious. Yummy. Good work Nizar, you get an  A+ .  

						
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I seem to succeed motivating and inducing people toward a successful happy career, friendship, a relationship or whatever may lacks motive or encourage.   you are a natural born motivator  . That's what my friends tell me and thank me for. But why cant i at least for once encourage and motivate myself toward something, anything! How do you call a person who is concerned only with his own self? Selfish? Self centered? What's the opposite of that? What does psychology have to say about that? Is it a common classic phenomenon? Is it a phenomenon? 

						
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hmmm this is interesting. Someone today told me that men usually ask the woman they are about to marry if she makes good coffee before they propose. I never knew that! But what about the food?? 

						
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Could it be that i'm that much of a brainless? I was watching TV and on the news there was a special report about the Israeli law pertaining to the private detectives.. Anyway, as always, I'm not able to understand any of these laws! Some are tending to contradict to each others, some are pointless, some are lacking the ability of enforcement and for all the rest, I never knew they exist!!  I.e: there is one law that "alleges" to keep the detective discreet by preventing them from mentioning there profession in their resume! Another prohibit citizens to insult a public/ governmental personality (policeman..) in public! Why the hell not. SHUT UP.  

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's a hot day today. I can't concentrate on anything.. I'm tired, I wish i can get some sleep but it's so damn hot. This is strange but it makes me feel horny, somehow.  Last night it wasn't better. I could barely sleep in boxers only without any blankets. It was like 30 degrees at night! I also had my window open and a fan on. I even watched some TV to try to get me tire but that didn't work.  We need A/C!  

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was wondering if there is a formula for the ultimate lucidness joy of life?! I suddenly don't feel well about my life, my whole life.. I don't where did that feeling come from! I mean i'm a joyous full of life person, this is so unlike me. Shit.. I thought writing here would cheer me up a little! This is not helping. I have too many things running on mind right now. I think it's better to close here. 

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is good stuff for my Blog, enjoy it.  "Perspective on life according to George Costanza (Seinfeld)"  "The most unfair thing about life is the way it ends. I mean, life is tough. It takes up a lot of your time. What do you get at the end of it? A death. What's that, a bonus?!? I think the life cycle is all backwards. You should die first, get it out of the way. Then you go live in an old age home. You get kicked out when you're too young, go collect all your super, then, when you start work, you get a gold watch on your first day. You work forty years until you're young enough to enjoy your retirement. You drink alcohol, you party, and you get ready for High School. You go to primary school, you become a kid, you play, you have no responsibilities, you become a little baby, you go back into the womb, you spend your last 9 months floating with luxuries like Central heating, spa,room service on tap, then you finish off as an orgasm! Amen."  

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This cracks my whip. One of the hottest most expensive Hollywood stars in now days, Cameron Diaz, is furious after a steamy S&M video showing her getting down and dirty has been put on the internet. The kinky footage, made when the Hollywood star was a 19-year-old (an unknown actress back then), shows her posing topless and walking a leather-masked man like a dog. The video is offered on the net for only $39.95 !  I've dld the movie (the full 30min.from the bearshare). To be frank, i dont think it's worth it. I was more expecting sex scene than  CRAP . I wonder what does Justin Timberlake have to say about it.    

						
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It has been two and a half months since my last job, and since then I have gained lots of kgr.. This is driving me crazy. I'm  FAT  I look like Cartman from South Park!. I used once to go to the GYM and work out my muscles, and to the pool.. I miss these days a lot. Now, I spend most of my time on the computer, chatting, studying, surfing the net and eating..  a lot . I have been trying to avoid the refrigerator, but I cant help it! I'm in love with it.. It's a luring world, full of attractive places, has some kind of passion, magic,.. Something that I cant explain.  This is like talking about sex, portraying. God, I eat like a pig.   So every day is the same as the one before! fuckin' routine. I think I need a challenge or maybe go shopping, this might help, I guess. Anyway, that's about all, I think I better go study a bit.  

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I woke up today, didn't have my breakfast but had only a cup of coffee, a very fine coffee, took a shower and went straight to paint my room and the corridor. It usually takes me a an hour or so to paint a room with a corridor, but this time it took me something like 5 hours! Maybe cause i worked like a professionalist or cause it has been a while since i last worked in painting houses. It was fun but i'm so tired, the final result was  PERFECTO ! My family were  stunned  by my work, it's the first time they see my work, so they decided they want to paint their room, change it's colors, style, bla bla bla.. Yes, you guessed, i'm the chosen one for the job.  Anyway, after i finished everything, i took a shower, cooked me a Chinese food, had an instant coffee, watched the news and that's all.  Maria went to Sharem Al-Shekh with Aleef and his family, except for Tony, he is in the US in Virginia with my uncle and his wife.. They went to see Afnan. God, it has been ages since i last saw him. He immigrated 14 years ago and never came back for a visit.. He has his own business and seem to enjoy himself.  I better close now, i want to read the newspapers, see if there is any action, read the career index, maybe watch South Park and go to sleep cause i'm soooo tired. I don't believe i will sleep cause i know that no mater how tired i am i cant sleep before 3 or 4 o'clock AM. 

						
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Since yesterday night till hmmmm.. An hour ago i have been writing my resume, rewriting actually. I have visited over 15 sites discussing resumes and cover letters examples, interviews tip, Hi-Tech jobs and even the body language.  I've prepared me two copies one for the Hi-Tech career and the other is for whatever i might find as an interesting job beside HI-Tech. I think i've sent some 30-40 copies to different Hi-Tech companies, human resource companies and others.  There seems to be some kind of recovery in the Hi-Tech field.. It has been a year or two since i last encountered such a mass of openings. I can be positive and optimistic but leery about this. I don't think i should start building any expectations what so ever.  God... I need a job before i go crazy.  HELP!    One more thing that i noticed while i was searching for jobs was that there is a new technology, two technologies actually, the first is called   J2EE  , not really a new one but a "young" one, and it is very   IN   right now and so is   GUI  . Most of the companies require the knowledge in these two technologies regardless the job definition. Any applier should be able to control at least one of them, experience is not always required though, knowledge is.    J2EE   and   GUI   are going to occupy me for the next couple of weeks. I've found some good sites with good materials, lessons, tutorials and code samples. I just need to install the tool kit in order to practice both theoretical and practical. Hey, what the hell?! I'll give it a try. I've managed JDBC so i think it'll be a piece of cake for me.  Oh, one more thing before i go,  REMEMBER TO CALL ADEEB CONCERNING THE INTERVIEW . 

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well..My dreams sucks! I was disappointed being rejected by Pelephone from getting the job. I had a dream where i got a letter from these suckers telling me that the job was mine..Back to realty.. I finally got the letter from them and i was very excited, but the excitement didn't last long due to the letter content. I guess you know what i meant by that.  I think i prefer living a dream more than reality. 

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok.. I think i'm ready for the interview. I have been studying for 3 weeks now, and it was so hard for me, specially the JDBC! It was the first time i had to work with it, but i think i'm ready for any challenge now.. I master the JDBC more than anything else that i know i'm good with.  I can't keep on studying the same materials.. I've searched for new articles and tutorials but didn't find anything new. I hope the interview will be in the near future. I wish myself good luck. 

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's known that i dream a lot.. and i've mentioned that already in my blog. My dreams are mainly weird and blurred. I have incubus or nightmares but they never seem to scare me! I don't snap out of one sweating...I actually like them more than my sexual ones.  Last nigh i had a dream in where i was with someone (a girl).. Her face were out of focus, so i couldn't tell who she was! I suddenly found myself reading a letter that i got from Pelephone telling me that i got the job.. And i was so happy.. It's a feeling that i can't describe really.. I felt i was flying and very excited.   I went to Pelephone some last week ago for an interview. It went very well, and i had the impression that the job was mine. I haven't yet got a replay from them, they say they will contact me in the very near future, and it always takes them 2 to 3 weeks to do that. 

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ruba called me when she got back, and i was excited to hear from her, too excited i guess... I can't help myself not to! She said: " Nizoo 7abibi, the minute i heard your voice, i found out how much i missed you, how much you mean to me and how much i love you". Isn't this the most romantic thing a bird can say to her boy?   I ask you lord to watch her in every step she make, i ask you to send her an angel every time she is in need. God...Oh god...Writing this post made me realize how much i love her.   I'm feeling great, just great. I'm listing to the Diva, Annie Lennox - "Here Comes The Rain Again" from the best of MTV Unplugged album, great song, it fits perfectly in this situation.    Here comes the rain again  Falling on my head like a memory  Falling on my head like a new emotion  I want to walk in the open wind  I want to talk like lovers do  I want to dive into your ocean  Is it raining with you  So baby talk to me  Like lovers do  Walk with me  Like lovers do  Talk to me  Like lovers do....   &nbsp;  &nbsp;I guess i've found me somebody to love. Ok, that was really outstanding.. I think i better go to sleep now in a good mood.. In sweet emotions.
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I added my picture from the HOT OR NOT web site so you can rate me. Be generous, i'm  HOT  anyway.    

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have been away for a while.. I'll tell you about it later, or maybe i won't. Interesting things happend in the last couple of days.. FUN, SEX, MUSIC  and  ALCOHOL   

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   If there is a day i wish to erase from my memory then it is yesterday. But if there is one i would like to inscribe then it must be today. I never thought i would have such a fun happy day. I was surprised to talk to Mauricio today.. It has been a while since we last met or talked. We talked for some time on the MSN and it was so damn good, He saw me after 3 years on my camera, but he didn't have a camera, so he went out and bought one. We talked about all the things we used to do when we were together in Spain.. Shooting frogs, killing turtles, peeking at the nannies... The best days of my life were probably in Spain and the UK. I went to Spain 3 times maybe and twice to the UK and it was fun with Mauricio.  I was glad that he is doing well, getting married next year. Carol has an 8 days old baby girl. The business is going well, and they are all seems to be ok since my uncle passed away. I had the chance to see his mom Mary, she is an amazing strong woman, his fiance and a client :D.  I was surprised to know that Mauri is managing the business and doing so well with it. I never thought he would make such a success in his life.. He is smart, but he was a big trouble for his mom and dad, lazy, bad in school.. I'm happy for him.  This is touching.. I love them all and i miss them all so much. Hope i'll be able to meet them soon. 

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I think we are done. As much as i liked her as much as i hate her. She is acting like a spoiled baby, no answers, no nothing! She needs a break from us.. I don't. I'm not happy for me or sad, but i'm relieved. This was my first relationship with an Arab girl, and i swear it's my last.   

						
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have a bad feeling about my relationship with Ruba. Ever since we were together the last time, she doesn't seem to be as she always were. Many things have changed.. Her tone is different, she seems to choose different words than before. I'm very pessimistic about this. She chose not to replay to my messages last night, and the reason for this was, and i quote: "I went to sleep early last night and didn't have the time today to replay". I called her couple of minutes ago and she was with her family on their way to Canada Center, and i told her that i want to talk, and that i have some questions to ask. She had a cold attitude, nothing i'm used to in her, she said she'll call me back after she gets home, and she wasn't sure that everything is ok! She has something  BAD  to tell.  I'm not a natural suspicious person, but i'm a natural fortune-teller. If i have a feeling for something then i know it for sure. For my sake and for this relationship sake i hope i'm  WRONG .  I cant concentrate on anything right now! I was studying JAVA and was doing well so far, until that phone call.   What drives me crazy is that i'm 100% sure we are going to break up, but what i don't understand is why? I've done nothing wrong, neither did she! Everything seemed to be perfect.. Reality, reliability, trust, mutual respect,.. What the hell happened? Did i miss something?  Funny thing.. I noticed now that this post i all written in the  Past Simple  syntax.   Ohhh God,... 

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It has been two or three days since i last wrote something here, i guess i wasn't in the mood for writing. Many things happened to me during the past couple of days, some were nice and some were shit.    Shit No. 1   I'm not able to find a job. This is so frustrating... It is known today that if a person, specially an Arab one, no matter how talented he is and no matter what he knows and what he don't, i f he don't have any favoritism or "influence" he'll never be able to integrated in the market. We the Arabs are seen as a second, maybe third priority. We don't serve the Army, our parents didn't, we are not Jewish.. We are sooooo screwed.    Shit No. 2   I forgot all about Ruba. I wish i didn't.. But i can't keep on missing her. It was so damn good and fun with her, she is an amazing person. What happened between the two of us? Only Ruba and god knows, though i doubt it the god knows. I guess the good memories are the only thing that is left of her.  Enough with the shit...  let's GET BUSY BABY  I got back home from a  kick ass  night. Me and the guys went to Tibirias for swimming and BBQ. Nizar brought his speed boat, Anan his Jet ski, and so we had a great time. It was one of the most hilarious nights ever. Since Nizar, Zacky and Nazeeh got married we don't get to meet that much. Naseem is in Eilat most of his time, Mario is getting engaged tomorrow- just to satisfy and to serve his father's desire, Crazy thing ha?- Morad is totally fucked up, so it's me, Maroon, Roni, Esam and Anan know. I miss the old days very much. We used to travel the world a lot together and go out looking for chicks and getting drunk. LOL  I'm building my own site know, i'm thinking of something big and very impressive. It'll give me some good practice for what i have studied in the college and satisfy my arrogant.  One last thing before i close.. I met this person on the net, she is from Nazareth, an Arab of course. She attained amazing me. I mean though being an Arab she is so opened in sex talks and whatever might come out of it. She loves to explore herself in sex, she is never shy to talk about it, and don't give a fuck of what people might say about her. She is a virgin, and she manages very well keeping her reputation and fame clean. She is amazing, just amzazing.  It's 4:00 Am now and i better go to sleep now.  

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I had a dream last night about winning the Osacr as the best actor. I guess many people have a fantasy where they stand on the what you call it? Rostrum in front of the cameras and millions of people.. Getting your Oscar or Grammy or whatever it is.. I would love to be in such a situation. So i've prepared a speech and it goes something like that. By the way, i'd prefer winning the  Best Actor Oscar .   "Oh my god... Thank you all..Thank you very much..Mmmmmm.. I'm very excited.. My hormones are just too way out of control to be dealing with this..I've written a speech some 3 years ago when i was first nominated for this category, and i'm dying to read it so...I want to first thank god and my family. I want to thank Steven Spielberg for believing in me and giving me the opportunity and the honor to be a part of this respected prestigious academy... A special thank to the staff and my agent..By the way, George Bush is a FAG. I also want to dedicate this award to the people raising their voices in favour of peace and international legality.. My experiences of making this film made me very aware of the sadness and the dehumanisation of people at times of war..  Thank you all for this, thank you America, thank you Palestine. I love you."  Stupid but worth trying. 

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Jesus.. why is it that in every time i cook something i have to cut my finger, my thumb. Every time i cook it has to be something BIG that needs lots of work and preparation. I guess i love to work with the knife and cut vegetables, but i'm never careful with it, it is  very sharp . Vegetables salad and Chinese are my favorite, so you can imagine how much cutting i have to do. It's a pity that the final result have to have a taste of blood. 

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     I hope this won't sound discriminating to women. 
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ut an "X" next to the ones that are true about you.  Have you ever... (X) been drunk? (X) tried drugs? (X) kissed a member of the opposite sex? (X) kissed a member of the same sex? (X ) crashed a friend's car? (X) slept in your car? ( ) been to Japan? (X) had a ride in a taxi? (X) been in love? (X) been dumped? (X) shoplifted? ( ) been fired? (X) been in a fist fight? (X) snuck out of your house? ( ) had a crush on someone of the same sex? ( ) dated someone of the same sex? (X) had feelings for someone who didn't have them back? ( ) been arrested? (X) made out with a stranger? ( ) had a major surgery? (X) stolen something from your job/school? ( ) celebrated new years in Times Square? (X) pretended not to see someone you spotted out in public? (X) gone on a blind date? (X) lied to a friend? (X) gone skinny dipping? (X) had a crush on a teacher? ( ) celebrated Mardi Gras in New Orleans? (X) skipped school? (X) been caught fooling around with someone? (X) cheated on your significant other? (X) been to Europe? (X) slept with a co-worker? (X) had a crush on one of your friends? (X) slapped someone? (X) been on a plane? ( ) seen The Rocky Horror Picture Show? (X) been moshing at a concert? ( ) had feelings for someone you knew only online? (X) gone to college? (X) graduated college? ( ) tried killing yourself? 

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I miss high school so much. I cleaning my computer cabinet.. I had to throw out some books and documents that i don't use any more and found my high school Diary the one we used to call  "ZIKHRONOT"  and some photos we took back then. It brought up some very nice and funny memories, my high school days was so fun, funny, cheerful days. I started reading the book and it cracked me up. Most of my class mate girls are now married, except for 3 or 4. Some lives in Nazareth and some went to the USA, Canada or the UK. I miss them all. They all started there essay with the following line: " To the dearest of all Nizoo the cute.. It is 2 am, 3 am... I love you... I'll miss you". Here are some of what i read and liked.  There was Soheir Awwad, a dear friend and a smart one also, who i used to copy my home work from here, specially the French lessons(god, I hate French). :) this is funny, we used to site together, open the French book and since it was hard for me to spell or pronounce the words correctly she used to read the article for me and i would write the words in Arabic in their exact pronunciation. She remind me of Miss Tmam. She called me the pain in the ass kid who had a little bit of manners, very smart and close to be a genius but a lazy one (she got that right) LOL, So sweet but a fool also (no fucking way). She wrote:"  i'll miss you a lot, who will copy the home works from me? Who will steal my pens? Who will trip us in the yard? Who will always say : I know this, I know that, I know?"  Saeed Awad. A weirdo! One of my best friends back then, we know meet occasionally.  He wrote me 2 lines!!   Amal Ghttas. She was smart and dear to me also. I liked these lines: "...By the way, i wish i had an older brother like you, sweet, cute and smart. I'll never find someone like you in the future. Who will call me home and play games on the phone and burp? Who will eat my lunch and steal my chocolates?..." "...This is an opportunity for me to wish you a Queen because you are real King and you deserve one. And live happily with her because she will with you."  Shadya Sroor. She wrote me 4 full pages, front and back!! "Do you remember the pens you used to steal from us???" why did they have to mention this? Sorry, I guess ;). I met Shadya a couple of months ago. She works in a beach in Tibirias with her sister and brother-in-law. I used to work their as a waiter. We shared some memories together. We associated in our last 2 years in high school and became very good friends. She wrote about the morning routine ".. The principal on the microphone... Move it, Yalla move it,.. Not again! Please god no... Make him someone else than Nizar Dirawi! You are late! Again! See you in my office..." She wrote some memories from the school trip to Taba.. It was a  Hell On Earth  for our teachers. LOL. I'll never forget it this one. Dancing in the Lobby, Singing duet with Saeed our song (we were the band that day), swimming together at night. I'll call her today, i miss her.  Shirin Danial and Wafaa Awad wrote me 5 pages, front and back. Me and Shirin used to fight a lot but we were also very close and she wrote a lot about it. She was very Hooooot. Wafaa once told me when we were at Maria's "I hate you", well.. me too. They wrote mainly silly stuff, and i couldn't read them, their hand write is sooo bad!!  Areen Rsheed. Never been close or friends. "... I'll remember you for your funny jokes.... The hilarious plays you wrote with Roni, and brought up in the class..."  Reem Abu Rajab wrote about the S.A.T (psychometric) course. I used to make fun of the trainers. I was much better than them.  One Bitch wanted my picture, naked, so she could remember me!!  Many many wrote in my book, I can't keep on writing here a brief of their essays. There was the unforgettable Mary Mazzawi we know each other ever since i remember myself, Raneen, Rozan and Joumana Nseer, Maria Mazzawi, Raneen Njar and many more. They are all my friends, more like brothers and sisters. I miss them all.   

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Did you know that there are som 7-8 farts types? I accidentally ran into a web page about farts and funny stuff, It is called the  urlLink FART FILE . It is so fucking funny, plus the are sound files for each type.    The Common Fart  The Common Fart is the fart heard most often. It is a very close relative of the "Ripper",but is released with less force. It is usually heard in groups where people aren't yet comfortable with farting amongst each other. Therefore, one person in the group gets up some nerve and releases this common-sounding fart in such a manner that everyone now feels comfortable with group flatulence... Usually there is no smell with the Common Fart.   The Anxious Fart  The Anxious Fart is let in a place where someone does not want the fart to be heard. You may have seen men and women in book stores or grocery stores, or even on the street, letting these farts. They are generally controlled, usually barely audible, and require much skill to master.   The Coughing Fart  The Coughing Fart is one that the farter tries to cover up with a cough. My Dad used to let these farts all the time when he worked at the Bingo Hall. He would stand at the back of the hall and cough, just as a nice "common fart" was let. It can be embarrassing for the farter, and those around the farter, if the timing is off at all, or if the fart is longer than anticipated.   The Wet Fart  The Wet Fart is one that sounds quite juicy. Quite often this fart is cause for alarm, and an indication that a trip to the toilet is imminent.   The Blower  This fart is similar to the ripper, except it has a bit of a hollow, windy sound to it. This is due to farter blowing all the gas out quickly. This fart will almost always get a laugh.   The Tight Bun Fart  This fart is always recognizable. It sounds like the farter's buns were so tight that he/she was in pain while farting.   The Ripper  One of the best farts around is The Ripper. It is loud, rough, and always raises an eyebrow or two.  Characteristics of The Ripper often show up in other farts, but make no mistake - this fart is a single, powerful gas-bubble that comes screaming from the farter's butt.  enjoy!    

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I want to get a tattoo but dunno exactly what. I've searched the net for some pictures and studios, but none of what i found really pleased me except for one tattoo, it is a  urlLink portrait of the legendary Bruce Lee (click me) . I al urlLink so found a poster of him, Bruce Lee High Kick (click me),  and i really liked it. It so powerful and the colors are so simple yet very distinguish. I'm not a big fan of arts and so; but i like what i like. Anyway, i guess i'll have to decide between these two pictures.  

						
</post>


</Blog>