<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sorrow behind the wall of character, Archived as just "part of me." If only people could understand, Out these eyes, sorrow can see.  Drowned sorrow has gills. In silence, it treads felling. Beneath the crashing of the waves, Our humanity sorrow is stealing.  Sorrow - Ha - I laugh at you. All you are is solemn calamity. However, never once did I think, The sorrow I was laughing at, was me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "Why is no one sitting with me?"  "I am sitting with you."  "Yeah, but you're not sitting WITH me."  "Ok, I'm sitting WITH you."  "Why are you the only one sitting with me?"  "Everyone else is outside."  "I have an eleven inch penis...AROUND...think about it."  "I'm sure you do."  &nbsp;  Friendship is fleeting.  Enjoy it while you have the chance.  Even&nbsp;straight&nbsp;roads meanders,  and memories are a fading dance.  &nbsp;  "The fan is spinning."  "Yes it is."  "I want to be IN the fan!"  "Well that would be interesting"  "Do we like me?"  "We all like you."  "I can walk a straight line, on my HANDS."  "I'm sure you can."  &nbsp;  Don't think about it now.  Think about it&nbsp;with your friends.  Now you may be contented,  but we separate and meet different ends.  &nbsp;  "Well this is fun."  "Yes it is."  "Let's do it again sometime, ya?"  "Sure thing."  "But next time I'll sit with YOU."  "Sounds like a plan."  "I am going to puke."  "I know you are."  &nbsp;  Obsticales come and go,  but we clear hurdles in stride.  Forgiveness is all in a days work,  And in the end friendship knows no pride.  &nbsp;  "Ow my head."  "I bet."  "What happened?"  "You played it smooth."  "Did I throw up?"  "Yeah."  "Sorry."  "No need to be."   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       (Musical theme)  ‘Tis the season to be jolly.  Take your money, buy a dolly.  Mark it up on e-bay.&nbsp; Sell it!  Now go buy some drugs and get lit.  (Musical theme ends)  &nbsp;  (Serious note)  Take solace in a song of truth.  Yesteryear gave way to tomorrow.  Where sugarplums once reigned,  Now dances incoherence and sorrow.  &nbsp;  But feeling has no buoyancy  Under waves of tuning out,  For pleasure is nothing,  And stimulation is in drought.  &nbsp;  We follow no paths  Since ebbing tides smooth the trail.  Simplicity and solidity  Leave the taste buds dry and stale.  (Serious note ends)  &nbsp;  (Ponderous thought)  What happened to Yesterday...?  (Keep pondering)      
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It is unclear why our yearning belies our purity, For isn’t every fallen angel heaven sent? With reproach we question our divinity. On greed and power our hearts are bent.  Plunge the depth of your inner springs In search of answers, and there you will find Unknowingly baptized, now to your soul grace clings. A waiting spirit, and to you it is kind.  Religion is only what a book commands? There’s so much more which He filled us with. Our inner soul has so many demands. Blinded, we must be led by blind, is just a myth 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      He's out there you know. Always has and always will be, Wondering how long yet knowing. It's up to you to open and see.  Did you notice you talked to air? You cried sorrows to a useless end, Prayed for something to nothing. And yet he always listened.  You were born perplexed and driven. From the start, built to seek. The thorn of pleasure aching inside. You're so strong, so great.  So weak. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dig deeper inside, you're almost there. Not even close, yet still will I chant. One day you will unearth what you seek, But this tilled soil grows no plant  To reminisce should be a crime; We hang by our last thread. When the lines break and we crumble, Will life's answer be buried under dead?  Don’t worry though, I'll be here. I’ll stand by your side ‘till you kill me. Please use my blood to soften the earth. Where you dig is where my coffin will be.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I’m not sure this feeling inside. Her face, rekindled fire in my soul, Yet thoughts away, to hide them I’ve tried. Apart and incomplete; with her I am whole.  So in toil to figure out Thoughts impure, yet all I know. Why question, when missing i search in doubt? Fine – But two dancers crowd a show.  If is perfect; why is pensive, Yet always my dreams sustain. Question why; dream if.  A chance I’ll give. Lose ninety-nine, for a dollar to gain? 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>