<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			I shouldn't have let my blog get away from me like this. Its just like not wearing retainers. You leave them out one night because you tired, and then it just keeps going on and on until your teeth have moved and oops! you get braces again! (that hasnt happened to me, and this isn't quite on subject)  In other news, so far I have been awake for 33 hours straight. I'm wondering just how long I can keep it up. This wouldn't normally be of much importance, if it were not that I happen to be leaving for a long backpacking trip in New Mexico....tomorrow. I'm going to meet up at my troop's meeting place around 3 pm tomorrow. We hope to leave by 4 for Union Station in LA. From there, its going to be more than 24 hours of train. After going insane for such time, I will arrive at:  Philmont. Yeah, its cool. I went with my troop two years ago, and I think its going to be great going again. We'll be on the trail for 12 days, backpacking as a crew--carrying all of our clothes, food, tents, and general gear for more than 60 miles. I think changing pronouns is bad. So anyways, its going to be much fun, and i wont be back until the 16th. I may try to keep a bit of a journal while I'm at philmont, but don't expect much out of me. Anything I do write down I'll post after I get home.  That'll be enough for now I suppose.  Time to return to the longious awakedness. 
			
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			I havn't posted for awhile, mostly because blogger has been kind of annoying about posting. It seems to be alrightish now though. At least this got posted. So anyways, the past few days I've done more sailing of course, and started work on a computer for my dad's project business thingy, star drug testing. In my sailing class I've moved up to the laser. It's a lot more fun than a sabot. Faster, and a lot more fun to capsize. With a laser, when you capsize you can just jump up onto the side, then down onto the centerboard. That tilts the boat upright, so you just jump in when its about 45 degrees above the water. I've done that a few times by now.     Another fun thing you can do with a laser is hiking way out. Of course that's more than just a fun thing you get to do, but a requirement of keeping your boat upright. Today I discovered the great funnage to be had in dunking your head underwater while leaning way out off of your boat trying to keep it upright. ...Damned run-on sentence.     Ok then, so sailing is much fun. Oh, and I have 6 new shirts. four of them are the same color. I like it. And this way I don't have to worry about having shirts come school. Ugh. School. I don't want to go back.     Enough rambling.  post! 
			
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			Sailing today I decided to come up with a new term. I have no idea if it actually is any new, but I like the sound of it. Today my sailing class piled onto four lasers, one flying junior--a two-sailed, 14 foot sailboat used in collegiate racing--, and two motor boats, and headed out to the beach. There we pulled our boats up onto the shore, and ate pizza. Yum. We spent some time sailing around on the ocean near the beach, and I stood up on the stern of a laser and guided the two kids who were with me in chasing after the fj.    After some of that, everybody came back in and the kids played around in the water and sand. I read a book, The Green Hills of Earth by Robert Heinlein. I've read it before, but its a nice collection of short stories. After a few pages of that it was time to go. I got into the fj again, and we headed back.    While the fj is commonly used in racing, and has two sails--a main and a jib--it is generally beaten by a laser for speed. But that didn't stop us from trying to pass a laser.   The best way to pass a boat is on the windward side, stealing their wind. This is where my new term came from--its sort of like you're putting the other boat in a wind shadow. I went through quite a few of those in my sabot yesterday, and its a pretty annoying thing. Not only do you slow down quite a bit, but the wind that was previously leaning your boat opposite from the way you were leaning but is no longer there.     And so that is how our fj passed up half of the lasers. By rocking our boat to gain speed, and to move our sails windward of the lasers' sails, we got back pretty quick. This is a pretty boring post I know, but oh well. Posting is good.
			
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			Today was the thursday night sailing race that my summer class puts on. I wasn't able to go, because my mom had scheduled to go see the community band play in the park. That was alright though, I was feeling pretty tired when I got home from class anyways. I did however get a taste of the racing today during class when they taught us how the course would work and had us run through a few practice races. I feel like being creative, so here's a diagram showing the course:        Just realized I forgot to draw the wind on that diagram, and I dont want to put a new one on. So yeah--the wind is coming from the top. So you start at the line, and tack upwind. Then, you have to round the windward marker, without touching it, and head for the jive mark. After you jive around that, you head for the leeward marker, and then start tacking upwind again to get back to the starting line. Sometimes you race two laps, with the finish line restricted. That means that if you pass through the starting line when starting your second lap you're disqualified. "oops!" Luckily that wasn't me. But anyways, racing was pretty fun--we raced three times, I ranked 2nd, 1st, and 2nd out of about 12 people in my group--level two. Tomorrow I should be moving up a bit though, so I'm looking forward to that.     That was about it for sailing class today. We ate lunch at the park again, and one of the laser students covered the slide with sun screen and got little kids to ride it down. Pretty much uneventfull other than that.    
			
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			Back by popular demand, its Cigarette Smoking Man, also known as Cancer Man.  A little thing about the image on the top of the right vertical bar--I plan on changing that from time to time, pretty much just whenever I feel like it.  I find the current "pretzels, not bombs" to be pretty funny, but not very asthetically pleasing.  Anyways, here's Cancer Man:   
			
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			 urlLink http://biz.yahoo.com/rb/040712/tech_google_7.html   My favorite search engine--Google.  My email provider--Google.  Perhaps soon to be the owner of my soul--Google?  There's been a lot of speculation about google and its growing mass.  Speculators believe that Google may soon start releasing software for use in searching your own desktop for files.  And about gmail--those who know about this sort of thing have noticed that gmail is very intrusive.  Nobody really deletes emails from their 1 gigabyte of gmail storate, but it is possible, although apparently Google will always have your emails, even if you see them as deleted.  And then of course the google ads, specially tuned to advertise specifically to you.  I really don't know if it's something to worry about or not.  On one hand, google has done quite a bit for us, and is a wonderfully useful tool.  On the other hand, any company that is growing so quickly and expanding into so many different regions is to be questioned.    My crazy hairbrained theory about Google that I made up the other day is as follows: Google appeals to the computer-oriented folk.  These people are Google's main following, and feel that the infallible Google could never harm them.  Then, Google slowly expands into everything--every technology, every field, every commercial product.  Soon we have toasters that consult google as to how you should have your toast prepared, and vacuum cleaners that occasionally report in on your cleaning habits in order to better suggest a good brand for a replacement vacuum bag.  And now Google owns the world, when their start was nothing but a search engine.    I don't believe it, which is good.  If I did I'd probably go insane.
			
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			Yesterday I started a summer sailing 'camp.'  Its a two-week program that runs every weekday from nine am to four pm.  My only previous sailing experience was a little bit in scouts, so I chose to enter at the beginner level.  Yesterday they taught us how to rig up our boats, and some of the basic terms and such.  Did you know that the holes the rudder attach to are called gudgeons?    Today we got to start sailing, which was fun.  The advanced-beginners and intermediate sailors left off on some trip through the harbor or something, while my beginner class sat around and discussed tacking.  I learned that tacking specifically refers to a U-turn during which the bow of your boat passes through the eye of the wind.  The opposite would be turning with your stern to the eye--that's called a jive.    So we got out to the water, and rigged up our boats.  They launched a chase boat with an outboard engine to cruise around and help out if any of us happened to capsize (I'm happy to say I didn't).  So after the chase boat was out, half of us were clear to launch our boats and try tacking a figure-eight around a couple of bouys.  Pretty soon I mastered that, as well as avoiding some of my smaller classmates.  I did have a near-spill when I had to swerve to avoid a kid, right when the wind started gusting.  I took on a few gallons of water, but managed to keep from capsizing (yay for bailers!).  So I've talked with the head instructor, and we've decided that tomorrow I'll go with the more advanced group, leaving behind my beginner class.  And if I do well enough I'll be moved up to the bigger boats, the Lasers, by the end of the week.  I must say it is quite a pain tacking when you're kneeling in a floating fiber glass bathtub.  More to come about the sailing class tomorrow.  Oh, and about my modem--my dad went and got a new modem from my ISP today.  Its the same model, but hopefully it'll work for awhile.
			
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			Ok.  I was going to post about my sailing class.  I know, I should.  But there is a much more pressing issue at hand at the moment.  My modem.  I want to kill it.  My connection rarely lasts longer than 10 minutes, most of the time closer to 3, sometimes as low as 10 seconds between modem restarts (meaning i have to get up, walk around my desk, and flip the power switch off and on).  This is simply ridiculous.  I looked up my modem online, and found a useful review explaining that it cannot be within three feet of any electronic device.  My modem was sitting right next to my desktop tower.  Ok, I can fix that I thought.  Nope.  The modem from hell noticed I was shopping for modems online.  "Mozilla firefox could not load the page."   Ok then.  So the search for a usable modem continues.  Although--I'm afraid to say it at the moment, but it would appear that my modem likes its new spot away from the computer...sailing post to come tomorrow. 
			
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			Much has happened to my blog in the day...or so that its been in existance.  I'm now using a subdomain from my friend's website  urlLink normlife.com .  So if you're reading this on my blogspot URL, then check out  urlLink http://shmeew.normlife.com/ .  Ok, its late.  Merp.
			
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			Yes, three posts in my first day, oh-so-many.  But the first two don't count.    Because I said so.   Exactly.   I created this blog so I could have a safe place to write my thoughts.  I hope that by recording my thoughts, I might be able to better organize said thoughts.  Also, I hope to keep a bit of a journal of what's happening, so that I can possibly look back and see 1) what I did, and 2) just how incredibly stupid I sounded.  Tomorrow I'm going to my first day in a sailing class down at the harbor.  I had to get a whole bunch of stuff for the class, Including a life jacket, sunglasses with a strap thingy, board shorts (there's going to be a swimming test I believe), and some other junk I can't remember.  I'm actually sort of looking forward to any swimming test they throw at me, I havn't been swimming since my High Adventure crew's workup hike on the Fish Bowls trail.  And swimming in the Fish Bowls doesn't really count as swimming--more like jumping into a 10 foot pit of ice water.  But that was fun, and I've rambled from my chosen subject.  Ok then.  More to come about my first day in class tomorrow afternoon.  ...Not bad for a real first post i suppose...
			
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			 I've created a couple of pages just now, the first of which is my  urlLink start page.   From there is a link to my personal  urlLink index  for  urlLink newegg.com   I'll start using my start page as my homepage for now, and will probably keep adding to it as needed.
			
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

			 
			After about three posts on my  urlLink livejournal  blog, I've moved here, to blogger.com at the advice of a friend.  I had originally planned to use my livejournal blog as something to keep track of my  urlLink gunbound  usages, but I think I'm just going to keep this a "regular" blog.  
			
</post>


</Blog>