<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The subjects: ~~~~~~~~~~~~ The subjects are good and going on well. I am quite happy with the courses taught at IIMK. All the profs are of high quality and make an impact in the class. Here in tests, there are no questions on theory. Only problems. At most derivations maybe asked. Focus is on applying the theory to problems. Another common thing here is case studies - a case writeup is given and one has to give a solution for it - this can get pretty boring. The subjects for the 2.5 month first term are introductory - the fundamentals for the remainder of the course. The first year has 3 terms and all subjects are compulsory. The subjects are quantitative methods (I like this), microeconomics (I like this, it has a lot of problems, but the prof screws everybody with tough problems in the test:(( ), financial accounting (this one is good too), organizational behavior (this is taught at a practical level and we had MBTI personality tests), marketing (taught by tapan panda and he is one of the best profs), communication, IT (seems boring after studying computer science)  Grading system: ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Grading system is CGPA. For each subject there are various grades (A+ is 4.33 , A is 4 and F is 0....). C+ is a pass (C+ is 2). The grading is done throughout the year. Every assignment given in class has a weightage. Class participation, projects, surprise quiz all have a weightage. The midterm and end term exams account for only 50% of the total marks. So one has to perform throughout the year.  Specializations in second year: ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ In the second year, one specializes. One can specialize in more than one stream. tHe streams are systems & IT, finance, marketing, HR and operations. To major in a field, one needs a minimum of 15 credits (5 subjects) and to minor one needs 9 credits (3 subjects) in second year. Most people major in finance and marketing, However I do not seem to be very inclined to marketing. I am likely to go for finance, operations and IT (yes, I plan to major in 3) - fin is interesting, Operations has supply chain, ERP, CRM in it and as a consultant in these areas one makes a lot of money (there was a talk by a person from accenture who is a partner/consultant there. He is a 1999 IIMA grad who started at PWC and gets a commission on all the multi million dollar projects he leads)  Life at IIMK: ~~~~~~~~~~~~ The environment is cool and good. The students are also very friendly.  The food is ok. Things are going on smooth. Have a quantitative methods test tomorrow and am studying for it. There are a few consulting projects with Dr Saji and there is a call for volunteers. I may take up one project - not sure though....with the mid term looming ....  Some funny things at K: The students are very good at bargaining. There were some 80+ people to take a loan. Educational loans given by banks have an interest rate of 11.5% generally. These people showed their bargaining skills and negotiated with SBI, SBT, PNB, Indian bank and finally Indian Bank is giving a loan at 8.5% - very good bargaining skills.... I have the cash and do not need to take a loan. But they say there is a lot of tax saving if one takes an educational loan and I am thinking about it...  Student Profile: ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ 			The student profile is very diverse. Most are engineers and have some IT experience. The experience could be 0 years to 5 years. Most have 2+ years experience. There are a lot of students from bangalore and I get to speak a lot in kannada - that is something I enjoy a lot......         There are atleast 6-7 students who are already married. Must be quite tough to study after marriage - not sure :)  Likes and Dislikes: ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ I seem to like subjects with numbers and problems with them. Some subjects like marketing management are a bit on the boring side..... The greatest thing that I miss is appa, amma, thangi and bangalore.   Life goes on....Am enjoying blogging. When I turn 50 I can look back and read all this - that would be fun indeed............ 
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am in Indian Institute of Management, Kozhikode (www.iimk.ac.in) campus since last week. IIMK campus is beautiful on a hilltop. The view you get is very good. There is a tower in the campus and from the tower u get a hillside view that is amazing......It is a treat to the eyes. The breath of fresh air gives a feeling of ambience.  The campus is a good 15-20km away from calicut city (after having been brought up in bangalore, calicut can come close to a town...!!!). The canteen is also good - food is decent. Hostelwise the rooms are single occupancy furnished with a table/chair/wardrobes/cot/bed/fan/ lights .... Pretty well furnished. Each hostel room has a balcony from where you can enjoy the scenery even more.  With a network interface card, I can get internet access 24 hours. There is a computer center that is open 24 hours. The library is also amazing ....open 24 hours and has some 25000+ books, subscribes to all leading journals of all parts of world and has a digital library also with several e-books. The setting is perfect for a rewarding period of study.   THe profs are good - head of marketing is prof nargundkar - who is author of marketing research text book - it is text book in all iims. Our finance head prof Uday damodaran writes for leading business magazines. Our operations head saji gopinath is visiting faculty in asian institute of management, thailand. All profs are either Phds or fellows in management from some iim -a or c or b. Some have taught at abc or in B schools abroad.   We also get a lot of visting faculty.eg Equity research is done by UTI capital markets, project management by Wipro - all electives in second year. Electives are given based on CGPA and so CGPA is important. Average work ex of my batch is >21 months which is good.....  Every year has 3 terms, term 1, term 2 and term 3. Between terms there is a 10 day break. For the  term 1 my subjects are: financial accounting, microeconomics and strategy, organizational behavior, quantitative methods for business, Information technology for business, marketing management, social transformation in india and managerial communication. From seniors, I learnt we are lucky to have some real good profs. Prof Tapan K Panda for marketing (he is one of the best profs in marketing in india after nargundkar who also teaches here), gopal chowdury for quantitative methods, Dr Barokha (formerly univ of southern calif) for accounting, dr cyriac (formerly XLRI) for organizational behavior and dr sumit sarkar for microeconomics.   First year subjects are compulsory. Electives are in second year allowing one to specialize in one/more of finance/accounting/systems/IT/operations. That is the catch -  i can take electives across streams - not necessary to major in a particular stream....  I find a diff b/w university and IIM evaluation systems. In universities the CGPA is dependent on the final exam only. Here it depends on the tests/assignments/quizzes/mid-term/final exams. eg: each assignment has a weightage of 5-10% and the final exam weightage could be 30% -varies depending on profs.  Professionally,  I feel the stage is set for a rewarding period of academics. Personally, it is the first time, I am staying in a hostel and away from home. I miss my parents and home a lot - making up by calling home once or twice in a day :))  Of course I miss working in the software industry and the fat paycheck I used to get at the end of every month....  IIMK is like a resort infrastructure wise. You will never get bored at IIMK. The place is a 100 acre campus with the best scenery. It has ambience about it and you are in a relaxed frame of mind all the time. Some good beaches are nearby. I plan to visit them......... There is also a good gym. I need to focus on acads - mid term exams of term 1 in aug mid and final exams sep mid :o. My future is in my hands:))  Life moves on!!! Will post more new blogs
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Myself - in my cube at motorola&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      About me ~~~~~~~~ I, Kiran R was born in Puttur, Dakshina Karnataka, the best place to live in india (in my opinion). I was brought up, studied and worked in Bangalore, the garden city of india. I did my schooling from Cluny Convent, Jalahalli and high schooling from Vidhyavardhaka Sangha High School, Bangalore. I did my engineering from M S Ramaiah Institute of technology, Bangalore.  Post BE: Hunting a job ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ After my BE in computer science engineering, I wanted to work in a software products environment for a cutting edge technology company.   I was a recruit of IBM in campus in April, 2001, but the offer was withdrawn due to slowdown. It was June, 2002 when I graduated and offers were hard to come by. I got another offer from Future Techno Design on campus but they did not tell about a 3 year bond that I was required to sign when they recruited me, and so when I came to know of it a fortnight before joining I decided not to join FTD.  Merindus ~~~~~~~~~ I got an offer from MerIndus consulting. It was a startup started by Mr Babu Subramanian, a MTech from Indian Institute of Science. He is managing director of Merindus. It had an IIM Calcutta alumnus Mr Ravi Ande who was looking after the technical side of the operations of merindus. I was the 6th employee of merindus and wow! what a team we had - Vikram Rai, BITS Pilani and Tuhin - IIT Chennai and Deivani - an IT professional with 3 year exp and me Kiran - MSRIT Bangalore. I was working on a product called kronos scheduler entirely written in java. It was great being part of a startup right since its inception. I was there from the first official working day of merindus. We did everything - installing OS on computer, installing software, troubleshooting, getting kronos up and running......Wow...what an experience. Babu was a great motivator and we had many sessions on how to make merindus successful. I was enjoying my stay at Merindus working on a latest product (that had won the Java developer journal award) and with the brightest minds (in our team) and headed by Babu - a very experienced and able person and Ravi - our tech lead....  During my stay in merindus, I got an offer from infosys. I was not sure whether I must join - but the infosys "brand" was too much. Infosys was offering the same pay as merindus. Friends, relatives and everybody suggested I jump to infosys - my mind said stay in merindus......"When things seem to be glittering around, it is difficult to close your eyes" - It was indeed - I jumped to infosys........  Infosys ~~~~~~~~~ I was to regret joining infosys later - I learnt practically - "all that glitters is not gold". I was supposed to have some "training" - it was boring for a computer science grad......I was initially put in a team called WenaTest - that did black box testing - I did not like the idea of a testing professional career. I requested a change and I must say infy was kind enough to employee interests and changed me to cisco project. Our customer was cisco and the project was static analysis. THe project involved running a set of static analysis over cisco operating system code (IOS - the heart of cisco) and finding/fixing errors/warnings that can cause problems at run time. Typical examples are null pointer deferencing, comparison between signed and unsigned, array out of bounds, double free, memory corruption, unmatched set/reset of interrupts and so on. We used tools like prefix, gcchecks, flexelint, purify, ...... all run over the cisco ios code. All warnings reported have an error code corresponding to the tool. We from prior experience know that for this error code say x, this tool say A is the best. All tools are run over the IOS code over some branch. If the same line number has warnings reported by two different tools, then the one which is more likely (from past historical data) is taken. This was about the work... I did a major contribution during my stay - There was a new tool called KlocWorks in the market. I brought out a proposal to my project manager to evaluate this tool and see if it can fit into our existing toolset. If the tool was useful we could include it and if otherwise we could recommend changes to the tool to KlocWorks so that it can be added later. I would run the KlocWorks tool over several parts of the Cisco operating system code and verify the warnings reported by KlocWorks for correctness and then compare the correct warnings with the warnings reported by our existing toolset. I drafted a report on usefulness of KlocWorks and how it can be made more useful with our recommended changes. The KlocWorks team implemented the changes and I am glad to say that we had one more tool that would help us in making the code more robust. I received appreciation mails from managers at Cisco, our client. It was a very satisfying experience.  Leaving infosys ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ I wanted to work in a software products environment doing coding and design. I was not at all happy with the "unchallenging!!!" work of infosys. So i made a shift to Motorola....Motorola turned out be a technically satisfying time as I write now ::::  Motorola - techie world ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ At motorola, there was a mandatory induction training. It covered the policies of the company (well articulated by the HR Manager Jaleel), focus of the company on quality, code reviews and CMM ( I must say motorola is one of the few companies in the world that actually follows CMM level 5, and the code reviews in motorola are of the highest quality), software design, testing .... I enjoyed the induction ... there was some bright minds who had joined with me and it was great to know therem.... I was looking forward to challenges - this is May 2003.....  I was put into SSPD (system software and product division) in the MMS team (multimedia messaging service). In this point in time, it is believed that future phones would sell because of MMS - the software component and I was thrilled and excited about joining this team. I was given the protocol module of MMS called the user agent (UA) and I was to take care of it in TRIPLETS - a product line of motorola.  I got what I wanted when I joined - cutting edge work and that too software development. I developed a number of features for the motorola MMS phones: 1) read receipt feature: Sending out MMS messages requesting read receipts and handling read receipts from the network 2) progress bar: a progress bar to be shown while sending a MMS message 3) pending notifications on power down: when a phone has a message that has been sent to it waiting on the server, the server sends a notification. We could typically have some 5-6 notifications waiting in our queue, when we are processing a notification. These were getting lost when we power down the phone. So this feature was to save the pending notifications to a file and on power up process them. 4) Linger timer 5) the engine user agent: We wanted to sell MMS on any platform. Our code was tied to the synergy platform. This project was to write an adaptation layer and make our MMS code platform independent. I wrote the adaptation for the user agent. Also our code was made API driven from event driven - atleast the engine and i re-architected the module for the same. 6) Changes in encoder - decoder module to conform the 1.2 spec. Support for several new fields in the PDUs.  I from around November took care of MMS Protocol across ENGINE - another product line of motorola. I also took care of the entire encoding /decoding module of MMS protocol - encode PDUs and send out to server and decode the PDUs from the server.  Developing and testing features that actually go on the phone is a great person. It was intellectually and technically and personally a very satisfying experience when the features I tested on my simulator and then on the phone were released......Today a V600 phone - the latest from stable of motorola inc - has my features and it is used by the millions who buy the phones.....  Wow!!!  Another major work in motorola in software maintenance. Bugs are reported from testers /users and CRs are logged. A CR is a change request - it has a certain severity level. If it is my module, I check if it is a CR (many times understanding issue by the submitter), analyze and fix the CR. Test it on simulator/phone and release it.  Another work is log analysis. Based on a PDU log, I have to identify the problem. I was an "accepted expert" in this - all logs lead to me - KIRAN ha ha:))  I was now handling the MMS protocol for all phones of motorola across releases and this was appreciated by Motorola. I got two hikes and a promotion in one year.  Decision to do MBA ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ Though I was technically happy in motorola, I felt that I was not fulfilling my ambition - which was to be a top guy in my organization, to be very rich and a successful businessman. The growth path in motorola would mean that I would need 8-10 years to be a project manager and I would be an operations/business development manager after 12 years. This is what I wanted to do - business development and I wanted to get there fast. I felt a MBA would give me a headstart in achieving my goals. I got a percentile of 98.91 in CAT (not high by CAT standards) - got 3 interview/GD calls (these are areas where I have always been "strong" with prizes in fests in GD/debate/extempore) from IIM Bangalore, Indore and Kozhikode. All GD/interviews went very well and I was expecting final calls from all IIMs. However I got calls from Indore and Kozhikode IIMs. As Kozhikode is nearer to BAngalore, and also since the faculty there seemed to be better and I had heard about the beauty of God's own country, I decided to join IIM Kozhikode.  My strong technical experience (product software development) and technical knowledge (98.87 in GATE ) will blend with my management learning (MBA from IIM!!!) and lay the foundation to be a leader in the technology intensive business world...so I hope  So, now my MBA journey begins in IIM kozhikode....  
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My recent photo @ IIMK&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>


</Blog>