<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Maybe I get a little "Woody Allen" or "Dennis Miller" with my sense of humor.&nbsp; The post after this one (which was, chronologically, before this one) has a sort of cerebral joke in it.&nbsp; If you haven't read the post yet, please read the one after this first.&nbsp; That way, if you don't catch my "goober humor", you can come back, read this post for an explanation, and then go back and re-read the next (previous) post with the new insight.&nbsp; That way, it's like reading two posts for the price of one - like looking at the world from a new point of view.  So go read "Party Of One" if you haven't already.&nbsp; Then come back here...  ... for the explanation.&nbsp; My joke is that I've been repressing my loneliness, and the horoscope brought it out.&nbsp; See?&nbsp; We had foreshadowing - "...insight into what is in the brain, but repressed", a setup, the punchline - "does that seem rude to anyone else?", I emotionally string you all along, and finally a big one-two punch at the end - "party of one, please!".&nbsp; This kind of stuff just cracks my action RIGHT up.&nbsp; I am my own entertainment.&nbsp; My own... lonely... entertainment.  I joke a lot about repressing my emotions, and then I'll just let them out in a big mess, then finally act like it's really funny.&nbsp; But, sometimes, I don't feel funny.&nbsp; I get afraid that people won't catch my humor, and then they'll think less of me.&nbsp; When I was a child, I drew a picture for my grandmother of stick figures running around a room, and there was a door that had a sign, which read "Egg-Zit".&nbsp; My mom said "Jay, it's spelled E-X-I-T", and I said "I know, but my way is funny".&nbsp; My mom made me change it so my grandma wouldn't think I'm dumb.&nbsp; To this day, I see an Exit sign, and think "damn you, world... damn you!&nbsp; My way's funnier!"&nbsp; But I remain silent. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I read my horoscope.&nbsp; Not that I believe in astrology or anything.&nbsp; Rather, I believe that horoscopes can be vague enough to trigger a thought in one's head based on their own interpretation, giving insight into what is in the brain, but repressed.&nbsp; Kinda like that Horshack Test.   So I actually read one that is customized for my very birthday, on My Yahoo, and this is what it said to me today.&nbsp; "...be ready for a party -- a party of one, that is."   Does that seem rude to anyone else?&nbsp; I mean, okay, yeah, I'm divorced.&nbsp; And yeah, I broke up with S***n.&nbsp; And all my friends are going to a party next Saturday while I have to go take care of a show that no one's going to go to anyway.&nbsp; And I'm going to be all alone on my birthday.&nbsp; But really, should my freakin' horoscope be taking a poke at me like that?&nbsp; I now think of my horoscope as a living being, saying "Jay, Jay, here's you, here's you... 'party of one, please!'"&nbsp; Freakin' jerk.   Oh, and yeah, I realize that it's a "Rorschach Test", not a "Horshack Test".   
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got one of those emails from some dude whose dad was President of Lambada, but he died with like 22 million dollars hidden in a mule, and now they need me to launder the money.&nbsp; The funniest thing was that he felt convinced by "my profile" that he could trust me.&nbsp; The only profile he could possibly be talking about is:   urlLink http://profiles.yahoo.com/jcvonrosen   Obviously, a man who can quote Beck and lists "actin' the fool" as a hobby  must  be trustworthy enough to handle 22 million smackers.  Okay, I know the rule - never reply to spam.&nbsp; But I couldn't resist...     DUDE!&nbsp; SWEET!&nbsp; My bank account number is 8675309!   Oh, man, I've heard of these kinds of things happening before, but I never thought it could happen to me!    
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a drink with MSLDB (My Sweet Little Dutch Boo) last night, and we get to talking about relationships and how I'm still missing S***n, and what type of person I am, and who I attract, and how I continually attract girls who don't really want me, but they've been conditioned by society and Oprah to think that they do.&nbsp; So MSLDB tells me what she finds attractive about me... MSLDB: "You're sweet, and nice... and you're approachable.&nbsp; You're not intimidating" Juan:&nbsp; "Aw, crap, Boo, you know how tired I am of hearing that?" MSLDB: "You can't change who you are, Jay"  So then we started talking about how I've avoided "The L Word" with women for well over a year now (although I wasn't 100% successful in avoiding that with S***n).&nbsp; I went into how a young lady brought up that word last December, and how, at the time, I knew less about this girl than I know about MSLDB.&nbsp; Women!&nbsp; They don't know me.&nbsp; How could they start feeling like that?So here's My Sweet Little Dutch Boo, in her Sweet Little Dutch Way...  "Jay... I know we've only known each other for about a month... but, well... I love you"  Actually, it went more like this...  MSLDB: "HAHAHAHA!&nbsp; You know what would be too funny?&nbsp; If I got all serious right now [giggle] and go 'Jay, I love you!'" Juan:&nbsp; "Aw, crap!&nbsp; This SAME THING happened to me last night!"  So now that's our little joke. MSLDB: "Jay, I love you" Juan:&nbsp; "Aw, crap!" 
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here's a fun little game you can play at home to pass the time.&nbsp; This will give you some great insight into how my goofy little mind works.  This game is based on the pesky habit some people have, in which they add "in bed" to every fortune received in a fortune cookie at a Chinese restaurant.&nbsp; Examples... Fortune: "The superior man is modest in his speech, but exceeds in his actions"...  IN BED!  Fortune: "If you enjoy what you do, you'll never work another day in your life"...  IN BED!  Fortune: "You will be blessed with great riches"...  IN BED!   My variation on this game is to add the phrase "In my pants!" to the end of every movie title.&nbsp; Some classic examples... Anaconda... IN MY PANTS! 21 Grams... IN MY PANTS! Mission Impossible... IN MY PANTS! Tales From The Crypt... IN MY PANTS! I, Robot... IN MY PANTS! Intolerable Cruelty... IN MY PANTS!  You get the picture.&nbsp; Just think of the possibilities.&nbsp; You're ready to go see a movie with your parents, and you ask "What would you guys like to see?" "Oh!&nbsp; How about Scooby Doo 2: Monsters Unleashed?" ... 
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My friend Inigo (name changed to protect the innocent) had to reel me back in like a fish today.  I was off swimming into the vast open ocean of emotional brine in which so many of us bathe merrily on a daily basis.  Yes, that same immeasurable ocean in which some revel in the mad currents that keep us out of control of our own lives.  The same ocean of emptiness that tastes like the sweet tears of despair.  I'm not talking like this to be artistic - I'm being quite facetious.  And yet, I was swimming out.  I was about to submerge, and I knew I was losing control of my emotions.  So I IM'ed Inigo.  And it went something like this...  Juan de la Rosa: Dude Inigo Montoya:   Sup Juan de la Rosa: I need you to talk me down Inigo Montoya:   Oh no, what happened Juan de la Rosa: I'm thinking of contacting S***n Inigo Montoya:   Nah, dude, you gotta let her come to you when she knows what she wants.  That's the only way you both can be happy. Juan de la Rosa: You're right Inigo Montoya:   I know Juan de la Rosa: Thanks - I feel better Inigo Montoya:   You got it, baby  I've paraphrased most of that conversation, and I threw the "you got it, baby" in there, even though Inigo would never say anything like that.  I just thought it would be funny.  So I put "Hey Hey What Can I Do" in WinAmp and set it on repeat.  That's been going for about 4 hours now.  It's great being a guy.  All I need is some Zep, the All Star game, a beer, and a place where I can pee outside, and I am completely content.  And my remote control.  And this chair.  And that's ALL I need.  Oh, and this slinky.
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm really tired today.  Tired, sad, lonely and depressed.  I feel like... dang, I don't know.  I think I'm confused to top it all off.  I'm just a medley of bum-ya-out kinda stuff today.  I didn't get a lot of sleep last night.  Sleep is important.  Whenever I feel depressed, I take a little time, eat a healthy meal, stay away from the booze, do something peaceful and relaxing, and get a good night's sleep.  Yup.  "Nothing that a good night's sleep won't cure" is what my future grandchildren will hear me say.  People nowadays don't take enough responsibility for their emotions.  We expect to feel good all the time, and when we don't, we try to figure out why we're not feeling good.  People try to find what there is to blame for their negative emotions and remove it from their lives.  However, I think that this is futile.  I think that the natural state of a human being is wanting.  Sometimes all we need is a good night's sleep.  We can deal with the natural strains of life better then.
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I haven't written anything for a while.  You want to know why?  No you don't.  Okay, I'll tell you.  Super-Smart Mega-Genius Jehosaphat F. Peabody broke up with the most perfect girl in the universe a few weeks back.  Yeah, that's right.  I found my third ex-wife, and apparantly decided to save some time and just leave her now.  Save myself a few bucks, y'know?  Aside from that, things have been absolutely ducky.  Yup, aside from a bleeding heart stabbed repeatedly with the rusty blades of my own self torment, things have been allllll right.  I'll just make myself a great big helping of F***!  But back to the subject.  I'm like that thing in every children's story - the misfit.  I'm a funny guy.  That's what I do - it's my life.  And I'm feeling like the one funny guy in the world who is the totally unfunniest guy around.  Like the elf that wanted to be a dentist.  Or the little train that couldn't pull a big load.  Heh.  "Load".
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday had some real positive vibes in it.  I got the headliner for the 7/3 show booked; I had lunch with Faith, who is always fun to talk to; I took my first Economics test and I think I did well; I had a hearty dinner; then I watched 10 innings of a decent ball game.  So what's missing?  Probably sex and booze.  I didn't have any sex or booze yesterday.  There was something inside of me that said "Jay, things are going well... time for some sex and booze".  Am I a bad person?  Nah.  I had my cake, now I want the icing.  I downloaded the new Yahoo Messenger last night, and I feel violated.  It put icons all over the place.  It tried to make their web mail my default mail client.  Let me repeat that... it tried to make their WEB MAIL my default mail client.  Furthermore, I now have the most irritating smiley known to man in my system tray.  It did some very cruel things to me, and now all it can do is smile at me.  I feel like I've been molested by a mime.
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bookin' shows, drinkin' beers, kickin' butts, takin' names.  You!  Name!  [smack!]
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've figured it out.  I like being messed up.  I love dysfunctional relationships and pain and loss.  I must love it.  I keep doing it over and over. 
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was called "witty" today by some girl I never met.  That is a sure fire way to get a guy, ladies, or at least a sucker like me.  Honestly, I logically know that girls are taught this somewhere.  I'm sure Cosmo has an article that says "call him 'witty'", but it works.  Part of me is thinking "I've got to meet this girl".  Why?  I don't know.  Cosmo has it all figured out.  I sure don't.
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      There's a multitude of reasons why I haven't found happiness in a relationship, despite trying heartily for over half of my life.  Oh, and I'm not dissuaded, bitches, so don't think I'm throwing in the towel and being bitter, despite trying heartily for over half of my life.  Back to my point, though... today, I will reflect on reason #1275 that Jay has not found a blissful relationship (reason #1274 is that I use the term "bitches").  I want attributes that don't stereotypically match in a single woman.  I want a Compassionate Conservative.  A girl who can yell "Free Mumia!" and bakes good cookies.  A girl with a good job who likes to party hard.  A girl who can feel as at home at Bomacs as at Lochmoor.  It doesn't fit the mold.  However, I think I can/should get a Compassionate Conservative as a woman.  I am a Compassionate Conservative.  Everyone's going to say right now "yeah, Jay, everyone wants that, join the club", but I don't think you idiots are listening to me.  I know which fork to use.  I snuck a shot of Popov with a homeless dude the other day.  Everyone says "oh, yeah, I'm like that, too".  Liars.  I want a pretty, stuck-up girl who says things that freak people out.  I want a party girl that says "can you take a shower, because I don't want you touching me when you smell all icky".  Anyone know any Compassionate Conservative women who like goofy bass players who say things like "where my bitches at?"
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay - this makes some sense.  So here we go, kids.  I'm going to start posting some of my past ramblings in this crazy new world of "blog".  I've dated the titles, so you can see when I wrote them, even though they will all be posted in rapid succession right now...  Ooga chagga - ooga chagga...
      
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Okay, I'm not too smart.  This is my first day blogging.  I've written a few things over the past couple weeks, but I haven't posted them anywhere.  Now I need to figure this thing out so I can post them. Bear with me, please.
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's a cop-out.  Every comedian with children does the whole bit about the crazy things children do.  However, I'm not a comedian - I'm a funny guy.  So it's cool.  Saturday morning.  It's time to think about groceries, cleaning, laundry, etc.  So I flip the switch on the vacuum, and it sounds really funny.  I put my hand by the... do they call it the exhaust?  Whatever it's called, it's where the air blows out, and there was barely any air blowing out.  I won't go through all my troubleshooting, but there was a clog.  So what was clogging it?  Seashells.  I don't know what else to say.  I think that this should be enough to cause a mental train wreck.  Seashells.  Say it with me.  Seashells.  Someone thought it would be wise to vacuum up seashells.  I'm a slow person mentally.  Not that I'm dumb, but it takes me a long time to fathom things completely.  I actually took a brain chemistry evaluation, and it said something about my slow neuro-transmission.  Hell, I already knew that, and I'm the one who's slow.  So I stood there, picturing the scene, trying to make sense of what would possess any human to vacuum up seashells.  It actually did whet my imagination.  Think of the satisfying sound of seashells clattering up a vacuum hose.  So the conversation followed... "Child" "(yawn) What?" "Why did you vacuum up seashells" "I didn't"  Heh - sweet.  This is the essence of having children.  Kids rock.
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just figured out THE ENTIRE UNIVERSE!  I know the secret of living, the essence of happiness, etc, etc.  Here it is...  Mankind is dysfunctional because we expect to figure it out.  Think about that.  The source of emotional pain is the fact that we can't resolve something.  But this is based on one presupposition - we are able to resolve it - which I contend is untrue.  This is why people say ridiculous things like "time heals all wounds".  Time didn't heal it - time just dimmed the memory, so you forgot how much it hurt.  Now follow with me for a moment... why can't we just accept our emotional pain without trying to figure out how to avoid it or resolve it or change it or anything?  Would we be as afraid of the pain anymore?  I'm gonna try it out.  So here's my new catch phrase - "Damn, that sucked... oh well".  My old catch phrase was "Is your mom hot?"  I say that to the 20-somethings who walk around acting all glamorous.  I wanna get with their moms.
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yup, I have received another request to transfer millions of dollars out of Africa.  I don't even have the spirit to make any cocky remarks.  Oh dang.  I just deleted it, and I should have replied with "no thanks - I'm already illegally transferring $31 million for two other people - try back next week".  I'm in a faded at 4am mood right now.  Letting the world in on my terminology, "Faded At 4am" is a sample file that comes with FruityLoops 3.  I think the phrase is very descriptive of a brand of techno.  I'm hardcore into drum'n'bass techno, which brings me to today's ramblings...  There is a techno scene, with some artists that I would seriously consider to be some of the world's greatest musicians.  I have to rave about my absolute favorite underrated techno artists, negative pH.  Grand.  Right after I discovered them, they split up temporarily, then they got back together, and now they've got a CD that's about to be released.  They are the most consistently great drum'n'bass techno that I've ever heard.  Okay, done with that.  I like hot pretzels.  It has to be just the right amount of salt, though.  But there's something else.  I'm letting you all into my deep, dark, personal world here.  If you melt Velveeta cheese, then dip the hot pretzel in there... it reaches me in a way that I'm not used to.  Finish it with a Samuel Adams, and I'm on a freakin' ASTRAL VOYAGE!  Who's ADD?  Wanna fly kites?  Oh look!  A bird!  I'm an airplane - reeeaaaowrrrrr! 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am weak.  I have been getting weaker over the past couple days.  Sinking into an illness.  It's painful, I'm dizzy, it's very hard to eat, and even harder to carry on with anything resembling my daily life.  And now... it has been harder than ever to accept that I walked away from her.  I do, though.  I accept it.  It's what needs to happen.  But I finally noticed some words today that I had heard before...  And when we meet Which I'm sure we will All that was then Will be there still I'll let it pass And hold my tongue And you will think That I've moved on  If it were easy to do the right thing, everyone would be doing it.
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I must be pretty lucky.  I just got another email from someone in Africa who wants to give me millions of dollars.  This one's pretty good, though.  I received it from Dennis Thompson, Esq, who is a "solicitor at law" in South Africa.  His client, Charles Rosen, died leaving $9 million in the bank, and the government is going to take it because Charlie has no kin.  The deal is that Chas and I share a last name, and if I declare myself to be Charlie's kin, Denny T, Esquire, will fill out all the paperwork to make it look all legal, and he'll split some of the bucks with yours truly.  Pretty tasty deal, I must say.  However, I'm a little wary.  That is, I was wary until I read the following line: "I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of law".  I have a guarantee!  What is the risk when I have a guarantee?  I have a guarantee from a man I have never met.  A guarantee from a man who is requesting that I become a party to fraud.  Iron clad!  My oh my... how to reply?  I started to write a reply, which began "What a coincidence! Some guy named 'Thompson' just died over here in the States!  Give me your bank account number, and I'll transfer his cash right over."  However, I'm thinking that that may not be cocky enough.  Maybe "Pinky swear?" or "Uncle Charlie's dead?!?!?!  NOOOOOOOOOOO!!!!!!!  I just talked to him last week!!!!!" or how about "Enlarge your pen!s naturally!"  Heh.  I like that last one.  Spammed ya back!
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I get some of the most spectacular errors in my code.  I actually had one a few months ago, which merely said "Catastrophic Error".  Personally, I think that the runtime is overreacting.  However, today I got one that just makes me giddy with the implications.  I was able to create an error that reads "Index 8765 is not non-negative and below total rows count".  It's basically an index out of range exception, but the wording is like a zen koan.  It cannot be understood by applying logic.  Think about that.  Let's break it down into manageable chunks.  First, we have to assume that there are implied parentheses around everything after the "is not", hence the statement "Index 8765 is not (non-negative and below total rows count), which can be expanded to say "Index 8765 is not non-negative, and Index 8765 is not below total rows count".  Index 8765 is not non-negative.  Well, I know that Index 8765 is positive.  So positive is not non-negative.  Pull two out of the triple negative, and you have a single negative.  Hence, positive is negative.  We know that is false, so we've evaluated the first part of the expression.  Second part of the expression... "Index 8765 is not below total rows count".  I'll have to assume that this is true, since I don't know the total rows count.  So the first part of the expression is false, the second part is true.  Now, to the conclusion... false and true equals what, kids?  FALSE!  That statement is inherently FALSE!  My index cannot be both not non-negative AND not below total rows count.  That's patently absurd!  Anyway, my logic is plainly flawed, but it was a lot of fun to say.
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today's: "Whoever is on your mind right now has absolutely no idea how far you'll go to make your presence known".  My interpretation: S***n thinks I've forgotten about her and moved on.  Here's more...  Horoscope: "Sometimes anything worth having is worth fighting for" Interpretation: I should try to get S***n back.  Horoscope: "Right now, finances are on your mind" Interpretation: I need money to take S***n out to dinner.  Horoscope: "Consult a professional if you think you may be in over your head" Interpretation: S***n is a professional. Professional hottie!  When will my horoscope quit talking about S***n! Damn!
      
</post>


</Blog>