<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I went to see The Bourne Supremacy w/PJ and Frank and a few other folks on Sunday.  The movie was pretty good.   I'm glad I went.  I met some of PJ's friends and we went to play Tennis after the movie.  The courts out by Ebanezer Church are fairly nice.  I noticed they have a rock climbing wall, but it's surrounded by a barb wire fence.   I think it's a bit ironic that they place something that will hurt you in the way of getting to something that might let you hurt yourself.  I guess most people recognize the danger of barb wire, but not so much falling from a 2 story rock climb.    I didn't play much b/c it was so hot out and I'm horrible at tennis.  I need to get my own racket and tennis balls and practice on the half-court wall out there some before I risk the lives of others ;-)     My interview went well on Tuesday, but I didn't didn't get the job.  They called me today (Friday) to tell me that I was their second choice and that the only reason the other candidate got the position was because he had 2 years of experience doing what exactly they're doing now with the county.  He'd been working on that type of stuff while I was in College.   Don Neuner called to tell me that he'd be passing my resume along to another aquaintance and to expect a call from them soon.  Maybe he can help me get another job in town.  We'll see.  I'm still waiting for a call back from Florence School District Three about their job opening.    I got to enjoy a nice dessert with friends at Ruby Tuesday this week.  Melissa, Jenifer, Robert, Jason, Leslie, PJ, and Mac were there with me.   Mac's a friend of PJ's that I met at the movies and the tennis courts.  Stephanie was our server.  :-)    We had a great time.  I laughed so hard, I almost cried.    I'm a little disappointed I didn't get the job this week, but I'm hopeful that Lake City will be a better fit for me anyway given my level of experience.  I'll just brush up on some books for dummies and play around with Linux some at home to prepare for that type of work in the future.  Maybe something better will open up for me, but in the meantime, I'll try to stay positive and just work on other things.    I need a drink.   Stargate better be good tonight!    In Vino Veritas. -- There is truth in wine.        *one is more likely to reveal the truth when drinking*   

						
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've completed another application -- AND, I got an interview for next week for a PC Tech job w/Florence County!   I don't know if I'll get the job, but at least I have an interview!  That's progress at least.    In other news, I was too sick to hang out w/my friends the other day :-( , but I'm feeling better now.    *gasp*  I don't know what I'll do with myself if I actually get a job in the 30-43k range!  I might explode!  :-)   Parrrrty!   

						
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yesterday, Candi Called. My mom picked up thinking it was dad at first, then handed me the phone. I asked her who it was -- she said "some girl". I figured it was likely Jenifer -- possibly Melissa or Leslie... maybe even Stephanie or Nancy... nope. A familiar voice on the other end at first sounded a bit like Jenifer -- because that was what I was expecting, but I knew it wasn't Jen.    So, I asked who it was. It was Candi. She finally decided to call me out of the blue. It's been nearly a month since we last spoke -- and longer than that since the last time she called here. It wasn't an unpleasant call. It was nice to know that she still thinks of me and misses me some, I guess.     She tells me she got her A in English, so she keeps her scholarship. She got her permit and has been driving some, though she was pulled and given a warning b/c her tail light was out. I hear Ernest and other friends have been dropping by at night to keep her company, and she's been visiting her church every weekend and is now part of the choir along with her sister.    She told me that I could call her sometime and invite her out if I'd like. I told her that she could call me if she wanted, but I doubt I'd call her... though I might enjoy spending time w/her. I'm a bit torn. I have mixed feelings about hearing from her and spending time with her. It's more fear of emotionally spinning out of control than anything. I think a part of me is still in disbelief that things are over between us and will motivate me to try to date her again. If all we'll ever be is friends, then I'm not sure I can handle that b/c I'm much more emotionally invested than that.    I guess time will tell. In any case, I'm not going to make the first move or invest a lot in trying to build a friendship with her after all that's happened between us. Less investment = less risk, so I'll just go with the flow. If being friends is important to her, she'll make the effort and I'll do my best to meet her half-way. I think that's the best strategy. It doesn't burn any bridges and allows some room to grow together or apart naturally.    In other news, I've had several professors volunteer to be references for me and I sent three of them forms to fill out for a job I'm applying for. :-) I hope I get it.     Once I get a job, then I can work on all the other things in this so-called life ;-)        There is no "I" in TEAM, but there is ME !!!   :->   

						
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've succeeded in creating my own blog, now I just have to get a life so I can write something interesting in it!  ;-)  Jenifer took me out the other night for some fine dinin' at Ruby Tuesdays.   I don't know how, but with coupons and discounts, we made outta there w/ 2 dinners, 2 salad bars, and 2 megaritas for about $23 before tipping.  Remind me to eat at Ruby Tuesday with Jenifer and/or Stephanie more often -- especially when they're working... lol.   those discounts pay off!  :-)    Later, we went to the Swamp and met up with Aaron, Robert, and some guy named Goat.  They were mesmerized by a golf video game.   Jenifer and I waited for an open pool table and considered playing darts, but we tested our luck at shuffleboard instead.   I've discovered I have no control at the game at all.  I either toss the dang weight too hard so it slides off the table or I only manage to move it a little farther than half-way to the scoring zone.  I think the secret is the sand on the table -- always pour some near the scoring end to slow the weights down more b/c when you play, the sand is brushed away over time.  Just when the pool tables finally freed up, the guys left, so jen and I finished our game and headed out.  The score isn't important...   okay, i lied... it is, but I lost -- that's why it isn't important.  lol.   Jen kicked my butt somethin' like 17 to 1 ! haha!  As for today, I got a phone call from some sort of IT staffing company that I had been referred to by Melissa.  I tell ya, that girl's more determined to find me a job than i am -- how sad!  lol.  I was already planning on visiting ManPower or Olsen for some temp or contract work if I didn't hear anything back from the places I'd applied in the next week or so.   So, I'll call them back tomorrow and see what the deal is and if they have a position available.   The message they left on my answering machine was for a 3 to 5 week contract job.  They made no mention of it becoming permanent or an hourly wage, so if Melissa hadn't recommended calling them, I probably wouldn't.  The company is alien to me, so I have lots of questions.  At least I know what I'm getting into if I go work for ManPower since I've dealt with them before and know people that work there.  It's got offices in Florence.  This company, TekSystems (subsidiary of Allegis Group), called me from somewhere in the 864 area code -- most likey Greenville/Spartanburg.  Eh, I guess since it specializes in IT staffing I should go for it.   It couldn't hurt to see what they want and possibly give it a try, I suppose.  I'm still hopeful that I'll get a decent job in town and won't have to go hunting in Columbia, Charlotte, Greenville, Charleston, or Atlanta.   hmm...  I wonder if there's an opening for me somewhere as a corporate tyrant.   I'd love to make millions while playing golf and making simple yes and no decisions with the knowledge that if things go under, I have a nice golden parachute to whisk me away to safety.   Where do I apply?   :->  

						
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hey... this is my first Blog.   Let's hope I don't incriminate myself ;-) 

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    The Beginning...   My recent illness started small -- like many things do. It began with a sore throat on weekend. I thought I could fight it off , so I took care to swish my mouth with listerine and gargle with salt water, etc. My worst fear at the time was that I'd lose my voice for my interview the Tuesday after I first got my sore throat. My throat slowly got worse and I began to run a fever. It was about 102 on Friday, so I figured I'd tough it out over the weekend and go to the doctor on Monday, but that didn't happen. By Sunday, I was weak... my legs were shakey and I had trouble keeping my balance. My muscles would shiver and tremble at times, and I didn't feel up to even watching TV. I just layed in bed slowly getting worse. My fever reached 104 Sunday and I was preparing to get in the tub w/ room temperature or cool water to cool down my fever... and asked mom if she was able to drive me to the doctor on Monday -- which is when she caught on that I was seriously ill and the folks decided to take me to the emergency room.   The Emergency Room   I knew that the ER would take forever, so I took juice with me and cold water so I could stay cool and keep my fever down 'til they could see me. They took my temperature -- 104.8 degrees. After a while, they took me in a wheel chair to a room and started me on my first IV. The IV was painful, but I've never had one before to compare it with. They drew a lot of blood from it at first which may have been why it was so bad. Then, they made me move to take off the sheets which they'd spilled blood on (I soooo did not want to move w/ that needle in my arm). They started me on a saline drip... gave me a bit of morphine since I was unhappy about my arm hurting (which was cool b/c the morphone made my throat stop hurting for about 15 minutes). They gave me x-rays of my chest and throat, ran every test they could on my blood, and took a swab of my throat to test for strep throat. Everything came back negative. They had no clue what was wrong with me. My white count was about 16, which means my white blood cell level was slightly above normal (normal is from 5 to 10), but that's to be expected when you have a fever, so they didn't think I had a bacterial infection. They were looking on the x-rays for an abscess or something more sinister that must be causing the infection. The docs were baffled. They kept coming in saying things like "that's really weird" and "strange... we may need to bring in a disease specialist". They weren't exactly inspiring confidence. Meanwhile, I'm hooked up like the Borg to a bunch of machines monitoring my heart, blood pressure, temperature, and other vitals -- they even took an EKG.  They'd run every test except for a urinalysis -- b/c I had gone to the restroom before I left for the hospital and I wasn't ready to go yet... but, they threatened me with a catheter... and man, I was ready to try to go then! Of course, the urinalysis came back with nothing, so they admitted me to a room for observation for a few days.   The Hospital Stay   Sooo, I got my own room... with basic cable -- no HBO, no Encore.... geez, every hotel in florence gets free HBO at least! I'm stuck in bed hooked to a bag of saline solution w/ a needle in my arm and poppin' 2 tylenol every 4 hours. A guy came in to put a heart monitor on me -- which requires 'lil sticky pads to be put all over my manly, hairy chest. He said that they'd give me an option -- he could either trim my chest hairs, or I could wish he had later when I'm ripping the pads off... lol. After having some experience taking off the EKG pads, I figured I'd tough it out since they came off fairly easily. They gave me the heart monitor b/c my heart was racing. At rest, it was beating like it normally does when I'm running -- even faster than when I get on the treadmill. My heart rate at rest was as high as 185, but slowly went down to 120 as I got fluids in me (normal is usually between 80 and 90). I was severely dehydrated because I hadn't been drinking or eating as much as usual due to my sore throat, they think. I got up just to brush my teeth my second day there, and my heart rate jumped to 144, so the nurses came in to check on me. I think they were worried I might have a heart attack w/ the rate so high.   Changing of the Guards   My folks decided to stay with me constantly during my stay. That was fine for the first day when I was too weak to do much on my own, but I hated having to kick them out every time I had to use the restroom -- which was a lot since they were pumping me full of fluids. As if it weren't impossible enough to sleep in the hospital with nurses coming to check on you and poking and prodding every so often... not to mention the bed's not as comfortable as my own, but Mom made it impossible to sleep with her in the room. I already couldn't lay back far the first night b/c if i did, I'd choke on my swollen tonsils... I finally got to sleep even with mom's constant shuffling and scooting and scraping the chair around the room, and the nurse wakes me up to take tylenol! argh... I got maybe a half hour's sleep that night. The folks always wanted to talk -- especially with visitors, and I hated not having just some peace and quiet to sleep or watch TV. I also didn't care for them being there to listen in on phone calls -- not that I was taking many b/c I was too tired and sickly to feel like talking much. My mom and dad took shifts at the hospital. I did my best to convince them to leave. At least I got Mom out of there at night so I could sleep better. It wasn't until the last day that I eventually got her to go AWAY, but sure enough she waited to leave until only a few hours before they told me they'd let me go home... lol.   The Nurses   I had some interesting nurses. Many were adorable single females. Victoria and Courtney Cox (cuter than the one on TV) were especially nice. I also had a somewhat feminine male nurse who threatened me with a sponge bath if I didn't take a shower one night... lol. Of course, I was dying to take a shower since I got there, but I didn't know what I'd have to deal with with the IV and heart monitor if I took one. That threat was enough motivation to get me up to take one. I took one after they took the heart monitor off and told me I could shower w/ the IV wrapped up in plastic for about 10 minutes... best shower I'd had in a long time, I tell ya. I saw a few familiar faces from when I'd been to McLeod before. One of the nurses was the one who was there when I took Candi to get her wisdom teeth out. Come to think of it, wearing the hospital gown, being in a hospital room, and the IV and the nurses... it reminded me a lot of when I was there to help Candi when she had her surgery. I remembered how weak she was... and for a time, I wished she were there to take care of me -- especially since noone seemed to know what was wrong with me and I could get worse. I called Jenifer to tell her I hadn't dropped off the planet -- knowing she'd get the word out to quite a few people... later, I called Candi just in case something happened to me... b/c I'd like to know if it were her there instead of me.   The Fever Breaks   My second night at the hospital, the docs decided to give me Levaquin, a powerful broad-spectrum antibiotic, for my sore throat since I seemed to have a lot of puss on my tonsils. My sister and a few others like Leslie were a bit shocked I still had my tonsils. My sister had them removed when she got married -- something she'd wanted to do for a long time. She said she's only had 2 sore throats in the past 14 years since her surgery. I'd say that's a good deal. I may have mine out as well.  In the middle of the night, after I'd kicked mom out and found a comfortable position in bed to sleep where my tonsils wouldn't choke me... I fell asleep. I was asleep for about 3 hours and woke up in a pool of sweat. I was drenched. The bed was soaked. My fever had broken and my temperature had dropped to 98.3. After that, I felt a lot better. I'd get dizzy if I stood up for more than 15 minutes at a time, and I was still weak, but I didn't feel as hot or as miserable. My fever kept going up during the day and I still needed tylenol to keep it down. It climbed up to 100.5, and the feminine male nurse threatened to stop using the oral thermometer if my fever kept going up... he said the anal one was more accurate and that he'd have to use that if it kept going up. Needless to day... I immediately turned the AC to as cold as possible, stripped the sheets off the bed, and started chugging down ice water!!! That fever was NOT going up. lol.   The Visitors   Whenever you're in the hospital, you can expect to have at least a few visitors. I've been on the other end of this situation plenty of times. I usually go to visit people -- just to show that I care -- during regular visitation hours and usually when I know others are going and we're expected.  Now, don't get me wrong... I love people in general, and I am always happy to see my friends... but geez... When you're wearing basically a sheet w/ underwear, haven't had a shower or shaved, and have to get up every couple hours to use the restroom (They make you go in a jug so they can measure your fluids... ick -- you'd think they'd rig the toilets to do that automatically -- also, the IV doesn't reach the bathroom all that well even w/ the extension cord to the monitor)... it's nice to have a little warning before someone just pops in -- b/c those doors don't exactly lock and I'd prefer to have at least a little privacy and a chance to get situated and look a 'lil decent for company. Most of the people that visited were family and friends of family -- many were freinds of family that I don't know. It's a little weird having total strangers pop in randomly and spend most of their time talking with my parents (you know... on MY time while I'm waitin' for them to leave so I can have some peace)... but, some were nice, and I appreciate the gesture. I just wish that they'd CALL FIRST. All of my friends did... but, apparently my family members and their friends didn't see the need to. It was just a bit frustrating not knowing if and when random people would be walking into my room and not being able to carry much of a conversation w/ them b/c I don't know them. Also, even with the family and friends I did know, I felt like I had to entertain them, but I really didn't have the strength or the mentality to the first day or two.  Having said that, I did enjoy having visitors. Mrs. Brooks, the wife of the principal of Wilson and a well-respected nurse in high authority at McLeod, came to visit me a few times. I hear she works two buildings over from my room at the time. Since she's in administration, she turned a lot of heads walking my way. She asked me if there was anything she could do for me -- and I mentioned a percoset that a nurse offered me to help me sleep. As soon as she left, a nurse, Victoria, popped in and introduced herself, gave me a percoset and did a 'lil song and dance telling me if I needed aaaaanything -- a pillow, another blanket... something to eat or drink... anyyyything to let her know. lol. I think the nurses on my hall might have had an extra skip in their step knowing that I was a friend of Mrs. Brooks and that if I wasn't happy, they'd be hearing about it. lol. Of course, she could have just been a real sweet nurse :-)  Another nurse, a friend of my parents, dropped in to see me a few times. She was very nice and offered to get me magazines or anything I needed. She dropped off 2 devices that are supposed to help you breathe better -- one exercises your lungs and the other breaks up gunk in your chest to help you cough it up better. They looked pretty funky. One looked like a large kazoo and the other was like a funpark game w/ a ball that floated up when you breathed on a tube. I told people that came in and asked what they were that they were my sex toys. lol.  The Flecks, long-time family friends, dropped in for a bit and offered to let me borrow a camcorder and dvd player so I could watch movies in the room, but I declined. I was fine w/ the basic cable and sleeping. They brought their youngest granddaughter, Charley, with them. She's only 4 and had just been to her first funpark w/ rollercoasters. I told her I was jealous. I wanted to go back to Carowinds when I got out and ride the BIG rollercoasters when I got better. She had the cutest expressions and talked w/ her hands and rolled her eyes as she spoke. I love kids. :-)  My Grandmother Bell dropped in to visit me -- she forgot to stop at the desk and get a tag from the security guard. I picked on her about the guards coming to get her if they see her in the hallway like that. I told her to act like she was senile and pretend she was a patient who forgot which floor she was on... lol.  Jenifer was kind enough to stop in for a while. She brought me a mug filled w/ candy and a balloon. It was very sweet of her to visit. All the other girls called, too. Everyone always asked if there was anything they could do for me or bring me. After hearing so many folks ask me if there was anything they could bring me, I decided to get a bit creative. I told the girls they could bring me some strippers ;-) Jenifer said I wouldn't want those nasty girls dancin' around in my hospital room... so, I told her that the girls could come and dance naked for me instead -- I figure they're clean ;-) lol. Hey, what are friends for? I coulda been on my deathbed! lol.  So, the girls came over and took their tops off and danced and played w/ each others nipples... okayyyyy so maybe that didn't happen, but i had a fever of 104.8, morphine, tylenol, and Levaquin in my system -- and let's not forget the lack of sleep among other things... so, I coulda been a bit delusional, but hey, i'll remember it the way I want to, okay?!?!? hahahaha. ;-)  Leslie asked if I had any hot nurses giving me sponge baths... I told her no, but she was welcome to come over and do that if she liked... lol. She was real sweet and got out of work early so she could try to visit me one day, but I had to call her and let her know I was going home that day. She got me a card, but I think I'll get it in a few months -- kinda like her belated birthday card ;-)  The Brooks and Wilson's staff sent me flowers, and my pastor, Jim Crooks, visited me and even gave me a lead for a possible job opening which was very nice of him. Lots of others visited and family members dropped in on their lunch breaks to check on me -- real nice of 'em.  I was overjoyed that I'd be going home to my OWN bed, my own room and my own digital cable TV w/ my computer and the internet... Now I'll definitely have to buy a laptop -- just so I can use it for vacations, hospital stays, and other such times. Even if I don't have 'net access, I could still write e-mails to send later.... and play games 'n watch DVDs on it :-)   Home At Last   I was dog tired after getting home. I slept constantly -- even more than my usual lazy self does. I was weak and found it difficult to stand for more than an hour or two without getting dizzy. I've slowly gotten better since then. I think maybe the antibiotic made me sleepier than usual along with my being bedridden for a while. I think I'm back to my normal self now, and I'm ready to party or ride some rollercoasters now that I'm done w/ my antibiotics and well! :-> 

						
</post>


</Blog>