<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No friendster?! I need my daily dose of surveys!  Am not so busy kase e. Especially now that he's not texting me pa.  Blogger experts, help pls? I can't even figure out how to fix my URL. I wanna make my blogspot more creative, eye-catching, SEXY. Hehe. Grash, I know you can help me. A.S.A.P. Hehe. Just wanna do it now kase eh. Kaya nagmamadali.  Boring classes today. Especially lit. Oh, i posted something na nga pla about our sh*tty teacher right? Man, she really knows how to piss people off. PHYSICS. I failed the test! Hello? The test questions naman kase were really hard. No, not naman. The multiple choice part was ok. BUT THEN, the problem solving thing. F*CK! This was also my problem during the 1st quarter of junior year. Chem. I got 78 in the card because of dimensional analysis. Stupid Stef. Sheesh. Oh! Check this out. 6:45a: parked my bag at our tambayan, then off I went to the bookstore and bought Kitkat White. 9:40a: recess time, again I bought Kitkat White. 12:05p: I bought chicken and rice then Kitkat White for desert. 4:40p: I bought the ever-so-delicious footlong. Man, am I not a pig?! I swear if I'm gonna be like this for the whole year, I'm gonna be as fat as someone who is fat. Hehe. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sheek.  Sheesh.  Shush.  So boring.  Ms S** D****. what the?! Can't you at least be more firm with what and how you're teaching? At least sound like you are credible. I mean, how are the students supposed to know if what you're discussing is actually a fact? Heller?  Why did this school accept you in the first place?
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think there's something wrong with the way I think. I expect to much from him i guess. That's why everything he does isn't enough. Maybe i should loosen up a lil. Be more considerate. Right. Be. Be. BE.   Shit man, i love him. I love him too damn much.  No doubts.  No regrets.  Just dropped by.  Hang on stef.  You're a tough cookie.  Nah.  I am cuz I'm sorrounded by tough people. Including him.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just created this thing. What's it called? Oh,according to grash it's a blog. Hehe.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sheesh. It's been quite a while since I last updated my blogspot.  Anyway, had somethings in mind that I wanted to share to those who check out my spot.  This is 'bout me and my boo.  Guys can be so unpredictable. One minute they can be the sweetest creatures ever created since the history of mankind, and then the next, they can treat you as if you don't exist at all. I mean hello? What's with?  Lester's like that. He has UNPREDICTABLE written all over his face. Ako naman si tanga, super bait parin sakanya. Argh! This can really be so irritating. The fact that I'm stuck in this relationship. Stuck as in stuck because I love him TOO much and I can't leave him. I'm the one who's gonna have to suffer.  *sigh*  How ironic. Despite all the pains he has caused me, I still manage to go on. Even love him more. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>