<Blog>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have no idea how I missed this the first time, but apparently   urlLink Slate  published an article recommending Firefox over IE (Slate is owned by MSN/Microsoft).  Oh and now Microsoft is looking to  urlLink sell slate . 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      CNN.Com has a story up about Bloggers getting  urlLink credentials  at this years political conventions for "official" commentary. 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Picked  urlLink this  up over at Laura's  urlLink blog . Funny stuff. 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here are a few quickies from the last few days: The birth of the  urlLink iPod . I need to get into  urlLink Duke University  now. No  urlLink 2.7 kernel  branch any time soon.  
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Is it sad that my  urlLink Bookmarks  file is over a half-meg? The good news is that I'm still trimming it down.  
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, just picked up the  urlLink latest issue  of this title, so expect a full review later this week (probably sometime this weekend). Quicky review is just to say that I think it sucks that Randy Green isn't doing penciles on it anymore. Staz Johnson, who penciled issue 3 just doesn't capture the feel of the book as well as Green did.    Anyway, more information to come later.    
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink This  is pretty damn funny.
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Picked up a new manga at the store last night called Princess Ai. So far  urlLink it's  pretty good.
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bill Gates has now  urlLink predictated  that DVD's will be obsolete in 10 years time. I'll point out that tech wise DVD was obsolete before it was standard. From a consumer's point of view though I think they'll be here at least as long as VHS (20+ years as primary media outlet).  Wyldwolf
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I gotta agree with   urlLink Seraphim  on this one. The Gaiman v. McFarlane decision is pretty cool. You can find the full text of the decision at  urlLink Find Law  under the 7th Circuit court of appeals (do a search for Gaiman or McFarlane).  Wyldwolf
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, it finally happened...  urlLink New PHP  is out. Though it'll probably be a while before my host upgrades.  Wyldwolf
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I've been reading various books in the Marvel Reload that last couple of months and while I'm not really super impressed by any of them, the only which is really bothering me right now is the new Excalibur. Guess what - Magneto's still alive! bah - they should bring back Psylocke and Colossus if they are gonna ignore their own "death is real" rule.  More later.  Wyldwolf
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Changing up various settings. The current URL is  urlLink http://sackofhappy.org/blog/blog.html . Let me know what you think...  Wyldwolf
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Trying out "Blogger" while I get my own code working.
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      If anyone has an invite to the google mail (gmail) beta that they aren't using and don't mind donating drop me a note.
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here's and interesting  urlLink read , and here are  urlLink some   urlLink pictures . 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Created a  urlLink DevBlog  to work on some template changes for this site. 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here are the semi-regular weekend quickies:     urlLink Mozilla  is doing a big  urlLink migration  plan next Tuesday for the Thunderbird email client.   Apparently  urlLink Disney  is trying to become even more  urlLink evil .   Apparently  urlLink PHP  5.0 now equals  urlLink Java .   Now  urlLink Apple  is an  urlLink evil company  too.    I may add more at a later time. 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I picked up the latest issue of  urlLink Dungeon , and I'm already sceptical because they're doing the whole "reformatting" thing, yet again. So I'm flipping through it and I notice one of the new columns, on the last page, written by Wil Wheaton. Apparently  urlLink Wil  is a gamer... I did not know this. It seems very strange to me - but *shrug* guess we'll take what we can get. On the plus side the new Dungeon format seems solid enough, and all the new columns were quite good. 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Scott Kurtz has  urlLink annouced  that he's gonna let news papers print his comic for free... Interesting. 
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink Bowling For Soup  has a great new single, called  1985 . It's true greatness. Update: Here are the  urlLink lyrics  for the song. 
      
</post>


</Blog>