<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Quin  I had a mad desire to just copy and paste Ray's previous post.  After all, it fits my own situation so well, and he was the one who said... what was it? that I might be able to someday get some attacks that hurt?  Oh well, such is the price of being a healer.  At least my abilities are in high demand.   Having recovered from my cold briefly, I now seem to have come down with something else.  It is ironic, isn't it, to be a healer and yet be cursed with being purpetually ill.  It isn't really my fault, though.  I could blame it on my parents.  Or on that stupid doctor they sent me to.  I suppose without the strange events that conspired to make me the way I am, I never would have become a superhero, though, so I can't really complain. You see, I was born with a very slight empathetic psychic ability.  So slight, in fact, that it was entirely undetectable, and comepletely useless.  It was too weak to show me when or where or why someone was feeling pain or sickness, but my immune system seemed to figure it out.  So if I so much as touched anyone who had been very ill, or would be very ill in the near future, I myself became sick.  My parents couldn't figure out what was going on and brought me to a varaity of doctors, both magic and mundane.  Finally, fed up with the whole thing, they brought me to a healer who claimed that she could cure me magically for good.  Instead, she put me through a process called a Changeover which gave me magical healing powers.  I guess her idea of curing me was providing me with the means for curing myself whenever I became sick.   It was later discovered that my mild psychic powers were both responsible for my perpetual illness, and unable to be completely removed.  So instead my parents sent me to a trainer to enhance both my healing powers, which were much stronger, if magical, and not mutant in nature, as well as my psychic powers, in the hope that they could do some good for mankind, even while they were destroying my immune system.   My trainer registered me in the SOA (Superheroes of America) and I've been sent to work in Paragon City.  It's nice to be around other superheroes, instead of trying to hide my identity 24/7.  Some of these heroes have even stranger stories than I! That said, I should probably get to work.  Maybe Ray needs a healer to tag along and help him out with his missions. 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Raker.    Okay, so I doubt that I'll really be able to "solo" any time soon. I keep running into these insane people who cackle a lot and then toss me around like a little rag doll. I've been able to finish most of my missions thanks to grouping with Quin, but I really feel a bit... inadequate... because I can't stand alone easily. Now, hopefully this will change at some point in the future, maybe after I study some healing arts and upgrade my armor a bit... I hope :(   
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Quin  The Vahz can vomit all over me... so why can't I have a snot attack?&nbsp; I think that it would be a better use of my illness than wasting about half a forest worth of kleenex.&nbsp; But, as my supernatural healing powers dictate, I am getting better at a rapid pace.&nbsp; I was even able to go to work (the work that pays, not the park ranger, or crime fighting work) and entertain 60 little kids.&nbsp; One fell down on the stairs and I thought he was about to start screaming, so I made sure no one was looking at quickly did 'Heal Other' so I wouldn't have to deal with a crying kid along with 59 others who were already on a sugar high, 10 minutes into their tour of the candy store.   I am able to continue my training at a reasonable pace.&nbsp; I've gained two more security levels in the last three days - not too bad, although a certain Cryoblast might disagree.&nbsp; I don't know if I could possibly beat his record of nine levels in two days.&nbsp; With only a bit more training, I will be able to fly.&nbsp; This, as Raker knows, is going to end a major source of my complaining while on missions - that they are just to damn far apart! I've&nbsp;decided that if SOA (Superheroes of America) decides to relocate me, that I will ask to be put in a small town.&nbsp; Perferably with only one or two main streets.&nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Raker.    Classes are still in full swing here. I got back a couple papers today, I managed to squeeze off some A's magically. Do you understand how difficult it is to type with one hand? I have to remove my arm so I don't get frustrated and stab the keyboard. . . Anyways, I almost feel like going to fight crime is relaxing now. I mean, I need some break from the monotony of trying to persuade my teacher that I deserve good grades. I'm currently in the midst of two papers, one that deals with the evils of corporate America (anyone else thinking of Crey, Inc. right now?) and another that deals with the "working poor." I've got some pretty nice insight into the latter recently, having to deal with the Lost and all of those strange missing persons cases.   Anyways, I ought to get to work writing, I need to turn this paper in tomorrow. . .&nbsp;it's too bad crime fighting can't pay the bills, otherwise we'd all be set for life. Maybe I should be a cop. . . nah, they'd expect me to follow all those uptight guidelines and shit. . . probably wouldn't even be able to use my arm. ANYWAYS. I'm just procrastinating now.   Okay, I'll go work and attempt to finish in a reasonable amount of time to hit the streets tonight. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Quin  Who ever said that superheroes didn't need sleep clearly has never woken up with a stuffy nose, sore throat, and hacking cough after a night of crime fighting.&nbsp; I, of course, understand the importance of our job.&nbsp; Without us, Paragon City, and then the world would be overrun with all sorts of unnamed horrors.&nbsp; But the question here is; should heroes, with all that they already give to this city, have to give up their 6 - 8 hours of sleep as well?&nbsp; Surely, there must be some time one could fit it in!&nbsp; &nbsp;Well, after massive amounts of Tylenol and calling in sick to work (again.&nbsp; I really have to stop doing that.&nbsp; Oh well, it's not like they pay me.&nbsp; Being an intern to a park ranger has it's benefits in allowing me to surreptitiously monitor the woods for crime, but it sure doesn't pay the rent) I took my costume to the dry cleaner's.&nbsp; (Why do they pick sewers? Why!?&nbsp; It takes twenty minutes at least to get the gunk out of my hair.)&nbsp; Sometimes I try to imagine showing up at a dry cleaner's in another city with my costume - it's a good thing the Paragon Pressers are used to heroes coming in.&nbsp;   Johnny Pyre asked me out for lunch again, and I have nothing better to do than cough all over the plate of Mexican food that he buys me.&nbsp; This time, though, I don't think I'll wear a skirt.&nbsp; I have this sneaking suspicion that he's trying to look up it every time we team up.&nbsp; Hover can be a pain in the neck sometimes.&nbsp; After lunch, I had better clock some hours on the job or my contacts might be a little put off.&nbsp; I'll try and take down some clockwork, they're really starting to piss me off.&nbsp;   Training with the rest of the group has me averaging about one security level up each day, but I'll see how well I can do on my own this morning.&nbsp; I might be sick, but at least&nbsp;I remember the importance of catnaps.    
    
</post>


<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh man, I just got back from what must be the funkiest thing ever.  Probably hasn't been done since the sixties.  Eight kids, sitting in the middle of a huge grassy area, beating on drums.  Hand drums, bongos, Pat's drum-that-i-can't-name, mine from africa, a couple odd ones Jon got from India.  It was awesome, man.  A ton of fun.  And while I couldn't really participate in all the talk about who was high/drunk/messed-up and when, it didn't bother me.  It's funny to listen to other people talk about stupid things they do, as long as they're not trying to pressure you into stuff like that.  And the people in question are good about that.  They have resepect.    Got my tech job today:  usher.  Whee.  =P.  While other people might not like being an usher, I'm quite happy with the assignment.  A.) it means I get to dress nicely and greet people, which is more fun than dealing with cranky actors, and B.) it means I have nothing to do, ever, while the show itself is running.  Which means this week?  I'll only be actually  doing  stuff about half the time.  And that's incredibly nice during tech week.    So what did I do with all that spare time today, you might ask?  I told Brady and Claire the story of my life, basically.  It was good times.  Course, Brady's in the show I tech for, so he periodically had to run to the stage to be in a fight, or to say something, or to die.  After he died, he kinda got to stick around for a while.  Can't possibly imagine why.    But yeah, the afternoon was great.  So great.  Nothing to do but lie in the shade, talking with good friends who actually understand you.  How I've missed CTC people, and miss the people who are now gone, and... I don't know.  I got here too late, I didn't grow up in the system -- I'm an outsider.  But I had missed having so many people like this around me until, well, it started maybe four months ago?  I don't remember, whenever Joseph started... and then the second phase of this bounty of good people started this summer.  And I love it.    Anyway, I'm writing really short, clipped sentences and not feeling very thoughtful right now, and I think it may be from fatigue.  So despite the fact that it is before midnight, I'm now going to sleep, and hopefully tomorrow I shall feel well rested and wonderful and life will be good.    Goodnight.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Stay or Leave"  by Dave Matthews     Maybe different, but remember   Winters warm there you and I,   Kissing whiskey by the fire    With the snow outside...   And the summer comes   The river, swims at midnight:   Shiver cold.   Touch the bottom, you and I   With muddy toes...      Stay or leave,   I want you not to go;   But you should.   It was good, as good goes.   Stay or leave,   I want you not to go;   But you did.      Wake up naked drinking coffee,   Making plans to change the world   While the world is changing us...   It was good, good love.   You used to laugh under the covers;   Maybe not so often now.   The way I used to laugh with you   Was loud and hard...      Stay or leave,   I want you not to go;   But you should.   It was good, as good goes.   Stay or leave,   I want you not to go;   But you did.      So what to do   With the rest of today's afternoon, hey:   Isn't it strange how we change   Everything we did -   Did I do all that i should?      That I could'a done      Remember we used to dance,   And everyone wanted to be   You and me   I want to be too...   What day is this,   Besides the day you left me?   What day is this,   Besides the day you went?      So what to do   With the rest of the day's afternoon, hey   Isn't it strange how we change   Everything we did:   Did I do all that I could?      Remember we used to dance,   And everyone wanted to be - you and me -   I want to be too   What day is this?   Besides the day you went, babe.  What day is this?    -------      The music is gorgeous too, I just can't post it.  Alas.    Anyway, it's way too late, so I'm not gonna put an actual post up.  This is all you get.  Now I'm off to sleep so that I wake up in time for CTC.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    What I do in my spare time... fly around a fictional city in Rhode Island.  If only I had a life.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      http://www.yale.edu/lawweb/avalon/imt/kbpact.htm    Ironically, I noticed that Afghanistan was a signatory on the treaty.  What's going on in this world?  Why are humans the violent species that they are?  Why do we ignore impending self-destruction in favor of other goals which we formed without a "big picture" view of the effects that they would have?    This is not just about war, either.  For example, I once had a thought -- what if environmental costs were factored into the price of every product on the market?  What if, for example, paper's cost was determined not just by the price of the machinery which it takes to make it and the wages for the workers at... well, at wherever produces paper... but you also had to pay as much as it would cost to produce another tree of the same age and type and in the same location?  And you had to pay as much as it would cost to clean the air of the exhaust produced by the machines that mulch the wood?  An item as simple as paper would become prohibitively expensive.  And yet it seems to me that Humans are Cheating the way of the universe by not paying such costs.  We are irresponsible.  We are careless.  And, well, we don't care.    That's not to be repetitive -- it's one thing to be unwittingly careless, but it's another entirely to just be apathetic towards any damage you may be causing to anything simply because it better suits your purposes.    Even the electricity I'm using right now to both look at this and send this information out to the world at large can never be totally replaced.  Not by the understanding of current physics, anyway, which is certainly flawed (ex: explanation for creation of universe in the first place?  No clue.).  But that said, we should not just assume that there will be a way to turn heat back into electricity, or a way to turn smog back into breathable air, or a way to, in general, turn waste back into the useful things which we used up.  If there is such a way to break the "laws" of chemistry and physics, all the better.  If there is not, we're just screwing ourselves over.  Every day.  And not caring.    So this is a challenge to the world.  I don't think many people will pick it up, but here it shall stand:    Think.    Think about what you are doing.  Think about the consequences it will have.  Know what damage you are causing in your day to day life, and ask yourself if it is worth it.  Evaluate what truly is important not in your life, but for the good of humanity and all existence on the planet far beyond our lifetimes.    And of course, nobody is perfect.  Which reminds me of another line of thinking I came up with this morning on my run, but I'll save you from it.  The point is, just do your best.  That's all you can do.  And let's make sure there's still a place to live for everything that comes after us.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      1929:  Herbert Hoover proclaimed the Kellogg-Briand Pact, which renounced war as an instrument of foriegn policy.    I think I'll look that up later.  Not like I have anything better to do =P.  But I do find it funny, how many different excuses humans can find for making the same mistakes over and over again.  Shame on us, humanity, shame on us.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If only that were the case.  I'm so freaking tired -- I keep drawing  on energy reserves to get me from day to day, and then not  sleeping enough at night to replenish them.  At this point, I don't  think I've been well and truly rested yet this summer.  I guess  I'll just have to hibernate the two weeks between when I get  to visit Carey and when school starts, or something, because that's  all the time I have to sleep this summer.  Not that I'm complaining:  that's just why I'm tired.  And of course, at this point you'll look to  the bottom of this post, see that I posted it at 12:50 am, and feel  no pity for me whatsoever.  The only reason I'm awake is because  I'm writing this, though, so there. =P    On a somewhat random note, anyone who wants to come to my  show, please tell me what dates you can come, how many tickets  you want, etc.  I need to sell tickets ahead of time, so it's better if  you actually tell me and don't just say "Oh, I'll show up at the door."  Also, my play's on the smaller of two stages, so it'll only have 101  seats, and may well sell out.  I'm not sure how many more tickets  we have to sell.  So tell me, and tell me quickly.    Life's ok right now.  I feel really weird, though, in general.  On the  outside again, I guess =/.  I miss feeling like I really exist, like I  am serving a purpose in my everyday life.  Right now I feel like  I'm marking time, waiting for something, and I don't know what,  and the feeling is just rough to live with constantly.    CTC is, though, of course, a blast.  Wow, good grammar, Jeff.  Way  to go.  *Sigh*... it's late.  I forgive myself.  Anyway, the days are so  action-packed that I'm hard-pressed even to take a spare moment  to breathe.  Today was our last official rehearsal, and it went alright.  There are still some line problems, which is disheartening, but I'm  certainly not perfect either.  Which is also disheartening.  Damn, I  guess life is just disheartening.  Ah well.    I'm still not over "A Walk in the Woods".  That play rocked, and  unbelievably so.  Wish I had a recording or something.  It'd be  illegal, of course, but I still wish I did.  That could also be made  into a great movie -- it wouldn't be mainstream at all, but that's  how it should be.  It would be amazing though:  the script is so  well written, and the fact that the play takes place in one location...  Well, if a movie version of it comes out, let it be known that I had  the idea, today, Saturday July 24th, at 1 in the morning.    Moving on...    I was down today, and was hoping for someone to do something  with this evening, but Scott was off with his girlfriend and Nick  was as well, and this was -- guess what?  That's right:  disheartening.  Lucky bastards... lol.  Oh, but then I realized that  Meaghan is back in town for good and so I talked with her and  she came over here.  She brought her new laptop, showed that to  me for a while, and then our internet went down.  So we decided to  play Scrabble.  My father wittily observed that the net being down  is the 21st century equivalent of a rainy day.  But scrabble was fun,  too, just because I love word games.  That said, it was the weirdest  damn game of Scrabble I've ever played -- at one point, there were  three E's on the board, three in meaghan's hand, and four in mine.  This was like the third turn of the game.  There are only 12 E's in  the deck.  Figure it out -- that's not the way you want to be making  words.    (I took pictures of my hand turn by turn once it got truly obnoxious.  I understand that Meaghan's hand was similarly bad, though of  course I never saw it myself.  I'll post pictures of it just for fun.  And  just because I took them.)    Anyway, she went home eventually.  By this time, Scott was back home.  She and Scott and myself all got on City of Heroes, flew around, blew  some stuff up, had a generally good time, despite my own death on  one occasion, and then it was about half an hour ago, and I thought I'd  better go to sleep.  I wish I'd remembered to call Carey tonight.  Not  that she needs me to, but it's so nice to talk to her.  Plus, I meant to  call, I just didn't remember.  I was too focused on feeling like crap =P.  Ah well.  Self, don't do it again.    Yeah, that's it for this post.   More later.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am lonely.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh.  My.  God.     (Wow, I'm from California.  But moving on...)    Walk in the Woods was absolutely amazing.  It was the best  serious piece of drama I've ever seen in my life, I do believe.    I'm really tired, so I'm not going to post much.  Just, if you  ever hear of a play by that name being performed near you,  go and see it.  Especially if you're an internationally-inclined  person, like myself.  And if you're here (in the bay area) right  now, there's one show left.  I'll figure out when tomorrow, and  post it up here.  When I do, call CTC's office (the # will go up as  well) and reserve tickets.  It's so very very well worth it.  Wow.  I just can't say enough.    "If mankind really was a peace-seeking creature, there would be  thousands of diplomats and only two soldiers."    One of those profound moments of bizarre truth.  I love it.     So tired I'm repeating myself every other sentence.  So now,  to bed.  Goodnight, world.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Wow.  The last few days really have been just one big blur.  I'm having trouble even remembering what day it is -- I keep thinking  tomorrow is thursday, and the only reason i catch myself is because  that would mean that tonight was conservatory night, which it  definitely was not.  So yeah, my sense of time is pretty screwed  up right now.  Sorry for the lack of posts -- I've been really busy.    So first off, our show's really good.  It gets better by the day, mostly as   people get more of the lines we were supposed to know all of by  yesterday or last friday.  But yeah... CTC owns my life for the next  few weeks.  Tomorrow at noon is the halfway point.  Kind of scary.  Hard to believe it's all over so fast, especially when I've worked so  hard to get to where I am now and then all my friends will leave next  year, just as I've gotten here.    This, however, is not what I want to write about.  I want to write about  my good friend Brady, one of the few who probably won't leave next year.  I've been in conservatories with Brady since our first year, and we've  always hung out, and basically, Brady just rocks.  He's an awesome guy,  and he's hilarious, and just all around fun to have around.  But for reasons  of his own, Brady had an incredibly shitty weekend.  If I told you what  happened to him, you'd cry.  And he'd be mad at me.  So I won't.  Suffice it  to say, I confirm it as quite shitty, knowing exactly what happened.  But  here's the kicker:  yesterday was Brady's  birthday !  And he was having  a crappy day!   And in my world, that's just not allowed...    So, since all the IITs were off at their little exclusive party (rant on elitism  to follow at some point.  I love them all dearly, but they do need to get off  their... whatever it is they're on.) and none of them were going to do  anything for him (not that they're great friends, but you know... it gave us  an excuse...)  my sister and Claire and myself made Brady two CDs, then  Claire and I went to Cupertino to deliver them to him.  This decision was  also because he had said he wasn't going to have a birthday party, so we  figured we'd just brighten up his day with a bit of a surprise.  But little did  we know, the plot was about to thicken.    Outside of his house, there was a sign saying to please be quiet and gather  by the basketball hoop.  From this, we knew there was a surprise party in  the works, but we were already there... So we decided we'd just, at the very  least, stop by, say hi, and drop off the CDs.  But then his mom invited us in  for dinner, and stealthily informed us that it was wonderful luck that we had  arrived, because the more of Brady's friends were there, the better.  It felt  really awkward, somehow crashing a surprise party, but it turned out alright.  We, along with some other guy from Saint Francis who I didn't know but both  Claire and Brady did, kept Brady occupied in the backyard while his parents  set up the surprise.  Then we went out front and yelled with everyone else.    Everyone there was, of course, from Saint Francis, where Brady goes to  school, so I was just a wee bit out of place.  But it was alright -- some of his  friends were pretty accepting, and Claire introduced me to her friend Laura,  which is funny cuz now I know maybe five or six girls named Laura, and it  always seems to me that they're borrowing the name from my sister or something.  Unless their name has funky-awesome alliteration which makes it cool  and different.  Namely Laura Lucas.  Laura Lucas, if you're reading this, your  name rocks.    Anyway, the point is, Brady's day went from shitty to really really obscenely  good in a very small amount of time.  and that was good.  Mission Accomplished.    That was my yesterday.  In addition to that, yesterday was one solid day of  rehearsals, unbroken by classes.  That was no fun.  I had been too busy totally  redoing my room on the weekend, and hadn't spent enough time on lines.  So  now my room's still a mess, the hallway's a mess too, I get yelled at a lot more  than normal, and I get pissed off at myself for dropping lines.  Not a very good  situation to be in.    Today, I got up really early and made crepes.   One rather heaping plateful.   Brought them with me to conservatory, along with sugar, nutella, and kumquat  jam.  Nick, Brady, Claire, the other Nick,  and myself made a breakfast out of it,  and some others grabbed a crepe or two here and there.  It was definitely good  times, despite how tired I am now because of it.    Speaking of being tired, It's been forty-five minutes since I started this post,  and I want to go to sleep.  So despite my having plenty more to say, I'm off to  bed.  More will probably follow later, if I get time at my computer.   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Jesus and Jihad By NICHOLAS D. KRISTOF 	  "Of the latest in the "Left Behind" series of  evangelical thrillers is to be believed, Jesus  will return to Earth, gather non-Christians to  his left and toss them into everlasting fire:  "Jesus merely raised one hand a few inches and  a yawning chasm opened in the earth, stretching  far and wide enough to swallow all of them. They  tumbled in, howling and screeching, but their  wailing was soon quashed and all was silent  when the earth closed itself again."  These are the best-selling novels for adults in  the United States, and they have sold more than  60 million copies worldwide. The latest is  "Glorious Appearing," which has Jesus returning to  Earth to wipe all non-Christians from the planet.  It's disconcerting to find ethnic cleansing celebrated  as the height of piety.  If a Muslim were to write an Islamic version of  "Glorious Appearing" and publish it in Saudi Arabia,  jubilantly describing a massacre of millions of non-Muslims  by God, we would have a fit. We have quite properly linked  the fundamentalist religious tracts of Islam with the  intolerance they nurture, and it's time to remove the  motes from our own eyes.  In "Glorious Appearing," Jesus merely speaks and the  bodies of the enemy are ripped open. Christians have  to drive carefully to avoid "hitting splayed and  filleted bodies of men and women and horses."  "The riders not thrown," the novel continues, "leaped  from their horses and tried to control them with the reins,  but even as they struggled, their own flesh dissolved, their  eyes melted and their tongues disintegrated. . . . Seconds  later the same plague afflicted the horses, their flesh and  eyes and tongues melting away, leaving grotesque skeletons  standing, before they, too, rattled to the pavement."  One might have thought that Jesus would be more of an animal lover.  These scenes also raise an eschatological problem:  Could devout fundamentalists really enjoy paradise  as their friends, relatives and neighbors were heaved into hell?  As my Times colleague David Kirkpatrick noted in an article,  this portrayal of a bloody Second Coming reflects a shift  in American portrayals of Jesus, from a gentle Mister  Rogers figure to a martial messiah presiding over a sea  of blood. Militant Christianity rises to confront Militant Islam.  This matters in the real world, in the same way that  fundamentalist Islamic tracts in Saudi Arabia do. Each  form of fundamentalism creates a stark moral division between  decent, pious types like oneself — and infidels headed for hell.  No, I don't think the readers of "Glorious Appearing"  will ram planes into buildings. But we did imprison  thousands of Muslims here and abroad after 9/11, and  ordinary Americans joined in the torture of prisoners  at Abu Ghraib in part because of a lack of empathy for  the prisoners. It's harder to feel empathy for such  people if we regard them as infidels and expect Jesus  to dissolve their tongues and eyes any day now.  I had reservations about writing this column because  I don't want to mock anyone's religious beliefs, and  millions of Americans think "Glorious Appearing"  describes God's will. Yet ultimately I think it's a  mistake to treat religion as a taboo, either in this  country or in Saudi Arabia.  I often write about religion precisely because faith  has a vast impact on society. Since I've praised the  work that evangelicals do in the third world (Christian  aid groups are being particularly helpful in Sudan, at  a time when most of the world has done nothing about the  genocide there), I also feel a responsibility to protest  intolerance at home.  Should we really give intolerance a pass if it is rooted  in religious faith?  Many American Christians once read the Bible to mean  that African-Americans were cursed as descendants of  Noah's son Ham, and were intended by God to be enslaved.  In the 19th century, millions of Americans sincerely  accepted this Biblical justification for slavery as God's  word — but surely it would have been wrong to defer to  such racist nonsense simply because speaking out could  have been perceived as denigrating some people's religious  faith.  People have the right to believe in a racist God, or  a God who throws millions of nonevangelicals into hell.  I don't think we should ban books that say that. But  we should be embarrassed when our best-selling books  gleefully celebrate religious intolerance and violence  against infidels.  That's not what America stands for,  and I doubt that it's what God stands for.  "    I couldn't have said it better myself.  Which is, of course, why they pay him.  But honestly... how can people spew such hatred?  I don't understand it at all.  And maybe that's a good thing, because it means it's far from anything I myself would do.  Still... I wish I knew what caused this disgust with other fellow human beings, because then maybe I could do something to mitigate it or stop it altogether.  Well, there's time yet.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CTC Festival Weekend(s) Schedule!!!  As Follows:  Saturday, July 31st:  4:00 -- Servant of Two Masters 5:30 -- A New Age is Dawning 7:00 -- Henry V 8:30 -- The Crucible   ________________________________   Friday, August 6th:  6:30 -- The Quest of Perseus 8:00 -- A New Age is Dawning 9:30 -- Servant of Two Masters 9:30 -- Rosalynde  Saturday, August 7th:  11:30 am -- Servant of Two Masters 1:00 pm -- The Rememberer 2:30 -- Henry V 4:00 -- A New Age is Dawning 5:30 -- The Quest of Perseus 7:00 -- The Crucible 9:00 -- Henry V 9:00 -- Rosalynde  Sunday, August 8th:  10:00 am -- Henry V 11:30 am -- The Rememberer 1:00 pm -- Servant of Two Masters 2:30 -- The Crucible 4:30 -- The Quest of Perseus  ______________________________________  And wow, is all I can say.  That's like a powerhouse of excellently done, very affordable theater.  All shows will be performed at Freemont High School, in Sunnyvale. PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE, for the love of all that is good and right in the world PLEASE!!!  Come see us!!  Erm, what I mean is, if you want tickets, I have them for you. Tickets are six dollars for an individual show, and cheaper if you want to see three, four, or all seven different plays.  And tell all your family... and all your friends... shoot, you should even call up random people in the phone book and tell them to come.  That's how good this is going to be.  I'm in Servant of Two Masters, Nick Enge is in The Crucible, and my sister is in A New Age is Dawning.  Just so y'all know.  And seriously, these plays will rock.  IM me on Azeroth172 or give me a call if you are interested in tickets.  I'm always willing to answer questions, as well.  That's all for now.  Buy tickets from me, and I'll love you forever =P.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Woke up really early, after getting to sleep around four am earlier that morning.  Needless to say, that was none too fun.  Went to CTC -- brought swords! Morning classes were very cool.  Looks to be fun in general.  Afternoon:  rehearsal.  Went well. Claire and I basically talked the whole time because neither of us were on and there are only three people our age in the cast, ourselves included.  The other one is Lia, who I for one am none too eager to talk to. So we ran lines and stuff, and talked about school. Rehearsal went sooo slowly, though, until break -- when Nick and I went out to his car and brought in our three swords.  Then things went really fast, all the way to the end.  P.S.:  Damn, my play's gonna rock.  If you want to come see it, let me know.  the first date is july 31st, and then there are two shows on the weekend after that as well.  So then CTC was over.  I crashed at home for a bit, exhausted, but then got up off my ass and went running. Ran pretty hard for five miles.  It felt good, I guess, but difficult.  I wish I were in better shape already. Ah well, that'd take all the competition out of it =P.  After that, I bolted down a quick dinner at home, called Carey's cell and left a message when she didn't pick up, then went out downtown Mountain View with Blythe. Despite the fact that I live here, I really like my downtown.  It's a cool place.  Long story short, Blythe and I hung out for a while, talked a lot, and enjoyed ourselves over both pearl tea and "gelato".  Lord, I miss Italy... with the real stuff, every day.  Mmmm.  So then I got home, and had to be rude and push Blythe out the door because Carey called and I really wanted to talk to her, and it was a bit past one am already on her time zone.  So Blythe, if you see this, I apologize for my rudeness.  But, again no offense, it was worth it.  It was very nice to talk to Carey again, especially when it just occurred to me today that it's been more than a month since I've actually seen her.  Kind of creepy.  Kind of saddening =/.  But I'm going out there!  As if I haven't told everyone already... lol.  Well, I'm really looking forward to it. Can't wait, in fact.  Even flying out the night after the final performance will be worth it. Wheee.  And now it's late again, and I really need sleep.  So to bed I go.  Later, all.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Man, someone should take away my internet connection or something.  I just can't go to sleep, because there's so much going on, and I read about it, and then I think about it... and as if just those weren't enough to keep me up all night, now I can write my opinion about it too.  Well, here goes.  Might as well get this out of the way. This one's about gay marriage, which is an important topic to me as I truly do believe in equal rights for all humans. Which is to say, if one human has the chance to do something, it should be possible for any given human out of the entire population to be able to do it.  That's the ideal, anyway.  So here's the thing about gay marriage, and it spreads  to more than just gay marriage but to marriage in general. Gay marriage has been championed by a few cities such as San Francisco and Portland, along with some minor players in upstate New York and in New Mexico.  It has been  advocated by the Massachusetts state supreme court.   And it has then been most vehemently argued against and venomously denounced by the right-wing idealogues who  currently run this country and the giant band of mostly religion-inspired zealots who follow them.  The Conservative argument seems logical enough, on the surface. They say that marriage is a long-standing tradition with roots in religious and cultural history, and that to arbitrarily  change the meaning of marriage is akin to a crime against humanity, or worse (by their count), a crime against God.  While this  argument does seem to have some legitimacy about it, something  about it has always bothered me, besides the obvious fact that  it goes against gay marriage, an idea which I feel to be a  positive thing.  But tonight, I've hit upon what it is, and it ties into normal marriage as well.  The problem with marriage in general is that it is both a legal status and a religious status.  This, of course, totally violates the concept of 'separation of church and state': that a religious ceremony confers legal benefits upon the  participants seems totally ludicrous if you take it out of context.  So, to those out there who would ban gay marriage, I say to you this: let us create a new type of marriage altogether as a legal institution. Let this marriage be between whomever wishes it upon themselves, and  let it be conferred upon them by a judge or a court official, as it is today in nonreligious ceremonies.  And let this sort of  marriage be available to any who would have it, so as to rid from our  government and our society the spectre of shameless discrimination  that so  threatens our wholeness and our collective well-being today. And let whatever religious institutions object keep their own marriage: the government would never interfere in affairs of religion after all, right?  And if those who various religious institutions would not offer marriage wish more than just the same legal bonding  available to all  others, then let them join the Universalist Unitarian church. Cuz they're cool like that.  Not that anyone needed my thoughts on that, or that two cents  is worth anything nowadays. And if random people come across this, please don't flame me.  It's just a thought.  But yeah --  I figure, if I propose enough solutions to a given situation, eventually one of them will work.  And I dedicate this post to Tess, whose blog brought my  attention to the matter and whose links stole my sleep from me =P  Now to bed.  For real.  I wake up in fewer than four hours.  Goodnight.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Rather, here's the one laying down.  Give me a few days to figure out this software... =P.  Wish I knew HTML... but too many other things going on.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    My new smallsword... on my nice, clean desk.  First shot is of it laying down, second, it standing up.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I never know what to say.  I'm a fairly bright guy.  I speak English well. I can talk for hours and hours and keep conversation relatively interesting.  But at times like these, I never know what to say.  I should be happy for others, and yet part of me can never be that selfless.  I go on doing it, but it hurts.  When it really comes down to it, now, I never know what to say.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, not that I didn't  already  do stuff with it. I went to see Spider-man 2!! Man, it was awesome.  I watched the first one again last night with Scott, who hadn't seen it yet, specifically so that we could go today.  And it certainly didn't disappoint -- I just hope the other five (five?!?) are just as good.  But that's not what this is about.  Right now it's 1:18, and something inside of me is yelling at me to throw on my shoes, bolt out the door, and never look back.  It's not that anything's wrong here... it's just that there's a world out there, that I can see, and yet that I don't feel myself to be a part of.  It's kind of funny.  And I know the same is true for everyone, and it doesn't cause  them  to do wacky things like that, but still... I don't know.  All I'm saying is that it's appealing.  I love nighttime, just in general.  When the night is right, it has a serenity and beauty to it totally unsurpassable by anything to be seen by daylight.  Even when you really should be sleeping because you have to get up before seven tomorrow.  The night also is a unifying force, for me. During the day, I'm always doing things (duh.), but this action causes me to think about what I'm doing and thus focus mainly on myself.  At night, I always think about the other random people out in the world; people I may never know, but who are still under the same night sky, watching the same (half of them, at least) stars as I am, seeing the same moon.  And the lack of activity that comes  before sleep brings peace with it.  I couldn't possibly describe all that I like about it... or pinpoint it all, even if I wanted to.  Suffice it to say that, while I certainly enjoy the sunlit hours, I love nighttime in  an entirely different way.  I had a really interesting spontaneous monologue in Nick's car tonight, while he and Meaghan and I were coming home from the movie.  I hope it's ok if I say it was interesting, considering I was the one who made it up... but it was all about the ideals of respect and love, and how humans don't seem to realize that the only reason they're alive is because of love.  And no, I'm not talking about Jesus:  I don't subscribe to that.  No, I mean good, ol' fashioned human love.  And people don't think about that too often. And yet, all human existance really revolves around love. For instance, look at music.  Pretty much any genre of music you look at, you find love songs, and a whole lot of them. As I made this statement, I flipped through nick's radio, and found that almost all the songs playing were about a girl or guy of some sort, depending on who was doing the singing.  And even classical music, without words, has its own love songs. Take Clair de Lune as an example:  a woman, standing in a white dress at a french window, looks back over her shoulder and smiles at you, silver moonlight glowing off of her white dress and illuminating the flowers in her hand.  *sigh*.  Right, where was I.  Oh yes, the love song.  It's been around forever.  There are plays about love, too.  And paintings, and literature, and poetry (TONS of poetry), and some of pretty much every other art form I can think of.  Hell, I bet there's even  architecture  about love.  And with all that history, with all those past records of intense emotion, I don't think modern society should be able to so shamelessly disrespect and un-love each other.  But these are just my thoughts on the subject.  I don't pretend to know everything =P.  If you have any thoughts regarding the necessity of love to the animal that is the homo sapiens sapiens, go ahead and post 'em up here with mine.  I'd love to see what other people come up with, and what they think of my ideas.  There was more to my thoughts, too -- I'll probably post the rest later, but first I have to consult Meaghan and Nick because now it's late, I'm tired, and I've forgotten what I said two hours ago.  Ah well.  I think that does it for me for tonight.  Goodnight, world.  Back to CTC tomorrow, and I'm sure that'll leave plenty of interesting reading material.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For those of you who don't know, I could be fairly described as both a theater and a medieval fantasy fan.  That said, it  then seems rather natural that I should do what?  That's right: collect swords.  So my newest addition just arrived =).  This, obviously, is a good thing.  I think we might be using it in "Servant of Two Masters", the play I'm currently rehearsaing, and I know we'll need it for "Complete Works..." next fall.  Man, that's gonna be awesome.  As soon as I can figure out how to post pictures, I'll throw some up.  Edit:  I've put the pictures up on my photosite, which also has my Africa pictures, because at least this way I already knew how to do.  If you want to see them, the link is  www.soulsevolution.photosite.com .  I do hope you all will take a look. =)
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I've been meaning to start writing stuff in my life down,  and looks like maybe I've finally gotten around to it.  Hello, world.  My name is Jeff.  I'm a 17 year old with all both the glory and problems that come with that territory. I am, in general, a positive person.  And here I shall first be posting excerpts of my trips both to Africa and to Ashland, and then shall be using it just as a daily blog.  So yes, that'll be fun.  It's almost 3:30, so I'm not actually going to write about today's events right now, but I will start daily writings soon.  Until that time, goodnight.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey all -- I'm back! =)  I had an absolutely fantastic trip.  It was, to use a bit of understatement, very nice.  And now I'm back here, and am in search of something meaningful to do with my next year.  So leave me a note.  Tell me something you've noticed that needs changing.  Basically, I'm looking to change the world somehow.  Give me ideas.  For now, I'll listen to my over-the-top music and smile.  Laugh at myself, maybe.  Love my life.  And then go to sleep.  Goodnight. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In the process of packing...  Lord, am I looking forward to this trip.  So yes.  One more show, one more ushering job, a bunch of eating, laughing, and maybe some tears, and then I'll be on my way.  So I'll talk to you all in... a week?  ish?  Something like that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Oh, Mr. Bush, you've really put your foot in your mouth this time... I've seen you do it before, but this one is impressive.  "Our enemies are innovative and resourceful, and so are we. They never stop thinking about new ways to harm our country and our people, and neither do we."                                                                                       --President George W. Bush  How true.  Anyone know of any good books on the evolution of society in recent years, specifically regarding the growing acceptance of dishonesty and lying since, say, 1980?  I know I've heard of some, just can't think of the titles.  If you have one, let me know about it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CTC Festival part 1 is now complete.  I get four days' rest, and then it's back to rehearsal, and then we have our crazy weekend of love and doom, and then it's all over.  How sad.  I don't know what I'm gonna do next year.  IIT would be fun, but I'll have lost so many friends, I'm just not sure if it'll feel worth it anymore.  It might just feel like high school does, where I'm wondering why the hell I haven't moved on yet.  Well, another year to go to decide, so I guess we'll see when the time comes.  It's really really late/early right now.  I'm tired.  Going to bed.  Just felt like I needed to update.  Maybe tomorrow, I'll post more of what I've been doing each day.  A little retrospective updating never hurt anyone.  Anyway, 'night all. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>