<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      test
     
    
</post>


<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Early off :D...Didn’t feel like working much today anywho. My hip is somewhat hurting. Alkidaa, way back then, ashkii yazhi nishli yee' daa', I got my hip worked on :P. Every now and then my hip hurts like crazy, especially during the winter. Dang especially when I had the metal plate inside, screwed to my bone. That was crazy. I think working out in the "extreme" outdoors, lifting heavy equipment on uneven lands has put a hurt to my hip, just a little. Not so much, but it hurt's whenever I go like this... Yea, just like that.  Well I started the day at 5:30. I fed the livestock, showered, oh and loaded up my aunt's PC(finally finished that job). I went down to the office...walked to the store for coffee and cigarettes(damn, I bought another pack), and waited. Everyone came back from the MCU office(ExxonMobil), jobs were described and handed out. I(we) had an easy one...well there wasn't much a couple of us could do because the truck we use is in the shop getting fixed, something about faulty electrical system...oh, yea, my job was to go out with "birdman" and load up a huge Flange, like 800 lbs or so. I drove(at times jumping/hopping) the back-hoe from the CO2 plant down to the pipe yard, connected all that needed to be, and *beep beep*, it was loaded.  I then got dropped off at the office after everything was ready to go. What we loaded was taken to NM for coating, extra protection on the flange and other pipe that went along. So I stayed at the yard, then left, gassed up...bought a soda...and came back. After I got back, I went down to the corral because my uncle was down there welding. I helped a bit, grinded here and there and lo and behold it was done...a new gate. Not sure what happened to the other one. It looked good to me.  Speaking of welding, I went to my cousin's brother's place(they have different mothers, same father) Sunday evening...I got there and they were welding :D. They made a top shade for the horses. It's not complete...still need the other half. Anywho, I helped with their project. Broke out my math, measured, cut, remeasured, and finally grinded. I didn't do any of the welding there because...well it's not my corral or project. So all I did was cut pieces of metal with the torch. Afterwards we chilled for a bit, had a can, and said "well I'm gonna head out now..." "Alright then, thanks for your help, good to see you again.." was all I heard.  One day I'm going to do a lot with my acquired welding/cutting skills. Just need to learn to shape sheet metal now, then I'm all set. :D Yeppers. Hmm..As I mentioned before sometime ago, I type all my entries beforehand on WordPad before I actually publish whatever it is I write. And right now...I don't have much else to write about...so, I'm going to post this entry now...oh yea, I just found out that I'm lacking one course to obtain a minor in Probability and Statistics. Wish I could say that for Mathematics(both for a major and minor), but dang them upper division courses look tough..Bout 20 credits is all I need of them. 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...a busy week, and the beginning of a somewhat promising weekend. On Friday, we had a safety meeting at 6:00. The topic was on "How to work around H2S Safely." We watched a video on all potential hazards H2S has to offer. Afterwards we trained as if we were in an environment which the SCBA was needed. We all had to use proper steps.  Otherwise, the H2S would get into our system and do what it does best, KILL. The maximum a person can take in(H2S) before he/she falls dead is at 600 ppm's. Anything below could still cause death, but at 600 ppm's you fall dead in your tracks. Around here, the maximum ppm's is 10 ppm's. We have to evacuate our work area when our monitors read/beep at 10 ppm's. Even at this level you can lose your sense of smell, etc. Anyhow I passed all given tests on Friday morning, oh and the required SCBA test as well.  For the past couple of days, we had to do clean up work. We were supposed to do a fiber glass line, but that went to another crew. So the crew I was in did more clean up work, mostly back-hoe work. I guess what happened is Elkhorn shut down their facilities. When they did this, all natural gas produced on Ratherford leases(ExxonMobil) had no where else to go except back into where they came from along with newly produced gas. This pressurized Batteries and satellites. Through this, all incoming chemicals/fluids produced from a pumping unit have no where else to send their fluids, so fluids in these batteries/satellites pressure to their maximum capacity. When this happens, flowlines rupture, seals and gaskets expand and tear, overflow tanks and fractanks overflow, and so on. Lots of pressure, thousands of lbs of pressure. I believe the maximum rating within most facilities out here are set at 10,000 lbs per square inch, according to Quadco's pressure testing.  Anywho, I worked four hours today, Saturday. I was watching "Starsky and Hutch" and the "Birdman" came around, "Do you wanna put in some hours?" I said "sure." We were at Battery 19 for those four or so hours. Sort of kicking back, and cleaning the separators. *L* Cleaning these separators suck, mainly because we have to harness up. Whenever we work above 6 feet off the ground, it's required we wear harnesses. So that was pretty much it, clean up oil stain on the separators and shut in VRUs, ventilator release units’, valves.  Hmm...my sickness has been getting better by the day, as I am writing this entry I'm feeling great, well aside from a few *coughs* here and there. About a month or so I caught pneumonia, and it was sickening. I was told that this sickness can be easily obtained again once you have had it, especially if one is exposed to the cold for a period of time. I'm not sure how this could have been, because it's hot as hell out here. I'm thinking it’s maybe the constant sweating on the job, along with cool breezes every now and then...and maybe a mixture of H2S. I've been working at Area 4 for the past couple days, and that's H2S central, well partially.  I don't know? It seems my throat has been...jacked lately. I think It's something more than a common cold, or pneumonia or whatever. I'm thinking it's something more "hardcore," I don't want to say...but every time I come into contact with smoke or like for instant a small amount of H2S out in the field my oxygen intake feels limited. My throat starts itching and whatnot. I try to cough whatever it is that's making this itch, most of the time it's nothing, then I start with the coughing again. It's weird. Hopefully it goes away soon...  ...It's dark once again. Last night, or rather early this morning I had a Nightwalker experience. Nightwalker meaning...uhh, skinwalker and such. Yea, it was freaky. Honestly, I'm somewhat scared of what tonight will bring me. Last time I had an experience like this was...2 years ago or so. That time I actually saw a dark figure standing over me, mumbling jibberish I couldn't understand. Yup...*shrugs* all I can say is.."Can’t ya'll fuck with someone else?" I wrote this piece after my last experience with these...creatures...persons...whatever they were at that moment. It goes like this...  *SKINWALKER* Creature of the darkness living to kill dwelling on the innocent brainwashing the mind claiming what you think is yours all the envy inside you haunting human targets using the prayer of hatred out for blood loyal to evil so hypnotic no one knowing what a killer looks like im caged in a rage take one take two brainwashed into burning blood bleeding for days living to die dying to live inside my soul I wont back down cant get you off my mind slowly rotting away the difference so close to me these streaks of blood the beast of modern death whats on your mind you got me to hell and back ive been im trapped in a dream flying in this blue delusion blue light turning red in the end your dead to us all I now awake Copyright &copy 2004 SJohnson 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Where to begin...Since yesterday I have been extremely busy, I started actual oil field work. I must say "Wow. I can't believe I actually missed this line of work." It's also cool that I have been placed in my cousin and uncle's crew, Errol and Spencer. Before I got there, started work for the company, they were working on cleaning up a spill that occurred at location 2-11-B. Today was the last day on that job.  It’s complete. Onto what's next on the list (fiberglass line at Area 6).  So, yea...since yesterday I have been helping with the final clean up in that area (2-11-B). Mostly Back-hoe work, back dragging and what not. Since there were three in our group, we all took turns operating the back-hoe (I still know how to operate :D). Kinda funny because we could only fit one back-hoe in that area, so when one was operating the machine, two persons kicked back in the truck, doing nothing *L*. Anywho, that area is along the river. We had to use extreme caution because of all the flow-line that run through the area. One mishap and the San Juan River would be polluted with either gas, oil, or salt water.  Well I got off early today, at 5:00 or so. I went to my aunt at the counseling center. This is where her office is at. The other day she asked if I could clean up her computer (A company system). So I went there to do this, but she was working with a patient and I offered to take her PC home with me and I can work on it here. All went OK, until she couldn't find the OS disk. Because of that, I couldn't work on her system. So I left for home without the tower. I'll probably work on this when she does find the disk.  I got home and started on cleaning up the house and what not, finished this and started to write an entry for my blog...I do all my writing on WordPad before I post it on my blog. I was a bit tired so I laid down on the couch and fell asleep, spaced my entry I was typing. I slept for two hours or so, got up at 8:15 and was like "whoa," thinking "huh?" I got out of that daze and remembered the "aminals," and walked down to the corral and fed them. I also took apples for the horses, *crunch* *crunch* is all I heard.  Altogether we have 14 cows, four bulls, and four horses...oh, and nine sheep :P. I killed a lot of our sheep with the latest batch of hay we've had. Pure alfalfa...sheep can't really handle all that protein I guess. Our cows, hmm...only two or three of them have papers, registered. The rest are reservation cows, cows without papers :P. All the bulls are registered, and are used for breeding purposes only. Yet local stock contractors still come around asking if our bulls are for sale. We have four horses. Only one is registered, the Arabian, "Dynasty M Dancer." The other three, despite their good bloodline are not registered.   We've tried to get the Arabian impregnated, just to have another pure bred Arabian around the corral. Twice, a $1000 stud fee was paid, but to no avail, no lil "horsie." All I can say is...*Hmm*. In the horse industry this type of service can range from...in the low hundreds for a stud that doesn't have a “good” bloodline up to...heck thousands, or even up into the hundred thousands for a good bloodline. That would be cool though, to have a stud fee for your services *L*. Money in the pocket :P.  Our "aminals" are always kept in the corral, in their pens. Only time they get to be out is when they go to the pasture. It's kind of a good thing to keep them in the corral/pens when they are out here because they don't contribute to overgrazing like some other peoples livestock. One time, way back then, it was...ugly looking out this way due to overgrazing. I don't know what happened, all of a sudden there were fewer livestock out there roaming and grazing wherever. And now it's starting to look...really nice out this way, green and colorful with native plants, bushes, etc.  Whoa. Yea...Anyhow, I'm actually starting to feel a whole lot better. Mainly because I keep myself busy with whatever I'm doing at the present moment. Working with Errol and Spencer also contribute to myself “feeling better” as well. When we're just sitting around, they talk crazy nonsense in Navajo, and it just makes me laugh. I don't know..."Laughter is the best medicine" I guess :P. I don't know what else to say. Wish I could keep writing about this and that, but that would only take more time and I need that time to sleep and rest for tomorrow. 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I decided to work in the oil field despite the crazy fee, well not so crazy. Since the company is really close with the Drug and Alcohol Testers, I got a discount, half price. I hear its going to be the same with McGuire Industries :D. This is the company that issues H2S certifications. Since I've already been certified, in 2001, this refresher course won't take long. I will be doing this tomorrow, Tuesday.   Today I met with the safety representative for JR construction. I had to fill out an employment packet, which included 50 somewhat pages of Safety Issues and guidelines. This took about an hour. Afterwards I drove out to Cortez Colorado to take my Drug/Alcohol Test. I sped out there because I was running a bit late, got there on time, pissed in a cup, signed papers, and sped out of there. A funny thing happened to me while I was there waiting to sign papers...a bit weird, but funny. Sort of *wow, are they really this nice* kind of thing, or *hmm, I think I was just hit on* kind of thing. *shrugs* Anywho, I got back into MC, UT., at 12:00 or so, sat around for a while at the office (I can't go out into the field yet, my H2S hasn't been updated)...Then played the role of a mechanic/electrician until the 'part' was fully installed (Lighting harness wired from inside the motor compartment along the frame to the end of the truck). I got back home around 3:00, got online to check email, chatted with Chelle and Mel for a bit, got a call, was like "oh crap," and took off for Cortez again. There I picked up materials for a landscaping job I have to do. Had dinner, then came straight home...fed the "aminals"...and took a short nap (Was up since 5:00 a.m. :P). What a day(Two trips into town in one day)...tiring...*yawn*    

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   What to do...I've been thinking. School is going to be back in session August/September. This will be my final year. I'll be taking three classes over a period of two semesters, three classes...Then I'm done. I will have completed all requirements for a Bachelors degree in Computer Science Information Systems, with a minor in Sociology. The thing that sucks is the structure of courses at the college. For example a course being offered one semester throughout the entire school year...or a course offered a semester every other school year...an odd/even year type of deal. This has screwed up my original graduation date. I was actually supposed to have been done in May of last year. But since I took a year and a half off of school to work in the oil field, that date was pushed back another year and a half. So I was supposed to be done completely this December. I ran into...hell, I don't know what I ran into...but it's these damn courses with the odd/even year deal. So one of the three required courses I need will be taken during the winter semester of 2005. Which is all right I guess...A kick back semester. &nbsp; This wasn't what I intended to write...The reason why I've been thinking is because...Since this is my last year of school, I was hoping to concentrate on these last two semesters. For the past two semesters I've been taking upper division CSIS courses...and hell they aren't as easy as they seem. Honestly, my schooling has been like shit these past two semesters. I have dropped out of the Dean's list. Each upper CSIS courses taken these last two semesters I have passed with C's and one B. I'm thinking if I really focus on these remaining three courses and pass them with A's, I could get back on the Dean's list. I'm not sure how this will go, time will tell. I'm the one to blame for this...downfall, or whatever it might be called. *L* I just can't believe I actually passed those classes without even opening the required text books. If I were to have read from the text books, then the outcome would have been a lot different. I guess I can't really rely on my...what I have learned long ago and still remember method. I don't know, this method worked wonders for me in the Mathematics field...hmm, I'm 20 credits away from completing requirements for a degree in mathematics, I wonder...I better not. &nbsp; Hmm, sidetracked again. Anyhow, I need to focus on these remaining two semesters...I've been thinking if I should ask a certain person if we could take time off...I have my mind set on school, then again with what's going on within in my family, and other stuff I can't get my mind off of at this point. My mind at this point is cluttered with a lot of stuff. I'm not sure how to go about this...questions will arise...answers. I mean if that person understands I'm guessing it would be ok...then after I'm done with school, after things settle within my family, and others work out, we could do away with the time off. I'm just worried I might lose this person...which I don't want to happen. Damn, all this stuff, it's enough to break a person down. I'm just trying to stay focused and on track of my surroundings on a daily basis, "one day at a time." I've broke down before and it sucks@ss...barely made it out of that hole...not completely, but still living to this day. I just don't want to bring this person into what's going on in my life up to this point. I've been hiding my "blah" thus far, it can't go on like this...I don't know, maybe I shouldn't say anything. &nbsp; Well this past weekend I had the option of spending time with family. Family from my dad's side invited me to go camping in telluride. A birthday outing for my cousin, "Jhah." "Maybe" was my answer. I didn't go. Saturday evening was my other cousin’s birthday on my mom's side. Again "maybe" was my answer. Again I didn't go. It seems lately I've been staying away from family. Well after what happened, this started. Sometime between then and now I did mention that I would in fact keep away from family for a while, just to be alone, and think. I'm not sure how long I'm going to do this. Not much longer I'm sure. The only person I associate with now is my little brother. We talk, laugh, play guitar/bass, and make up all sorts of stuff, musically. I'm happy to be spending time with him. So instead of going to these happenings, I stayed home...chilled with my little brother. We drove around, here and there, watched kung fu movies (corrected mistakes in the actors' form :P), took turns caring for the livestock...basically that's it. A kick back weekend.  July...three or four more birthdays this month (within my family), including mine :P. I'll be 23 at the end of the month, on the 31st. I probably won't do anything...Another day of the year, another year to my life. Yea...Dang, 23...K'ad daats'i Hastiin salii *L* :P   Here's a lil something... &nbsp; *Tired and Alone*  Take a good look  I know what you see  shot in the back  left behind  livin through the day  dead and buried is the joy I once found  as I walk this world tired and alone  got one foot in the grave  no time to rest  refuse to bleed  no end in sight  the loss of hope  the loss of friends  nothings going to change  the more they do  the more they're the same  forever wanting more  starting all over again  now that ive seen  what has come and past  forget all that is pure  it never lasts  one can't deny  kill your past and all that you knew  in the end we find whats true  take your time  sooner or later you'll find your place  Copyright © 2004 SJohnson  

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I took this writing from a friends blog with her "OK"...just because I thought it was really good. Here it is...&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  ******************************************************&nbsp;  &nbsp;  The Insanity I have created...   There are days when I wake up and I feel so alone that its like I'm being sucked into some kind of vortex that I will never get out of. I fight, I cry, I try and I try to escape that feeling, yet it persists. But today, today was different. I woke up with that feeling...like I was being pulled into something that I knew I would never escape, then the miracle of friendship happened. Yes, I have friends, and while I have never touched them, or hugged them, or kissed them on the cheek, great friends they are. They are but a font on a computer screen...yet they are so so much more than that. They are the ones I can tell anything to and have no fear that they will desert me. They are the ones I can pour my heart out to, and I know that they will understand, or if they don't, then they will try to. They are the ones who are like me, sitting in front of their computers, searching as I am, for the ones that will do for them,&nbsp; as they do for me. They are loved and needed...and I dont know what I would do without them.  &nbsp;  This world is such an odd one. Here I sit, in front of my computer, typing out a spiel that I'm not sure will be read or not...and yet I still do it. I go into chat rooms, I am greeted by cyber hugs and kisses, and the occasional lick, and I feel wanted and liked and needed. The words I type bring laughter to some,&nbsp; anger to some, disgust to others...yet...I do not leave. In this life, the one called reality, if I brought anger to another person, I'd likely get an ass kicking for the things I freely say in that world of chat.  &nbsp;  Some think I'm a touch insane for living so much of my life in this world...but I think they are small minded individuals for thinking such things. The fonts I see on the screen are put there by real people...flesh and blood human beings who have feelings and wishes and dreams just as I do. They aren't unreal, they are&nbsp;at times&nbsp;more real than those who I know in this thing called reality. Had I not discovered this world, I would have missed out on so many friendships that I find I cannot do without...and I would have missed out on a love unlike any other.  &nbsp;  I am thankful for my chat friends...I have turned to them so many times to help me make it through my days and they have always pulled, pushed or dragged me through that vortex I would almost get lost in. So my friends...always know that you are appreciated,&nbsp;you are needed and most of all, you are loved. Thank you so much for being my backbone at times...or for giving me laughter when I needed it the most, or for offering me much needed reassurance that above all, I am not the horrible&nbsp;person I sometimes feel I am. I treasure you...  &nbsp;  "Alone is not a bad way to be; it clears your mind&nbsp;and focuses you on the journey. Cherish the short intervals during the quest you have with others, but be prepared to walk alone in the darkness."  &nbsp;  ******************************************************&nbsp;  Her writings never cease to amaze me...oh, and here's a quickie that&nbsp;I just wrote. A bit cheesy...but oh well. I have other writings that are half done or less than half done. I need to get back to these...mind block is a bitch.&nbsp; &nbsp;  *DOWN*  Alone in the darkness  is this all I need  what can I say  is this how its going to be  need to get fucked  do you feel that&nbsp;deed  say it aint so  is this really creed  Fuck it all  just let me bleed  I ask you  could you take the lead  Copyright © 2004 SJohnson     

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Damn, $120 for a refresher course, and another $90 for a drug screen, a $210 fee. I'm having second thoughts now. Since I'm going to be part-time, and only going to be working for a month and a half, the safety rep of the company said that I might be paying this fee out of my own pocket. I guess only full-time peeps have their courses and screening paid for. Seems only fair because moving along in time, long term/full-time employees pay back to the company what the company pays for them. It goes something like this...the company charge the oil/gas companies around $22 an hour for a person ($22 an hour usually being the top pay around here for experienced peeps), and that person is only paid half of that $22 charged, or more (peeps with the years and years of experience...the ones making somewhere around $18-20 an hour), or less (peeps with less experience which are paid between $7-9 an hour), depending on that persons experience. What the company charges to the company they work for also depends on the experience of the person being used, it could range from $16 and hour to $22 an hour. Anyhow, the reason why I'll be paying out of my own pocket is...basically because I'm not going to make enough money for the company working part-time and for a month and a half or so. *shrugs*   I'm having second thoughts on this because...well I was going to work there just to earn some school money. The last couple of months I've been spending my savings because of the incident that happened within my family and I don't have much left in my account. And I'll be using more of my savings to pay for these course/screening fees. I need the money that’s in my account now and the money I was suppose to make during the next month and a half for school and other important stuff. I was also planning on taking a trip sometime in the fall...I don't think that will be happening now. *argh* money sucks @ss. Well "Dick Fuckin All"...*said best by a friend of mine*...*L* I guess for now self-contracting will do.  

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Another early morning entry..fuck, I can't sleep. I tried working on my template for my blog. It sucks that it has to be written in the style of object oriented programming...even though html isn't considered programming. What the FUCK! Anywho, I think I have lots on my mind. Earlier I was writing a song on being brainwashed. I have the guitar part somewhat down. Not sure if I want to use the riffs I came up with for this piece. The lyric itself isn't done yet...so, yea. Damn it Shit to Hell...I'm just pissed. Why? Why?...Fuckers!!! When this song is done with...and eventually gets into an album...hell, the credit is going to read..."This is to that fucked up family..." or something along those lines. My lil brother once said, "If shit goes down like this again...I'm going out there and gonna start blasting away..." That's been on my mind as well...so yea, next time (I hope there will be a no next time), oh yea...I'm there standing beside my lil brother. I always wondered what it would be like to do something like this.   Yea...well I was told to come in today, Friday, to check in with the safety rep. She has to see if my H2S and 9 element cards are still valid. It's been 2 years since I used them. Might have to take a refresher course. Monday is when I officially start. I'll be working part-time, thank god. Doubt I could take full-time in this weather, especially with the skin condition that I have. I got an insight of what I'll be doing. I'll be going out to this location called Area 6 with a small crew. We'll be doing patch-up work with fiberglass. Last time I did that was at Area 4 with a co-worker and it sucked, just because we had to dangle by harnesses attached to overflow tanks and all the itching afterwards. Oh well...I'm ready.   Something cheesy...   *UNTITLED*  message in blood  engraved in flesh  you call my name  you want me to play this game   kill death kill  all for the fukin thrill  come a lil closer  a lil closer   whos got my back  im not the one to blame  fuck this  i'm dead to the world  trapped inside my own  a noose around my neck  what the fuck?   kill death kill  all for the fukin thrill  a lil closer  closer   there's no time  stand here with me  as I take one last breath  before I die  save me from myself  set me free  Copyright © 2004 SJohnson 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   *DUNDUN DUNDUN DUDUDUDUDUNNDUN DUNDUN DUDUDUN*...ahh...music, there is no way I can type out what I hear. I guess I could go with A #A #D #D #D or whatever...but that doesn't bring out the...err...feeling *L*. Anywho, I just got back from the corral, smelling a bit like manure. Last night the bulls broke out of their pens. The Brangus tried to get to the Brahma, to play or fight, whatever it is bulls do. During the process I guess the Brangus broke down a couple of the re-bars that kept the Brahma from the main pen, or it might have been the other way around. Didn't see this until this morning when feeding the "aminals." It was dark by the time we chased the "aminals" back into their correct pens yesterday evening. So I was there working on that this morning. I guess I could pull the welder down there and weld them back together, but it's not my corral and I don't want to do anything to it without my uncle's consent. So I used bailing wire and twine *L*. *JIN JIN JINJINJINJIN JIN JIN WIERWIERWIER JIN JIN* *L* that's all I hear I tell ya. If you make this out you can actually bring/sound out the distortion. *L* I'm just being a dork. I'm listening to Korn and Black Label Society.  Yesterday I was informed that my former boss might contact me sometime today. No word from him yet. Right now I hear it's really busy out in the field. This guy is cool, I mean most people with supervisor/owner positions around this area don't go out into the oil field and work, get dirty. People with those positions usually overlook a project from a distance or through one of their main peeps. They're the type who sits in their office chair and do whatever it is they do all day, and around here it's usually just kicking back and acting "BIG," which amounts to nothing. My former boss, now he's way different. He's the opposite of these "BIG" peeps. Since he's the opposite of these peeps, and it's busy out there, I know I won't hear from him until the end of the day...between 4-5. So in the meantime I'm going to wash this manure smell stuff off and afterwards head down to my cousin's. He wants me to take him to estimate a roof...might end up helping him with this project.  "Its like a grizzly bear sleeping. Its been poked in the face enough times with a fuckin stick. Its ready to start killing people now..." *Zakk Wylde on Music* 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I Never thought writing could be so addictive. It's been awhile since I wrote...what I've been writing. Usually my writings are source codes for programs, documentation for source codes, and all that has to do with creating Software. Since I started this blog, it seems I've been posting on a daily basis, about what I do...or whatever I write about at that time. I've been posting for the past 3 days, I'm sure sometime in the near future this blog will be ignored and abandoned.  Oh yea, something worth posting :P. Turns out "Somehow" the bulls got out of their pens yesterday evening (Wednesday night). My uncle asked me to help chase them in. I was being all cool about...handling them how they should be handled...and here comes my uncle with the whip *CRACK*. I was standing near the entrance to one of the pens and the herd of cows/bulls ran my way. I jumped out of the way just in time, another second and I would have been gored. That would have sucked...wonder what that would have felt like *shrugs* I still have years ahead of me to find out. The rest of the time I was being more cautious. I bet I would make a good rodeo clown. Yea, my uncle went crazy with that whip though...I was just like "Easy..." Right now them bulls/cows are people friendly. Anyone could go up and pet them. But more of them whippings, hell they’d go crazy and wouldn’t be people friendly anymore. And that wouldn't be good.  Another Something...  *DEMOLITION MAN* The damage has just begun a fist to the mouth a kick to the jaw bleed once bleed twice bleed mother fucker bleed have you lost your fuckin mind? what you do fight yourself beyond empty feeling dead as the day before now look at you torn to the flesh torn to the bone torn and splattered face it you were born to lose I beg you to stop before you descend into your grave fuck it fuck you I thank you punk everyday you shall fall feel the pain up until my final hour at last the end Copyright © 2004 SJohnson  

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   A friend of mine came around this evening. He said that he heard about my brother and was just wondering about his condition. "He's doing good...really good to be exact...just wish he realizes the place he's at isn't good for him," I responded. He responded with "I saw that girl’s mom and she asked if I knew about Brandon...I told her no I didn't.” He then said “she said this is what happened...”...I tried to tell her “No, don’t say that to me...but she kept saying it to me in my face...and I told her that it was probably his girlfriend and your family that made him do it.” Her response he says was “No, it’s not our fault...it’s his family...” After he said this I thought “here we go with the blaming again.” I mean the way I see it my brother is fully brainwashed...under that girl and her family’s control or whatever. He believes what they tell him...it’s a bunch of bullshit that’s all I can say. Every person we talk to say the same thing, “Why is he out there with that family? That family is no good...etc.” Wish I could say more, but I’ll just leave it as that.  Oh yea, I now know what it's like going from low E to high E then back to low E...it's amazing what one can do with a guitar. 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today is the day I was going to check in...into rehab. *L*...I can only wish. No, my former boss from two years ago or so asked if I could work for him again because he was short handed. He owns JR Construction, which contracts with oil and natural gas giants such as Chevron Texaco Inc., ExxonMobil, Elk Horn Operating Company, US Oil & Gas, Harken Southwest Corp. (also known as Rim Southwest), Giant Industries Inc., and Tricore. There are also other smaller companies, privately owned. It’s hard to believe all these companies fit into this tiny area. Well not so tiny, it's pretty much spread out, ExxonMobil and Chevron Texaco having the most leases, acreage-wise. US Oil & Gas also has a huge lease, but they’re located in the canyon area. Harken...hmm, they have smaller leases south of where I live, scattered. They also have leases down in Arizona. Elk Horn is based northwest of here, right along the mesa. Giant Industries is located in the town of Montezuma Creek. Not sure where Tricore is located. Private owned companies have leases way out in the middle of nowhere, places hard to get to. Places where not a lot of oil and gas are produced, 10-20 barrels a day, compared to 10,000 barrels or so produced daily by ExxonMobil, and Chevron Texaco.   When I started with JR Construction, I was a roustabout, an inexperienced laborer. I worked my way to an operator, then started my training as a field technician, also known as a "pumper." Somewhere between being an operator and my training as a field technician I also went through training at the Gas Plant. The Gas Plant is located in Aneth, UT...a property of ExxonMobil, not Aneth but the Gas Plant. That place is very wicked. It’s like a tiny city way out in the desert that looks like Gotham City. At night it's like something from a zombie flick *L*...as cool as that sounds, that place is very dangerous. If a glitch were to happen, *BOOM*...left with a huge crater. The Gas Plant is the Central station. This is where all oil, gas, and water go for the separation process. Out in the field there's smaller separators and whatnot at locations called Satellites, Batteries, Areas, and Sections, but the Gas Plant is where all the action takes place. After the entire separation process each fluid flow in their own destined flowline and out of the area into New Mexico. Oh I forgot to mention, during my time with JR Construction I mainly worked with ExxonMobil. I have gone out to work with these other companies mentioned, but ExxonMobil is the one I stuck with.   Anyhow, I'm not sure what I'll be doing when I get hired on again. I already talked with my former boss (soon to be boss again), and mentioned to him that I will be going back to school at the end of August, and he was like "oh yea, that’s cool, it's going to work out." So I will be working for a month and a half, I just need to check in. That was my plan for this morning, but yesterday evening I went to Durango to pick up my hard hat, Steel-toed boots, and my work clothes. I left Durango about midnight, and got back here at around 2:00 this morning. I didn't go to sleep until 3:00 or so. I set my alarm for 5:45, I woke up at 8:00, my aunt called then and I looked at the clock and I was like DAMN. Then I fell asleep again...phone again, :D it was Ana, she was on her break. I talked to her for a couple of minutes. Afterwards I sat around strumming my guitar. I need to re-string my guitar :P.   On a good note, I will be still doing self-contract work, only on weekends though. Mostly landscape work. It pays well, just because I set my own wage :P   

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today is a good day. Woke up this morning feeling...Yeah! Bring It On! Nothing yet so far. Anywho, yesterday I got to see my brother again for the first time. There was a rumor started that he was stolen from the hospital at the beginning of this past weekend. It got me worried. I wanted to see him just to make sure that he was ok and doing good up to this point. Because of this rumor, things were said between family and I was sort of put on the spot. It wasn't good. I said what I had to say and took off for the weekend just to be away from this place. I went down to Arizona...Myself, my uncle, and another uncle hauled and rode horses for those two days. It was to dang hot, 120-degrees, but fun. Yea, yesterday my aunt came around and suggested to my mom to look into investigation firms so they can search for my brother's whereabouts. I said to them, "heck before you do that we should go to that place and ask the family on that side if they know anything about what’s going on." I drove out there to my brothers gf's place, knocked on the door..And who comes out to me? My brother..I was shocked and surprised. Altogether I spent about 3 1/2 hours talking with him..My lil brother included as well. It was a great afternoon/evening.  As for today, I'm not sure what I'm going to be doing. I think later this evening I'll be going back to Durango. Right now it’s too hot to do anything outside. Usually I'd be outside in this weather doing a lot of stuff from welding, too caring for the livestock, and building whatever. Since I was out in the 120-degree weather this past weekend im too red and burned to be outside now. That will be my excuse to work on the layout for this blog I created. Cheap but "pretty good alright." :D that’s all for now. Here's a lil something...  *INDIFFERENCE* I now feel the end everything seems so real a sad image to see I walk these dirty lands feeling the hatred of the world I will not follow your rules living life for my own I guide my internal self trying to change my ways look at me following the steps that lay ahead seeking new paths what and where ive been will never return I walk on this path made of ideas everything around me a void stepping on skulls of generations that have not formed to create everything from emptiness to awaken the buried and teach the new  deep and well defined an undetermined but straight path created what ive seen and heard will never return now I live life with indifference Copyright © 2004 SJohnson 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Cool. I now have my own blog. I doubt there will be much posted on this thing..Then again I may be wrong. *shrugs* I figure I'll post whatever...Probably mostly my writings, lyrics/poems or whatever. Not sure what they're called, but they seem more...Poetry structured I guess, but I call them lyrics. With that said, I will post my first "BLEH" that I wrote out of boredom. Oh, it's untitled..Haven’t thought of a title yet. I will someday. I've also got the music that goes along with this piece, not recorded, but in my mind. It's bad@ss. I will also be working on my template or whatever for this blog, right now it is cheesy looking. In a couple of weeks it should be better. I don't have much else to say, except that I had a fucked up weekend..*FUCKERS*  *UNTITLED* Once again Im just killing time Just throwin it all away Left behind Im bored to tears Too numb to cry I am hated Living through hells wrath Aint life grand 22 steps to nowhere the damage has begun hey you peddlers of the night bringer of termination what the hell are you lookin for you wont find it here no way... the things you do I refuse to bowdown fuck you fear me I am stronger than death Copyright © 2004 SJohnson 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...*L*...some crazy bullshit. My time was spent Saturday evening in Window Rock AZ in hopes of seeing/hearing Soulfly perform. This wasn't the case. The outcome was "Fuck Soulfly!" I don't know what to say about these type of performances on the reservation with major headlining artists such as Soulfly or any other "big named" bands. Personally I don't think they should have these types of events on the reservation...should stick with LOCAL acts only. Mainly because the lil towns in which they have these events are small, not enough audiences (unless of course it is known that there will be a huge audience). Peeps have to come from distance towns just to see these acts (three hours for us). I feel major artists should stick with cities or bigger towns, just because they have the numbers to fill venues, etc. That's just my opinion. Well I had no feelings whatsoever about what had happened. My thoughts were "I'll see them in the future." And despite what others feel/think about Soulfly (out of those who witnessed what happened), I still think they are a great band and will continue to enjoy their music. Oh, and at least I got half of my money back :P  While we were there, we ran into Hear Lies Treachery and Swell Chemistry. What's cool about running into them was....well at first I recognized the natives in the group...I was like "hey, you’re *insert band name here*" for both bands...and the entire band turns around and are...heck, helluva cool, shaking hands and talkative...unlike other bands where your like "hey, you’re..." and only one of the members turns and are like "hey." So yea, that was cool. I think both performed a great set...better than the rest I think. There's a lot more to mention about this event...but I won't go into details.  I'm thinking of adding music to my blog..but I don't know of any host sites where I can convert MP3s to .wav files. There are probably simpler ways to do this...I know there are peeps who view this blog of mine...and I guess right now I'm asking for help from whoever reads this blog and knows a bit more about what I'm trying to do here. Email details to jkd_johnson@yahoo.com. I don't have much else to say...I should post this entry now, and work on putting music on this thing. 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...Tired and Alone...Oh, If it leads me to you." *great song* Yup, well I'm just here chillin, typin, and sippin...a pepsi that is. Don't do that other stuff anymore :P Well work has been busy...really busy. Heck, I'm happy. Dang, this evening I was one weak F!@&%#. I got off work and fell asleep. When I woke, I went down to the corral and fed the animals. I was all being tough and *UGGH* "what happened to me strength?" So I spent more time down there than the usual time I spend there. I guess that's the disadvantage of work being really busy, oh well. I was reading/skimming ExxonMobil's overview...this is how it is exactly written.  **********  OVERVIEW OF THE MCU/RU FIELD AREA OPERATIONS   The ExxonMobil owned and operated properties in the McElmo Creek and Ratherford field areas are located in southeastern San Juan County, Utah near the towns of Aneth and Montezuma Creek. The BLM and Navajo Nation have jurisdiction over producing operations. The Navajo EPA and Region 9 Federal EPA have jurisdiction over environmental concerns.  The Ratherford Area has facilities that are under secondary oil recovery, through the use of water injection to extract additional hyrdocarbons. The MeElmo Creek Area has facilities that are under tertiary oil recovery, through the use of Carbon Dioxide injection to recover additional hydrocarbons. Tertiary recovery involves the injection of both water and carbon dioxide (CO2) into the production reservoir. This is generally done on an as needed basis at injection pressure of approximately 3000 psig.  At present McElmo Creek has approximately 173 producing and 127 injection wells currently operating. The Ratherford approximately 97 producing and 74 injection wells currently operating. McElmo Creek and Ratherford total production currently stands at:  	10,000 barrels of crude per day 	12,000 standard cubic ft gas per day 	36,000 barrels of producing water per day  Facilities in the McElmo Creek and Ratherford Area include:  	(2) Water Injection Plant 	(6) Production Tank Batteries 	(20) Production Test Satellites  The facilities are used to separate the produced fluids (gas, carbon dioxide, water, and oil) meter and measure qualities and quantities, and then either transfer or sell the production.  The hydrogen sulfide (H2S) concentration in the McElmo Creek and Ratherford Area Operations casinghead gas varies from approximately 80 to 3,000 ppm. H2S concentrations will be higher at all tank battery crude storage tanks and production satellites. Area where the H2S concentration is greater than 10 ppm (OSHA action level) are posted with warning signs.  The production office for the McElmo Creek and Ratherford area is located: 1.5 miles northwest of the Aneth Mustang on highway 262 then 3 miles North on the McElmo Creek Injection Plant lease road. ********** Umm, "Yeah, OK." The company I work for just got fined 5.5 million dollars. Dumb@sses. There's an article of it in The Navajo Times and in our local newspaper, The San Juan Record. Goes something like this...  **********   Multi-million settlement reached over oil spills on Utah Navajo lands   SAN FRANCISCO - The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency and the U.S. Department of Justice on Tuesday announced a settlement with Mobil Exploration and Producing U.S. Inc. for spills from its oil production activities on the Navajo Nation in southeastern Utah.  The $5.5 million settlement includes a $515,000 penalty and requires the company to spend about $4.7 million on field operation improvements to reduce spill incidences, according to a press release from the U.S. EPA.  Mobil will spend approximately $327,000 on environmental projects that include sanitation facilities and construction of a drinking water supply line extensions that will provide running water to 17 residences located on the oil production fields.  Currently, local residents may drive as long as an hour to fill 55-gallon drums with drinking water.  In March 1998, the EPA and the U.S. Department of Justice filed a lawsuit claiming that between December 1991 and March 1999 approximately 83 spills at Mobil's oil fields reached tributaries of the San Juan River - a violation of the federal Clean Water Act.  Mobil's oil production fields are located on both sides of the San Juan River in southeast Utah on lands leased from the Navajo Nation.  The EPA worked closely with the Navajo Nation Environmental Protection Agency in addressing the spills, which the Navajo Nation EPA first brought to the EPA's attention in 1996.  ********** All I can say is Wow. I'm actually one of the few that are working out in the field improving facilities and locations. Mainly replacing old flow lines, all types of valves, and what not. I guess I could say I'm doing a good thing for my community :P Wish they could do something about the pollution in the air though. The air we breath is sickening at times.  Well just thought I'd post all this crap...since I have nothing better to do at the moment. 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ...those were the last words I heard from Ana. My thoughts on this...I'm not entirely sure. I'm not sure what she means by this, either temporarily or permanently. All I can say is "I should've kept my mouth shut." "You’re too good for me" she says. I disagree, I'm just being me is all. Darn, I wish I could talk/ask her what she meant by this. No, I think I should just leave it be. In the end I guess it will work out to where we’re both happy. "When you find something that works you don't look back," a saying by Zakk Wylde. I guess I could live with this...Something I wrote for her awhile back...  *MY CONFESSION* Two different people so close yet so far apart all the things you say and do Could you promise me? Would you keep your word? never letting it go I carry your love this never ending feeling it gets me through thinking about you everyday wishing you were here how I long to be in your presence so close by your side taking me higher and higher the feeling of a human touch seeing the comfort in your eyes the warmth inside your smile tears of joy falling but you can’t see I awake to quite nights this isn’t the first nor the last I can’t get enough of your love I just want to love you a prayer once whispered now answered one step closer forever and ever until the end you're all and everything to me you know we will always be I'm glad I found a friend in you  close your eyes between you and me tell me what’s on your mind? Copyright &copy 2004 SJohnson  ...I relate somewhat to this song now. This piece is written by Zakk Wylde...  ( No Other)  Stoned once again How long has it been? Oh, there can be no other My ever constant fix For in the stream which drowns my sin Oh, there can be no other   Oh, could I be wrong, could I be wrong, oh no Oh, it's where I fear I belong Oh, I've lost myself along the way Oh, yeah, ain't got nothing left to say I've burnt my bridge to the past And I buried my broken bones How I long for what I once had known  Cinder blocks and chains Laid by the insane Oh, there can be no other Worthless to the core Diseased forever more Oh, there can be no other  Oh, could I be wrong, could I be wrong, oh no Oh, it's where I fear I belong Oh, I've lost myself along the way Oh, yeah, ain't got nothing left to say I've burnt my bridge to the past And I buried my broken bones How I long for what I once had known  Oh, could I be wrong, could I be wrong, oh no Oh, it's where I fear I belong Oh, I've lost myself along the way Oh, yeah, ain't got nothing left to say I've burnt my bridge to the past And buried my broken bones How I long for what I once had known How I long for what I once had known How I long for what I once had known  ...  Well I just finished playing the guitar. In one of my past entries I stated that it's been a while since I played the darn thing. I put in 30 minutes or so, mainly working on my speed and precision. It turns out I still kick@ss. Oh yea, I saw my friend Dennis of W.E.S. He gave me a flier of the "WINDOW ROCK FEST," and I told him that I would buy tickets from him at the end of next week. $30 dollars...The Navajo Times advertise it as $25, hmm. I think I'll be taking my lil brother, seeing that he's a hardcore music fan. Should be...Fun? Something worth checking out.   I'm listening to him play the guitar as I'm typing this entry(my lil brother). He's gotten pretty darn good...I guess that's what you get living and learning from the best :P. His style is a lot different from what I play. He's more into the hardcore metal stuff; Six Feet Under, Cannibal Corpse, Slayer, and the likes of them. While on the other hand I'm more on the side of Black Label music, Hard Heavy Rock. As he puts it, "we're pure iron...fuck that nu-metal shit..." :D  When I first started the guitar, about six years ago or so, I started by playing Metallica and Pantera stuff. First song I mastered was "Welcome Home Sanitarium." As I progressed through the years, my style changed. After Metallica and Pantera, I went on to the styles of Stevie Ray Vaughan and Jimi Hendrix. Then to Steve Vai, Joe Satriani...and to now present day Black Label Society, a.k.a. Zakk Wylde. Well these named are major influences, but there are others such as Eric Clapton, Eric Johnson, Yngwie Malmsteen, and so on.  Oh yea, I also play the bass and the drums. The bass I just recently started playing, going on two years or so now. The drums...hmm I've been banging the crap out of drums since the 7th grade. My friend Dennis taught me all that I needed to know as a beginning drummer, and I picked up the rest along the way through the years. I also play other percussion instruments. I started piano lessons, then stopped. I guess that's it on instruments that I can play...   The band I'm trying to start now, or want to start, will be in the style of BLS. Right now I have nine songs written and half of those nine songs I have the music on the guitar. Hopefully when I get out there, peeps will like my stuff. I was hoping to make a guest appearance during WES's set in Window Rock. I didn't get a chance to ask him when I saw him this past Friday. I feel that since he earned that spot why should I try to get in on his set. So I left it as is. Some day I'll have my chance.  ...Cool, just got done talking with Ana and everything is all good between her and I. I'm happy :D So all has turned out well. And here I was thinking something else and got a bit worried...something that had been on my mind all day long.... 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Wow. First time I've seen a dog fight again. Too cool...well my brother and I walked to my aunt's house and our dog followed. My aunt's dog was being tough when we got there...next thing you know they were fighting. I was like "whoa" because they came toward me. Anywho, I jumped in and grabbed our dog’s collar and tried to tug back on him...but damn, tough lil guy...finally got them apart and the other dog went after our dog again, and they're fighting, again. I had my nunchaku with me...so I waited for a good shot and *CRACK* swung it at my aunt's dog, all while thinking *you fuker, that’s for starting shit with my dog*. It finally took off...I sent our dog home, and that fukin dog ran after our dog again, but backed out when it got really close to "Jimboy."  Dogs, pretty cool animals, although some can be...I don't know, I mean I've had my experiences with them. I used to have a Rottie, went by the name of "Jesse." A retired police dog. She was cool and all, then all of a sudden something happened, and she didn’t make it through that "something." One time we were playing basketball and it just so happens the ball bounced right into her territory and she got happy and playful, and I ran after the ball and just as she was about to bite into the ball I moved it out of her way and she ended up biting skin off the side of my stomach. Hurt like crazy but in the end I was like "It's ok 'pubby'..." and petted her. Oh and I was ok :P  One of my friend's raises dogs, mainly pitbulls. He takes them to shows, and fights. He's talking about buying a couple from this person down in Alamogordo or whatever. One of my cousins is also in that hype, I guess he just wants one for the heck of it, not for show and stuff like that. I've been thinking of getting one myself, but im not really ready for a dog right now, besides they are $425.00 a pup. I don't have that kind of money to be playing around with...I have school to think about before anything else.  Anywho, work is good so far. I'm hoping to reach 40 hours by the end of today’s(Wednesday) work day. Right now all we're doing is going to each location given and searching for oil and gas spills. More cover up jobs. Well I shouldn't say cover up. It is a requirement that all leases be cleaned at all times. Cover up refers only to huge spills and leaks...I better keep it a hush :P.  What else to say...I've neglected my guitar. By now I probably suck...hmm, every time I say that, it seems I only come back playing way much better. I mean I’ve practically outplayed all guitar peeps in this community. Most of these peeps have been playing long before I even started. I also hear by word of mouth that some people are intimidated by my playing *grins*. I hear all this stuff...makes me look good, guitar playing wise. But I always seem to not take it all in...I mean of course there are a lot of great guitar people out there. I just have to get out there and put my skills up to anyone.  My friends band, War Eagle Society will be playing in Window Rock, AZ on the 14th of this month. I was hoping to ask him if I could make a guest appearance and see what others think about my skills, others meaning peeps who haven't heard my "stuff" yet. I doubt I will be making this appearance on stage with his band though. If I do, I have to bust @ss every day until then to put together a piece, or to master one of WES's songs, and I don't really have the time to do this because I need that time at work. Oh, Soulfly is going to be there as well, one of the reasons I'm going. A music fest of some sort I guess. I can't wait to see this  Anything else?...all is good so far. I saw my brother again...I try not to go out to where he's at, just because of the constant blaming, it sucks. To this day I'm still questioned about what happened, mostly by close friends and other relatives who are now finding out about what happened. All has and is slowly turning well. Whoa, the time...well I need to rest for tomorrow...gotta trade my time for money. 

						
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Tired and exhausted...Yep, that's what I am......well, that's what I was. I started to write an entry for my blog on Tuesday. The beginning of this entry was the only sentence I wrote. Well like the intro of this paragraph, this past week has been a busy one. Can you imagine 50 hours in four days? :P It all started with locations pressuring to their maximum and then finally bursting, making a huge mess which had to be cleaned before word got out to Navajo EPA...cover up jobs.  Tuesday, was the beginning of these so called crucial jobs. We got to the job site and there was a strong odor of H2S. There were oil and gas everywhere, puddles of it. We had our tailgate safety meeting, planned what to do in case if something goes wrong, and finally chose an escape route. We started with connecting hoses to the vacuum truck and pumped as much as we could into the truck. After this we disconnected all flanges and valves that connected to the Skim Tank that blew. Oh yea, the skim tank bursting is the reason why we were out there in the first place. After we unbolted all that needed to be, we started blinding off lines, and changed around valves because there was a section of flow line that was taken out of the entire set up. This took us the entire day into the evening. I got home at around 9:00 or so, soaked in oil and H2S...  On Wednesday we continued work at the same location because all we did the day before was unbolted lines, flanges, and switched valves. This is the day we started the actual clean up and it sucked because there was no other way to get all that mud oil out but to use wheel burrows and by hand. I didn't really mind because I had a good workout, even though it sucked. Again, Thursday and Friday was a continuation of the job at Area 6. Only this time it was sort of laid back because the past two days before these days we got a lot done, but still, a lot of hours.  Yesterday I turned 23. I didn't do much except sleep in, then head into town just for a drive and to eat out. Kinda funny, I ran into people whom I haven't seen in the longest time, family included. I got back...oh, and I talked with Ana for an hour or so, maybe more. I got a beautiful gift from her and a card included. Just as I got off the phone with her, my brother came around..."yea, we were told to pick you up" and I was like "ok." I ended up at my aunt's home, and she had a cookout for the occasion...it was good. During the Lil celebration I got called out to work. I needed the hours so I took the call.  And now that I'm back from work, at 2:30 in the morning or so, I've decided to continue where I left off when I started this entry, seeing that it's been five days or so since I wrote anything. Hmm, I guess I could write more but I'm too tired to write anything else, and anything else probably wouldn't sound good in my condition...I'll just post something along with this entry. This piece isn't done yet...and it doesn't have a title as well.  *ABC-123* Finally our time has come to kill off the less fortunate and take whats ours  You better watch out cause here we come destruction using the mind  *my mind, my mind, my mind* *yea*  you tell me im wrong but look at you all i see is envy taking what was once yours  what do you have to say? nothing comes from your mouth this is how its going to be destruction using the mind  *my mind, my mind, my mind* *yea*  what you see is what you get its time to get use to the new destruction using the mind welcome to my world Copyright &copy 2004 SJohnson 

						
</post>


</Blog>