<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Before I start off with today's topic, let me set the stage for you, so you'll better understand the situation and it's repurcussion.   A few months ago, a juvenile prostitution ring was dismantled here in Quebec, and some clients were kinda popular 'round here. The most notable client was Robert Gillet, a morning man on a very popular radio-show. Throughout his trial, he was the target of loads of insults and assumptions, even before the verdict came out. Jeff Filion, another famous radio-man, and a very controversial one too, said some really crude stuff about Robert Gillet. What he said was true, Robert Gillet was a criminal and a pervert, but since it's not the kind of thing to say on air, his superiors told him to ease it up on him. And so he did.  The Canadian Radio-television and Telecommunication Commission announced this morning that they would force the radio-station broadcasting Filion's show, to close down by september of this year. The last radio station that has closed in Quebec by the CRTC was because of financial and technical problems. But this time CHOI-FM, has to close down for a question of content. The CRTC received close to 10 000 letters backing CHOI-FM and a mere 38 asking for its end. These 38 letters were sent by high placed people, friends of the system as we call them. And since the CRTC is a government organisation, you can guess who had weight in balance. It seems that 10 000 peeps aren't enough for the CRTC.  And moreso, CHOI the most popular radio station around! Isn't that proof enough that the majority of the population has no problem with CHOI's content? Minutes after the announcement, the population was already crying their outrage, even those who hates CHOI was angry at the CRTC. This is one the biggest censorship in Canada, and above all, it was decided upon one or two crude comments said on air by Filion. Beleive me, I've heard them, there's much much worse out there. Filion has always been controversial, but every radio station has a controversial guy! And even then, if you don't like controversy, just change the channel.  It seems the CRTC thinks we're not able to do so, we're too stupid, so they'll close it down for us instead.  As an artist, I am outraged to see that stuff like this still happens. We need our freedom of speech! I need to feel free to express myself. And with something like that in the air, I don't feel like talking against the CRTC will do any good. Think about this: 38 key people decided something 10 000 normal people clearly did not wanted. Over 50% of the population of the city listens to CHOI once in a while, that's another big chunk of peeps that doesn't seem to weight in the balance. In a survey, 96% were in disagreement with the CRTC's decision. But I still feel like our voices will never be heard, because their blocking out their ears.   Oh, and did I mention that the Mayor of Quebec was part of the 38? He's supposed to be our voice, we elected him. And he's going against us anyway. Where's the democracy? A commission that exists because of us, and paid by us, closes down a radio station in a very unjustified way. And they do so because our mayor (and others) thought CHOI was annoying them.  CHOI was at the bottom of the chart 8 years ago, and made it up to the top with almost nothing. It run by a very small company, no wonder competitors are pissed off. But even then, I heard that some other radio stations were ready to help out CHOI!  This is a very messy situation, as you can see. I thought it was too important to ignore it, and as messy as it can get, I thought it be ghood if wrote about it as soon as possible. So, next time there's any development, I'll let you know. For the time being, I'm going to bed, as I should've done before writting this lol   G'night folks!  -Sim-
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey there readers!  My name's Simon Villeneuve and I'm a movie lover, a videogaming aficionado and a music junkie. I used to write movie reviews on a message baord, but I thought it was too limiting and I lacked a good audience to make myself heard.  Plus in the past year, I've grown a huge interest in music. An interest for music still unknown to most, the underdogs of the scene. Bands that has 4 songs on major soundtracks, but are still never recognised. I have a few in mind right now and I'll gladly share my thoughts in a later entry. Bear in mind though, that many of you still knows much more than me about music. I'm just a music fan with a few artists in his top 5 that aren't even known to most.  But as far as videogaming goes, well, I'm pretty well informed on the subject. I mainly play console games, but I do take notice of great PC games. I believe that videogames should be considered an artform. Games sometimes have a message, they have moving soundtracks, well-written stories, just as in the movies and sometimes more. I worked in a videogame shop and one of my biggest thrill was to convince the girlfriends that games are for everyone, and are not only about violence. I was good at it! ;)  And third, but not least, this blog's about movies. Not strictly reviews, but rants, thoughts and comments on the industry. I'm a graduate in Cinema and Arts and Technology in Medias, that might speak for itself as far as credibility goes ;) I'm also "working" (lack of jobs these days) in the business, so I know a thing or two about how it's done. But don't go thinking I'm an experimented movie-maker or something, I'm only 23 and just got out of school, that pretty much puts me at the bottom of the ladder.  One last thing though: english is not my first language, french is. I consider myself bilingual, but still, if there's something awfully wrong in my writtings, please tell me, it'll help me more than you'd think. And please, do give feedbacks on my posts, it motivates me to write more.  Seeya later readers!  -Sim-
     

    
</post>


</Blog>