<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Staying at my Dad's in  urlLink Porthcawl  in South Wales. In a way it is fun - Dad is the first place I've yet been where there is  real , old-fashioned digital satellite - except it's of a new-fashioned 'Sky Plus' variety which allows you to record two things simultaneously to hard-disk and 'pause live TV'. So I'm pretty much like the rat with the morphine drip. On the downside, my Dad's weight problems (although he is by now easily slimmer than I've ever seen him, and looking pretty sprightly for his 68 years, moreover)continue to mean that there continues to be no snack food of note in the house. Basically visits to Dad have not significantly changed in the 10 years that I've been coming alone to see Dad. That dreadful continuity again. Changes are superficial: Dad has coloured his hair chestnut and now has a golden Buddha hanging round his neck - ten years ago it was a golden inscription from the Koran. Dad is a bit more serious about his Buddhism than his Islam, but then again, this is only because it is possible to be a Buddhist with a relatively low level of commitment. Anyway, Dad's about to move to Thailand more-or-less, which should make visiting him a bit more interesting - not that I don't love seeing him. Although I mean that, I have to say it - which is the weirdest thing about blogging. There's a lot of things, or  people , more to the point, that I'd normally be fucking caustic about, but who could read this, so whom I just can't diss.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Catching up with England, I just watched my first episode of  urlLink Wife Swap , a reality show in which wives are swapped, not for the sexual functions, but in their matriarchal capacity. This is very similar to a much lower-key and underrated proto-reality show on BBC 2 years ago in which two people swapped lives. I can't even remember what it was called, but clearly remember a show in which a New Age traveller was swapped with a conservative farmer with hilarious results. In tonight's episode of Wife Swap, a woman from a rural Devon family with, by my estimate, four kids is swapped with a fat woman from an urban Northern family. I tuned in half way through the show, just before the point where, after trying out the lifestyle of the host family, the swapped wives impose their own regimens on their hosts. The Southern mother demanded healthy eating, exercise and family cohesion, to the utter chagrin of her temporary husband and unbounded joy of her temporary daughter, who had been suffering in an environment of emotional and physical under-nourishment. The Northern mother determined, and it was pretty surreal to watch, that the cohesiveness and incessant activity of the Devonian family was pathological - she resolved to smash their family routine and locked their bicycles in a container. She did try to clean their house up, which I thought was fair enough. But her recurring claims that the family had an unhealthy obsession with exercise which they obviously did freely for enjoyment was patently preposterous. The background to this was spending most of the day with my sister Laura and my new constantly-vomitting nephew Moss. Laura explained to me her philosophy of child-rearing, which is commendably child-psychology centred. It incorporates peripherally the hypothesis that inadequate child-rearing is to blame for broad social ills. While I tend to balk at these conclusions, it is undeniable that breeding needs to be done deliberately, and that where due deliberation is not taken, the consequences are deliterious for the pretty much everyone. As things stand, such consequences are ubiquitous - both Laura and myself are the products of decisions to bear children which were not part of a plan which had our welfare at its heart and have suffered the consequences (Laura much more so than me, I must say). Family planning doesn't mean just planning whether to have a family, but actually having a plan for that family. Do I sound like Bill O'Reilly?
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am coming to the end of my sejourn in Wellington. I find myself wanting to prolong it. I feel pretty secure here - more secure than I've felt in a long time, and, I know, a lot more secure than I'm going to feel for a long time to come. So i think i'm going to stay one more day, one more day than I wanted. I'm just so bloody tired. Seeing old people from school (foreigners, read 'high school') over the last couple of days, people I haven't seen for anything from two-and-a-half to four years, was pretty uneventful. Things were the same as they were eight years ago, following a pre-set pattern now. A lot of people live in London, with partners. Everyone except me has a job. We are engineers, a solicitor, an actuary, an accountant. But we play football and I still cannot play football, and everyone else can compared to me and we fuck about in a park and go back and watch cricket. There's less drinking and no drugs now, more eating, but we still separate along the same lines: me, John and Jamie end up going out in Welly on a Saturday night and go to the Vint, which has completely changed, so that we only stay for one drink and head home to my house where John plays Tony Hawk's 4 on my iBook for an hour while me and Jamie watch, then Jamie goes back to John's house where he's staying, the same pattern we've followed in fact for ten years. There've been subtle evolutions in that time, but seamless. It makes me sentimental.
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      - Hello? - Hi Laura, it’s Mark. - I can’t hear you. - Laura! - I’m sorry, you’ve got the wrong number. - What? - You've got the wrong number - No I don’t! - Yeh, you do. [pause] - Oh right, sorry then. [hangs up] 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This was the front-page banner headline of the weekly  Wellington Weekly News  last week. I bought the paper to see what was going down in  urlLink my old hometown  and was delighted to see this bold use of local dialect. I showed it to my brothers, who grew up here, and neither of them could even readily understand it. 'Wed' of course means 'married'. The gunman in question was the sometime boyfriend of the local pub landlady - the landlady of the Sanford arms, known locally as the Sanford, the pub closest to  urlLink my school , the only pub serving the southern part of town, about a 5 minute walk up the road from me and a few years ago the main pub for pupils (in my day, it was the Vintage [known as 'the Vint'], but I think the cops cracked down on that years ago) - who according to this story planned to marry her. But she got back with another boyfriend and the 'gunman' came into the Sanford one night earlier this year and shot his rival in the face with a pistol, killing him instantly. He claims the gun went off by accident. Another thing about England is that no-one here has seen  Supersize Me . In fact, no-one here has even  heard  of it. This would explain why Australia is the only country in the world to have addressed the film in its advertising - it is probably the only country in the world where McDonald's diners have actually been watching the movie.
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should put a post in to say that I am now back in the bosom of my family, or at least my irrascible brother James and my Mother. Here, as Mum warned me yesterday on the way from Taunton station, nothing has changed. I have not been to this house since December 2001, but I feel as though i had never left. Indeed, the change such as it has been, is for the reality to transmogrify into my golden image of the place, since my mother's long-time associate, with whom I never got on, no longer lives here, and thus it is far more stress-free than it actually used to be. This is somewhat mitigated by the disappearance, with him, of wide-screen TV and digital satellite, but otherwise it's blissful. Otherwise though, Somerset in Summer is so beautiful - this morning I woke up in my old bedroom at dawn (due to ongoing jet-lag issues) and opened the window all the way and climbed out and sat on the edge of the water tank, and just looked at the garden - kind of surreal through the sheer dislocation and the tiredness, but still just awesome. I'm a bit stressed that here's not really somewhere i can work, though - and I really do need to get this thesis written (I am informed by Entourage that it is due in 254 days!) That being the  final  draft. . . Another incredible thing in England now, which has enabled me to connect my laptop to the internet for the first time since getting back, is the existence of  free  dial-up internet - apparently with unlimited downloading etc, though I haven't tested that yet.
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, it’s nearly half eight in the evening and the sun’s still up. It’s been up for 16 hours already! This shit is freaking me out considerably. It’s like science fiction or something. I’ve been up since 2am, which is probably contributing to my overall freak-out. Also, my conference paper, due to be given in erm two-and-three-quarter days is not finished. Well, it’s not ready at all. And I haven’t done any work on it. I just keep reading this trashy crime novel set in Leeds that I found in the bedside table. I think Lucy Payne had more to do with the murders than she lets on. . . I feel like I’m on holiday and can’t be bothered with this shit. 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a weird one. After my experiences admiring the various bubbas of many nations on my flights out here, I am surprised to find none of the kids here being anything but offensive, ugly, blonds ruffians. All the more so, as I seem to be over my Northerner-phobia, and getting on OK with the rest of the monkeys. A lot of the girls under 25 even seem to be quite attractive. 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Firstly, I went in to a Maccas – to use the toilet, I hasten to add. Firstly, the prices have gone down since I went away. Second, they now have a bigger main burger called the McBig One or some shit that costs more than the others. Third, the have the standard array of healthy crap that all McDonald’ses have been adding to their menus worldwide. Fourth, they appear to be the only internet ‘café’ in town, offering 30mins for a pound. Unsurprisingly there were no takers.  I remembered the expansive promises Blair had made about putting internet into public libraries, so headed to the public library, where I indeed found that I could fuck about on the internet as much as I wanted by obtaining a library card, which I did for free with a minimum of fuss. Apparently foreign tourists were in the habit of doing this, somewhat to the staff’s chagrin no doubt.  In the library computer room I ran into Melinda Cooper from Sydney, who was editing her paper for tomorrow. We hung out for a couple of hours later, talking about geopolitics. I offended/irritated her by being an apologist for ‘fascist’ Islamic fundamentalist movements. I am a bit worried about this, as it was not my intention. 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This university is weird – it’s the only university other than Oxbridge I’ve ever seen where accommodation and teaching is architecturally integrated. Hence, in the building I’m staying in, the third floor is student rooms, the second is the Linguistics department, and the ground floor is English.  Graduations, which were happening yesterday, continue today. Fuckheads. The question for me is, who the fuck are these people? I had never heard of Lancaster University or of anyone going there until this year.The weirdness of this place has shifted from the weirdness of being in England, which is still there, to a dislocation around the continuities between this place and Sydney. Being in an institutional environment makes it much the same – wandering around lost yesterday afternoon, I could almost have been wandering around UNSW lost. Moreover, the weather here, the weather of a typical British Summer, is continuous with the Sydney Winter weather I left behind. 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Major Australio-English misunderstanding: I ‘forgot’ that, unlike Australian universities, English universities do not provide public-access internet at all anywhere ever. Except for the   urlLink ANU , every university I have been to in Australia does this. No university I have been to in England ever has, but somehow I really managed to assume that I would be able to use the internet here. I think this might be like the hair thing. I now have two dilemmas: 1. Ellen probably thinks I am dead and/or an arsehole; 2. I have to register for a conference by tomorrow but cannot get the registration details. I will obviously have to go to town however it is now too late too realistically get to town before the banks close to make my conference payment, plus Ellen will probably be in bed by the time I send one, so I might just stay here and relax after my insanely long journey and perhaps call my mum later and get her to text Ells on my behalf. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh jesus, they don’t even have a shower, only a bath! Welcome to fucking England, dickhead. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’m realising the depth of my problem in understanding prices. I paid something in the region of £13 a night for this room months ago, but now that seems crazy. Moreover, I nearly bought a mobile phone while waiting for the bus from Carphone Warehouse, and the salesman, Anas Patel, himself looked at me like I was crazy, because I clearly thought £19.95 and £15/month was nothing. Have resolved to go back again tomorrow after thinking it over, but the bus fare to town is £1.  After my earlier victory in eating those genuine pork pies (Aussie pork pie manufacturers: the jelly is supposed to hold the pork and crust together, not constitute a liquid layer between the two), I went and got a genuine Gregg’s cheese pastie.  Lancaster makes me realise that in fact England has changed very little. Thus far, other than a couple of seemingly random price hikes, the changes appear to amount to:  The Independent and The Times have now adopted the tabloid format (NB they adopted the content years ago), leaving only two national broadsheets, The Grauniad and The Torygraph; Abbey National is now called ‘abbey’; aforementioned crazy travel advice console, which gave me ultimately useless directions to the bus stop in Lancaster, thanks fuckwit . . .; polyphonic ringtones; and it seems Deutsche Telekom has become one of the main UK mobile networks – thinking about it, it must have replaced BT Cellnet, a terrible network which I had forgotten about.  It seems it is me who has changed. In particular, note my consternation at how men all still shave their heads here. I mean, I thought everyone had just grown out of it, but in fact, I now realise, I have just become Australianised! When I arrived in Australia, shaven-headed, everyone else there was wearing hair. Then I thought, how fucking backward, but at some point I started thinking that they were being fashionable, when they were actually just lagging decades behind. Fuck it though – I’m keeping my Newtown mullet! 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Approaching Manchester we travel through suburbs, going back in time. At first, borough after borough of semi-detached houses, a strange paradigm for living, I think. The gardens shrink as we get back toward the beginning of the twentieth century, presaging terraces as the semis cluster closer together and develop alleyways at the back. Then, suddenly, we are in Manchester proper, the Victorian city, with acres of terraced maze, warrens of nineteenth century redbrick. After Sydney, Manchester is like Pompeii, an entire Victorian city preserved whole. A city I had once thought a depressing shithole now has an incredible Gothic majesty. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Missed my train – though I still don’t understand how.  After the initial shock of discovering that bottles of Coke(c) cost £1.30, i.e. A$3 – and these are 500ml not 600 as in Australia, I rediscovered the fact that shops produce their own knock-offs of Coke which are barely distinguishable&nbsp; - I got 500ml of Marks and Spencer Cola for only 60p, Also two Melton Mowbray (i.e. miniature) pork pies for 79p. Then at the counter I tried to pay with a pound coin, since I automatically thought of it as a two dollar coin, which is the same size. When I produced &nbsp;a second pound coin, shinier and larger than the first, the fifteen-year old acned shop boy realised that the first one was an Australian two dollar coin. I then corrected my mistake by giving him a 20p, a 10p and a 5p and a 5¢. He returned the 5¢ to me – I then gave him a 10¢ thinking it was a 10p, at which point he realised that the original 10p was in fact also a 10¢ - I took them all back and gave him a 20p. I don’t really understand any of this, since I’d thought I’d got rid of all my Aussie change. He was uncomprehendingly fascinated by my explanations of Australian numismatics.   
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My level of disorientation at being in England is really extraordinary, although I did pretty much anticipate it. Licence plates are cartoonishly large, and the money is also very large, but seems more antiquated than cartoonish. Still, my overall impression is of having suddenly been transported into the not-too-distant future (I feel like this is a common enough fictional premise, but actually the only example I can think of is that movie Demolition Man). I just bought a ticker to Lancaster and then thought, had aboot, how does one find out the train information? Do they have electronic displays, or just timetables? The enormous flat-screen display just had plane times, so I wandered over to the timetables, but came across an information terminal right by it. The touch sensitive screen allowed me to discover the possible routes, employing public transport, between any two points in the entire country, and give me a timetable. What’s more, it gave me directions of how to get from one place to another on foot. And what’s even more than that, it then gave me a comprehensive free print-out of all the details. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I did actually see some Westerners, two of whom were on a cyclo, in the tourist district on the way back to the airport. The cute chick quotient had completely exploded, with nightfall, making me vasodilate.  The return flight was weirdly different, with the cabin crew being even ruder.  I was seated with this couple who I’d actually met while we’d been transiting in Saigon and they had their four-month y.o. bub with them. He was a beautiful little bubba, incredibly well-behaved and happy, really inquisitive, and obviously out of his mind with sleep deprivation. They weren’t too keen to have me sitting with them, since they wanted space, but I was overjoyed to be able to spend the time with their bub, having a thing for bubs as I do. I am sensitive to allegations of paedophilia on this front, so don’t even touch it. I slept most of the way anyway, which was definitely a good thing, as was had had like 6 hours sleep over the two nights combined before I’d started travelling. Most of the way into the flight little bubba’s dad discovered that we had entertainment consoles built into the armrests, which allowed me to watch a big slice of LOR The Return of the King. The bits in Mordor were irksome, the Liv Tyler bits remain intolerable, but the subtly racialist  battle scenes literally made my nipples hard with delight.  My transfer in Paris was very smooth. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let me make this clear: I am in fucking Saigon!  They have given me a three-star hotel room for two hours while I transit planes. This is because it took an hour to clear customs and another hour to drive through the solid flows of low-cc bikes and scooters that passes for traffic around her.  Observations: Vietnamese sighted – at least 10,000; non-Asian people sighted (outside the vehicle i was travelling in)– 0; old-school conical oriental hats –3, all worn by old women involved in low-status work e.g. picking through garbage; cute girls – hundreds.  Motorbikes and mopeds sighted – thousands; bicycles sighted – 3; cars sighted – about 10; cyclos sighted – 3, but none of them appeared to be operational; other vehicles sighted –about five.  Also, all the buildings are the same width, which is about three metres. They’re all terraced, but some are up to six stories tall and a block thick, standing in amongst two storey buildings, they look hilarious. From air it looked like the entire city was a mixture of shipping containers and parked cars.  They still have the same French guy doing the weather on CNN that the did last time I watched the channel four years ago.&nbsp;
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, let’s blog:  I’m in flight over Australia. Vietnam Airlines. I managed to get put in a seat with decent leg-room, which is a big deal for me. I’m not that tall, but I guess I have exceptionally long legs, because they don’t fit quite comfortably behind economy class seats. I was seated next to an overweight Australian couple. They were in position when I arrived and I tried to open with pleasantries, unappealing though this pair was, but they studiously ignored my presence. I had assumed that the male’s enormousness has led them to request this seating as I had done, but it seems either that that is not the case, or that they really disliked my presence, because they fucked off as soon as they were able to sit elsewhere in the somewhat deserted plane.  Now of course, that pisses me off, having paid A$2129 for my six-stage return flight. I hate feeling like a sucker, and I hate the nagging feeling that I could’ve gotten a better deal on my flights. I’d really prefer it if airlines just charged fixed fees, like suburban railways: when you’re on a train and your deserted, you possibly feel like the railway is overcharging, but not like you’re a sucker.  On the other hand, now that those Aussie fuckwits have pissed off, I have an entire row of three seats entirely to myself: I’m sitting in the middle seat, with the seat to my left for my bag, and the seat to my right for reading matter, pillows and detritus.  One thing that was comforting about those Aussies though was that the man was wearing generic blue cotton tracky daks just like me—I couldn’t imagine that anyone else would be gauche enough to go to Vietnam dressed like they were lounging round the house, which in his case is probably in Newcastle, given his huge size, tats, and his turning down the offer of VB from a steward (i.e. he drinks enough beer to think himself above VB—but when offered Tiger beer instead he’d patently never heard of it, an reacted as if quite impressed). He was wearing a Namibia baseball cap too, which probably means he’s a rugby union man, but beyond that for me the semiotics are unclear.  The cabin crew’s English is a bit poor. Well, whatever, but this flight is, to my moderate surprise, mostly Westerners. Moreover, they seem baffled by my self-confessedly rather good English. My first resort, from habit, when met with incomprehension, was to speak with a distinct Australian accent. This didn’t work so I switched to RP, from where I retreated to hand gestures. Asked whether I wanted beef or fish, my answer, beef, was interpreted to mean fish, This is poor, rather like the fish. 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi I'm establishing this weblog as something to distract me from the realities of my predicament re: my PhD while I senselessly galavant around Europe all Summer. To set the scene, after living in the UK pretty much my whole life, except for really quite brief stints in France and Germany, I relocated to Australia two-and-a-quarter years ago and now I'm going back to the Northern hemisphere for the first time since then - in fact, it's the first time I've been North of Brisbane or out of the Easternmost three states of Australia in the entire time. So, tomorrow, first stop Saigon, second stop Paris (technically the day after tomorrow), third stop Manchester, and fourth stop Lancaster, where I have never been before. 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       	 		 		 Fr. Johnâs house is decorated on the theme of Christian kitsch: glow-in-the-dark virgins,  Life of Brian  poster, golden icons, pictures of comical scenes from ecclesiastical life. The best piece is pictured here, tinily, he has came from  urlLink Viz , which does parodies of the kind of tat that advertisers in the  urlLink Radio Times  hawk to old ladies: itâs a collectorâs edition plate, entitled âThe Life of Christ in Catsâ, depicting pertinent scenes from the messiahâs life with cartoon cats instead of peopleâat the top is an image of a cat being crucified, with the legend 'IDRIS' on the top of the crucifix. On the other hand, John has an overweening obsession with IKEA. He talks about it a lot. He even goes on about how good the food is at IKEA. Itâs taken me a while to notice the Nordic furniture beneath the clutter. Most of Johnâs kitchenware, for example, is IKEA; also his bookshelves and, I noticed yesterday, every piece of lighting in the house too. Then there is his computer, a brand new monstrous black desktop from  urlLink DELL . I cringe to remember that it wasnât long ago that I nearly bought a laptop from DELL myself. DELLâs computers are so ugly. I mean, itâs kind of nice that all Johnâs electronics share a consistent style theme, but all the black is so oppressive. Black plastic, with flashes of silver plastic and green LEDsâgrody. And he runs Windows! 		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink christcat 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink XmarkX .			 		 	  
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had this really clearly-developed image attached to my return to England. I would be at Richard’s parents house in Wellington, sitting around, having a barbecue. I’d be asked if I wanted something to drink or whatever, and I’d say, I’ll just have a glass of waduh (Australian for ‘water’) and everyone will laugh and make fun of me and I’ll be exotic and the centre of attention. I think I was nursing this fantasy for about two years, from the time I found myself first asking for a glass of waduh in Jo’s kitchen in Paddington. It didn’t come to pass: Richard’s parents had moved, and going round to Richard’s flat I was treated totally normally, even being asked disinterestedly how long it had taken me to develop an Aussie accent. Even that’s gone now – when I saw my cousin the other day, rather than remarking how Aussie I sounded as people had been doing a couple of weeks before, he made the  opposite  remark. I mention this because I just played over this favourite fantasy and realised that I would have to abandon it now.
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have just got back from Lodon  again , where I was hiding out while Fr. John's tiny Northern mother was visiting him. I hope he doesn't read this because, well, mums are special aren't they? I actually saw quite a few attractive 'birds' while i was down there, like 20-30. This would still only have been a statistically irrelevent 1% or so of the munting female population, but is still notable. The second or third one I saw, I noticed had a strong Australian accent (using the word 'park' to mean 'parking space' and pronouncing parallel with the emphasis on the last syllable). My first thought was, fucking London sucking all the talent out of Sydney. But this I realised was applying my old 'capital attracts talent' theory, which I was actually refuted by previous forays into London. So instead I applied my new 'birds in London are rough' theory, which of course would work in this instance, with the proviso that the only attractive girls there are from somewhere else. Sadly, it's pretty difficult to actually ascertain where people come from when viewing them on the street, but it is worth noting that of those I did hear talking, three were some kind of Latin, and one was American. Note that i am not claiming that all girls from these countries are fit - most Spanish and Italian girls in London are as rough as sandpaper. On a related note, it seems fairly obvious to me that God does not exist. However, it is becoming very apparent to me that many of my peers do not feel the same way. In fact, since I left the West Country, which I would have pegged as one of the more religious parts of the country, most of the people I've met, including most of my friends I've been hanging out with, have been practising Christians. So I feel it might be worth spelling out why Christianity is rubbish, at the risk of fucking off Fr. John even more: 1. Trinitarianism is ridiculous. All Christians, except some way out ones (Unitarians, Jehovah's Witnesses, etc.) believe in the Trinity i.e. that the father, son, and holy spirit are equal parts of the 'Godhead'. This is a completely stupid theory. The divinity of Christ is in fact itself totally stupid. How can a someone simultaneously be infinite and a human being? They can't, that's how. note that there's nothing about the trinity in the bible, and it was only invented like 400 years later. The divinity of Christ is in the bible and is patently stupid, broadly because of my next point. . . 2. The infinite cannot have personal attributes. This is where the Moslems, while realising the stupidity of a man being God slip up, although nowhere near as much as the Christians. The infinite doesn't care about things, have emotions or do things. Fucking about is the province of finite beings. If you're infinite you just do everything all at once, encompass everything, know everything, be everything. This implies pantheism. Which is basically the same as atheism as I see it, because if, as Spinoza had it, God is everywhere and everything, then as I see it his existence basically doens't mean anything either way. If, on the other hand, God is not everywhere and everything, then he's just a super-powerful space alien, in which case he's as fucking lame as the rest of us, amen.
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The biggest difference in London now as compared to three years ago is rickshaws, i.e. cycle rickshaws, i.e. bicycle powered taxicabs with seating for two under a canopy behind the rider. I saw a couple of these last time I was in London, but on a rainy Wednesday night in Soho, they’re everywhere. Their Euroboy drivers hawk their trade in bad mawkish English. A few of them are actually English, so God knows what they tell their parents – probably the truth, namely that they’re just doing it for the Summer to clear credit card debts. Maybe they deal drugs to the passengers too – who knows. It’s a whole new world, based on that one Seinfeld episode with the same premise, except that in that they at least had the realism to accept that introducing rickshaws to a post-industrial city is a stupid idea. After what was basically a £20 tapas dinner, a tiny group of us was persuaded to go to a vodka bar called ‘Garlic and Shots’ in Soho. I only went because apparently they played death metal, which they did. Eight years ago, visiting this bar would have induced me to start making plans to move to London. Today, I just ask, where’s the hardcore? Found a magazine there called ‘Alternative London’ but it was all Camden Goth bullshit, nothing alternative at all. On the way out, they had Vices, which made me whoop with delight. The British edition seems a bit lamer than the Australian edition, but only because in the context of London the  urlLink Vice  agenda just seems like a fantasy that would be completely incompatible with actually living there. Also, I figured out why it is that all English children are not cute: it’s because they all have grade twos. Please: this is not a flattering hair-cut for a five year-old. There was this woman and a kid on the tube this morning, apparently not British. The kid was sprawling out with his back arched back. The mother’s response to this was to straighten him by basically punching him in the fucking guts, then strapping him in a fucking pram (even though he looked like he was about four) and appearing genuinely consternated as to why he was crying so loudly, and try to shut him up with a bottle of chocolate filth, which he wisely rejected. Then this apparently-Jewish older woman went over (she’d been trying to get involved in someone else’s business ever since she’d got on the train) and started trying to help. Maybe it worked – I don’t know because I got up and walked down to the other end of the carriage.
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have just returned to Colchester after my longest foray thus-far this trip into the depths of London. As I see things, the City of London is the second biggest nexus in the administration of global imperialism after Wall Street. Walking through it, along the Strand from Blackfriars to Trafalger Square, stoked the dying embers of my anticapitalism back into flame. I felt again the anger that had made me come to London for May 1st 2001, with the intention of smashing up as much of the place as I could. It made me want to resist again, want to fight back against the sheer lameness of the whole get-rich-and-fuck-everyone else project that my homeland has come to represent. It cannot produce anything aesthetically worthwhile: what it produces is ugly, clumsy, half-suited fucks dancing around with drunken insouciance to pub bands while drinking £3.50 bottles of beer JUST FUCKING KILL YOURSELVES ALREADY, YOU STUPID BASTARDS! These lives are not worth living. Maybe mine isn't either, but at least I'm not dedicating my life to ugliness and oppression. Speaking of ugliness, everyone (and I'm especially referring to the ladies) in London looks really rough, as does everyone in Colchester. Both places are crawling with Latin (French, Spanish, Italian) teenagers who stand as a living testament to how easy it was for out ancestors to wipe the floor with the Roman Empire in the first place.
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hanging out with the newly-ordained Fr. John is a strange proposition – at least when he wears his dog collar it is. Walking into town today, a gang of metal kids shouted assorted shit at him, like ‘Hail Satan!’ Being a priest is a bit of a liability these days. Later on, horsing around proves to be difficult – play-fighting with and swearing bawdily at a priest doesn’t go down with the old ladies. The only really good effects occur when John breaks character: in the local computer shop, one of the machines is running Doom 3, which both me and John are eager to try out. On John’s turn, the guy who works there comes out and is watching John as he explores the first level. Coming to a scientist who is trying explain something to him, John takes aim and shoots him in the face. The computer shop guy, who John doesn’t realise is there, gives a surprised burst of laughter. John tries to claim that he just thought he was supposed to shoot everyone and we leave. Excited by this foray, John is now noisily machine-gunning zombies in the next room.
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am exhausted. My exhaustion from all this peripeteticity, itinerance and nomadism has settled over me uncomfortably, because I've finally come to rest. I'm supposed to keep moving, but the temptation to just stop for a bit is massive. The place where I've come to rest is  urlLink Fr. John Stather 's house in Colchester, a 4-bed semi on the Roman Road that he gets rent- and tax-free for being deacon of St. James'. I have the room in the loft. On my way out of Copenhagen I saw two funny storefronts. One of the batteries had fallen out of my camera and I couldn't find it, so I have no evidence of this, but I saw one store called BIGE KØKKEN, which was funny enough until I saw a ladies' fashion boutique called SLUTSPURT. My plane was delayed so I didn't get into Colchester until nearly one in the morning, and then obviously had to sit around for another hour eating leftover Thai food (the Colchester variety being somewhat shitter than the Sydney standard), while John procrastinated over writing his Sunday sermon. John is much the same as he was when we were up at Durham, I guess. He still survives on very little sleep. I was really surprised five days ago passing through here at how tidy and civilised the house is - John's room in Shoichi was a complete tip, trash strewn everywhere, with a pungent male odour. I surmised that possibly John had actually cleaned up in anticipation of my visit, which hypthesis is borne out somewhat by the fact that the place is now far more entropic. Also, there's a hell of a lot more space to absorb John's spread.     Fr. John's vicarage (actual size) * *Turns out 'slutspurt' actually means like closing down sale. Humph.
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I kind of didn't finish my post yesterday as I had to go to our dinner at Copenhagen town hall.I was going to mention how  urlLink Gerd Achenbach , President-for-Life of the  urlLink International Society for Philosophical Practice , under whose auspices this conference has been organised, and is generally credited with founding the profession of philosophical counselling in 1983, had sat down next to me at dinner, and basically had given me shit about not drinking, which made me lose x amount of respect for him, although I guess I didn't really have much anyway. I tried explaining to him about straight-edge in German, but quickly slipped into what I generally do in German, which is lying by saying what I know how to say instead of the truth. Ultimately I told him that my edge was something I had sworn myself to as a youth and therefore upheld. His response was to say, literally, "Respect". He has a much, much younger girlfriend with him and is surrounded by a cabal of black-wearing grey-haired German acolytes. Other than them, no-one seems to like him. Last night me and my conference-buddy Drew Chastain rented bikes for 20kr. (the system here is like with shopping trolleys, where you put 20kr in the slot and the bike is released, and then when you bring it back later and plug it back in, the 20 is rereleased) and cycled over to  urlLink Christiania . It was kind of difficult to work out what was going on there in the darkness - there wasn't a lot of street lighting - but it was a bit different to what I'd been led to expect. We basically though it was like  urlLink Tivoli , where we'd been earlier in the evening, minus the entry charge and rollercosters. Cops were patrolling and there were heaps of little capitalist enterprises, like restaurants and bars. The had a big screen TV projection. Clint Eastwood's Unforgiven was showing so I watched that while Drew drank. I was pleasantly surprised by what an awesome movie it was. At the end of the night, after a visit to one of Copenhagen's zillion 7-Elevens, where I palmed a Daim ice-cream, I rode home on my twenty-krona bike and abandoned it outside the hostile hostel, where I found it this morning, gone, unsurprisingly. Ok, as a final musing on this country, I have to observe the incredible unhealthiness of the diet of these people, which undoubtedly goes a way to explaining there porcinity. First, smoking is rife and you can smoke pretty much anywhere compared to Australia. Secondly, beer drinking is of course very popular. Thirdly people drink Coca-cola as if it was water, much as I once did - well, actually, I've been off that wagon since I've been here becuase they've been laying the shit on in glass bottles. Fourthly, the most ubiquitous food is sausages. In the Seven-11s, there's like a massive frying area with five types of sausage, including sausage wrapped in bacon, plus sausage rolls. Hot dog stands are everywhere. Just thinking about it makes my stomach contract painfully. On the other hand, this shit is counteracted by the incredible bicycle culture of this city. Cycle lanes are real lanes, not just a designated area at the side of the road, on all the main roads. 50% of Danes reportedly cycle to and from work. It's awesome. Sadly the 20kr. municipal/tourist bikes are, though of sturdy desing, fucking slow, which diminished my enjoyment somewhat.
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have been having unprecedented problems staying straight-edge while in Copenhagen. I actually underwent somewhat informal philosophical counselling for this problem in a bar last night. I actually had a sip of Carlsberg from a bottle I was offered and in fact found that I wanted to drink the lot. The counselling session had the function of refreshing my ideas about why I became sXe in the first place.It also invovled reflection on why I felt the need to drink now. Being here, staying in a shitty youth hostel away from friends means that I do not have positive alternatives to the nihilstic resort to drugs. Except, as I realised, it was my guiding thought in becoming sXe that there were  always  positive alternatives. In this spirit we set off for the red light district, except that in fact I didn't really want to go there, but anyway I didn't drink the beer, so good. Earlier in the day I was so fucking close to having a cigarette. I'd managed to tell myself that I could smoke here and no-one need ever find out. The only thing that stopped me was that the lady I was going to blag a fag off of, Michela, only had one left in her pack, I saw, which meant that poolitness overcame my craving. So my edge remains essentially unbroken (I am satisfied that the sip of beer didn't count - I had one before a few months ago. I've had drags off cigarettes too actually, which is far worse. Still I consider this behaviour really fucking mild to the point of not really mattering in the general scheme of abstinence) due oinly to chance and not my strength of will. But whatever. Fuck, it's a close shave really, because I guess once you've had one cigarette the danger of having more is enormous, because once you've broken the edge you might as well just go crazy. This is the whole reason to be straight-edge: your edge is the only thing that stands between you and uncontrolled drug-use (because then the drugs and the highs and the cravings control your use). It's also why what Ray Cappo said in an interview I read is so important, that if someone breaks their edge, the last thing we should do is turn our backs on them, but rather try to help them, because otherwise they will never get back on the wagon.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, I'm just skipping out on a session of the conference I'm at (Philosophical Practice - A Question of Bildung?, The 7th International Conference on Philosophical Practice) to blog. It is incredibly hot in the 'info-bar' here I am, in the gorgeous Copenhagen Business School - business schools being generally nice for obvious reasons. First thing to say: do not stay in  urlLink Sleep-In Heaven  if you actually want to sleep. The IKEA sleeping barn is located right next to the IKEA bar and common area, in somewhat un-IKEA backpacker noise is generated until 2 in the morning. Lying in bed I nearly fell asleep until some Australians got in from the bar and woke me up, mostly by making me panic that they were stealing my stuff. Then I found it really hard to get to sleep. Evidently I was not the only one - every five minutes new sleepers would enter the dorm and make noise and there'd be a chorus of ten people simultanously shushing them. I thought that that was really gay, but I guess at least it was an international way of telling someone to be quiet. Then at 8 everyone got up, including me. I was in a massive hurry to get to the Business School for my conference breakfast, but when I got there it was just a croissant - a far cry from the fried filth buffet they had laid on at Lancaster. They're feeding us pretty well though - the lunch buffet had some really awesome roast beef. That said, I fucking paid enough for it. Anyway, those Australians, apparently Sydneysiders, made me realise how joyously dislocated I am - their accents sounded so weird to me, but I also haven't reaclimatised to the whole English thing - all English people sound like Northerners to me (except a few Essex people) with their clipped vowels. I'm sweating too much in here now, so I'm going to fuck off.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes you just gotta take time out and write in your blog, y'know?  I've been in Copenhagen for 12 hours and am dying to share my observations with people. My primary observation is about the people. Danish people just have this hilarious thing going on where they all have this kind of short, round-faced phenotype, like they've been eating too much of their Danish bacon or interbreding with their Danish pigs. It's funny because all the population around them, the othr Germanic people, us, the Germans, even the other Scandinavians, are taller than them. The Danes are blonds, but that's about it. On the other hand, I totally fucking dig this place. Cycle paths here are full on lanes in the road that you step into at your peril. The girls are all kind of pleasantly pretty, although none of them are really hot per se. And everyone's so nice! This must be like the nicest country on Earth. I was expecting them to be like Germans, having hardly met a Dane before coming here (presumably since their all just sitting around Jutland trying to restrict their gene pool), but in fact they (a) all speak  perfect  English, even more so than the Dutch and (b) they're just really fucking helpful. On a tangent, I can't believe how rough the girls are in London, which I transitted through yesterday. I think I saw a cute Latin girl crossing King St. in Hammersmith, but that was it, and I can't even be sure about that one. Bang goes my theory that concentrations of capital suck in fit girls from the surrounding areas. Ok, so in Copenhagen I'm staying in this backpackers called Sleep-In Heaven that looks like an army barracks you bought at  urlLink IKEA . Just one large hangar with three-storey metal bunk beds in an IKEA-style. Of course, the entire town is like an IKEA version of a world in which the Nazis had won the Second World War. Except there's a few darkies about, speaking Danish and being preposterously cheerful.
    
</post>


</Blog>