<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So today was not the best day. I stopped by the management company that i was suppose to be renting a townhome from today and they told me the maintainace man for the complex resigned and they would not be able to get the place ready until September, so they gave me my check back and wished me luck. To say the least I was a little frustrated. And of course what do I do when under stress, but cry. I wish I could just get mad and yell like other people, but not me I just cry. I now have two weeks left on my lease and no place to live after that.  All of the apartments in my current building are fully leased. So now I have to find a place in the next two weeks from the few places that remain available. Yeah, so that really sucks.  This past weekend I went to Green Bay for my nephew Owen's baptism. It was nice to finally get to see him. A lot of my family was there which was nice but a bit overwhelming at times too. I was really tired from the whole event. It was a long drive up there for a short time, but I don't think I could have handled much more of all of the stimulation that was in my brother's house with the numerous loud nieces and nephews and opinionated siblings and overbearing in-laws (not mine, my brothers).   So I dont' really have anythign else to report here. Sorry for the somewhat negative post, but like I said, this wasn't the best day. Hopefully the rest of the week will be better. I will keep you updated on the under-pressure apartment hunt.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So here I am back to the prairie that I call home in Champaign Illinois. I actually wish that I didn't have to be back here already, not that I would like to stay in the desert of Las Vegas, but I was home in Wisconsin this past weekend and would have like to stayed longer.   So to go to where I left off with my last post, I was waiting to leave on my trip to Vegas. On Tuesday I went to get a few last minute things at Wal-mart before I left town and ended up being stuck there for over two hours. It seems that a tornadoe came through Champaign and so Wal-mart was in a code black which means that everyone has to go to the center of the store and hang out in the clothing department. It was a pretty interesting experience and I ended up buying a lot of unneccesary items from the department of the store. There was one couple in there who were getting it one. I am pretty sure they wanted to write in to cosmo as the craziest place they have ever done it being in the center of a packed Wal-mart. I did get a free cookie and bottle of water out of the deal though. When we were finally able to leave, the electricity had gone out and we weren't even able to buy what we had come there for. We leads me to my next point.   I had gone to Wal-mart to buy a camera. As you may know, I have terrible luck with cameras. Just so you know I have not lost my digital camera, but it is in need of repairs. The zoom button keeps popping out and I keep losing it. It is a pretty common thing with my model of camera. It is still under warranty if I can find the reciept. The problem was however, that if I sent it in I would not have it for my trip and at that point I had misplaced the little zoom button. So I went to Wal-mart to buy a camera. I had been thinking about buying a film camera again, but had planned on getting one on ebay, but under the pressure of time decided to try to get one at a real store. At Wal-mart I found an awesome deal on 115 zoom pentax camera so I decided to buy it. I also had to buy the 7 dollar battery and film. I did end up getting my button back before the trip however so I took both cameras to Vegas. At the airport, I could not check my new camera however because the x-ray will ruin the film so I had to carry the camera, and I didnt' have a carry on bag. We got to Vegas and left our luggage at the hotel but could not check in. We walked around the strip all after noon and I had a bunch of random items because I did not have a carryon bag to put them in. Well by the time we got back to the hotel to check in, I was one random item short but had not really noticed because my hands had been full the whole time. I no longer had my new camera. I am pretty sure where I left it but of course it was gone by the time we went back there. So a brand new camera with a brand new battery and roll of film went to someone. I did not take one picture with it.   Other than that the trip to Vegas was pretty uneventful. We did a lot of walking around in the desert heat which was not so much fun. Overall, I was not very impressed with Vegas. Contrary to belief, I don't really like to gamble that much and when I did gamble the slots there don't pay out for crap. All and all though, for gambling I came out about 4 dollars ahead thanks to a 20 dollar penny slot win. Our trip was not well planned so we spent most of our time trying to decide what to do. If I were to go again, I would plan it better and go to one or more of the big shows and do some tours of the area, such as the hoover dam or grand canyon. We did end up going to a pretty funny topless show on afternoon and then to a female impersonator show. There are a lot of men out there way pretty than a lot of women I know. Pretty than me. I didn't really like Vegas as a whole very much though. If I were a terrorist Vegas would be the first place I would take out. It is such symbol of American waste and greed. Standing there looking at all of the huge casinos in the middle of a desert trying to outdo each other just because they can, I can understand why we as americans can so easily be hated. Vegas seems to celebrate all of the worst parts of humanity.   I was in Viroqua this past weekend for a high school friends wedding. That was a lot of fun. It was fun to see a lot of people I had not seem in quite a few years. It is great how there are some friends you can be apart from for years but things don't change. After the dance we went to the bowling alley and I saw Joey my used car salesman and crush. I also found out who he is currently dating, and he is so in my league. If only I were closer so i could woo him.   My nephew Spencer from Phoenix, formerly of Salt Lake City, is in Viroqua right now and I spent as much time as I could stand with him on Sunday. Monday I drove back here. I had my nephew Trevor along for the ride and delivered him to Indiana where he is staying with my sister Dawn for a week or so. I am back here avoiding work and tending my garden. My garden was damaged by the storm that trapped me in Wal-mart, but is still producing strong. My tomatoes are finally beginning to ripen at a good pace and I am getting ripe corn. I even already have pumpkins that are orange. It is kind of crazy. I am beginning to prepare to move in couple of weeks to my townhouse. I am having a hard time finding moving help as my family is busy or on vacation that week/weekend. I guess they dont' think helping me move is a vacation.   Anyway, I think that is all for now.  I would love to hear from you all so please feel free to leave comments on my posts.   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So here is my first official Carrie' Life update. Some of you reading this may already know some of this but I am going to just bring you all up to date on my summer.  So anyway, we are told here that the summer is some of the best time to get research done since we do not have classes and can focus solely on our lab work. This however has not been the case for me. I feel like I have done no work this summer. This is partly due to the fact that I have been gone from Champaign basically every weekend and some of these have been long weekends. The nature of the work I do is such that I have to set up experiments a few days in advance. When you are leaving every few days this makes getting work done some what difficult. This however has not deter me from taking up nearly every trip or diversion offered to me. Another setback I encountered was that at the beginning of the summer I managed to kill the cells that I work with. When this happens, it takes about a week to get some new ones going again before you can do any experiments. The result  of all of this is that I feel I have putzed around this whole summer. I am thinking I will get some work done sometime in August.  Tomorrow nite I am driving to my sister's near Chicago because my sisters Dawn and Julie and I are going to Las Vegas for a few days. It should be an interesting trip. I have no idea what all we are going to be doing. I don't think any of us are that big of gamblers. I plan on spending some quality time with the nickel slots though. Other than that I don't know. Dawn and I are pretty much going because Julie told us too. Julie is going for a convention for work so her company is paying for our stay at Caesar's Palace. Julie is paying for my plane ticket because I am going to stay with her kids when she and her husband go to San Fransisco. So I will go pretty much anywhere if they trip is free. I am not looking forward to the scorching heat of the desert though. Maybe I will find a man and get married while I am there.   When I get back from Vegas I am going directly to Viroqua for the weekend where a friend from high school is getting married. I am not sure how long I will be staying there but I am looking forward to seeing friends I have not seen in some time.   My brother Vince and sister in law Amy had a new baby boy on June 10th.  They named him Owen Paul (or Opie as my sister Carla likes to call him).  You can check him out  urlLink  here  . They have asked me to be his godmother which is exciting. I will be going to Green Bay the second to last weekend in July for his baptism.   I have been to Indianapolis several weekends this summer. I was just there this past weekend with my new roommate and her son. We went to the zoo and a minor league baseball game on Saturday. It was both fun an exhausting. At the end of May a friend of mine, Donna, from the micro department, and her 6 year old son, Ethan ,moved in with me after she found herself  without a place to live. It has been interesting having a kid around. It has been okay having them live with me but I do not think we will continue to live together through this coming year. (Yes I still view years as school years). I like Donna and I like Ethan, things can just get complicated though. It was a fun weekend with them though and it was nice that Ethan and Grant got to play together.   I think I have found new place for next year. I have my application in on a two bedroom townhouse. I am excited to move to a place a little more independent and with some green space. I will have a front porch and a back patio as well as a yard. I will  have washer and dryer hookups so I will feel grown up. If I decide, I can even have a dog at this place. It is all very exciting. It is about 100 sq ft bigger than my current place but feels bigger because it has an upstairs. Rent will be about $100 a month more than I am currently paying but I definitely think worth it. The only other downside will be that I am moving further away from campus, but I don't think that will be that big of a deal. I think I will be moving there the first weekend in August.  Besides work, I have a garden to keep me busy this summer. I rented a garden plot from the Champaign park district for the summer. So far it has been very productive. I planted tomatoes, peppers, beans, peas, pumpkins, watermelon, cucumbers, zucchini, summer squash, canteloupe and corn. So far I have had a lot of squash and corn. In about a week I am going to be up to my ears in Tomatoes. Right now I have well over 100 green tomatoes not even counting my cherry tomatoes. I think my corn will be ready soon too. It has been a lot of fun and it is great to have fresh vegetables.  It bring the extras to my lab and offer them as gifts to the crazy chinese tech. It seems to please her. She dislikes me less now and is in a better mood for the whole lab.   Not much else is new with me. Oliver and Kingsford are doing well. They have gotten big and Kingsford somewhat fat. He has man boobs.    Hope you have enjoyed my update and I will post again when I return from Vegas Carrie  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so it was probably only a matter of time before I got a blog.  I really didn't want to a blog because I think they are a little pretentious; it assumes that people out there really want to read the day to day happening of me. Sounds a little self important. But here I am with a blog. Whether or not you read it is up to you.  So why did I get a blog if I don't really like them? Because I am lazy. I want to keep in touch with all of you (ie my friends) but tend to get a little involved in nothing and don't keep you all up to date enough in my life. So here I will post what is happening with me and if from time to time you wonder what I am up to you can check in here.  Of course I will still welcome phonecalls, emails, and visits to catch up with me, and I will continue to do the same, (at the same rate I do now, which I apologize for it being so infrequent).  So I hope you will check in from time to time. Carrie
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So it has been awhile since I posted. I have been kind of busy lately. I moved last week to a new apartment in Urbana. I think I am going to put a weight limit on all new furniture I acquire. The hassle of moving I think is almost enough to keep me here for a long time. I am settling in now. I think it will be awhile before I finally get everything unpacked. I have just mostly been doing it as I need to. I got my phone hooked up on Saturday so I have the internet again and just got my cable hooked up today. I have now settled in to watch the Olympics.  I like a lot of stuff about my new apartment better than my old place. It has a nicer and more usable kitchen and more useful living space. On the down side it has a smaller bathroom and less overall storage. It does have washer/dryer hookups which will be nice if I ever buy them. I am waiting to see how much of my deposit I get back from my old place and maybe use that as good down payment on them. I was planning on trying to find a used set but after moving a new set seems apealling because I can have them delivered.  I have had guest at my new apartment already. Dawn and family stopped here on there way back from vacation in northern Wisconsin on Saturday and spent the night here. I am looking forward to hosting more visitors here. Hopefully I will soon have a futon in my extra bedroom for guest to sleep on.  I am trying to get into a groove at work and get all the stuff I wanted to get done in August done. I am not being nearly as productive as I planned. It would be helpful if some of my experiments would start working. This summer has really flown by and unfortunately I have very little to show for it. The end of this week I have TA training to teach me how to teach and to not date my students. I am not too excited about that because it starts at 8 and goes til 3. That is early for me to be on campus and that is a long time to sit. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I am feeling a little better at the moment than I have for the past week. I just signed a lease for an apartment. I did this less than an hour ago at about 10:30 at night. Kind of strange, yes, but I think I am going to kind of like this place...mostly because of the apartment managers.  At first I thought they were a little strange, but by the end of tonite I really liked them and they were cracking me up a lot. They are from the former Soviet Union (from some small country I had never heard of) and with kind of thick accents. I can't understand a word the husband says which is funny because the wife warned me "my husbands english is not good but he likes to talk a lot". They are super friendly though and she told me I had beautiful eyes and was full of energy.  What I was thinking though was she thought my eyes were pretty because they probably looked really green because my eyes were red from crying all day. Yes, it was a stressful day.  I had a long talk today with my boss about whether I really wanted to be here. It was not that I dislike the work or the the program or my lab...it is just hard being here with no friends near. It gets kind of lonely. I think these are feelings I was having for awhile but didn't surface until I was under the stress this week of trying to find a place to live in less than two weeks. When I came down to it, I was frustrated about having to put so much effort into finding a place to live where I had so little that makes me happy here. I decided to talk to Joanna and let her in on what was going on with me, so that if I did decide to do something like leave, she wouldn't be shocked. It was good just to talk about things with someone. I think we decided to just take it a little at a time. Not that this is a huge break through. The problem was, I need to sign a lease and a year is a long commit to make when you are not sure you want to stay somewhere.  So, I went with a place I found that offered a 6 month lease. I do like the place I though. It is big...1000 sq ft, has w/d hookups, dishwasher, central air, lets me have my cats, two bedroom. Otherwise, it is just a standard apartment building. It is in Urbana, so I will be moving to a whole new city. I almost rented a pretty nice apartment right across from a park with a great view of a lake. It was nice, less expensive, smaller and without a dishwasher and washer/dryer hookups, but it did have a garage. I have the lease and everything. I think I got spooked by the whole commitment though. So tomorrow I have to go back and tell them that I am not going to rent the place, which I am not looking forward to. In other news, this past weekend (well actually from about midnite on Wednesday nite to midnite sunday, so kind of a long weekend) I had my niece Corianne while her parents were at a wedding in wisconsin dells. It was fun to have the little one here but she can really tear a place apart. I wish I hadn't been so stressed because I think I really would have enjoyed the weekend more. We went to a fair and to the park and just kind of hung out. She is and adorable little girl, with some wild hair. I think she will have hair just like Sarah's. She is the only baby I know that they send hair products with in the diaper bag. Anyway, I have lost my train of thought so I will wrap this up. I hope to get to see you all soon, as I miss you much
     

    
</post>


</Blog>