<Blog>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Time : 2:23 P.M.  Date : July 20, 2004 Tuesday  Status : Tired  First things first, I have no classes and tomorrow will be my PE classes! ^_^ yipee! Since I have no classes today, I decided to pay a visit to my school and buy myself a PE uniform and a textbook for English. After the ride, I made my way straight to the school bookstore, look for the textbook and uniform and *poof*! Guess what?! The PE uniforms were SOLD OUT!   But it’s ok, there are more thing that have happened later this day ^_^.   After that surprising moment, I decided to go to the mall *harharhar*. But, the thing is, I rode a different jeepney! O_O. But my optimistic mind said that “Hey! This is your chance to make an adventure in the city!” So there I was, with my little “adventure” in the big city! ahihihi.   From Herrera Street, I started walking and guessing my way to G4. While walking, I realized that “Hey, there are so much business people walking around within the feet of the buildings with towering heights!” I know it sounds so much like “promdi” but hey!, I’m just a 15-year-old kid walking alone!   While walking at the other side of the street, I passed by the building of Allied Bank of the Philippines. I was impressed by their security system! It’s like, you’re going inside an airport! Before I continue, I would like all of you to know that I am carrying Kuya Lance’s laptop because my other files and documents are there AND still not uploaded by Kuya Lance, that’s why his laptop was on my hands.  Where were we? Oh yes! Te Allied Bank of the Philippines! I was passing it by and got amazed by it’s security system. So, while passing their main door, I was looking at their entrance, a security guard so me and *poof* the guard became a genius an suspected me as a *drum roll* HACKER!!! If you can imagine me, wearing casual clothing, carrying a bag and a laptop, will I look like a hacker? (Kuya Lance, you owe me one again!)   The guard approached me and asked me some questions. After some time, I was finally clear! I have no idea that that’s the only thing I need to do! And “that” is to show my ID to prove that I am a legal student. So finally, the security guard let me go and still, I have my mission, “To find my way to the mall!”  After minutes of walking and seconds of breathing, I’m finally here! Outside Greenbelt, sitting here on a platform, watching the cars and jeepneys pass by.  That’s all for now.  Ciao!  P.S.: Kuya Lance, you have one kick-ass laptop!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Time : 8:47  Date : July 19, 2004  Monday  Status : Tired  Well… the first week of college is over and guess what? I SURVIVED! ^_^ So… I want to share with you guys what happened from Day 1 till today (yipee! sharing time!)   	 DAY 1 : A fresh start 	 monday  The first day (of course!) It all started in the hallway. I don’t know what I am going to do! Then… the bell rang… everybody was gone… they were in there respective rooms… but me, I’m having doubt entering the room because I heard someone saying “Alam ko hindi pa pwede pumasok sa room ‘pag walang prof…”.  Since I don’t see any “Prof” that time… I decided to stay in the hallway. After 15 minutes of doing absolutely NOTHING… I decided to enter the room since the lights are open… And after 10 minutes of sitting and behaving myself in the best manner… someone stands up and said “Sige na nga! Simulan na nga natin!” And there goes the first subject!  The second one… well… we met a professor who speaks like a very popular person in politics!   As for the third class… I don’t really want to blog about it ^.^ just IM me if you want to know what happened…    	 DAY 2 : I’m one lazy bum! 	 tuesday  Nothing special ‘bout this day… except for the fact that I finally got my ID! That’s all!  	 DAY 3 : My “piss off” day! 	 wednesday   This day was supposed to be my first “PE” classes so I woke up early, got on a bus, and at last! I finally made it to school! I arrived 30 minutes earlier and waited there for my classmates… After a few minutes, I saw Ronnie and Joel (I met them during our medical examination) and chatted with them a little bit… After I told that it’s my PE classes that day, Ronnie told me that there are no PE classes until July 19! So to make the long story short, I came to school for NOTHING >_  The fun thing is… Our professor in our last subject was absent! It only means one thing… EARLY DISSMISSAL! So our barkada decided to have a snack at Mc Donald’s. After loads of foods and laughs… we finally bided our farewells  	 DAY 4 : One fun discussion! 	 thursday  At this day… we only have one class… do you think it’s good?…. NOT! Can you imagine a subject that will last for 3 hours? So much for that, I thought it was gonna be a boring subject… but no! It has been a great one!   DAY 5 : A new alliance! 	 friday  This day is the start of a new and improved “alliance”! yipee! Before the class started, Mojo-Kat invited us to watch a movie! Then… our professor came in and we convinced him to watch with us the next day since he will be the only professor for the next day… Sadly, he declined but he gave us a consolation, he promised us that he will dismiss us early the next meeting! w0ot! Its’ final! Our block will have a gimmick the next day!  	 DAY 6 : Bonding Time! 	 saturday  At this day… we only have one subject… AGAIN! This time, even longer! 4 and half hours of just one subject! But because of what our professor promised us, we were dismissed early! WAY too early! Our class just lasted for like 2 hours!   After Classes… Me, Mojo-Kat, Tina, Joey, Marco, Vincent, R.J., Benrie, Ei, Bren and Ryan decided to go to the mall and watch a movie! But before that, we ate our lunch/snack for the day and then… whooooooooosh! there goes the idea of watching a movie but there’s even a better idea! We will have our “class picture” there and hang out in Timezone in G4. I have to say “I’m sorry…” to all the guys that we left behind that day, I really feel like a total jerk whenever I leave without saying “Goodbye” to everyone. So… SORRY!  	 DAY 7 : Yet another “piss off” day! 	 sunday  It’s CWTS day! But still, I don’t know my section! T_T. I went to Mapua-Intramuros but still no sign of my section! So, I called my mom and say “Mom, I really have no idea what exactly am I doing here!” O_o. Of course! I ended up home! And ranted in front of my mom like “Is there such room as W430” O_o          DAY 8 : the wild side of the ride         Monday   I dunno if I’m gonna love this day or hate it… It all started in a jeepney. Well, the first incident was like this… a policeman was chatting with the driver in the front seat, they’re chatting ‘bout the laws and ordinances in the city… after the policeman was gone, I noticed that the road is clear, but yet, the driver isn’t driving forward… minutes later, I realized that there was another driver chatting with him which causes *pam pam pam* TRAFFIC! After the “jeepney” incident, the came the “bus” incident! What happened was, the highway was under the wrath of Mr. Traffic! I was sitting near the driver, it was an ordinary bus… minutes after, a song was played, an OPM one! At first, I found the song quite impressive, it SOUNDED like a pinoy version of Vitamin C’s song (Graduation: Friends Forever) but after a few more seconds, I was like “What is this?” The lyric was good but I dunno (again) if I’m going to be impressed by it! If you wish to know the title of the song, just IM me! The third was the ever-memorable “Drag Racing” incident! It was raining that afternoon and I rode a bus from Ayala to Pacita via Skyway. It was a medium kind of traffic, meaning, the volume of the vehicles was just few to many. I was glad to see that! But, the bus driver seemed to be a drag racer racing in the roads of Filinvest! With the slippery road cause by the rain, every brake is like a shoe sliding in the ice of Megamall skating ring! To think that we’re on Skyway, it was like a wild roller coaster ride! The last one, but definitely not the least, was the “jeepney accident”. I think I don’t need to explain this one anymore… >_   So that’s all for now…   Ciao!  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Time : 9:06 A.M  Date : July 19, 2004 Monday  Status : Sad... very sad  They finally bid their farewell to me... To clarify things up, here is the story...  I'd rather not to mention their name -_-  It all started in a message board when we met, then we decided to meet up in a mall... and that's where our "FUN" time began  After our little "adventure", we decided to form a group... with that group came contacts to each other... with that contact came our little "bonding" (awwww...)  After days of laughter and months of sharing insights... One of us decided to leave... It's okay for us if that one will just leave the group, but, that one decided to leave the country...  We were all shocked of that announcement. Now, I proved it to myself that whenever there are laughters, there will be tears... T_T  As of now... our friend is now on the way to the other part of the globe... We don't know if we will have contact again because of the timeline in other countries...  That's all for now, I'll blog again later 'bout some "school experiences"  Have a nice day!   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Time : 1:14  Date : July 13, 2004 Tuesday  Status : Blank  Well... my first blog in here so... nothing special...    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>