<Blog>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In my so-so recent history, I was confronted with an illness that left me in a desolate state. A helpful book at that time coined my infirmity as chronic fatigue. A friend advised me to go vegetarian and so I did. It was such a challenge to go veggie; not only for the simple fact that getting down strict and stringent with one’s meal is so un-Pinoy, but also, most people in society find the concept of vegetarianism boggling. Apparently, my willowy physique didn’t help much either in justifying my newfound remedy. But eventually, I started reaping the rewards of my discipline in a year or two. Going veggie wasn’t only economical but it made my domestic life simpler at all costs. What followed was a down-to-earth lifestyle that was liberating in itself. But then, after a few so-so years, I returned to eating meat out of conformity [for one, my mother-in-law will be insulted if I don’t partake in her sumptuous Sunday dishes].   Nowadays, when someone’s cranky, I turn cranky. And at the end of any emotional debate my only query is: what’s eating you, ba? [Don’t you ask that?] Some philosopher imparted that we inherit the characteristics of the animals we eat—devour or wolf. Out of observation, I kind of believe that, really. I eat a lot of poultry, and like mother hen, I sit on my “egg”; but then, despite my tuna recipes, I still fear the ocean. Today, there’s a yearning to go pure veggie again. It seems that there’s something to it that I miss [or perhaps due to this yap and woof that I wish to dismiss]. As I recall, someplace tucked in my journals is this floating personal premise: discerning good food is to be discriminating of the company you keep. Hmm, so timely that I have remembered it today. Somehow, I can figure what’s been eating me all the while. 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last Friday, my husband and I took our first serious attempt at “night entertainment” [our first ever since we welcomed our first-born into our lives]. We decided to have a quiet evening of acoustic Pinoy music at Conspiracy Garden Café, where accomplished musician-poet Joey Ayala was playing for the night. The Friday crowd was greeted with  Panganay ng Umaga  and was entertained with more creations from the artist’s archive.  Among the audience was Pinoy folk musician Florante, sporting a pink shirt sans the familiar long hair. Mandated by his companions, Florante rendered us a few songs, and a load of hilarious quips that made the house [note: Conspiracy is literally a house] guffaw in all its corners. His songs brought back a lot of memories from the old days, and without intention, I can’t help but associate his songs with the Marcos era of my youth. His lyrics were so amusing [and funny at that] so much that  May I Go Out  brought the affecting realization that; indeed, those were the first most important words I had to digest in school! Well, aside from Florante’s hairdo, a lot of things have changed—yet much of the old world remains as well [a matter of perspective, here].   Part of our nightcap was some of Joey’s mellow alternative hits complemented with biographical inputs volunteered in jest. By this, Joey’s songs became more tangible to us in thought. For me, songs  [and other art expressions for that matter] are articulate expressions of a certain time and space brought to the surface; and underneath every poignant creation is a story that shall never be eliminated nor changed in any time in history. That is why probably, I favor to hear songs where it can possibly be most intimate and animated. When the phenomenon is heard, there is the realization of the universal connection, which some of us, if not all, seek to recognize and remember.  
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      People are often unreasonable, illogical, and self-centered; Forgive them anyway. If you are kind, people may accuse you of selfish, ulterior motives; Be kind anyway. If you are successful you will win some false friends and true enemies; Succeed anyway. If you are honest and frank, people may cheat you; Be honest and frank anyway. What you spend years building, someone could destroy overnight; Build anyway. If you find serenity and happiness, they may be jealous; Be happy anyway. The good you do today, people will often forget tomorrow; Do good anyway. Give the world the best you have, and it may never be enough; Give the world the best you've got anyway. You see, in the final analysis, it is between you and God; It was never between you and them anyway. --Mother Teresa 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having a new acquaintance named Macrina is a unique experience. To begin with, I haven’t met anyone named Macrina [there’s this song though that strikes in my head]. Young and pretty Mac, as I got to know her, is a creative and gifted being. She showed me some of her raw art, which she neatly collated in her journal; and I got to feel how elating it was for some people to share some particles and elements of themselves so candidly. Some people, on the other hand, exercise a huge amount of effort to keep others at bay. Mac and I didn’t talk much, such that our sporadic conversations consumed only 15 minutes [or thereabouts] of our built-up lives.   My short chat with Mac stirred a spontaneous depiction of two swirling rainbow atoms engaged in affable tête-à-tête. It is amusing if you see it this way [also a handy tool when you encounter intolerable atoms down the stream]. Spurred by a personal resolution to accept people for what they are and to accept myself for what I am in a larger field of reality, this “atomic inspiration” [as I call it], allows deliverance from what is commonly viewed as offensive, ghastly or cataclysmic.  That same evening with Mac, other observed atoms in the room were pulling attempts to combust with the seemingly delectable atoms in sight. Irksome, perhaps, but that is how some atoms behave. So as Mac and I continued to enjoy the music in between our conversations; and conversations in between songs, a glimmer of gratification graced our meeting. The atomic goddess dancing on the candle-lamp atop our table seemed to have been enjoying herself, too. And so, the evening faded, and the atoms turned into tiny yawning bubbles as the music played. I bade Mac farewell as we end another day, and perhaps, meet each other again in the stream of dreams.  
    
</post>


</Blog>