<Blog>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      harlox. i'm pissed today. i dunno y. i had nafa today. went quite ok i guess. my muscle hurts a lot. i'm gonna die. arghx. did 2.4 today.run the third round.. had leg cramp.hobbled all the way to the gate. sprinted a bit.then fourth round, my shoulder started cramping.ughx.&nbsp;after i finish the fifth round.. i had locked jaw..!! arghx.. not to mention my bloody scraped knee that i had when the toopid dance member pushed me down during captain's&nbsp;ball on sat. hurt sia.. ahah but the game was fun man!2.4&nbsp;timing was not that good though. 14.26s. i mean. 14 secs? lolx. wat eva.hmm. i dunno whether i wanna dance tchers day. i dun feel like dancing la.. but huda la.. she like if i dun dance i scared she not happy.dunno la. really dun feel like dancng. helpx. haix. ok. i can't even do sit ups lehx.. and i weigh so "lite" act like so light la.. 5o kg plus.. hahah i'm a piggy!! lolx.. i have heavy bones!! anyway,i went to malaysia yesterday to visit my cus land. at a veri posh place, called lesiure farm. had a horse riding place la.. club la.. swimming pool la.. sia la.. oh well. when i came home today i intended to use the com. buden my mom and dad use the fone like , going to tell dunno hu there life long story like dat.. i got so fustrated man. haix. so many tinks to do sumore. newsltter editing, ipw, maths homework, art home work. 2 painting lehx. tml sumore gt chinese spelling. have to interview that son of a bitch bala. then on wednesday gt bio and chinese test!! helpx~~~~~~~~~~~`` i'm dying soon!! &nbsp; gtg with dying love, shirin the dead 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, today nth realli much happened, cept' there was e.v today. e.v was FINE MAN! can't beleive that bala exaggerated it.. wat study the vision , mission. motto la.. wat rubbish.. they onli asked us qns. which was quite ok la..haha i was toking beri the loud.. dunno y la..the meeting onli lated for 45 mins tops. sooo short! we were told it will last until 3.30pm.. but we came out at 2 plus.. which is like BLISS~hahah after the e.v thing.. i had the sang nila utama thingy.. we wanted to use the hall at first but the dance members were there, with gym mats and all.. bvleahx.. anyway, we went to the music rm. we practised there.. it was quite fun..haha aniway, shino was doing lame stuff... wat the heck.. as usual. y does he always do tht man.. too bad his not in drama..he'll really knock the audiences out of their seats. aniwae, my class was practisin tq.. i tink its tml, if i'm not wrong.. wateva, not as if i'm big on i.. i dunno y but i dun have much confidence hahah wat the heck..i'm such a bitch..aniway.. ihave like loads of tests this week.. and i'm going to DIE SOON!! I'M studying for my social studies test now.. i havent even do my homework.. sobx sobx.. i tink i'm gonna be stressed out!!!!!!!!!!ahhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!! haix.. tired.. ciao~ gtg..study time. burn the midnite oils!!!  hugs and kisses: shirin!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      halloo babes! u mite be wondering wat CubBabe means rite. well, apparently it my username, ahha suggested to me by swenson..(thanks dude!) cos i was totally blank. i just used my name in my previousl blog. haha well CubBabe means chubby babe, tentatively refering to my chubby cheeks thats APPARENTLY baby fats!! and the babe is referring to me.. ahhaha! i'm a vainpot and a huge drama queen!! Arghx! I HATE it when ppl try to pinch my cheeks and end up pinching my jaw bones instead. tht gives me a bruise ya noe! so there, u buncha morons! pinch the CHEEK!! not the JAW BONE!! u BlInD oR wAt!! enuf of tht rantings. weell, i'm not gonna intro myself cos ppl who read my blog probably noes me , not tht well, but hu the heck cares.ok.. ii' really sleepy today i dunno why.. stayed in school for the humanities week play.. snag nila utama. i tink its gonna be cool larx. hope that we'll make it to b come a mordern history-play or sumtink like dat. ppl was having these cheers comp in the hall.. it looked quite fun man, although it was beri..erm..messy.. but wat the heck. i heard that most of the class that went to the cheer competition got into. well, congrats peepx!yawnx.. realli sleepy. guess wat. i forgot to bring my physics txtbk to class.. and no one cares!! muahahhah..i' lame forgive me.anyway.. nites freaks!!!!!!!!!!!11 ahha just jk!   signing off, sealed with deliverance, shirin!!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>