<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last 2 weeks - Crazy at work but found some time for play. 2 weeks ago went to the Goring on Thames Regatta - played at who can drink the most Pims whilst competing in tug of war competion (lost in final), and rowing race (came second too and fell in at end). Last weekend had a good night at a nice pub by river.. will elaborate at some point in future. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.thewhitehouselondon.co.uk/wh_main.html  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Worked 7 days a week for 3 weeks.  W/end 1 to see the chilli peppers @ Hyde park... Absolutely brilliant.  W/end 2 managed to walk straight into George Micheals 41st Birthday and stay until 0730hrs the next day. Included a number of silly stories I won't go into right now. You'll have to ask!  W/end 3, went to a very good friends new flat Nr Clapham common for a meal and wine, ended up partying at local cafe. This then turned into a next day outdoor venue called lovebox, absolutely awesome, saw groove armada, Mr Scruff, and some pixies when we overdid it...  W/end 4, back to the 7 days a week thing, holding out until our next major blowout in august/sept... HELP!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Men's English    "I'm hungry." = I'm hungry.   "I'm sleepy." = I'm sleepy.   "I'm tired."  = I'm tired.   "Do you want to go to a movie?" = I'd eventually like to have sex with you.   "Can I take you out to dinner?" = I'd eventually like to have sex with you.   "Can I call you sometime?" = I'd eventually like to have sex with you.   "May I have this dance?" = I'd eventually like to have sex with you.   "Nice dress!" = Nice cleavage!   "You look tense, let me give you a massage." = I want to fondle you.   "What's wrong?" = What meaningless self-inflicted psychological trauma are you going through now?   "What's wrong?" = I guess sex tonight is out of the question.   "I'm bored." = Do you want to have sex?   "I love you." = Let's have sex now.   "I love you, too." = Okay, I said it...we'd better have sex now!   "Yes, I like the way you cut your hair." = I liked it better before.   "Yes, I like the way you cut your hair." = $50 and it doesn't look that much different!   "Let's talk." = I am trying to impress you by showing that I am a deep person and maybe then you'd like to have sex with me.   "Will you marry me?" = I want to make it illegal for you to have sex with other guys.   and FINALLY... (while shopping) "I like that one better." = Just pick ANY dress and let's go home!   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...I'm a complete Blovice (Blog Novice) so any suggestions or comments are welcome!!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...wait out
     

    
</post>


</Blog>