<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Yep, Sunday was a sad day in our house. I hubby decided to get rid of his 1971 Camaro.&nbsp; He had it for 13 years.&nbsp; I was heart broken and mad because he traded for an 1986 Porsche 944 Turbo - 5 on the floor - with boarded out motor to a 951 that does less than 11's in the quarter mile.&nbsp; The car is candy apple red with black bra and trim work.&nbsp; Nice car but I want the Camaro back.&nbsp; I miss it.&nbsp; The Camaro is the car my then soon to be boyfriend - drove up in the first time I ever saw him.&nbsp; It was white with the most awesome flames on it.&nbsp; He won car shows with that car. But still, it's gone now. So, I will continue to mourn for a while even thought it is just a car.            
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
             I've noticed that most recently I have had a change in passions. I used to be all about books but since getting into cross-stitching -- the passion has faded slightly.&nbsp; Most natural, I believe.&nbsp; Soon I will tire of the stitching again and crave the books.&nbsp; Just need a bit of change in my life.&nbsp;            
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I'm tired but it's been a few days since I last blogged (oh that sounds naughty).&nbsp; LOL I realized today I have too much happening in my life.      Husband    Daughter    Dog    Cross-Stitching    Reading    Preparing for book discussions    preparing for quizzes    Chat groups - cat mysteries, cross-stitching, aussie dogs, 2 historical romance,&nbsp; and left behind    shopping    house cleaning    down time for me    Me - showers, sleeping, etc.    personal relationship with God     It's just way too much - time management is not my thing. (oh, forgot blogging on the list).&nbsp; LOL    How do I do it all - by letting some things suffer...by being selfish.&nbsp; The internet for me is very important - it's a drug...I feel that I must stay on top of stuff or I will lose out.&nbsp; Gosh, I wonder if I can turn off this thing. most likely not.&nbsp; It's my drug of choice.&nbsp; I wonder why I try to fit so much in a small day....longing for the simple life - before hubby and child.&nbsp; But it is the life I dealt for myself and I must live it.&nbsp; There are not enough hours in the day to do all that&nbsp; I want to do.&nbsp; Silly me requires sleep.&nbsp;     There is so much more I want to do....work a job, go back to college, write novels ( that will be tricky since I have no skills), do book reviews, and so forth!    What makes it harder is being with a man that doesn't help -- thinks that just because he works during the day out side of the home -- there is nothing for him to do here at the house.&nbsp; My hubby greets the dog better than our daughter - and I get nothing.&nbsp; No hug, No kiss, no hello - just grunts, complaints and where's my dinner.&nbsp; Ahhhh, the sounds of Ward Cleaver returning home.&nbsp; Yeah right - in my dreams.&nbsp; As the line goes in a movie (coyote ugly) "....he is good for a first husband..." or something to the effect.&nbsp; LOL I'm bad.&nbsp;     I'm tired.&nbsp; I want to be alone just for a little while to remember the good things about the stuff that is driving me bathe!&nbsp; Where's my pillow?&nbsp; It calls to me - begging for attention.&nbsp; And I will be its servant!&nbsp;     Later Gator     
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The back cover blurp caught my attention. ".....HELP! I'm stuck in Egypt with a pushy girl named Chloe, a cursed bracelet, and a hottie who makes my toes curl...." This seems like a silly type of book but I think I will enjoy it. It will be my next book to read and review.   I started reading this book and yes, it's silly.&nbsp; It is actually a Teen Romance genre.&nbsp; The language is annoying at times ... and I have to relax because this book is written from the point of view of a 16 yr old girl - who is feeling unworthy and unwanted by her family.&nbsp;   She has no self worth at times and it's make me want to slap her.&nbsp; Our Heroine (name escapes me at the moment) finds herself in Egypt on a dig.&nbsp; She meets a hunk of a guy that has a twin.&nbsp; Double the yummies.&nbsp;   The hitch is at first there is a comedy of errors because she is unaware of the twin thing.&nbsp;&nbsp; The first mystery is set when Jan (that's her name - January) is lost in a village outside of the Cairo.&nbsp; And 2 men attack her because of a "Handmaiden" -- Jan had no clue who or what that is.&nbsp; Mr. Hottie (aka Seth) rescues her.&nbsp;   Second mystery, why everyone thinks Seth is the evil twin (he and his brother are named after ancient twin gods) -- while I think it's the other twin.&nbsp; Seth is being cheated by his parents -- not being given the same chance to be educated in the States, etc.&nbsp; So Jan has been warned that being with Seth can lead to her getting hurt -- but she doesn't care -- she'll risk it.&nbsp;   What will the rest of the book reveal? We'll see!    I FINISHED THE BOOK......  Mysteries solved, Mr. Hottie finds redemtion with his parents and the girl gets the guy.&nbsp; It's a cute story and I'm not interested in the 2nd book.&nbsp; This book is going into the Wild most likely.    
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I just finished Canapes for the Kitties by Marian Babson.&nbsp; This is a good book. I&nbsp; love the cats: Had-I, But-Known and Roscoe.&nbsp; The first thing that bothered by about this book is the fact that it switched from Lorinda Lucas' novel back to the story at hand about Lorinda and her friends.The book of over 250 pages keep me guessing as to who the killer was - which I guessed by page 200 and confirmed later. Some of the characters were annoying - theAmerican Couple -- especially. I like the click between the 3 authors - Lorinda, Macho and Freddie. They are one big family. It's fun to see the differences between the authors and the characters that they created. But who is bringing their characters to life - is the question.&nbsp; And how many people will die? It's a fun book - some of the language throws me.&nbsp; Being an American is to blame for me.&nbsp; I'm not use to some words.&nbsp; It's a keeper. I give it an A.     
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         I've tried making wild releases in my town but no one seems interested.  Especially those that are B/C members - 51 on the rolls - most are not even active...just a name.  Those that are active - release their books 2 towns away.  Keep some of it in the area - would be nice.  I'm not traveling 20 plus minutes to hunt down a book - sorry.  Then there are non-members who pick up the book and do nothing with it.  That's okay I can understand.   I'm just bummed that I have set out 3 wild releases in a great little coffee house in an active strip mall and no one has picked them up. I feel foolish that I was able to seek out a great place for b/c, telling the owner there are members in the area, and so forth - but nothing! Plus bummed that it seems out of the 51 area b/c members I'm the only one that releases close to home. I'm tempted not to wild release anymore - yes, selfish - I do want the joy of knowing my releases are happy in a new home and not setting somewhere ignored! Part of the reason I joined bookcrossing.com was to get involved with the community around me - NOT the community 20 minutes away. And here is my other beef, those in my area seem to wild release at this one restaurant where the b/c meetings is held.  SPREAD IT AROUND PEOPLE!  SHARE!  BUILD UP YOUR OWN COMMUNITY! Thanks for listening -- I feel better now.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is my bookcrossing link - shows books in my library that are up for trade, have been traded or will stay in my library. http://bookcrossing.com/mybookshelf/angelnot  This is one of my book groups where I go to discuss Historical Romance Novels and what not. http://groups.yahoo.com/group/Romance_Historical/  This is my Cat Mystery book group. http://groups.yahoo.com/group/CatMysteries/
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Waiting for Gertrude by Bill Richardson Catnap  by Carle Nelson Douglas Familiar Mirage by Caroline Burnes Murder at Osgoode Hall by Jeffrey Miller Purrfect Love (3 novelas) by Macomber, Miller and Simpson Familiar Fire by Caroline Burnes Here Kitty Kitty by Winifred Elze The Cat Next Door by Marion Babson Tourist are for Trapping by Marion Babson
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I've been very busy. I'm sewing my little heart out. I have about 12 projects that need to be completed before December and I'm not sure it will happen.      I've not been reading a lot - maybe it was a mistake to join more chat groups....a couple of the new ones are the pits! Talking about silly crap! Oh, let's make this book into a movie...blah blah blah....     (thought just floated through my brain....My last blog didn't get spell checked...Oops.)     ....Discuss the books...There are 2 groups that read just one type of book (by a certain author) and therefore I guess they have to make things up just so they can chat. In one group I waiting for them to start RP...Oh boy!      I'm trying to read Sixpence Bride by Farmer and it's doing nothing for me! It's a average book - I keep hoping something will happen and when it does....It's blah! (yes, that's my word for the day.)     I'm going to have a busy day today: I need to finish a c/s project, start another one (ha ha), library to return overdue books, hit the craft store for floss, publix for some food, drive 30 minutes to pick up hubby because his car is in the shop. I still have sometime before I must go to the craft store...Maybe that will wait. I need more money to go.     OH GOSH...Forgot the most important part...Clean the ever dirty house! How do women keep it clean all the time? It seems impossible here.      The Peanut (DD) starts school in a week. Hooray....I'll be getting 9 hours of child-free time! Party Party Party     But what will I do with that time? Sew, read, excerise, clean the house, shop, ????????? decisions decisions     We'll see starting the 23rd. I have a parent meeting Friday the 20th - to learn more about her school and what is needed. I hope it all works out! I best be going - chat with you all later.     huggles   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
             This is the first book of Quinn's that I have ever read and was impressed!      When He Was Wicked is set in England and Scottland in the early 1800's. this is a powerful story about a man in love with his cousin's wife but no one knows. Michael loves Frannie with all his soul but is honor bound to keep away. But on one night, Cousin John, dies....Frannie is free....Michael is now Earl....but Michael still feels honor bound. Racked with guilt that maybe have wished it true. Poor Frannie losses her husband then days later loses the baby that she longed for....it took years for her to conceive.     Frannie also loses her best friend - Michael. Because he leaves for India to try and get his mind straight...get away from Frannie. But he still loves her. He can't hide for ever...so after 4 years -- he returns to find the love of his life in the manor house.      He hates the fact that he still loves her, wants her and can't have her.   But in the end love does win.       It takes a lot to push them in the right direction....but it was Michael who makes the moves.  Frannie's brother is the one who prompts Michael into action and somewhere on his way to find Frannie in Scotland does he find peace within himself to ask for her hand.  He forms a plan of seduction...but he wasn't expecting to be mutually seduced.  Frannie's passion wins but her mind fights her feelings.  It takes a long time and a sickness for Frannie to understand her new feelings for Michael and to feel that her late hubby - would be happy for the two of them.        It's not a fast moving story - but a gentle weaving of the emotions surrounding them and their mutual loss and love for John...then how the new love comes about.      It's a good book, well written, well told but not a great book...it deserves a B+.              
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
            Well, things are a bit better. Hubby has found a job - not the greatest but it will pay the bills and put food on the table until something better comes. Ex-Boss felt guilty and paid him a full week's pay. Then offered him a weekend's worth of work. So we'll be just fine. If a better job comes around.      I am so proud of him! He worked his butt off to get this job. He is a strong man. I love him to death. Each hardship makes me adore him even more.      He was so upset that I had to give things up because of the firing....that he made a little side money to give me the freedom to buy 2 books and buy some cross-stitching supplies. He is a cutie. He's so funny - he know me so well - I was going to shock the money away for a rainy day.....He says to me..."Buy the books and I want to see them." ha ha ha ha So I'm going out tomorrow and pick up 2 books.....but which ones.....there are so MANY!!!!!     I can't remember all that I blogged before but the baby (not such a baby) is off her sleeping schedule. I'll have to work harder to get her back on track.     As for me, I'm in a lot of pain with my back (herniated disks). I haven't popped this many pills in a year. The pills are very strong aspirins and anti-inflammatory. They eat my stomach up!     I've joined some new chat groups - hoping to find what is lacking in my others. I'm about to drop 2 old groups and drop 2 new groups. I won't mention them or why...because I know there are members of those groups that have read my blog. I will mention that I'm so disappointed in groups that promote group reads, discussions, etc and stuff is so out there.     Now I'm off to do a book review - When He Was Wicked by Julia Quinn.     Good bye all and thanks so much for your prayers and good thoughts.     One day soon I will be improving my blog. Stick around I may actually figure it out.     Huggles!        
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
            It started with me having very little sleep. This is not a good thing when it's been many days in a row. After waking up, Hubby decides to have attitude problems - nothing is right, no money saved, job sucks, he's overweight....Male PMS! Less then 2 hours after he leaves - I get a call .... He's been let go from the job. The boss wanted someone to work long and late hours. Hubby wouldn't do it. So a former employee offered to work 18 hour shifts - which will be rough since there is only 2 drivers (hubby is a tow truck driver) and they work 5 to 7 days a week depending on demand. The guy will not make it! Plus hubby was bring in extra work to the mechanic. The man will be sorry to have let hubby go.      Now we have little money to get through, bills are do this Saturday, rent is a hand full of weeks away......And so forth.     I'm stressed out and tired. My back is killing me - the disks are pinching nerves like there's no tomorrow. I'm taking my meds again and they make me cranky! I'm getting tired of some of my book groups - the Lion and the Thistle (they do almost nothing!) Why add another moderator when no one talks. The Historical Romance Group is getting too busy...They no longer do group discussions...I miss those. Then the biggest heartache was I was offered the ownership of my Cat Mystery group and I had to let it pass. I didn't think I could do a fair enough job. It requires a lot of research and I don't think I can do that. But it pained me so much that I ignored the message and let the other person answer first. Wahhhhhhhhhhhhhhh! Yvonne will be excellent. Debbie did a great job - it's just that I wanted it and couldn't in my hearts of heart take it! That sucks! I want my own group but I can't give it my all. So I will be looking for new groups - hoping to find chat groups that do things together.      Tonight, the baby refused to go to sleep tonight...Finally passed out. We are working on a new schedule to help her with preparing for school. She's fighting it all the way! ha ha. But she will love school ...Pre-K 3. What a big girl she is.      I have so much to do and there doesn't seem to be enough hours in the day. I have between now and the first of December about 6 cross-stitch projects, a half a dozen books to read and prepare discussions for, group discussions....And that is only on-line. I want to read more my book collection I believe is up to 180 books and more keep adding themselves to the group.      I need a break. I want to go to my sister in law's baby shower but can't go it's too far from here. "oh, I think I'll have some cheese with my whine!" Well, I must be off...I have to check out blogs of a couple friends, update my wish list, and prepare my new database for my cross-stitching stash. Oh, gosh! I need to check out Writerspace.com for the new contest and enter them. Okay it will be another long night. Plus, I just realized I need to finish up When He Was Wicked by Julia Quinn. I'm going to hate giving it away but no choice in the matter. More cheese please.      Huggles to all and thanks for listening .......Marta        
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
                      I need to blog today. It's been a while and yet still no time to devote to it. I have found myself very busy with with 2 adventures: Cross-Stitching (including the message board) and my CatMystery board (a moderator, leader of discussion, etc.) I love to read but I find as of late that working with my hands to create a beautiful piece of art work (cross-stitch) is very gratifying. Therefore, once again my historical romance passion is on the back burner on low heat. I'm happy just wish I had more time in the day.          But in a few weeks, my littlest one will be off to school 3 mornings a week. I hope to use that time for sewing, reading, physical activity, house cleaning....Things that are easier to accomplish without her willing fingers. God love her!          I had a wonderful surprise yesterday, Leya (wandeca - hope I remembered correctly) sent me a July in Christmas package - 3 books by Julia London: Beauty Queen, highlander Unbound &amp; Material Girl. The box also included a vanilla candle - yummy, post cards (which I love to mail to people) and a book mark (roses - my tattoo passion). Then I rec'd another book for my CatMystery group - Familiar Series and the beautiful historical cross-stitch.         The cross-stitch is called The Kiss. It would be a beautiful romance novel cover. It shows a lovely lady holding a cascading boutique of roses and the giver is behind her kissing the side of her neck. Romantic! I must figure out how to put pictures on this site, so you may see it. There is a whole series of these cross-stitches, I would love to have them all.         I best be off for now - mornings is my time before Sunshine wakes up. A little time to drink coffee, read, sew or watch the world start it's day. Huggles and Take Care                                 
</post>


</Blog>