<Blog>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nights @ CBC = 4 Days @ VVENT = 2
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Unabashed Racist Leads Tenn. GOP Primary   We've got Barack Obama; they've got this guy.  Your Republican Party: Building a bridge to the 19th century or the stone ages or worse.
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      after tonight, it's...  CBC = 4 nights VVENT = 3 days  can't wait.
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This has been a pretty normal week for me.  I'm finally getting used to the pattern and the way things work around here.    Every morning, my mommy comes home from work.  We usually go outside and play frisbee for a little while, unless Mean Max the German Shepherd who lives next door is outside.  Then, I have to stay on the leash because I'm not supposed to play with him.  But then, we'll go for a short walk so that I can pee-pee and poopie.  I usually go say hi to my friend Scout, the McCormicks' yellow lab.  He likes to play with me, and he tries to keep up with me, but he's too fat and slow to play very long.  My mommy calls him a "whale" and says that his family doesn't play with him enough.  One morning, there was new dog in our yard, a Jack Russell terrier, so I got to run around with him, too.  He was pretty fast and a lot more agile than me.  We wrestled in the grass when he wasn't hiding under the car!  Then we usually go inside and eat breakfast.  My mommy's pretty tired after working all night, so we take a nap until it gets really hot inside the house.  That's when I wake her up by crawling on her and licking her face.  Later, we get to go outside and have lots of fun.  Sometimes, we go mountainbiking.  Sometimes, it's hiking.  Or we play fetch with the balls and frisbees.  This week, I got to go to two softball games.  I was a very good boy and didn't bark too much during the game.  Sometimes, it's really hard not to though.  On Wednesday, I also got to run around with my friend Basco the Boxer.  He's bigger than me and likes to chew on my neck.  But I just figured out that I can dodge him with quick turns, just like that Jack Russell with me.  We tore all across the outfield after the game was over.  There were other dogs there, too, but I just got to say a quick hi.     Today, we went for a 7-mile mountainbike ride on the Optic Nerve trail in Eagle.  I must be growing because I can run a lot faster now.  I could keep up, even up to 17mph, for short time at least.  Plus, I know when I can get a head start sooner, so I don't get behind.  I like running through all the sage and chasing rabbits on this trail.  The soil was chalky, and when we were done I had white dust all over my face.  I wonder what we'll do tomorrow!  Love, Caesar
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Kerry Raps Bush on Initial 9/11 Inaction : "Bush spent seven minutes listening to 'The Pet Goat' being read at a Florida elementary school after his chief of staff, Andrew Card, whispered, 'America is under attack,' as televisions cameras recorded the anxious scene. "
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Panel Dismisses 'Fahrenheit 9/11' Complaint 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I ran out of gas. I, I had a flat tire. I didn't have enough money for cab fare. My tux didn't come back from the cleaners. An old friend came in from out of town. Someone stole my car. There was an earthquake. A terrible flood. Locusts. IT WASN'T MY FAULT, I SWEAR TO GOD."   -"Joliet" Jake Blues (John Belushi), The Blues Brothers (1980)   urlLink  more...   
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The New York Times > Opinion > Op-Ed Columnist: Reading the Script   
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CBC = 6 nights VVENT = 3 days
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Obama to Soon Have Black GOP Foe for Senate Race   Well, this is interesting.  GOP might put up former presidential candidate Alan Keyes to run against Obama.  While I obviously don't agree with Mr. Keyes on most issues, I've always found him to be an articulate and compelling speaker, much more so than say, Steve Forbes or Gary Bauer of 2000 also-ran fame.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Onion | Infograph   
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On reading:  "I was simmering, simmering, simmering.  Emerson brought me to a boil."  -Walt Whitman
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nights Left @ CBC = 7 Days Left @ VVENT = 3 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seeing as I only have about 2 weeks left here in the hotel and tourism industry, I feel that it is about time that I share some of the insights and funny little incidents that have happened to me during the last eighteen months.  The names may be changed, but stories are true.  I'm typing them up now, but I'll probably wait to publish later this month.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, regardless, his former legacy as a crusader against the abuses of corporate America is sullied irreparably by his continuing antics, including but not limited to running for president, thinking he can win, taking GOP money and ballot access help, etc. etc.    urlLink The New York Times > Washington > Campaign 2004 > Convictions Intact, Nader Soldiers On   The above article puts it nicely.  Like the "FNS: Fox News Sucks" section, there will more, much more.     Lefties love you, Ralph, but we are begging you to call it off.  And the latter does not exclude the former.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Nights left @ The Charter: 8 Days left at VVENT: 3 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The New York Times > Education > Education Life > College Prep: Trouble in the Ranks   Eliminate class rank in high school so that over-achiever students will focus on learning and pursuing their unique interests as opposed to chasing after hundreths of a point?  Wish someone had thought of that 10 years ago. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Plan to Ease Voter Registration for Spanish Speakers Stalled (washingtonpost.com)   ...do you think this would be such a problem?
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Convention Oratory, Increasingly Shoved Aside (washingtonpost.com)   Let's just see if Bill O'Reilly gives the Rs the same thoughful consideration.  I won't hold my breath, and neither should you, unless you're a Republican.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Polls Mixed on Kerry's Convention Bounce   Democrats are already behind this ticket and have neglected their usual intraparty squabbles.  Hopefully, we have learned something since 4 years ago.  The current state of affairs is what happens when the left can't get its act together.  Plus, most voters are already decided, so there were few to persuade.  The bottmline is that Ds are united and motivated to win, so look out come November.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Seek happiness for its own sake, and you will find it. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Onion | Infograph 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two nights ago, I got to go camping for the very first time.  It was pretty fun, but it was also very dark with lots of strange noises out there.  And I wasn't allowed to bark very much, even though I just wanted to protect my family and our campsite.  We slept in a tent, which reminded me of my "house" at home, but people slept with me in there, too.  The camp fire was very hot, so I couldn't get too close to it, even though I really wanted to stick my nose in it to see what it was all about.  Then the next day, we went for a 7-mile hike.  I ran around so much that I probably ran at least 10 miles when we were done.  I went swimming in Nolan Lake at lunch and chased pikas and squirrels.  Today I was so tired that all I did was sleep all day.  Love, Caesar
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink William F. Yurasko's Web site v. X - Updated Daily   ... my friend William for encouraging me to give in and set up the blog.  And now, go check out his blog by clicking above.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know that on my previous website I made some rather disparaging comments about web logs and the people who maintain them and now that I have one, I have reached the height of hypocrisy. Yep. Deal with it.  Maintaining a traditional website was just too cumbersome and inconvenient for me, given the tools available to me and my limited and dated knowledge of HTML, and that's why you saw so few updates to my previous site. So hopefully, with Blogger's much more convenient features, there will be more fresh content for both of you (and hopefully more soon) to read.  From this point forward, please consider me official converted to blogging!  Brenda  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Three Tampa city council members walk out during atheist's invocation: South Florida Sun-Sentinel   So let me get this straight...  If you're an atheist or agnostic or just someone who doesn't think prayer is appropriate in a government setting, you have to suffer silently through infinite numbers of invocations, prayers at football games, etc. etc. etc., but should you deign to ask for "equal time" in what seems a reasonable and appropriate gesture given the circumstances, you are some type of affront to moral decency?  If it's inappropriate for an atheist to give an invocation, then it's inappropriate for ANYONE to give one.  It's too bad this council and others can't see their own hypocrisy.  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink New Threat for Select Financial Buildings (washingtonpost.com)   The current administration would have us think so, but I think not.
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As of now, I am officially unemployed.  Yay!
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's see... on Tuesday, I got to go to doggie day care all day.  I was a little scared at first (I usually am), but once I got inside, I had lots of fun and made lots of new doggie friends.  The next day I was still pretty tired, but we did go for a short walk before heading over to the last co-ed game of the season at Ford Park.  My friend Basco and I got to run around before and after the game, and we really tore up the freshly-raked infield before the game.  Yesterday, I was a bit overzealous in chewing on my new bone, and it made me quite sick.  But I was a very good dog and threw up in the corner, behind a door, which my mommy said was the "best place in the whole house to throw up."  I don't like being sick very much; no one does, so we took it easy, and I feel much better now.  I like reading books now.  Well, I don't read them, but I can curl up next to my mommy while she does.    I think my mommy said she doesn't have to go to her icky jobs anymore and that we can play play play for the next two weeks before we do something called "moving."  Love,  Caesar
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The New York Times > Washington > Campaign 2004 > Report Finds Tax Cuts Heavily Favor the Wealthy : "The report calculated that households with incomes in that top 1 percent were receiving an average tax cut of $78,460 this year, while households in the middle 20 percent of earnings - averaging about $57,000 a year - were getting an average cut of only $1,090.  The new estimates confirm what independent tax analysts have long said: that Mr. Bush's tax cuts have been heavily skewed to the very wealthiest taxpayers."
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nights @ CBC:  0 Days @ VVENT: 0 and only 2 hours to go  There's something very comforting about the end of things - the last day of classes, Election Day, graduation, last day of work - about knowing that you'll never have to do something or go somewhere ever ever again... at least for a little while.  So much of life can be a grind, day in day out, with no end or change of pace in sight, that it's nice to have some closure.  Especially for things that you won't miss at all - like being a vampire front desk agent or "medical secretary."    On to bigger and better and brighter...
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - N.J. Governor Resigns, Admits Gay Affair : "At a point in every person's life, one has to look deeply into the mirror of one's soul and decide one's unique truth in the world, not as we may want to see it or hope to see it, but as it is."  - Gov. James E. McGreevey  The problem here is that McGreevey should be resigning over the corruption scandals clouding his administration, not because of an extramarital affair, regardless of whether it was gay or straight in nature.  So the whole gay thing - which should not be an issue and and the fact that it is speaks volumes about the state of American tolerance, society, etc. - clouds over the corruption.  BUt you have to give the guy credit for his frank admission and wonder how in the world he campaigned  twice  for governor and served for three years without it coming out until now, unless it was the worst kept secret in NJ.   urlLink Wonkette  has some interesting thoughts on this:  "We hope that someday it won't mean much to go on national television and announce, "I am a gay American." Someday, we hope that kind of announcement comes at the beginning of someone's political career, not the end."  "Sean Hannity, by the way, is having a little conservgasm over this.  "UPDATE: What was I saying? It's a huge conservgasm."  And so was Robert Novak on Crossfire.  Why does this guy have to be so nasty?   More:  "Calm down, my right-thinking friends. This is what I meant yesterday: McGreevey's speech was stunning, inspiring and perhaps even profound. . . It's too bad he's so corrupt.  "One of the reasons McGreevey's speech worked is that while he apologized for what he had done, he didn't apologize for being gay. He made it impossible for anyone to use his sexuality against him and the bluntness with which he did that raises the bar for every public figure who has to cop to a personal crisis on national television. We admire that.  "What would have been really great is if he'd also fessed up to ethical lapses that actually matter. We dream of a world in which McGreevey would have to resign not because he's gay, but because he's at the helm of a political machine driven by cronyism and kickbacks."  And so does the ever-enduring Rep. Barney Frank on coming out:  "I came out at 47, too, though not under threat or anything.  There was a period in my life when I was clinically depressed, on drugs, seeing a psychiatrist - I wasn't functional.  You can be a dysfunctional member of Congress, but not a dysfunctional governor.  In Congress, there are 434 other people. You can't put a governorship on autopilot."  (quoted in the  urlLink NY Times , emphasis added)
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CBC: 1 night left, 11.5 hours from right now VVENT: 1 day left, 3 hours
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The New York Times > Arts > Television > 'West Wing': Is It Facing a Struggle to Survive?   The West Wing is probably my favorite TV show, even though I've never watched it in prime time and couldn't even tell you when it's on.  I get my fix from re-runs on Bravo and the Season 1 and 2 DVD sets.  So this is unfortunate, but I had heard the show was definitely on the decline after Sorkin had left.  I'd love to see it continue but not in a diminished state.  Plus I still have 3 "good" seasons to enjoy on DVD in the near future.
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to admit to the very guilty pleasure of reading  urlLink delatacit .  It ranks right up there with those trashy dating TV shows (Blind Date, EX-treme Dating, Elimidate - awful but so fun to watch, you know) or easy paperback reads (like anything by John Grisham or any book you can read cover to cover in 2 days or less) or "Saved by the Bell" re-runs (only the high school years - Zach & Kelly's Prom, Jessie's overdose, etc.) or classic 80s music (Devo, Flock of Seagulls, "Mickey," etc.)  Anyway, it is a Delaware political/gossip blog, authored by still unknown person(s).  It's like the  urlLink Delaware Grapevine  on crack.  All the juicy stuff that everyone knows and talks about - but that we know Celia wouldn't print - is on delatacit.  Of course, a lot of it is just crap, and the anonymous comments are cowardly at best, and mainly incoherent at worst.  Ron Williams likes it, which is also quite specious.  And I am probably not helping matters at all by mentioning it, except for the fact that there are only like 2 people out there actually reading this.      Oh well, everyone should be allowed a few guilty pleasures.  It can't all be the New York Times and Shakespeare all the time.
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Onion | Kerry Unveils One-Point Plan For Better America   Don't forget... it's a parody.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CBC Nights:  2 CBC Hours:  28 VVENT Days: 1 VVENT Hours: 3
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Colorado Brewing Magnate to Be Senate Candidate   Salazar vs. Coors...big race, big money, it's go time. 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "A good friend of mine used to say, 'This is a very simple game. You throw the ball, you catch the ball, you hit the ball. Sometimes you win, sometimes you lose, sometimes it rains.' "  urlLink -Bull Durham (1988)    in honor of the last week of the summer softball season...
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      days @ vvent: 1 (only 3 hours) nights @ cbc: 3   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Colorado Plays Key Role in Control of Senate (washingtonpost.com)   Already cast my vote today for Salazar...
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CBC Nights = 3 VVENT Days = 2  Note to guests:  There will be absolutely no crap taken at this desk for the next four nights.  Thank you, The Management (ie ME) 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a good day.  I'm trying to be a good puppy.  I took a long, leisurely nap all day while my mommy was away at work - well, after I finished my doggy popsicle treat that she had left me in the morning.    Then we went for a mountainbike ride on the "old race course" in Eagle.  Well, I ran.  She rides that thing.  I chased a rabbit and almost caught it.  Then we missed the turn and ended up riding an extra mile and a half.  And I had to run really fast during this section just to keep up.  The last section of the ride was through some very chalky white soil, so I came home hardly even looking like myself.  I had white dust all over my face and legs.  It wouldn't brush out so I got a quick bath.  It was time for a bath anyway.  I have to take one about once a month, right around when I get my heartworm pill.  I think I heard something about day care tomorrow, so I am going to get a good night's rest tonight!  Love, Caesar  
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The New York Times > Washington > Crucial Unpaid Internships Increasingly Separate the Haves From the Have-Nots : "But as internships rise in importance as critical milestones along the path to success, questions are emerging about whether they are creating a class system that discriminates against students from less affluent families who have to turn down unpaid internships to earn money for college expenses. 'It's something that really makes me nuts,' said Cokie Roberts, an ABC News correspondent who spoke out about the problem on Capitol Hill several weeks ago at a gathering of Congressional interns. 'By setting up unpaid internship programs, it seems to me that without completely recognizing it, it sets up a system where you are making it ever more difficult for people who don't have economic advantages to catch up.'  Dalton Conley, a sociology professor at New York University who has studied how people get ahead, said: 'It moves the clock back when you need connections. It makes it doubly hard for social mobility and equal opportunity, because of the connections that it requires at an earlier age, the financial sacrifices and also the culture savoir-faire.' While half of internships nationwide are paid or have at least a small stipend, according to national surveys conducted by Vault, unpaid internships are concentrated in the most competitive fields, like politics, television and film. 'The more glamorous an internship, the less likely it is paid,' Mr. Oldman said. 'Washington in general has high-demand internships. In most cases they don't have to pay or they don't have to pay much.' "  This is totally true.  It was when I was trolling for summer internships, and now it looks like things have gotten worse.  The problem is that cash-strapped non-profits and government agencies (Congress, White House, etc.) will always offer unpaid internships for two reasons: 1.  They absolutely depend on this labor to function under their limited budgets. and 2. There will always be plenty of people to fill these positions unpaid, like the kids of their wealthy donors.  So having connections leads to more connections, while those who can't afford it are left out.  And anyway, how else would all those envelopes get stuffed? 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      revised...  VVENT Days: 2 CBC Nights: 4  I've just agreed to take tomorrow morning to fill in for my aunt Doreen. 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Bush Listens to Sermon on Material Wealth : "The Very Rev. Martin Luther Agnew preached Sunday to a packed Episcopal church just down the road from the Bush family's seaside estate. Its oceanfront parking lot was filled with luxury cars made by Jaguar, Mercedes, BMW and Volvo, testament to the wealth of the summer visitors at this southeast Maine resort.  'Gated communities,' Agnew said, 'tend to keep out God's people.' But, he said, 'Our material gifts do not have to be a wall.'  'They can very well be a door. Jesus says, `Sell your possessions and give alms,'' Agnew said. 'I'm convinced that what we keep owns us, and what we give away sets us free.'  Agnew, a guest minister from Louisiana whose summer assignment ended Sunday, swung a golf club to get his message across to the vacationing congregation.  The sermon culminated with a joke about the first President Bush's battle to chip a golf ball out of an anthill. Swinging the club in a mock re-enactment, Agnew said Bush had swung twice and whiffed completely, wiping out hundreds of ants.  The ants got together and agreed: 'If we're going to live, we better get on the ball!'  The former president sat stone-faced through this parable, even as his family, including the current President Bush, looked at him and smiled. "
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CBC = 4 nights VVENT = 1 day
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink washingtonpost.com: Media Notes Extra : "Alan Keyes (who once ripped Hillary Clinton as a carpetbagger) is reported by the Chicago papers today to have decided to run for Senate in Hillary's real home state of Illinois, even though he lives in Maryland. The Chicago Tribune offers this editorial: 'Mr. Keyes may have noticed a large body of water as he flew into O'Hare. That is called Lake Michigan. It's large. It's wide. It's deep. And we'll spoil the surprise: You can't even see across it. Welcome to Illinois. . . .  'In a move that seems a tad, um, rude, Keyes said he'd get back to them. He's off to Maryland. He'll let them know by Sunday if he accepts their nomination. Whatever he does, the state GOP has created a terrible situation for itself. If Keyes accepts, he will run and will lose. And then he will hop on the next flight back to Maryland, and the state's GOP will be left with nothing but the smell of jet fumes. If Keyes decides not to run, how stupid Republicans will look. They'll be back to finding a candidate from Illinois, because the candidate from Maryland spurned them.'"
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      But I think the  urlLink NYTimes.com 2004 Election Guide  might be a better way.  Plus, it's interactive! 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This website, the  urlLink Current Electoral Vote Predictor 2004 , gives the daily  actual  standings of the presidential race.  While I wouldn't completely trust the results - some states, like Delaware, have no polling data from 2004, and their prediction is based only on the 2000 election - it is a better indicator than the national horserace polls, which are basically meaningless in predicting who will win.  Those polls are only useful for looking generally at trends that might affect the few states whose electoral votes are in play.  If we learned anything from four years ago (although it's something we all knew already), the candidate with the most electoral votes wins.  The popular vote is meaningless, and its the state-by-state battles that matter.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a pretty good weekend.  On Saturday, we drove to Breckenridge in Summit County.  I got to meet Carl Schnee from Delaware and two of his friends, who were in town, for a hike up to Crystal Lake.  On Sunday, we hung out around the house, doing laundry and cleaning up and catching up.  For me, it was a little boring.  Or maybe it's just because I'm a doggie-teenager that I act up.  But my mommy sure seems to be yelling at me a lot and shaking that can whenever I jump or eat out of Cassidy's dish (isn't it my food, too?) or bark or pull ahead on the leash.  I'm sure trying, but it's tough being a puppy and a good one at that.    We went for a good walk on Sunday night in the neighborhood and up to the water tank.  We also got to play some fetch before it got too dark.  I've figured out that those black plastic things sticking up out of the grass are good for a quick and cool drink when I stick my mouth over them.  It stings a little, but it's worth it while we're out on a walk.  Love, Caesar
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Historical markers planned for The Green   Just as long as they save the diagonal path from Sypherd Hall to Grotto's on Main Street for me.  I trudged through that grass, diagonally across The Mall, scraping my feet, many times, and though many may have followed behind me, I returned to campus a few years after my graduation to find it paved in UD's glorious and ubiquitous red brick.  I certainly intend to try to claim credit for starting the practice.  UD's own "if-you-build-it-they-will-come" is "If you walk across the grass enough to create even a slightly worn footpath, they will brick it."  Try it, it works.
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nights @ CBC: 4 Days @ VVENT: 2  One week to go...
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Senator Frist's Political Rise Slows in Pace : "He has never steeped himself in the Senate's intricate rules and traditions, robbing him of advantages enjoyed by most of his predecessors, including Republicans Trent Lott (Miss.) and Robert J. Dole (Kan.). As a surgeon, Frist is accustomed to having subordinates follow his instructions quickly, and adhering to a workplace hierarchy that is alien to the ego-driven Senate. And while he calls himself patient, Frist tends to shift to a different bill when he hits legislative roadblocks, rather than grind through tough negotiations that probably would involve concessions to political opponents."
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Yahoo! News - Nader Doesn't Get Spot on California Ballot 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Wash Post:  Reprising a War with Words:   In that same speech to the minority journalists this month, Bush offered this definition of policy toward Native Americans: "Tribal sovereignty means that, it's sovereign. I mean, you're a -- you're a -- you've been given sovereignty and you're viewed as a sovereign entity. And therefore the relationship between the federal government and tribes is one between sovereign entities."   But can the man read? 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink JS Online: State's law students get free pass on bar exam   Diploma privilege = no bar exam in Wisconsin = suh - weet!    Of course, if I do not stay in Wisconsin to practice, then there will be a bar exam... somewhere. 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Memorable Quotes from Bourne Supremacy, The (2004) : "You're in a big puddle of shit, Pamela, and you don't have the shoes for it."  Good movie... very intelligent, and that's refreshing for a summer action flick.
    
</post>


</Blog>