<Blog>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "Will I shake this off, pretend its all ok, that theres someone out there who feels just like me....  There is..."     Today I've been thinking a hell of a lot about what I'm doin, how my life is goin, and to be honest I'm still stumped.To be completely honest to be depressed, heart broken, suffering from grief and confused about what to do next are things you really dont want to experience, espesh not all at once. Trust me. Yet as per usual my life can't be easy and always throws things at me here there and everywhere without even consideration that i might not cope.  It's so difficult trying to be the perfect child, to be the best friend, to be the listener, the happy, the helper, the one thats always there. Such high expectations, and believe me I'm not complaining because i want to be there for all my friends and I want to make my parents happy. but sometimes i wonder....  &nbsp;&nbsp; What about me?  maybe i'm just being selfish but last night i realised when talkin to my friends how little they know about me. I expressed so much raw emotion to them last night and just because i dont express it in the conventional 'tell em straight' mode, doesn't mean i'm not expressing feelings. and none of them heard.&nbsp;I was  screaming  and noone heard.  Its hard to realise that your alone...      "Will I shake this off, pretend its all ok, that theres someone out there who feels just like me....  There is..."     I wish.     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On the 23rd of June one of my best friends. James Winter age 19 was in a motorcycle accident&nbsp;and was killed. I took it really badly and when i found out that his family had, had a memorial service and not told me I was heart broken.&nbsp; I wasin love with James and still am and I just can't let go. Yesterday I went to my cousin Davids in ringwood&nbsp;and it was the first time i'd seen him since James died, (James was his best friend aswell) and I really appreciate it coz he took me to where the accident happened and also he took me to the tree they planted in Jame's memory and I got to see his ashes. It was heartbraking to go to the road where it happened. to see the serve marks on the road, it was so detailed u could even see where the car slammed on his brakes.&nbsp; Pieces of bike where at the side of the road and to see it was just horrific. and even tho i've seen that i still can't bring myself to believe that he is gone. I still believe that he here and that I'll see him nxt time i visit. and i wont it.  &nbsp;   It's just so hard to let go....  
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Finally  after roughly about 5 years of trying to get the money to get it done, i got my ears pierced for the second time, i  know thats kinda pathetic but i always spent the money on something else before i got the get it done and now finally its done. and its so true, i have caught the piercing bug. its a well known fact that u get one piercing u want it all! and yes, i have fallen for the bug, its so weird how it hurts so much yet u love it lol! pain for pleasure i s'pose although having to afford 2 sets of earrings rather than one isn't exactically pleasure, more a pain in the ass to a broke student like myself, so maybe its theory is:   sparkly metallic pain for non affordable in the ass pain.  but that still leaves  why the hell do we do it????    why do we get that..... *dramatic music*.....    piercing bug? .... mwah ha ha ha!!!   so anyways i'm gonna get my ears done a few  more times and i've wanted my tongue done for ages and maybe a lip piercing!!! lmao. indeed the bug is contagious... but it all looks so good! and sparkly too! hehe! anyways i'll write in me blog laters lol its not like anyone reads it!   .:: Laters ::. 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      omg it was brilliant lol!! i went to the shop to buy fags and asmuch as i am now slightly happier because i have a can of Dr.Pepper and a pack of 10, i know the drink will go the fags wont last forever and i''m stuck back here again not having seen any of my friends.... kinda puts a downer on the whole woo! factor of that trip... ah well for a precious few minutes, i'm happy! :D thats all really. nothing else to say. i dnt know if i'm intolerant to the sun coz its not out and i wasn't cold which was good! lol.  u see why i love my life so much! - note the sarcasum!
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is becoming slightly ridiculous and unbearable not only am i stuck in my house 24/7 and have bin for the past 5 days, becuase i have absolutly no availible friends to meet and go out with within a 100 mile radus, also have absolutly no money whatsoever, I have no fags and so i'm dying of the need for one, and I have more problems in my brain than some one with a medical emergency. so all in all i have slowly come to the conclusion that if i have to stay in this house and ponder about all the things that are going wrong in my life, i'm gonna insane and then, just for kicks, i might get sucidal and kill myself. I always do tell people that thinking to much is bad for you. but this is ridiculous surely solid wallowing and thinking for 5 days solid, 12 hours a day, isn't healthy.... right thats it i'm gonna have to leave this house.    how? .... ....God knows.   but i'll figure something out. stuff it i'm gonna "borrow" some money off my dad and go get fags! i have to, my sanity depends on it. If not then who knows what might happen. I might resort to.... dare I say it.... going to work with my mom....   *falls to her knees - movie style* Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!!!!!!!!   i can't let that happen. alright, i'll do it. i'll go to the shop and buy fags. :) i shall report back when i get back. wish me luck, i haven't bin outside for so long, who knows what might happen. i might've become intolerant to the sun or forgotten what the feeling cold is..... wish me luck.
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       These feelings inside, they're just to much too handle, my heart beating fast my brain screaming outloud, voices are shouting and screaming in my head, feelings clawing to get out but they can't, razors and knifes ease the suffering for a second or too, then the guilt the neverending guilt, guilt for the pain, guilt for the people, knowing u've failed, yourself and ur friends, knowing ur not there for them, never good enough, it drives into your mind, an old rusty nail, driven down into your thoughts by your own self hating, driven so slowly u feel every twist every turn, as it sticks there in ur mind, a rotten splinter that cannot be moved, the thought of urself and how u are no good, like old movies it plays over and over black and white, self hatred is near as has been always will, shouting in your head, its ur fault, Its your fault. Its ur fault. It drives deep beyond your mind, it seeps into your heart, then u truly believe, your paper thin heart bleeds as a knoweldge so hated, a memory that is of a distant spite, the one person whos fault, the one person who drives this pain into yourself, is you. you cry and u weep, no ones there, u killed them, U pushed them away with your spitefullness and hate, u killed off their love and stayed in your sorrow, u beat urself up and thoughts running, always running through your head all the time, u back away and scream to leave this world, u carve at ur skin at the veins, bleed bitch bleed. i need to escape from this torturous hell,  this victimising body, I need to escape from me.  
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok my names Helen and this is where you lucky people get to read about my saddistic and boring life. I have trails and problems just like everyone else and this diary is just here so that some of my insanity comes across in my writings rather than against myself in a stupid moment of self harm for example. either way I'm not forcing you to read this so if you do and critisize it then its your own problem really. remember Don't judge what you dont understand.     x:: Laters ::x   
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          The inevitable choices...   
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok for any americans that might read this (not that anyone does read this....ah well) you all get more heat than we prob ever will but still for england...    ITS BLOODY HOT    i mean it prob doesn't help that I hate the sunshine its nasty and i love rain, but i get heat stroke easily and i've already passed out today twice. its not nice :( me no likey 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I'm becoming a little to friendly with the bottles that contain alcohol... my taste buds are screaming "enough already its nasty white wine damn it" and my heads thinking. at the bottom of this bottle. it has to be here.    The answer has to be at the bottom of one of these bottles.....it has to    i dunno when i drink or smoke weed it seems to releave me of everything. ok i know thats what they're designed to do but its not good coz whilst I'm thinking, 'YES' my pain has gone its really just getting worse and an alcohol and drug addiction is just another problem that i really dont need on my plate at this moment in my life.   Things are becoming way to complicated    I dont know how much more of this i can handle. ok people think i'm strong cozza the things I've dealt with but really I know the truth on the outside i'm strong but inside, i'm crumbling apart.  I just wish someone would understand and show me the path I should be walking.  I re-applied for college, (of which Igot kicked out cozza not doin any work) so that was s'pose to be the first step to normalitly but i'm so scared that i waver from the work again. I'm saying i'll work etc but i said that last yr and i spent all my waking hours smoking pot and drinking at every opertunity i got.... :S i'm just so worried about whats gonna happen to me. i dnt want a shitty life. i wanna work, i wanna pay my way. i dnt wanna sponge all my life (contrary to what people might think) i do i just find it hard to stay on the wagon.   If only i had one person, one person to show me where I'm going wrong and to push me in the right diretion         but for now i'll carry on drowning my sorrows it just has to be here....   The answer has to be at the bottom of one of these bottles... It's just gotta be....
</post>


</Blog>