<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      If always do what you've always done. You will always get what you got. --Nicole 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Sometimes life is hard. This is one of those times. Too many road blocks. Although life is hard and life can be conquered now is not the time. How to say goodbye is the hardest thing to figure out.   Many people will be upset.. Will they get over the pain..Will they have pain for a long time…Will they forgive me…I hope so.. It never seems to get easier…What can anyone expect…Life is hard…From abuse to cancer to the end to whatever comes next.  Dark is the tunnel that lies ahead. There is no light. I am afraid of the dark. There are demons in the dark. There are demons that I have never seen. I have heard them and they are not pleasant. Scared to death. If there was only a shimmer of light in the tunnel. But no. No light, no hope, no dreams. So what is point.   There are many thing to stay for…The possibility of getting through this time. But I do not think that will happen. It can’t happen. The memories will always be there. What good does it do to minimize them. If they are there how can they not hurt.  Have I failed this life..Have I failed if I leave now…I don’t think so. I have accomplished much.. I have gotten through many things that most people couldn’t get through. Leaving is not giving up..It is a starting over…A new beginning.  My hope is that all will be forgiven in the next go around. And if there turns out to be nothing past this life then it doesn’t make any difference.   I contemplate why anyone would hurt a child and I have no answers. Why Why Why…As an adult I find there to be much companionship. Is that what the adults want that abuse children. Do they know how much people are willing to help…Ask …Why don’t they ask for help…  So many adults that abuse child have no concept of the life time of pain they are causing to the child. It’s as though it makes no difference. Like the child will not be harmed. It is only love right. I say no it is not love. A simple touch can be harmful. Sometimes more harmful than the worst abuse imaginable. Life is full of horrible ironies.  An adult abuser was probably hurt as a child. So why would they want the same thing for another child. Certainly they remember the pain that was inflicted on them. No matter how great your pain there is no reason to push that onto an unwilling child. Children can be so innocent. Abuse rips the innocence from them. No matter what age. An infant that is abused will know that something happened to them. There is no hiding it. There will always be at least 2 people that know. And even though the abuser moves on the child will always remember. Always.  I don’t get it.&nbsp; Surely my friends can understand. How could they not understand. Forgiveness is the challenge. It is not their fault. What I do is of my own freewill. No one held the gun to my head. No one made me take pills. No one made me burn myself. No one made me hurt myself. I only ask that someone take care of my cats. My belongings mean nothing. They are not me. I am me. But I am lost in the abuse. I can’t seem to get the other side. What is on the other side. Who knows. Many people have made this choice. And I don’t hear the fires of hell burning them. And it certainly can’t hurt as much as the pain I feel.  &nbsp; 
     

        
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A Feather in the wind. Floating through the universe.  A wisp of light. Passing through time.  We come into and out of lives without even the knowledge that we have made a difference.  At times it seems hopeless. As though we have no purpose.   Everyone has a purpose. It may not be apparent throughout our life travels.  Some journeys through are harder than others. Some journeys take all of our effort just to complete them.  Uncompleted journeys bring us back to this world. 
     

        
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I think I am going nuts.  &nbsp;  When I was a child I was sexually abused. I always thought I could handle it. At no time did I ever think it was affecting my life. But it did and still does. I began counseling several years ago. And there has certainly been a change for the better.  &nbsp;  One of the biggest problems I still face to this day are the memories. And let me tell you they SUCK. When they happen, I get sucked back to when I was a child. Everything I see, smell, touch, taste, is like I am back in the early 70's. Sometimes I even have physical memories. Those are the absolute worst. My body actually mimics the feeling of being abused.  &nbsp;  Well tonight was one of those nights.  &nbsp;  Generally for me to have a memory, I have to be triggered by something or someone. Something that brings back the past. Not unlike if you hear a sound or smell something and quickly your mind resolves to a pleasant time in your life. When that smell, sound, or whatever brings back a bad memory, I call it being triggered. Something in life I avoid so as not to be triggered. For example, movie theaters, large crowds, or certain foods. Other times being triggered is uncontrollable. Like if someone comes up behind you and scares you.  &nbsp;  This afternoon I was triggered by the environment. Everything about it&nbsp;brought me back to when I was a child at my grandmother's house. The temperature, wind, sound of the trees blowing, silence of the neighborhood, even the plane that went over head.  &nbsp;  As I was folding clothes at my friend's house my world started to crash. All of the sights, sounds, smells hit me. Then I looked over and saw a condom wrapper. Suddenly it was as though a Mack Truck had come through the wall and run me over. Instantly the memories began to flow. Both physical and visual. The place even began to smell like it had many years ago. There was no stopping it. Since I was in the bedroom,&nbsp;I tried to sleep. I think I fell asleep for a short time. Just enough to keep my composure for my friend. As it then turned out my friend was leaving for a concert shortly after my "nap" and I headed home.  &nbsp;  Another friend had come to my house to watch the 2nd season of Six Feet Under. He stayed for another 4 hours with me watching that show. I couldn't tell him what was happening in my mind. I was afraid he would rush me to the hospital.&nbsp;While he was here I tried my best to make the memories go away. But they never did.  &nbsp;  Once he left they came like Niagara Falls. I called 2 friends and neither were home. Both had gone to the same concert and I really didn't expect them to be home. The snowball had grown&nbsp;to gigantic proportions. And there was no stopping it. I then used my last resort, Emma.  &nbsp;  Emma has been my counselor for 5 years. I rarely call her. To me it feels like a sign of weakness. Hell, I talk to her once a week. &nbsp;&nbsp;Shouldn't that be enough. None the less I called her tonight. It was past midnight. She has always said that calling her anytime is fine but if I call&nbsp;late then expect her to take a few minutes to get herself into counselor mode.  &nbsp;  When she called back she said&nbsp;she figured something really bad was going on as I have never called so late. As sarcastically as I could I said oh no, there is nothing wrong, I was curious how the weather in your&nbsp;part of town. I then proceeded to tell her about the day. As I did things only got worse.  &nbsp;  I used to be a burner.&nbsp;When things would get to tough I would burn myself to help bring me back to reality. I haven't done it in years. And now I&nbsp;was having those feelings. Such a major set back it felt like. Of course I thought by finally talking about this one episode everything would go away. But it didn't.  &nbsp;  At one point I went numb. I could here Emma talking and telling&nbsp;me I was not a child and&nbsp;what I was seeing was only a memory. But that was not reality. It was as if I had dropped acid. Nothing was as it is now. I was at my grandmother's house, in the shed, with my grandfather.  &nbsp;  My grandfather was an abuser. To this day no one in my family knows that he was the man. They think he was great. After all he put up with my grandmother for so many years. What they didn't know was his&nbsp;big secret.&nbsp; My grandfather was a child molester.&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  I am someone who has always known about their abuse. I just chose not to tell anyone. There are so many reasons I had not to tell. Then once I finally came out of the closet&nbsp;about the abuse, I didn't want to admit that my grandfather did all that much to me.&nbsp;Again he was the great&nbsp;man that married my grandmother.  &nbsp;  In talking to&nbsp;Emma, I made it clear on many occasions that&nbsp;my grandfather only fondled me. But hiding within me was always this voice screaming just tell the truth. The truth is that there was penetration. Or as close as a grown man can get with a child of 5.  &nbsp;  When I was in the 4th grade one of the kids brought a condom to school. He chased people around with it. I seemed to be the only kid that knew what it was. And it wasn't until I began telling the other kids that it was used for "humping" (the term I knew for sex at the time) that the other kids got freaked out. The teacher asked me how I knew about them and I just clammed up. I think in today's world there might be a further investigation into how a kid knows about about condoms at such an early age. But back then no way.  &nbsp;  I began to recall how I was told the condom was to protect me. Because without it our fun time would hurt. Well, hold the phone, you aren't going to believe this, it DID hurt. As the physical memories come back today, it feels like someone shoving a piano in my vagina. Not that I have tried but that is the visual that must be close.  &nbsp;  Emma helped as much as she could. She made sure I was not going to kill myself. Which is the farthest thing from my mind right now. Even with all her wisdom it didn't help. My body went numb. It was the only way not to feel the pain. Then during our conversation, I did burn myself. Not real big but I did give in to the feeling. The overwhelming feeling to burn encompassed every thought. I felt like an alcoholic sitting in front of a full bar trying not to take a drink.  &nbsp;  So I did it. I am very unhappy with myself for doing it. It is a road I do not want to navigate again. Hopefully, this is a one time thing, stemming from a very stressful and painful memory.  &nbsp;  Shortly after my conversation with Emma, a friend called. She was concerned because of the message I had left. I talked with her awhile. The whole time the memory movie was playing. It did help ground me more. I was truly in La-La Land. She offered to come over. I said no. No need to drag her down this road.  &nbsp;  I guess if having one of these horrible memory episodes happens every 3 years, I am not so bad off. Man it sucks though. Life goes pretty well for me. However, sometimes it can be a real kick in the ass.     
     

        
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Great recipes !! Of course you have to like the 4:20 herbal stuff. Eve
     

        
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink dopey.de - Gas, Grass or Ass - Nobody Rides for Free 
     

        
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I thought I would give this a try. From here I can write what ever comes to mind. Nothing keeps me from speaking what I feel. If my friends make me mad I can air it out on the Blog.   I am interested in others experiences. Or your thoughts about my posts. The anonymity here is endless. We can post forever. No one will know who I am or who you are. It doesn't matter where in the world you are.   My goal is to present information to others. And to vent some when the need arises.   Signed,  Eve    
     

        
</post>


<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I never thought life could get so crazy. Family, friends, lovers, lesbians, and a dog. All have made Passion Fruit Manor a wild place.  Each summer we all get together to celebrate life and the fruits of our labor. However, one summer turned out to be extremely wild, hilarious, sad, and just plain biazare.  &nbsp;  

						
</post>


</Blog>