<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If there is one thing I have learned it is this: The moment you think everything is going right for once, it all goes wrong. When that happens you have a choice to make: sit down, cry and wait for your life to end, or forge ahead and keep going. If you decide to cry and wait for your life to end, I wish you luck and I pray the end comes swiftly. However, if you choose to keep going, never look back, except in happy times and with friends. If you look back at your life in sorrow, you just may change your mind and decide to sit, cry, and wait...  
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      With both older siblings gone all the time I am basically the oldest child. Actually, cassidy is home a lot of the time but she refuses to help, so that leaves me. I guess all this pressure is just building, and it is hard to handle right now.  B.J. is a good child, my parents golden child basically. He has followed everything they have ever taught him. In a few months he is going on his mission. Golden child. I don't really resent him, in fact I look up to him a lot, but I don't appreciate the way my parents want the rest of us to turn out as good as he did. Whatever. I'm gonna do things my way. Always have, always will.  Cassidy has rebelled against everything my parents have ever taught us. She has really hurt my parents, and me for that matter. She really resents my brother, and that ticks me off. She verbally abuses my younger sister, and me when i talk to her. She is not all bad, horrible-ness, but she has sent my family into turmoil many times. Right now she has us all walking on eggshells so that we don't set her off, AND THAT REALLY PISSES ME OFF!! Why the hell should we all be on edge just because she has a ****ing anger problem? I'm so sick of her attitude running this house. One more year and she's off to college.  Then there is me. I feel that because cassidy refuses to help around the house, my parents expect me to pick up the slack; watching the kids, cleaning, etc. I also have this lingering feeling that because their first daughter has rebelled so much, especially against our church, that they expect me to be their perfect daughter. I don't like this at all, because I am not one to conform to anything. I have my own way of doing things, my own thought patterns, my own style, everything, and I'm not gonna change just because I don't live up to my parents standards. If my mother wants a prodigy she has two other daughters she can try and mold.     
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yes indeed, this was a weekend of firsts. The first time i've been on a weekend trip with my friend and without my family. The first time i've seen the ocean. The first time I've eaten halibut, shrimp, clam chowder, lobster, and crab. The first time i've been allowed to walk around a city after 7, much less a city i did not know. The first time i've ever gone dune-buggying. Fun stuff...sort of.  The ocean was so gorgeous. It went on forever, and the clouds were hanging above it, but way out to sea. It also seemed like the clouds were trying to mimic the magesty of the waves, because they were curving around eachother. They were rounded off a little, just like the rolling surf. It all made me feel very small, and very alone at the same time. The thing i wanted most of all&nbsp;this weekend was to have Tyler with me so that we could&nbsp;build a small bonfire, roast 'mallows, and just sit and watch the sun sink below the horizon.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So, my life has been absolutely crazy as of late. Ever since monday my garage has been full of drummers, pretty much non-stop. We have been painting our drums charcoal grey. Cool cool. Or not.... We've run into a million problems, not to mention my family is being stupid about it. That and I have only gotten about 7 hours of sleep since waking up on Monday morning. That's an average of about 3.5 hours of sleep a night. It is messed up! Oh well, I'm thriving I guess. So, my parents pretty much hate me right now because painting is taking so long, and my little siblings aren't handling the change very well or whatever. It's all retarded crap. Moving on, tomorrow my family is having a family portrait done, then we come home, I get to work on the drums for about 2 hours, and then hopefully I'll get to go to my boyfriends house and watch band of brother, or at least part of it. Then on Friday I'm leaving with one of my best friends and we are going to the ocean. Newport to be exact. I've never seen then ocean in my life!!! I am so excited. Well, I got to get back in the garage. Some of the drummers make me nervous. Laterz.    
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey all. Goodness, today was a great day. I went to walmart with my grandpa and he let me drive his really nice focus. Usually i hate driving, only because i still have my permit and therefor must drive with one of my parents, and both like to yell at me when i do something wrong. Or even when i don't for that matter. It sux. Well, with grandpa it was so much better. He explained things to me, he didn't yell or get mad. It was so cool! Once we got home it was about 11:30, and i had to be at the highschool around 12:45 for our drumline rehearsal. Also, before i left i had to make pizza dough, so when i got home around 5 i could just roll out the dough, slap on the toppingsd and away we go. Well, between the dough, loading up my quads, putting away the paint for the drums, and saying goodbye to my little siblings, i was almost late. I made it there just after our section leader did, though. I felt special. Anyways, i had forgot to put sunscreen on before i left, and there was no shade around. It was about 103 outside during the rehearsal. Not fun. It did cloud over for a little while, but not long. Actually, for about 15 minutes we hung out in the dugout. That was fun. We played and marched, and marched and played until 5. I got home, made dinner, welcomed my older sister home, and that would bring us to this point. Yup, i've had a really fun day. The only thing that would make it better is if i could see, or at least talk to, my boyfriend, but he's out hangin with his friends. That's ok. I'll talk to him on monday hopefully. Well, my grandma's leaving, so i'm gonna go. Laterz all. Keep on keepin on. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I love finding nemo. That movie is so cool. My friends went nuts with that movie and nicknamed everyone they knew after a character from that movie. I was the little fish that, when introducing himself to nemo, says "I'm obnoxious!" Yeah, that name is pretty self explanatory i guess.  Well, last night was the worst night i&nbsp;can ever remember having, hands-down. It was ok to begin with, we had dinner, the little kids didn't scream which was a first. Then my little sister who is 11 got invited to go sleep over at a friends house. My grandparents said ok, so she went her way. However, with her gone that meant that i had to do two paper routes this morning: hers and mine. Usually my mom does both routes with us, but she was gone, so my grandpa was gonna do it. That meant that I would have to run to every house. (we drive the routes in a car. Lazy, i know, but it gets it done faster.) Oh well, i decided, at least my little sister would be having fun. And so the night progressed onward. Generally the kids go to bed at 9 or 9:30. Last night they didn't go to bed until 11:00, all because my grandparents had put on a 2 hour movie and the kids wouldn't go to bed until the end of it. I didn't really mind. I thought the more tired they are the easier they'll go to sleep. I was wrong. Dead wrong.&nbsp;  To put the kids to bed some one has to read three stories, sing three songs, and say prayers with them. Well, that someone is my mom who gives into them a lot, and only because both boys are autistic and half deaf. Autistic or not, they are extremely intelligent and should not be treated like babies. They're 6 1/2 for crying aloud! I told them last night that i would read stories to them in the morning, when i could actually focus my eyes to read. Bryce was ok with that, he just read himself a story, sang a song, said prayers, and went to sleep. Chase totally went to pieces. He was screaming for mom and refused to go to sleep until she came home. She doesn't get home until tonight, around 6. So i told him whatever, i don't care, sleep on the floor with all your toys, it really doesn't matter to me. So he slept on the floor for about 30 minutes, then crawled in his bed. I won that battle easily enough. Then there is Hannah. There is nothing wrong with her, except an extreme attitude that needs adjusting. I read her book but would not&nbsp;heat up the rice pack for her. Why in the world does she need it anyways? Oh. That's right, she doesn't! Well, she did this cry/whining combo that i could not stand. I turned around and started walking toward the door. All of a sudden both Hannah and Chase start crying and screaming that they hate me. For some reason it really hurt. I closed the door, laid on my parents bed, turned on my music and tried to tune them out.  Around midnight Hannah gets up and says she has to go to the bathroom, so i take her. Then she automatically thinks that she gets to sleep in my parents bed with me. My mom evidently lets her sleep with them, but i'm not my mom. I told her no, and she started her whole cry/whining thing again. I can't stand that cry because it is so fake, honestly, it is. It's all for show. I put her back&nbsp;in her bed where she commenced to cry for another 15 minutes, and then fell silent.  All in all, last night was absolutely terrible. Tonight when my parents come home i am not gonna help with the kids at all. I must say I am so sick of them. I have been stuck at home for the past 10 days straight, with only them for company. I have only left the house to go to the dentist and my paper route. Oh well. That's all in the past. This next week, starting on Monday, the drumline is coming over to my house and we are gonna be painting our drums. It's supposed to be around 103 all next week, and we're gonna be in&nbsp;my garage, but it'll be fun.  Well, today is a new day, with new chores and responsibilities. I have to clean the downstairs, bathroom, and upstairs, not to mention run to the store and get some groceries, paint brushes and tape. I have to do this by 1 because that's when the drumline rehearsal begins. I gotta get crackin'. Keep on keepin on.    
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This whole day i have been yo-yo-ing between anger and depression. I was angry this morning because i had to take all three of my youngest sibnlings to swin lessons, and sit in the hot sun. I was also wearing jeans and a black t-shirt, which was stupid. When i got home i had the biggest headache, and i felt so tired. I laid down o my bed, feeling thouroughly ticked, and was soon asleep. I woke up to my grandma pounding on my door, asking me to help her make lunch for the little people. My mom, dad, and older siblings were gone, so i had to help.&nbsp; That turned into a fiasco that i won't even describe. This afternoon my older brother left for eugene, oregon. My parents got home, and 3 hours later left for the same place. Tomorrow they are going to all watch my older sister and her cohorts perform at drum major camp. Then they are bringing her home. In the meantime, i am the oldest child left at home, but both my granbdparents are here too. For some reason i don't see eye-to-eye with either of them. they think they are right in everything, and though they may be, they don't have to force their ways and opinions on me. Tonight i have to watch ove the little people, getting their dinner, giving them baths, getting them to bed, and in between all that keeping them entertained. I'm feeling realy put upon right now and i don't like it. Tomorrow i have to get them all ready for the day, keep them entertained, and find some way to get down to the high school at 1 for our drum line rehearsal. I don't understand, whats going on?! This day s seeming to last forever, and i'm not looking forward to tomorrow. I just wish i could see, or at least talk to, one of my friends. I haven't seen any of them in a long time. I know i saw my boyfriend just last night, but i haven't talked to him at all today, and i wish i could. I can't seem to stop being sad, and it's driving me nuts. I have this desire to be happy, like everyone else seems to be, i just can't seem make it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Yesterday I couldn't sleep, last night I couldn't sleep, and today does not show much hope either. I don't know what's going on, maybe I'm worried about something, I dunno. Oh well. Yesterday was fun. I mowed the lawn, cleaned the whole downstairs of my house, got my little brothers ready for swim lessons, and practiced the quads, all before lunch time. After lunch I had a quad sectional from 1 - 3:30. That went pretty well I guess. Our music is all paradiddles, paradiddlediddles, rolls, and messed up splits and stuff. Don't worry, I'm gonna have a whole different post that only concerns drumline, cuz there's a lot of crap going on there. Anyways, around 4 my boyfriend was supposed to come over so we could take my three youngest siblings&nbsp;to a park&nbsp;and get them away from my mom because she was totally freakin out from stress and whatnot. Well,&nbsp; evidently he called around 3 and my mom didn't tell me until about 4:15 that he was waiting for me to call him.&nbsp; That ticked me because 1) my mom always gets mad at us for forgetting to give her messages and yet when she does it to me she gets pissed because I get mad at her. double standard? I think so. oh yeah, and 2) because my boyfriend had said he would come over at four, I had it already&nbsp;ok'd with the parentals and everything. Then on the phone he had the gall to ask "so can I come over?" Well,&nbsp; that was a retarded question, but whatever. He came over, we took care of the kids, had dinner, went to McDonald's, and then came home and hung out with my family/watched Emperor's new groove. Fun fun fun. Actually it was fun. I'll post again later. certain people keep looking over my shoulder and it's ticking me off!      
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's 9:08, and I'm awake and out of bed. This is a definite low point for me. 7:00 this morning my mom kicked me and my siblings out of bed. Why, you may ask. For the sole purpose of making us work. My two little sisters, ages 11 and 3, are at swim lessons while my two little brothers, ages 6 and 6, are destroying our downstairs living room. My older brother, age 18, is out mowing lawns for his business. My mother is at the dentist, and my older sister, age 17, is currently 6 hours away at a camp. That leaves me to tend the hooligans that are at the moment "making up stories". One is using Thomas the tank engine, while the other is using barbies. Basically they are talking aloud to themselves right now. They also have Mister Rogers on, and Mister Rogers just got a shot. I hate *twitch*  needles. But you see, if I were in bed right now, I wouldn't have seen that, and I wouldn't have to listen to my little brothers talk to themselves, and I wouldn't have to fold laundry or clean the house either. Oh well, at least now I can practice for our Quad line sectional, which is today.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Holy Kracker! I just got back from my youth group and I feel so sick, and yet extremely hyper at the same time. It's a weird sensation, but anyways. We played the chocolate game. You sit in a circle and there is a tray with a hat, scarf, two oven mits, two forks, and a heavily wrapped giant Hershey bar in the middle. You pass around 2 dies, and whoever rolls doubles has to put on all the clothes, take the forks and rip the wrapping off the chocolate bar. They then commence to try and cut up the bar and eat it. All the while everyone else is still trying to roll doubles. We played this game twice, and between the two games I ate about a whole giant candy bar. I am so sick of chocolate! At one point I had so much chocolate in my mouth at one time I couldn't breathe and my up-chuck reflex started to kick in. Not a good combination, but I'm alive. We also played the bubble gum game. This is where you have a plate in front of you. On the plate is one piece of bubble gum, generally bubble yum because it is bigger than normal gum. Whoever eats the gum and blows a bubble first wins...but there a catch. The piece of gum is buried underneath a  huge  mound of whip cream. My parents say I'm not American just because I don't like whip cream, but I don't care. I hate the stuff with a passion, and yet I have a very strong natural instinct to not lose. A very strong competitive streak in me I suppose. Anywho, needless to say I toughed it out, and came in a close second, but I'm still satisfied with that. However, as we were sitting there just chewing our gum, the girl next to me says "hey andie" as if wanting to start a conversation. I turn to look at her, and just as I opened my mouth to say "hey what" a whole plate full of whip cream lands in my face. It was so disgusting! I was pissed to the max. I threw my plate at her and it got all in her hair and on her shirt. It also got all over the floor too. We were forced, against child labor laws I'm sure, to clean up the mess, but we laughed it off afterward. But don't think for a minute that I'm not gonna get her back even worse for what she did. I also have a rather strong revenge streak in me too.  Oh, yeah, and my leaders are gonna get it too. As we all were stuffing our faces with chocolate, and as I was getting a face full of whip cream, they were taking pictures! Gaaaaa!!! Evil gits. Oh well. If I get any copies I might post them, but then again I might burn them. I dunno. I'm still really hyper. I need something to do. I might go burn about ten of my candles at one time in my room. Fire is fun.....
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday was a very good day, or as good as my days will be for awhile. I basically vegged out all day, until band practice. We were there at 5 - 8:30. After that we went to burger king. That was really nice, considering i hadn't had lunch or dinner. After burger king i went home with one of my friends to spend the night, but we didn't go to her house. We actually went to a house that they are house sitting. It was so big and pretty, that and they have a really cute dog. His name is toby, he looks like the ice cream "brown cow", he's a polmeranian, and he only has one eye. He's adorable! He slept next to me and it made me happy. My friend and i talked until 2:30 in the morning. We just sat there and talked. It was the best thing i have done in awhile, and it helped me so much. We pretty much decided that we are gonna make this next school year totally awesome, and i totally hope we have at least two classes together. Dang it. that reminds me, registration is this week. That totally awesome, completely incredible friend that i am talking about, i know you're gonna read this, so do you wanna try and plan a time to go to registration together? I don't really wanna go alone and you know you're gonna be the first one i tell my schedule to, so why not have you right there? Anyways, so yeah, Last night really helped. I feel somewhat refeshed, like i now have the energy, and will, to keep moving forward. I'm not saying things are perfect, because they are far from it, but i can now look at the world and say without fear "Bring it, moron!" 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      He's gone. He's really gone. I spent most of saturady with him. We went to see the village with his brother, matt, and matt's girlfriend allie. It was a pretty cool movie. Then we went home, and i just sat around for the next 2 hours, trying not to distract him from packing, which he still had not done. I played with his dogs, talked to his mom, and just hung out. Then we had a steak dinner and his friends (shay, seth, and jeremy) showed up. They certainly made things interesting. After dinner we all went into the study and watched strongbad emails from  urlLink homestarrunner.com  and from  urlLink joecartoon.com . The gerbil cartoons are the best. I would suggest joe fish. That one is hilarious. After all that the guys went to carls junior to get more food. Damn bottomless pits. They left Tyler and I alone. We just sat in his room and talked about everything and nothing. I had done so well the whole day, and then mrs.goodnight came in and said that matt would be taking me home at 9:30, which was an hour away. She left and I just totally broke down. It was completely ridiculous and retarded of me. I have known ever since last October when we first started going out that he would eventually leave for college. I know a part of me knew this, but i think another part of me didn't want to believe it. I believe it now. His mom and him ended up taking me home that night. I watched him drive away, then i went to the kitchen and sat in darkness for a half hour. I then went to my bedroom, sat on my bed, and cried. I know i fell asleep sometime after midnight, but i'm not sure when. This is only the third time that i can ever remember crying myself to sleep. Sunday morning came. I got up to do the paper route. My mom was ticked at me because i hadn't gone downstairs saturday when i got home to tell them that i was home. She said that she didn't even know that i had gotten home. "Well, that's your fault now isn't it." is what i was thinking. While waiting to go to church i was sitting downstairs. My dad asked my i was so melancholy. "You use to always be my little ray of sunshine!" he said. "Yeah, when i was what, three?!" was my reply. As these little excerpts of my day may show, i was in a very depressed and angry mood. Sunday was a black day. I did get to talk to tyler though. At nine i called him, but it just kept ringing, so i hung up. a minute after i hung up the phone rang and it was tyler. He's doing good. Having a fun time. Hanging out with dalari and whitney. I love whitney to death. She's so funny. I really dislike dalari though, for retarded reasons of my own that only one other person knows about. Unfortunately, i can't help but thinking that once his school really starts, and he gets busy, i'll either be mostly forgotten, or completely forgotten. Whatever happens happens i guess. All i know is that he is gone, but such is life. And time moves on. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Omigosh! I just got back from bandcamp, like, 30 minutes ago. It was so tight. This whole past week has been one huge blur, but it was so freakin worth it! We had three of the hottest drum techs alive, two who just got back from marching corps. They were so great, they pushed us hard, but they didn't break us. They came pretty darn close, but not quite.  At the beginning of the week I almost had the opener memorized, now I have it down really well, but doing it with drill it kinda difficult. I'll get it eventually. The third song is messed up, so I am gonna have to practice that one hard core. It is 180, and has so many beats. It's insane! Oh well. Maybe I'll get that one eventually too.  So, right now I am in more pain that I can ever remember being in. My feet keep cramping up, so do my calves. I have a slight sun burn on my shoulders, and my wrists are dieing.  Drill was fun, but we were hardly ever inside for anything. The average tempt this past week was around 100-102. At one point it was 106. Yeah baby!!!!! We made it! I have a killer sock tan too. I wore the high ankle socks just so that I could really see the tan. I know it's stupid, but I didn't wear sun block all week, and I only got a shoulder burn, which is good cuz it's not even that bad.  The last night there we had a potluck thing where all of our families could come. My family came, and so did my boyfriend. I hadn't seen or talked to him for almost a week, so I was really excited. What sucked though is I only got to talk to him for two minutes, then my mom started freaking at me because she couldn't find chase, my little brother. She was getting mad at me, as if it was my fault. It's not my problem that she can't keep track of all of her freakin children! Anyways, I had to go find him, which I did. He was with this girl named shaylee and they were looking at the turtles in the wildlife area. I went back to the cafeteria to talk to tyler again, but he was gone. That made me a little disappointed and pissed at the same time, but I had to go change into my shirt and study my drill anyway I guess.  We went through the whole rehearsal. It was fun...sort of. I was gasping for breathe by the end of it, but that's because of our last three sets. They are all double time, and you have to haul but in all of them. I would have to say that they are probably my favorite sets though.  After the rehearsal we had a dance with just our band. Walking out there I saw my brother and his friends that had just graduated. I asked bj where tyler was and he told me that tyler went home. He hadn't said a damn word to me at all, not even good bye or anything. I was pretty mad, but I decided that I would have fun at the dance without him. The dance was pretty cool, mainly because the drummer stuck together and we all just hung out there. I had fun anyway.  Next day was freakin hot, but we had an awesome rehearsal for three hours, then the drummer clan went to burger king. Real food, finally!!! It was great. Then I got home and that would bring us up to this point. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This day has been the worst in a very long time. Last night's sleepover was ok. There was someone there that I have never gotten along with, but limited interaction with her kept me good. This morning I was on call (babysitting) for a very special woman I know. I thought that the latest I could be back was 4, so that I could go to a movie with my friends. Come to find out, they were all busy later, so they had to go to the 1 o'clock showing. I didn't find this out until noon, when my mom called me at the peoples house that I was babysitting at. She said that Tyler had tried to call me telling me that they were going at one and no later. This really upset me. That is actually an understatement. I nearly broke out in tears infront of the girls that I was taking care of, but I was able to hold it in. I kept hoping that the girls' mom would get back before 1, but no such miracle occurred. She got home at 1:15, I was home by 1:20. I was devastated. When I got home, my parents and the little ones were all packed up and getting ready to leave for wenatchee. They left, which left me alone. I looked for my drumline music folder...And never found it. I searched this whole damn house, and never found it. Tyler called during my frantic search, and the tears that had been threatening to come all day finally found an exit. We didn't talk much, but just knowing that he was there helped a little. I had to get off the phone, and I resumed my search. Again, to no avail. Cassidy came home not long after. She told me about her day, then listened to mine. She then decided that we needed to watch a movie together. She chose finding nemo, and I fell asleep on the couch with her sleeping head in my lap. When I woke up, I had that same sense of hopeless nothingness. Also, this whole time it had been raining.  I  didn't miss it because I wasn't in a movie theater, but it wasn't all it was cracked up to be. So, in summary so far, I had babysat, felt rejected by my friends, left by my family, lost the most important thing I own right now, and had to listen to the miserable rain for hours on end. Needless to say I have spent most of the day crying. While in this attitude of despair, I decided to call Tyler and ask if we could do something. So, he invited me over and we "watched" princess bride and weezer/stone temple pilots/multiple other music videos. I had such a good time there. I know that in a week he is gone, and that whole week I am at band camp, but while I was with him I forgot all that. I like to sleep so much because while you sleep, you forget. You forget everything that has been happening, you forget why you were angry, you forget the world. Tonight, being with Tyler was like being asleep. I forgot everything but him. He was all that mattered, and as long as I was with him, everything would be fine. Even though I am at my own home now, he is not completely gone. In fact, he will never be completely gone from me. Knowing that is what gives me the strength to keep going. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Tyler came over last night. It may have been the last time I see him before he leaves, but I pray it is not. We watched a walk to remember, and then the end of emperor's new groove. My little siblings were pissing me off and stressing me out when my dad came in from outside. He asked what we were doing. "Catering to their needs!" Was my reply, and it had quite a bit of anger in it. I love my dad so much, because he said "no, that's not right. boys, upstairs now! Leave andie and tyler alone." So they left , but don't worry, we weren't alone. My little sister, chelsea, age 12, was still there. Oh well. We watched the movie together and that is all that counts. Then we had to go upstairs for prayers so that the little kids could go to bed. Earlier that evening tyler had given me a present, but I refused to open it in my angry state. The little kids, however, would not go to bed until they saw what it was, so I had to open it. When I did I was completely speechless. It was a porcelain Tinkerbell with 24 carat gold inlay. It is of Lenox make, so it is extremely beautiful, fragile, and expensive i'm sure. He got it for me when he went to canada last weekend. This is the link to a picture of it...I hope.  urlLink http://www.lenox.com/images/pg/product_images/087992_w3.jpg  Links and pics don't usually work for me, which is sad. Anyways, tinkerbell is currently in her box hidden in my room, away from the kids, until i can get a shelf made to put her on. After the movies we went outside, looked at the stars, and just sat there. Eventually he left. I didn't want him to go because I knew that it would mean that the day was over, and we would be one day closer to his departure. Needless to say I cried myself to sleep last night. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I hope that whoever coined the phrase "change is good" is rotting in hell right now. Yes, change is necessary, but good is not the word that I would use to describe it. Occasionally change is good, but in my experience it is mostly unpleasant.  When change occurs in my life, is all seems to happen at once.   Last Sunday I found out my favorite youth leader and closest "adult" friend was released, so she won't be working with us anymore.  this past week, all summer actually, I have been getting ready for band camp, the whole drumline has, and yet the line-up for the line is still not rocksolid. We have 2 people who are complete flakes, so even the line is changing.  A week from Friday one of the coolest families I know will be moving to Spokane. The Lewis's have been here since before my family moved here, more than 15 years ago. Margeaux, one of their daughters, is the sweetest, funniest, prettiest girl ever. She and I went through drivers ed together. Great times, great times.  The Sunday after band camp, and two days after Margeaux leaves, my boyfriend is leaving for college. This will be the hardest change to deal with. I love him so very much, and I am going to miss him even more. We have decided to try and stay together, and I truly hope it works out. We shall see.   These are a few of the changes that are about to happen. I do not even wish to touch upon the ones that have happened, and especially not the ones that are happening now, because those are the hardest to talk about.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>