<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey! it's been awhile...cuz shockness i got busy! haha my friend came over and i got my skateboard and fell for the first time...so i've been on it like everyday and it's fun...then i went over to Tiffany's to skateboard and then we saw THE NOTEBOOK! It was sooo good me and tif cried and my sister didn't hahahaa. but it was good. then my mom suprised me w/ the Ashlee Simpson CD..which rocks. But b4 that my best friend called me and said she was drunk...which sux...cuz we always said we'd do whatever together. So then i talked to her today and it had been like a week cuz i went to my friends house for 4 days while my mom was in San Fransico...w/ my friends was really fun...we chilled, saw SpiderMan2, got ice cream, bowled, watched movies, played games, haha just had fun lol. Then i got home and talked to my bff, lauren, and it turned out she hadn't been drunk had just been joking...but...she had gotten drunk later on @ a party and stuff...so i mean whatever...lol. But it was drama cuz my mom found out about the false being drunk and told Lauren's mom and lauren's mom and lauren got mad at us...so on the phone we got in a fight adn she cried and stuff...but now we're cool. and it's ok. so yay. haha. and i've talked to my friend robert and i think we're gonna get together, and i talked to my friend brittney and i think we're gonna chill on Friday and who knows whats gonna happen with her. :) haha and i think we're going to the beach w/ tif on thursday. so it's all good. school starts in 2 wks adn one day! ahh! but it's cool! haha...well i gotta go more latta xoxoxo layla 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ok so it's the next day....i woke up @ like 1:00 pm....haha cuz i didn't go to sleep till like 4:00 AM cuz i was writing and listening to music...haha...ok so i've done nothing today...i watched tv and talked on the phone. but tomorrow i'm going shopping 4 school! yay...and i think i'm gonna FINALLY get a skate board...yay...haha. I love skater boi(s)hahaha it's soo sad but true...i like almost went out with one..but then it went all crazy...haha...his name was matt...he was very cute but kinda out there! hahaha but neways...today has been boring...hopefully tomorrow will be better...i think my friend might be coming over so that'll be cool...ok nuff for today xoxo layla  
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...ok...it's the same day...ok it's like 15 minutes later...and i'm already writing in here again...i'm sitting here in my CareBare pj bottoms and an old, Old Navy tee shirt...and it's like almost 3:30...ahhh the joy of slumming around...i was going to curl my hair but i decided not too...i was gonna curl it just for the joy of making myself pretty while sitting around the house...haha. ugh my face is peeling SOOO bad...like my WHOLE face is like 3 different colors...on my nose instead of my usual freckles i have like red spots surruded my tan spots and THEN to finish it off my regular skin color...it's nice...lol. my peeling is part of the reason i'm staying inside...lol it better get better soon...cuz staying inside one day is fine...two days is ok...but ugh three days is gonna suck! lol lets see what's been going on in my life...a lot of sort of drama...my friends...haha...i hav a drams filled group of friends! one of my friends her like whole life is drama...cuz of her on and off boy friend...who i had had a crush on...gezze that was horrible. Cuz like i liked him and he knew i liked him and she knew i liked him...but they got together neways...and he dumped her after...they *cough* ya'knowed...if you kno waht i mean...lol...then she thought she was pregant! lol it was liek something straight of THE OC or like Dawson's Creek (which are two of my favorite shows hahaha) but she wasn't...and he like said he hated her and ALL of this...but now there back together! it's CRAZY...so like all this has been going on...and now he's like being mean to her all over again! lol but neways....lol....then my best guy friend he moved out of his house and is living with his 'god mother' who is like CRAZY rich and gives him like 1,000 dollars a WEEK! it's like crazy...he took me my sister my mom adn and my best friend out to dinner and payed...haha...but neways...this is probarly toattly boring i probarly sound liek stuck up and spoiled...but i'm not! i'm just trying to think of interesting stuff to write! i swear! :) haha well i better go! *nobody is probarly even gonna read this!* haha xoxo layla  
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok...so my mom really wanted me to do this b/c...i'm not sure why. *laughs* so i'm doing it! partly because i'm really bored it's summer and it's the 2nd day i've done nothing but sit around and watch tv. i acutally have like a secudle (sp?) of like whats on and when...it's very sad. Rite now i'm watchin The Ashlee Simpson show/Buffy...haha...loser...:) Ok so i guess i should write some stuff about me...hmm...ok i'm 15 about to be 16 in September...i'm gonna be a shopmore in high skool...i'm single...haha yea...uhhhh...i like Rock music...punk music...alternative...oldies like the Beattles...and sometimes pop... i like going to the mall/movies with my friends since none of us can drive yet that's what we're stuck to doing. But next year will be  THE  year cuz i go to a VERY rich skool so like all my friends are rich...not 2 sound like rude or something but it's true...i however am not one of them...i mean we're not poor we live in a Town House that is very chic haha but i mean it's just my mom and my twin sister @ home...but neways next year all my friends can drive and will hav cars! :) yay! haha...so yeah...i'm not sure what to write in here and like what not to write in here...cuz i mean it's like a diary but not cuz other people will be reading it...lol...i mean i haven't given my name or nething but still! haha i guess that's it for now! lol more later! xoxo layla (why not i'll give my name!) 
    
</post>


</Blog>