<Blog>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Young my mother be trippin.  Its like she never gets off my back..My company just left and she talkin about dont have people in the house this late..But its okay for my sister to come in the house when the sun comin up..... DAMN WHAT IS THAT ABOUT ....SHE IS HARD ON ME ABOUT EVERYTHING.....I just dont understand....but other then that i'm okay not feeling that well i might need to go to the doctor or sumthin but i dont know well see..
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I thought it was about time to make a new one.   Much better  than Blackplanet..  I`m not as immature as you may think. I`m very  grown  and  sexy  for my age. I'm not too woman and i'm not too man, but I am somethng you can never understand. There`s girls like me who`ve seen above of of all you seen. I probably know more about you than you do. I`m beyond your  peripheral vision , so you might wanna turn your head. I am  bi-racial . My mother is  Haitian  [Creole] and my father is  hispanic/black  [cuban]. No me consiga el mal porque se un poco espanol tambien! I`m  32 flavors  and then some. I believe in the  N.E.R.D.  theory. I support  N iggas. A gainst. S ociety. I have a deep passion for Television Production and how all things go down.. I`m currently in love with Kanye West...he`s intersting, plus i meet him over the summer. But Luda has my heart. The color red makes my day. God damn, I love the summer! I`m not looking for a  significant other  but I don`t mind making new friends, but what I wouldn`t give to find a  soul mate , someone else to catch this drift. I'm on here to just have fun. I'm definitely not looking for my husband on here!  Love is a battle which both sides end up with scars . If you get out of line with me, i`m definitely getting out of line with you. I do believe in  reciprocity . I`ll let you know if your workin` my nerves. I don`t have any respect for anyone. There are too many  heartbreakers ,  decievers ,  scandelous-ass  bitches to really care anymore.  Some say im` triflin`and a Bytch, sometimes i rightfully am . I have lil` tolerance for ignorance. Some people just can`t help themselves. I`m into all types of music. Music is what makes me (can you tell?). From Jay-z to Alanis Avril Lavingne. Whatever my mood is reflects on the type of music I`ll listen to. I live off of BET Uncensored. Most of the artist who get a chance to do an  uncensored  are off the chain. I`m into body piercing and tattoo`s as you soon can see. I`ll wear anything from aja imani to jordan.   I tend to wear my mind on my sleeve and I have a history of taking off my shirt . I`m very blunt. I tell people the things that go on in my head. I am very  nonchalant  as well. I don't like giving people the benefit of the doubt or any implications that i'm pressed. I can come off random or just plain nasty! My mind seems to always be in the gutter. I can refer anything and everything to  sex .  Life`s a BITCH in mini skirts and big chests . I`m slowly but surely trying to piece together my life right now. My future is being put on hiatus right now. I'm patiently waiting for an  epiphany  to come over me. I crave chicken and collard greens. I am a big `ol party animal. It`s  all about partys & drugs ! I watch Queer as Folk. Gotta love gay men! lol. Sometimes I think im a  photographer . I love taking pictures of anything and everything.  Im a  trendsetter . Not to sound big headed, but there are some who wanna be like me. I start the shit no one has even pondered across. What can I say? I`m just  doper than you. 
      
</post>


</Blog>