<Blog>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What is she thinking????????    &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I am not sure she knows.......she is pitiful.    &nbsp;  No one loves her but Jesus...........oh Alicia loves her...she needs her.....    &nbsp;  NANA...she says............why dont you come live with me?    &nbsp;  SAD HUH!! ROBIN....pull out of it.....wake up.....................................    &nbsp;   Dont let satan take you down... 
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HMMMMMMMMMMMMMMMM will I ever find my way out of my bedroom?  Will I ever find the way out of my head........?????  This computer is my only friend I know...oh sure I have lots of good friends ......online...cause I am too scared to make any outside my home.................  Well my youngest daughter Sarah lives with me..but she only is here I think because she has to be....she loves me..but I was a very ill and sick mother raising my two daughters...and I think they are both mentally ill also....and it is scaring me.  I see it developing....in them both...I pray it doesnt turn out like me..........Its hard to fake a smile all the time ... Its hard to take my medicene and be normal for one day........  I have the most beautiful granddaughter..I want so bad to be near her and love her and she is 2000 miles away...my oldest daughter loves me inside but wants to be no where near me....  She is a hypochondriac like I was I made her that way...she is making her daughter that way.........oh GOD.  She never calls me..I have TO always call her...she rarely lets me talk to Alicia..but I cherish the days when she does...she is so busy in her life...or is she? Or is it she just doesnt answer my calls......................YES I am paranoid.....you will see alot of that in my writing.........  I never know what to think...I am my own worst enemy..........I sit in a relationship with a codependant man who loves to take care of me ( no sex..yuck) we sleep in different rooms..we rarely talk.........yes this is what i did all my life seek out men just like him and they HATED ME and LEFT ME and ABUSED ME...and I LOVED THEM all...want ing more and more of them and dieing inside each time one left.............but this one LOVES ME..and I HATE HIM but ...he is a man who takes care of me...........  We fight alot....his mother who lived in a home for mental illness all her life lives here now and we HATE EACH other and fight all the time...what little relationship I had with him and gone because of her........he is her relationship..but I hold on.............and just bide my time..in my room............in my sullen depression and maybe tomorrow will be a day I will go out and do something different..................  Maybe tomorrow I will stay in bed..............and watch TV...or read..............or maybe I will go to JEOPARDY and beat that millionaire guy.......I can do it..I know I can.............  Well....delusional...paranoid....and all..........I still think I would chicken out once I got outside my bedroom.  Well maybe you will get to meet some of my other identities...I am not sure my Cat can type....but she sleeps alot and sometimes stays up late at nite...who knows..................!  EVEN I am curious to come back and read as I sit as MYSELF ..ROBIN and write this...to see if any of them have come on to write and what they have to say...........so see not only is this a JOURNEY for you all...its also a JOURNEY for me..to meet and deal and see what they are up to...since none of these damn psychs out there cant do anything about it..cept give me pills...PLEAAAAAAAAAAAAAASE...............  BE BACK LATER.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>