<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm... this whole week has been rather crappy and sad for me... firstly... last monday or tuesday... i was caught for shoplifting... i dont know if it's a police case... i hope not... and it was really kinda embaressing... but who cares rite... i hate life la... oh and also my dad... he went back to he philipines like last fri i think... kinda sad... cause i was so angry at myself for some reason, i doonno what... and i didn't say goodbye to him... it's like... i hated him for 12 years... and this one month that he stayed in singapore for some operation was to me like.... hmm... hell i guess... that's what my first thot was... when my mom told me he was stayin at home for 1 month plus, my first thot was... bloody hell... that loser is staying with me for one month... and well... i hated it... then as time went on... i felt really close to him... really got so much to catch up on... for 12 years i haven't really know what it feels to have a dad... and now... for 1 month i had him with me... i feel really... how to put it... happy i guess... but i guess all good things must end huh... he left... i was so angry that i didn't say goodbye... haiz... now i feel so fucking angry... he is all alone in the philipines. how is he gonna handle diebitiez... haiz... :(  ok carrying on... i went for a floorball selection on thursday too... kinda ok... so rough but fun. hope i get in the team la. then after that training, i rushed home... hoping to spend some last min time wit my dad after he goes to the philipines but guess what... he was not at home... haha... taxi money wasted... rush home sweaty for nothing. haha... but he was spending time with my mom... sweet huh... haha... didn't know that part of my dad... i know it's not like he will be away for ever... but he will be gone for a really long time... and i'm afraid when that time comes... i might forget this missing feeling and start to turn it into hate... pls dont let that happen... haiz... :"(  well... i guess... this week was so confusing for me.   > i got caught for shoplifting and i finally know what it feels to have a dad at least for a month  haiz. :::::((((( 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       heyz.....   today is such a boring day.... last sunday was hmm.... fun i guess.... went to watch ella enchanted with my family... such a kiddy show... but it was fun non the less....     &nbsp;  monday in school.... nothing fun happening today as usual...    ok that's all la.... nothing much to update... just that it seems that i can only update this blog using the schools com... my house com is so so so fucked up... nothing is working...     &nbsp;  ok... fucking teacher lookin at my com liao...     &nbsp;  haha... seee what see...   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well... last sunday was just boring i guess... nothing much happen... other then visiting my aunt... and they going on about my dad and stuff... really irritating... but what can i do... well.. at least sat was better... cause at least i could go fishing till late nite... but then... waking up on sunday was really diff... end up having to take a cab to church for choir prac... and still being late... haha...   hmm... monday... i think i end class at 4 today... but i think i shall go home at 7... why? cause i hate home... that's why....
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      looks like i'm starting another one of this journal thingy again... the last time i did this, nothing wen well... i just hate lettin ppl know things about me... well... gonna try it again... maybe this time thing's will be better...it's only a journal tihng rite... how bad can it get... haha....  another time then update bah... nothing to say also...
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haiz... can't belive this two entry in a day... haha...   hmm... let me see... today was fun i guess... choir was alright i think... got two new members today... oh and manz i must do the poster thingy by this friday... haiz... what should i do?  should it be just words? should i make it as qraff as possible? haha... i'm good at drawing on walls and tables... dunno if i can do it on vangard sheet... and i just can't wait to get the tees... can wait to pour out all my creative juices on it... hahaha.... make it look totally outrages and wear it... haha... can't wait... hmm... oh i also wonder how the cookies for that day will turn up... haha... still a long way i guess... 29 of aug rite? haha... long way la... anywayz... saw her again today... really cool... haha... chio and all.... but just no balls to talk la... haha... pathetic i know... hmm... well...got my hair cut real short... why leh... cause stupid teacher say must cut or else can stop studying... haha... ITE also must cut... dumb shit... so just cut lor... anyway so long and hot... i was just to lazy to cut... haha... now that it's all gone i feel so much more lighter... haha...   *thinkin* k... i got nothing to say... actually i only update this blog when i'm sad, in trouble or bored... haha... i nv update it when i had fun and stuff... haha... this is one sad blog to read... haha... 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      bored... nothing to do... my day went well... oh and i cut my hair too... haha... fuzzy hair... ok that's all....  just bored....
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haiz... my mum and grandfather just had a long quarrel... and well... i donno why my grandfather had to pull me into it... and well... i shouted at him... and well... said lotsa stuff and the moment i said: "i will not talk to u anymore" i could see his eyes just turning white and i felt my heart stop... i could see that he was hurt when i say that... haiz... sometimes i just say things without thinking. haiz... i dont know... i hate him... yet i feel bad... he was the one that started the quarrel. he was the one that irritated my mum first... when he was quarrelling with my mum, i was in my room with my sister just laughin... haha... dunno why but the moment they shouted i felt as if everything was back to normal... one family living together... haha... and in my room i was kinda like shouting... die la u old man... haha... it sounds bad... but i was actually laughin with my sis when i said that... heez... i know i should not have said it... but it's done... now i feel bad... haha... but i just can't forget the look in his eyes when i said i will never talk to u anymore... haiz... it's just sad... i felt bad cause he was there when i was so young... and now that he is old and becoming paranoid, i tried to be there for him... but he just... thinks he is right... fixing everything in the home... doing stuff with the phone line... and when i kinda ask him not too, he shouts back... haiz... old people... love them and hate them... looks like i will nv talk to him again... thot i could help him... i tried... i prayed... but i give up... as usual... haiz...  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FUCKING PISSED LA...  hate my stupid useless family... i know it's bad of me to say that...  but almost everyone that i know are all putting up an act... even myself... argh...  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well... just visited togoparts.com again... a mtb site... again i was looking at bikes as usual... for those that know me, i just love bike so much... but too bad i just can't get the cash to get the one i wan... haha... just so many... so many bikes that i would love to get if i got the blings... haha...   here are a few of my fav: 1. cannodale; chase 2. da bomb; XLR8R 3. Specialized; P.3  haiz... if just by luck i were to find 3000 bucks u bet i would get it stright away... haha... i dunno... is it just bad of me to say that it is unfair? i mean i am kinda greedy rite... i complain about this but i nv think... i should be glad that i have legs rite... haha... ok... *slaps* wake up seanny boy... u wan it, u gotta work for it... u ain't no rich kid ya know... haha....
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm... let me update this blog about last thursday. or yesterday la... haha... didn't make the cut for floorball... i guess i was not up to standard... well.. the ite team is one of the best ma... so i'll just come for practice... haiz... i'm sad but i'm used to it... haiz... after floorball prac went to church to see my mum... haha... wen for a talk... i thot the talk was like going to be boring cause it was held by a nun... haha... well... i was so wrong... manz. the talk was so fun... haha... i even asked question about some of my problems to the nun... haha... after the talk i felt that some of my problems were solved in one way or another... haha... well... that's the highlights of yesterday i guess... hmm... what else... well... today i skip school lor... nothing to do now... just slack a home... haha... or maybe going out later? i dont know... haha... this is wat happens when u slack i guess... suppose to go fishing today... but then my other friend got into the team and now if i were to go it would be me alone wit another guy... that would be kinda boring... so i cancelled it... hahaha... i asked for it... now i'm stuck at home wit nothing to do... heez...  oh well... ooo... yesterday i saw this someone... but i dunno this someone's name at all... haha... hopefully can see this someone again i hope... haha...   argh... aiya... my mind hurts so much la... dunno what to write liao... byez 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just decided to pop by and drop an entry... well... yesterday went well i guess... haha... grandma had to like chase me outta my house cause my school starts at 1pm and she has to leave at 11am. and she is afraid that i would fight with my grandad or something... haha.. so she gave me cash and chase me out... haha... irritating... but what the heck rite... haha... then wen tm walk lor... what the hell can i do rite... then wen to school... didn't really study again... can't be bothered to... then after school decide to play pool with my mates... haha... had a challange there... who is the best amonge the 7 of us... haha... i did a fucking big mistake... i hit the black ball in so fast manz... argh... stupid... or i could have got 1st... hahaha... ya rite... well... but it was fun la... then after that rush down to go for choir prac... didn't really eat dinner... so i was super hungry lor... then i thot i was late... rush into the church... haha... then wen in and i saw them all still talkin... haha... i was thinkin to myself... should have ate and appear even later... hhaha... then i guess only like... me, dom, carol, daphnie,grace and adrian and geraldine came... haha... so little... but it was still fun i guess... and plus i showed my design to them... hope they like it... thot of it within like 5 min... last min one... haha... sorry... but it was nice rite?  then after prac went to eat dinner but it was like 10 then... haha... so ate liao wen home... reach home about like hmm... 11 plus... just in time to watch csi miami... haha...  then now awake liao... preparing to go to school... for floorball... and also didn't sleep well... had a stupid dream about her leh... haha... stupid rite... so long ago.... den dunno why suddenly dream about it... hahaha... now neck super pain... haha... how? to go floorball prac again... haha... ok la... dunno what to say liao...  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heyz...  last entry was rather sad i guess.... sorry to make u guys so worried... i'm fine... nothing happen... well... just quarrel wit my granddad... and looks like this time he wont talk liao... haiz... i tried to talk to him... but then... he just ignore... haiz... old folks... why are guys like this? will i be like them? i mean after all i was being brought up by ladys... and from what i have heard... a survey showed that most turn out either gay/sissy or a rebel... I DONT WANNA BE THAT AT ALL... when my teacher told my class that, my friends turn around... hated it... hated it so much... am i a sissy boy? i mean i was always being bullied in pri school... and now... shoplifting, vandalisin, small stuff la... haiz...haha... okok... better stop... i'm fine... take care
     

    
</post>


</Blog>