<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Having a friend as a co-worker is not always the best thing in the world. It puts a strain on a friendship that you never really thought would be pushed like that. S learned that the hard way on Tuesday and Wednesday.  First is when J tried to "help" him finish what he was doing. Lets just say that it's not help if you have to redo it. Then came a job that had to be a little more precise. It didn't go well as afar a S was concerned. What do you do when you don't feel that the work is good enough?  You call the boss. At least that's what S did. I'm proud of him for it. It isn't easy to call your boss and say that you feel the work could have been better, and you don't want to put your name on it until it's done right. S offered to come back on his own time and fix the bad spots if it was necessary. That shouldn't be such a big deal right. Wrong.  When you call the boss, the boss calls the foreman, and the foreman calls your friend it's not pretty. Especially when you're ten minutes from home and stuck in a car with them right after it happens. It put me smack dab in the middle between someone I view as family and my husband. All I could say was, "You have to talk to S. I wasn't there so I'm staying out of it." That felt so wrong. I knew why S had called, I told him to do it if he felt it was necessary. But of course J wouldn't understand that.  So when I get home I break. I walk in the door with tears streaming down my face and all I can say is, "I hate being put in the middle! I can't take it!!! Next time I tell you I want you to take me somewhere I want you to do it not someone else!" Then S has to try to get me to calm down enough that I'm not rambling so he can figure out what happened. After about five minutes he can finally make some sense out of what I'm saying. Then he gets back on the phone.  This time his boss isn't there, but his wife K says to tell her and she'll pass on the info. But of course S can't do that, I have to do it since I was the one there when it all blew up. She tells me not to worry about it to much. That S has good work ethics and they like that. I try to explain to her that when he called the first time he wasn't trying to pin it on J. That he IS taking responsibility for it and that's why he wants to come back on his own time and fix it. She says she understands and that S did the right thing. She also said to tell S not to change what he did, good work ethics are to his advantage. Especially when working for her husband.  Chris, S' boss, was supposed to go out to he job site yesterday but he wasn't able to. So he's going out there today. I guess it's the Lord's mercy that the car broke down Wednesday night and S couldn't go into work for two days. It has given J a little time to cool down without S being around.  I know that things will be back to normal soon. But until it does it's going to a bumpy road. 
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        One little butterfly floating on the breeze     One little butterly perfect as can be     One little butterfly He calls to his side    Now to this butterfly I must say "goodbye" 
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I have a few updates to make before I do anything else.   &nbsp;
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Friday,723/o4,&nbsp;was the first day of our two day garage sale.&nbsp; It didn't start out all that great we were supposed to be set up by 9 am but my friend didn't get here until 8:45 to start setting up.      &nbsp;   Things were going relatively well.&nbsp; Superchunk was still asleep so we were able to get quite a bit set up fairly quickly.&nbsp; At 9:30 I went to the back of the house and I could hear Superchunk screaming like there was no tomorrow.&nbsp; Not a good start for her day.&nbsp;  
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Well S' first week of work went very well.&nbsp; He was able to do what the boss wanted him to do without a lot of questions.&nbsp; He framed out the closet on Tuesday, and the boss said that everything about it was exactly what he told him to do.&nbsp; He spent one morning cleaning before the inspector came.&nbsp; Then he spent the afternoon sheetrocking the closet and doing more electrical work.&nbsp;    The owner of the shop was very pleased that he did the closet.&nbsp; She was worried that it wasn't going to be done by this weekend when she moved in.&nbsp; (She will be living above the salon).&nbsp;   So far Chris has had no complaints about S' workmanship.&nbsp; S has asked him about different things so he will no what Chris is looking for in an employee.&nbsp; He says if he needs to learn about something to help him on the job he's willing to do it.&nbsp;(As long as I'll read it to him.&nbsp; Which he knows I will)>   Sorry if I'm rambling but I've been up since 5 a.m. and it's now 11 p.m.&nbsp; Good night.   Tomorrow post: Tragedy Strikes At A Local Garage Sale   
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        It's true.&nbsp; You never know what is going to come out of their mouths or when.&nbsp; I think that's probably the scariest thing about being a parent.&nbsp;         Sure, you have to worry about being able to send them to the school of their choice, if they want to go, and secretly you hope they don't so you don't have to pay for it.&nbsp; You have to worry about them turning into some horrible criminal because you didn't buy them the Barbie or G.I. Joe or Pokemon that they absolutely couldn't live without.&nbsp; You wait for the day that they tell you that they hate you, or that "you're not their friend anymore."&nbsp; And that comes sooner than expected.&nbsp;&nbsp;You have to worry about paying for a wedding, or in my case two.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;         But all of that doesn't compare to the things that they say, because it NEVER happens in the privacy of your own home.&nbsp; Oh no, it's ALWAYS in a public place where you are surrounded by people.&nbsp; If you're lucky it's in front of strangers, but the chance of that happening is a slim to none.&nbsp;    &nbsp;
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yesterday went very well for S.&nbsp; He worked with Chris, his new boss, and Tom the Electrician.&nbsp; I don't know much about either of them but they seem&nbsp;to like him.&nbsp; Chris is a big Italian guy who we've been told has a pretty good temper, which hopefully he'll never see.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Tom spent quite a bit of the day trying to figure out S's age.&nbsp;  (His beard makes him look older).&nbsp;   S&nbsp; said that he guessed pretty close to it when they were listening to the radio.&nbsp; He recognized a song by Joe Santriani and Tom said that that "dated" him.&nbsp; We have three of his cd's and I still wouldn't know it if I heard it.&nbsp;   &nbsp;  Yesterday was spent plumbing&nbsp;romex through conduit at a former sandwich shop now day spa.&nbsp;  (For those who don't know conduit is a metal flexible tube that you run the electrical wire (romex) through.) &nbsp; He says that there is a lot of electrical work to do since there are so many bays.&nbsp; They line both sides of the space and they all have to have there own breaker.&nbsp; He was also supposed to frame out a closet, but they didn't get around to that.&nbsp; That's his job for today.&nbsp; Then it's back to the wiring again.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Hopefully his day is going okay today.  &nbsp;   I almost forgot, Chris gave him a key to the site and a credit card to go by supplies for today, since he will be alone at the site for most of the morning.&nbsp; He has to give them back today, but at least they think that he's trustworthy.    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I have updated my  urlLink photo  albums on another site.&nbsp;  (They are under the name AmberSukiMommy)&nbsp;  Please feel free to drop by.&nbsp; Check out Josephine's albums too, I'm sure you'll enjoy them.     
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Tomorrow is a new day&nbsp;and we don't know how it will end.&nbsp;&nbsp;       S, my husband got a new job; sort of.&nbsp; He's going to be working in construction for the next two weeks at least.&nbsp; Chris, his&nbsp; new  boss, hired him on a temporary basis.&nbsp; So tonight he had the joy of calling&nbsp;"Mr. Pride," his old boss and tellig him that he was taking a two week leave of absence.&nbsp; Let's just say that his old boss wasn't exactly thrilled, but he understood; sort of.&nbsp; S had to remind him that he was told about three weeks ago that he needed a raise or he was going to find a new job.&nbsp; I guess he didn't believe him.&nbsp; S also told him that his new job was temporary and that he'd talk to him about it again in two weeks.&nbsp; "Mr. Pride" just said okay, I look forward to hearing from you in two weeks.       I think he expects S to come crawling back on his hands and knees begging for his job back.&nbsp; I can tell you right now, that is not going to happen.&nbsp; Even if it means going on unemployment for a couple of weeks.&nbsp; I don't think S could take going back there.&nbsp; Things would just be worse than before.&nbsp; "Mr. Pride would be able to say, "I told you so," and that's never good.      &nbsp;   There are three things that bother me about this whole thing: 
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I had a good post for today. It was all typed out and ready to insert a link.&nbsp; I went to save it as a draft "just in case" and the "page culd not be found."&nbsp; AHHHH!!!!!!!!&nbsp; So everything&nbsp;I wrote is now gone. But that's okay I'll just try again later.&nbsp; Here's what you can look forward to: &nbsp; My huband has taken a leave of absence from his work to go work at a new job.&nbsp;  &nbsp; :) 
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Have you ever been afraid of something so dumb you're embarrassed to say anything?&nbsp; Like a&nbsp;ladybug, or public restrooms, or maybe even driving.&nbsp; If not, I envy you.      I have come to the conclusion, that being 25 1/2, a wife, and most importantly a mom, means that I really need a driver's license.&nbsp; I'm now on my third learners permit, and I'm no where near ready to go take "the TEST."&nbsp; I know that I could go take my test with just a few hours of practice, but I'm terrified.     I can drive around the parking lot at my husband's work with no problem.&nbsp; That means remembering to release the parking brake; backing out of the space without stalling (we have a stick) or hitting anyone's car; pulling up past the dumpster; and then backing around it to park in front of the garage to load the mail.&nbsp; I can do all of that, no problem, no sweat, piece of cake.&nbsp; But let him get in the car so I can drive the mail to the post office and I kill the engine ten times before we leave the parking lot.   &nbsp;  WHY???
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You know the saying, "When it rains, it pours," well, I'm living it.  My husband has once again been told he's not getting a raise; we didn't get an expected, and much needed, bonus; and Rapunzel (my oldest little girl) won't be home from vacation for another 5 weeks.  They also say once you hit rock bottom there's no where to go but up.  I think we're there but every time we start to climb up someone throws something at us and back down we go.    I think "Mr. Pride", my husband's boss, is out to get us.  My husband works for our church and "Mr. Pride" is trying to teach us a lesson.  We both think that he withheld a bonus that we have gotten for the last three years.  Of course there's no proof, and the only person we could have asked moved earlier this year.  Oh well.  We did learn a lesson though, the people we thought were like family to us aren't.   The only good thing is that we have each other.  Yeah, yeah, I know.  How corny can I be, right?   But it's true.  Every night he comes home and the first thing that happens is he gets "rushed" by "his girls" as he calls us.  Our 19 1/2 month old, Super Chunk, runs down the hallway, or across the living room, screaming, "MOMMY, MOMMY, MOMMY, MOMMY, MOMMY!!!"  even though she knows how to say "Daddy."  He just looks at her and says, "I'm not Mommy."  Then he bends down and picks her up, he really has no choice because one of these days she's going to climb up his leg if he doesn't.  Then Rapunzel comes up and does the same, and a six year old screaming "DADDY!!!" as loudly as she can indoors is nearly deafening.  Then it's my turn, a quick hug, kiss, and how was your day.  Then he's lost in a whirl of hair and giggles.  But I know he'll steal away to the kitchen for a few minutes, so I don't mind.  There's nothing to lift your spirits like listening to your kids laugh.  Especially, when everything seemed so bleak before.   Sorry for the long boring post, but I'm basically writing to vent.  It makes me feel better and that's what counts.  If you want some better blogging ckeck out  urlLink  
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        We started out for the airport at 4:30 a.m. on Wednesday with Super Chunk screaming her head off in the car. Not a good start.    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        It's here, 30, the big three-oh.  Not for me but for S. He's completely paranoid. He now thinks he's "old."  Now that he's 30 and I'm still 25 it's a BIG difference in our ages. Is it any more of a difference than when we got married? No. I was 18 and he was 23. It's only 4 1/2 years.  I keep teasing him and referring to him as "an older man." In a good way though. As in "I'm seeing an older man." You know that mysterious thing you hear about in all the movies. Meaning an experienced man. But all he hears is "old man."  They say you're only as old as you feel. For S it should be about 25. He still likes to play in the mud, and go out with his buddies, but he knows when to be responsible also. Like if you find an abandoned car with keys in it you report it; you don't destroy other's property; and you don't do anything to get yourself arrested. Some people just don't understand those things. Particularly those who are only 21.  I found him a shirt for his birthday. I normally wouldn't have bought it but it was just to fitting. Here is what it says, " Let me drop everything and work on your problem." He completely appreciated the humor in it, and it made him smile.  Today is his day. Super Chunk went to a friend's house and we pick her up "whenever" as my friend put it. I'm making pork kabobs with fresh pineapple and bell peppers, served over a bed of white rice. We're going to have a dinner with just the two of us, watch a movie, and then go get Super Chunk. I'm not sure what we'll watch out of our collection, but it really doesn't matter to me. All I want is to lay on the couch with his arms around me. I need to get in as much cuddling as I can since it has to last me two weeks. (I know I will have two very bouncy kids to cuddle with when I get to California, but it's just not the same.)  Our evening is being shortened due to the fact that we leave for the airport at 4:30 a.m. It's a time I'm dreading and looking forward to at the same time. It means two weeks away from S, but it also means I get to see Rapunzel, who I haven't seen in nine weeks and four days. That's right almost ten long weeks without seeing the happy, giggling, smiling face of my six year old. I wonder who she'll hug first me, her Mommy, or Super Chunk, her sister? It doesn't really matter, does it?  I leave S with a lot of love and a two freezers full of food. That's right two. He has enough food to feed himself for five weeks, or himself and a friend for about two and a half weeks, and that's not counting the cheap frozen burritos, hamburgers, hot dogs, or 40 sandwiches. He told me to make whatever I felt like and he'd just ration what he had. What kind of a wife would I be if I did that? So I made enough for him to have company too.  What can I say, but I love him. I love him with everything I have in me and then some. I love that's he mine and no one else's. His mom had him for the first 23 years, and I plan on having him for the next 80. Yes, that would make him 103, but as they say, some things only get better with age. 
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Rapunzel and Super Chunk are the best kids in the world, really.  What six year old would could spend 10 weeks away from home, and not cry about it? Rapunzel, that's who. She left for Hemet on June 5 by way of an her Papa's 18 wheeler and she hasn't looked back since.  They went all the way to Florida before finally making their way to California. They didn't see any gators in Florida but they did see the tigers in Texas, her favorite state when she was little. The day after they got to Hemet they went to the San Diego Zoo and then too the Spaghetti Factory. The next week they were at a Christian retreat called Lassen Pines. Then on to Secret Agent Josephine's for a few weeks at the beach. Then it's off to the high desert for a week with my parents.  Yesterday they went to the mountains and had a blast. She made a "new friend" and had fun fishing with him and my uncle's family. (Her new friend is my six year old step-cousin, that she hasn't seen in two years). They each caught a rainbow trout and brought them back to take pictures with them. My dad said she caught it all by herself, but that she wouldn't touch the fish or the bait. They're working on that part today when they go fishing at the local lake.  Rapunzel is supposed to go back down to Hemet on Monday but I think she wants to stay a little longer. When I told her that I would be flying in on Wednesday she was very excited. This is what she told my mom, "My Mommy's going to come on Wednesday, so you'll have to take me back on that day so I can get her." I don't know how S' mom will take her being gone a few extra days, but I'm not going to worry about it. She was here in May and has had Rapunzel all summer and my parents haven't seen Rapunzel since Christmas.  Wednesday, only four short days away, yet it seems like an eternity. I feel like a little kid waiting for Christmas to come. I will be flying with Super Chunk to go pick up Rapunzel and bring her home just in time for school. We get to visit for two weeks which seems like such a long time but really isn't. Two weeks to spend time with S' family and mine. How do you squeeze visits with eight different families in just ten days? Luckily six of them live in the same town, Hemet, and the other two are only 15 minutes apart in the High desert.  This will be Super Chunk's first flight and my third. I'm not sure how fun it's going to be. Super Chunk is suffering from seasonal allergies. This has her little round nose all plugged up so everything is just going straight to her stomach. She spent most of the day with dry heaves trying to vomit up all the phlegm. This means that every time she has a dry heave she has to wait another hour before she can have anything to drink, let alone eat. The amazing thing is she doesn't even cry about it. She calls for me to come and hold her up while she gets sick but that's it. She didn't shed one single tear at all today, and it was 3 p.m. before she was able to drink anything. (She slept until 11 am then put herself back to bed at 12:30, and woke up again at 2:30. I don't want you to think I let her go all day without anything to drink while she was awake).  My girls are definitely two good little troopers. They'll follow you anywhere and be good, as long as they're not too tired. What more can I ask for? 
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Just a quick update then on to what's on my mind today.  
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        A carrot, an egg, and a cup of coffee... Believe me, you will never look at a cup of coffee the same way again.  A young woman went to her mother and told her about her life, and how things were so hard for her. She said she did not know how she was going to make it, and felt like she just wanted to give up. She was tired of fighting and struggling... It seemed as if when one problem was solved, a new one arose.  Her mother calmly took her into the kitchen. She filled three pots with water, and placed each on a high fire. Soon the pots came to a boil. In the first pot, her mother placed carrots; in the second she placed eggs; and in the last she placed ground coffee beans. She let them sit and boil, without saying a word.  In about 20 minutes, she turned off the burners. She then fished the carrots out and placed them in a bowl. She pulled the eggs out and placed them into a bowl. Then she ladled the coffee out and placed it in a bowl.  Turning to her daughter, she asked, "Tell me, what do you see?"  "Carrots, eggs, and coffee," she replied.  Her mother brought her over closer and asked her to feel the carrots. She did and noted that they were soft. The mother then asked the daughter to take an egg and break it. After pulling off the shell, she observed the hard boiled egg. Finally, the mother asked the daughter to sip the coffee... The daughter smiled as she tasted its rich aroma.  The daughter then asked, "What does it mean, mother?"  
</post>


</Blog>