<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It’s Tuesday working from 1pm to 10pm. yesterday I took my car in to get the breaks pad replace. Anyhoo, I was looking at a magazine or what not and this lady start talking to me. Its funny how people just start to talk to you. I was like so weird out and stuff. She was talking about how she is going to get married next year in May. She wanted to know my background. I was like I am Indian and I was born in India and work in retail and stuff. She was like I figure because you are dress well and she was like you are very pretty. I was like thank you.&nbsp; I real don’t think so but anyhoo. She was like I am scare to get married and stuff because the guy she is marrying has two daughter and she doesn’t know if they are going to like her or not. I was like don’t worry every thing will work out on its own.&nbsp; Also, yesterday my brother came over. It was good to have him over. Everyone misses him. So do I. We have strange relationship but its not that bad. However I find him very nosey and my sister says that, that’s the way he shows his feeling. That he loves me a lot.&nbsp; I was like I know… I gotta go now.. Byebye 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's Sunday night and I can't sleep. Just sitting here thinking what's going on in my head. I really don't know why I think a lot. Why I can't draw lately or paint. I really do miss it. I want to do so many things, but my heart&nbsp;does not&nbsp;desire.&nbsp; So scared in so many ways yet only one can understand the confusion, but not willing to do anything about it.&nbsp; My mind runs from the reality my physical&nbsp;&nbsp;being can't escape true facts about life that I hate to face.&nbsp; I would love to just be alone with nothing I know of my surrounding. Feels like I should be some where else.&nbsp; Don't ask me where because I really don't know.&nbsp; I do enjoy life but some how feels like I am not with myself.&nbsp; Nothing makes sense when I write, but some how&nbsp;it does.  got to escape my mind from reality.. Going to sleep  Chalo  Goodnite  Kiss kiss..          
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday… and I have to be at work at 12 O’clock. Oh well.. Well I am waiting for my cutie pie to come online but I don’t think he is going to.&nbsp; I was talking to him on the phone other day and I was telling him that I am on this Website and basically you can write about anything. So he asked me if I wrote anything about him. Which I didn’t… Well only reason is because I really really like him. Its kinda weird but we started to talk online since April and we talk on phone here and there. Sounds like real nice guy. Really scare to meet him in person and only reason is because I really like. He is all the way in London, but right now he is in India. However, I would love to meet him. He is on my mind all the time. So do I have a boyfriend I would say yes.. If anyone ask me. If my family members ask me then I would say no. Only reason is because they get in my way. They ask too many question and they jump to conclusion. Well my mom is open minded so I told her and my sister and one of my sister in law. I think I am crazy for him..  Well I gotta go now but I will write more..  Kiss kiss  Bye    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      First day writing on blogspot.com. Nothing much is going on. Just a beautiful day out. Only worked like four hours. I can’t really complain about anything. What can I say.. I have been single since Feb. 2002. Well not really singel any more but&nbsp;I am talking to someone&nbsp;I really like.&nbsp; Anyhoo, when I was with my ex bf for a long time, I really thought when I broke up with him that life had no meaning. Anyhoo, that all changed after year or two. I feel like that was the smartest choice I ever made not being with him. If anyone who is out there feels that or have doubt about there relationship. That u made the biggest mistake of being with ur partner and u tried everything to work it out and its not getting better. Well news flash its never going to get better. The thing is that u cant change a person. Always remember that u can only change urself. Either u deal with the problems in the relationship rest of ur life or change urself. I change the fact that I was not going to put up with bull shit with my ex. I face the fact that I was stupid that I ever went out with him. I learned so much from my past relationship… No worries any more… =) Well today I think I am going to hang out my friend Steve and Nydia. Steve is fabulous…. He just makes everyone smile. I use to work with him in Marlton. He dresses really good and smells good and he has lots of respect for his friends. Ummm yeah he is gay.. but he is the best guy to have has a friend. Nydia.. What can I say about her? She is pretty coo.. She also dresses real nice.. Has like thousand purses or handbag. Beautiful watches.. With nice pair of shoe. Well I should go.. Its going to be fun writing… kiss kiss byebye 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Masa’s mom (Masa = my mom’s sister husband) passed away.  My mom told me about it when I got up this morning. I am not good with dealing or talking about someone passing away. So I decided that I should write little bit about it and maybe that would ease my mind. I saw her in April at my cousin’s wedding. It was lots of fun and I was happy to see her there for her granddaughter’s wedding. She didn’t complain once when we all were there. All the kids made lots of noise every night. She didn’t complain at all. When we said bye to her and first thing that came to my mind was that, that’s the last time I will see her. Sadness set in and tear drop from my eyes. I looked her once more and she gave us all 10 pound. I gave that 10-pound to the charity for needy children on the airplane. We will all miss her and I know she is in a better place. goodnite kiss kiss 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I am happy and pissed at the same time. Happy because I talk to my cutie pie yesterday. Pissed because my sister is going to go to dinner with Angel tomorrow. That really piss me off because the way I see it is that he does not deserve to go out with my sister for any reason. Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!! That makes me very angry. I don’t want my sister to be a fool by a dumb ass.  Guys will say anything and do anything to get you back but once they have you back they treat you like shit. I mean you can give a guy one or two chance. After that if you give more then that, then we are just a fool as they make us out to be. I feel like cursing but I am not going to. Ahhhhhhh!!! Ummm I should think about something else isliye mera stress level Oh shit!!! I heard a loud noise outside. Something hit my window really hard. I looked outside and I saw a bird laying on the ground. I got really scare and ran outside but I was too late the bird had pass away. I need to go.. I have things I need to get done. Write later Take care Kiss kiss 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      iT'S aROuNd 1:30 am.. What can I say.. Couldn't sleep again.. So I decided to watch Yuva..It was pretty good movie. I am going to be soo tried tomorrow.. I am thinking I should just come home early tomorrow from work. I have soo many pto time I need to use. Had some weird dreams yesterday night.. Cant really talk about it.. Scare to go to sleep. Feels like I should take some time off from work. That way I can ease my mind little bit.. before my stress level goes really high and I wont be able to sleep for weeks. umm yeah ok!! That wouldn't happen but I need some time off anyhoo. Well tomorrow is another day.. Well.. I need to stop thinking about it.. need to go to sleep.. I have to write some other time.. chalo Gooodnite..  
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Absolutely I had a crazy night yesterday.. I went to sleep around 1 because I couldn’t sleep.. Thoughts ran through my head like there was no tomorrow. It was if I was writing my thoughts down in my head while I was trying to sleep. I don’t know if that happened to anyone but its very aggravating. Especially when you know you have to wake up early the next day and you have the hardest time to try to make yourself sleep. Not to mention I woke up three four times in middle of the night. Lets just say I got no sleep or rest. I am going to go now and write my email. Kiss kiss Goodnight. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today got up and got ready and went to work. I have not talk to my honey since Saturday. Miss him… Seems crazy and I never even met the guy. That’s what my friends tell me. Everyone should know that I am confused and crazy Indian girl. Anyhoo, day at my work was very slow and boring. Around 9pm it was raining really bad and power went off at my work and turn back on for like 3 times. Something went wrong I couldn’t close the one register. I was so frustrated that it wasn’t even funny. I got off work at 11 O’clock. I was so pissed and stress that I had to stay there longer then I should have. Just my luck. So I checked my email… got an email from my sister in law… the younger one. I have to really think about what my responds going to be. There are lots of things I want to say but I want to make sure I mean every word that I write down in an email. Anyoo, I have some crazy older Indian dude who comes to my store to shop and who is crazy about me… Today he came to my work and was like I brought something for you and I want to give it to you. I was like please I don’t want it. If he comes back again I am going to be like please leave my store. Ahhh!! I hate guys.. Another guy who is one of my friend’s ex bf friend wrote me a email on friendster saying that he was soo glad that he meet me last Friday and he wants to get to know me more and talk and hang out. Goshh.. Can people just let me be. It’s late and this Jalebi have to go to sleep and be a good Jalebi. I need my rest. Kiss kissGoodnight 
    
</post>


</Blog>