<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi all.  And by the title of this entry I know it sounds like I am talking about relationships, but I am definitely not at all.  I'm talking about friends.  Man.  Sometimes it bums me out that I really have no friends here in NC.  I mean, damn.  Part of me always thought I would love having all this time to myself and to chill and do whatever- watch tv, read, write, etc.  But now it all just feels sort of boring.  I mean, obviously I love spending time with Josh.  Duh.  But there are times like now when he sort of wants to chill around the apartment (and I don't blame him, he's been super busy as of lately and he is not feeling well) but I sure wish I had my girls here that I could call up and we could hang out.  Or someone could come over.  Or *gulp* even go to the Muncie Mall... lol Anyways, so I am just sort of bored and wish I had my friends here.  Glad I have my Josh, but sometimes a girl needs her crew! anyways, so just a shout out to all the people I love and miss.   "I live for the nights I can't remember with the friends I'll never forget."  ~bobo~ 
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just a quote from Nat that I could relate to.&nbsp; I hate those moments when you think of someone who you don't particularly want to think about.&nbsp; Of course hers is because she is still in love and mine is because my ex hates me!&nbsp; lol. Anyways!&nbsp; So today was a good day.&nbsp; Short day of work, but was good.&nbsp; Now I am tired and have the whole night to myself because Josh has to work late.&nbsp; Man, what am I gonna do?&nbsp; it's weird to have time home without him!&nbsp; lol. He bought me flowers yesterday which was awesome.&nbsp; He also was real sweet and said things that gave me those dumb girl butterflies.  I love butterflies.  Sometimes I just like to reflect on the simple fact that life is good.  really good. 
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So today has been a great day so far!&nbsp; I woke up in a wonderful mood.&nbsp; Not sure exactly why, but still it was a welcome change!&nbsp; :)&nbsp; Last night was fun.&nbsp; Josh and I went out to dinner and had crab.&nbsp; mmmm.&nbsp;&nbsp;good stuff.&nbsp; I drank a few cosmos and it was fun!&nbsp; We had&nbsp;a great night!&nbsp; Then today we went to IHOP for some Paradise Pancakes, which I have been CRAVING because of the commercials.&nbsp; They were good.&nbsp; I feel better having tried them.&nbsp; lol.&nbsp; And now I have had them and I don't need them again.&nbsp; lol.&nbsp; JOsh bought me a pair of running shoes and then we went to Barnes and Noble bought a ton of books.&nbsp; We are starting to work out and read more, rather than sit in front of television and waste our evenings.&nbsp; So that is good.&nbsp; :)&nbsp;  anyways, now I need to put laundry away now.&nbsp; I am making sushi tonight!&nbsp; :)&nbsp; That should be good! more later! it's a beautiful day!&nbsp; :)  also, today I looked in the mirror and again liked what I see.&nbsp; THat's a nice feeling.&nbsp; I think perhaps venting in here yesterday helped.&nbsp; thats good!&nbsp; :)  ~the bobo~ 
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    I had to... this is one is for the happy couple.  I love you guys!  Congrats on the baby!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    and last, but not least, my loving ex boyfriend.  glad it worked out okay with the new girl.  What's her name again?  Trichelle?  Tricanda?  Something like that.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Friends.   :)&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    "My Favorite Spot is Center Stage!"&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    In honor of the dress.  &nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    "We are LIKE dis.  We ARE like dis.  We are like DEEEES."&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Me being Zubaidah&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Me being Romaine&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    "May you (dramatic pause) have a long (Pause) life.  (PAUSE) and may you (PAAAAUUUSE) thank Matthew (PAUSE AGAIN) every day (PAUSE HOLY GOD) for (PAUSE)................it."  The longest monologue ever.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    why do i wear a wig in every show i do?&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Aw!  They're in love  :)&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The Snatch Patch- in all it's glory.&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Banquet 2003&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    we'll try this one again... freshly showered...&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    At Sarah's graduationg party&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp; am i difficult to be in a relationship with?&nbsp; i realize more and more every day that i am hard to please.&nbsp; i hate that about myself.&nbsp; i overreact, i get shitty when i don't get my way, i basically can go from fun to bitch in a few seconds, and yet i expect people to be okay with that.&nbsp; my biggest fear is that i will push josh away just like i do everyone to protect myself from getting hurt.&nbsp; and then in the end start the cycle over again.&nbsp; hence the title of my journal entry.&nbsp; what the fuck is wrong with me that&nbsp;i choose the push people i love away?&nbsp; i am trying to watch it, but even just this little incident i just had with joshua, if i didn't just start writing in here i would have flown off the handle and we would have had the biggest fight ever.&nbsp; i don't know why i am so hot headed.&nbsp; i just get mad and then right away want to lash out.&nbsp; i get mean and i hate that.&nbsp; i wish i could change, but i wonder is it so engrained in me that it is just a part of my personality now i don't know if i can change that?&nbsp; i hope not.&nbsp; otherwise i would be impossible to be with.  i have been feeling a little down lately.&nbsp; not sure what it is.&nbsp; i am PMSing so that could be part of it.&nbsp; i feel like iam gaining weight and i dont know if i am or not.&nbsp; i dont think so.&nbsp; but then i look in the mirror and i find myself liking what i see less and less.&nbsp; i know i am restricting my food again, and even though i try not to stop i find myself falling back into the old thoughts.&nbsp; all i think about is food.&nbsp; all day.&nbsp; from the moment i wake up in the morning, until the moment i finally fall asleep.&nbsp; it's sick.&nbsp;&nbsp;i think about what i am going to "allow" myself to eat today and what I am not.&nbsp; i feel like if i restrict all day and then eat normally at night i am being healthy around josh and all, but i am also not eating like a cow.&nbsp; i need to go to someone.&nbsp; i know i do.&nbsp; but i dont even really have insurance anymore and won't i think through work for a little while, so i guess i just have to deal with it on my own for now.&nbsp; i think the reason i have been so down is because i really feel like there is no one who can understand.&nbsp; and no one who knows what i am going through.&nbsp; i know it's not true, but still.&nbsp; it's not like i have anyone around who can understand how i feel because it is so fucked up and i know that.&nbsp; saying "you're not fat" doesn't work.&nbsp; saying "just eat" doesn't take the image that i am fat and disgusting out of my head.&nbsp; it's fucked up.&nbsp; and it's not like when i talked to Carrie it was anything major.&nbsp; we sat and talked and i just got my feelings out there.&nbsp; i guess i can do that with people in my life, but it's different.&nbsp; they are involved with me.&nbsp; it's not as if i can talk to my grandma because then she would spend all of her days and nights worrying about me.&nbsp; and it's not as if i can talk to josh really because then that gets into my fear of pushing him away and him thinking i have all this shit to work out etc.&nbsp; and i have&nbsp;a lot of friends, but i don't have a lot of good friends.&nbsp; and the ones i do are far away.&nbsp; and most of them i dont want to waste the time we have to talk with chatter about my stupid ED.&nbsp; Thats why therapy is great.&nbsp; you get to talk to someone who's only job is to sit and be there for you.&nbsp; they don't judge you.&nbsp; they don't leave you if they don't like what you say or what you look like.&nbsp; they are realiable and you can always trust them.  i need to get out of this funk.  She is the girl That everybody knows. Whenever she’s hurting It never really shows. She walks with confidence, A picture of grace. She never lets anyone see Tears running down her face. But I know the truth. Through her mask I can see  All the pain deep inside  Is only shown to me. I wish I make Her sadness disappear. I wish I could take beauty To replace all the fear. She’s killing herself,  And we all watch her go. She’s dwindling away  And only I know. If she can just make  Herself become so small Then maybe someday She just won’t be here at all. All the pain that she’s caused Will all go away. In the world so black and white She won’t be caught in this grey. I wish I could tell her That she is beautiful too. But no matter how much I say the words She won’t believe that it’s true. She’s so much unhappier Than she may appear. If she keeps going this way She’ll be dead in a year. Her body’s rebelling, A familiar routine. So many changes outside But more gone unseen. Each day that she struggles She knows how it will end. I try to be there,  Try to be a good friend. I reach out to her, To pull her a bit nearer. But my tear stained hand returns to me When it hits my mirror. 
      
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thought I would put down some poems in here, rather than just in my handwritten stuff...   Untitled  This is how it will go.  You’ll stand there confidently, regretfully,  and tell me that you can’t.  I’ll respond simply with “ok, I know,”  making no argument against you.  The reproach will be yours alone.  You’ll reconsider;  realize where you stand…  the consequences at hand…  I will stand unaffected,  knowing you would all along,  accepting your final decision  as someone singing the song  of plain indifference  &nbsp;of the one who has long known  that the sole purpose of their life  is to pinnacle at this specific moment.  And so you will come to the conclusion  that you have made the decision on your own,  to your benefit,  though you know you always accepted  you were the harmony in to my tones.  And then you shall realize  that you also have long since known  that each of us has wanted to,  that we would both be here  and both make this decision  me, free of fear.  You have existed with it  reciting its rhythmic words to your subconscious.  And a look of indifferent passivity  shall cross your face,  attempting to hide the triumphant discovery  of epiphany blatantly blazing on your face.  But realizing that I know each expression  your eyes can bear and the meaning,  you cover it with a nervous, half angry laugh.  Your face hard and mean.  But my look is different,  one you cannot decipher, for it is a knowledge that you have never seen.   Beautiful Broken Things  It's the broken beautiful things - shattered glass spiriting a window reflecting each light ray. a crack in the ceiling to watch the stars and raindrops leak through. the sculpture's feature-defining crack of an egg shell. broken record- beautiful symphony of broken people authentic and venerable how fragile likea glass-blown vase. And me. these are the beautiful broken things.   Lines in the Sand  We drew lines in the sand we said not to cross but sand shifted  as sand will do and we washed away I spent all day longing to build a sand castle but all we had were rocks so we built a cliff and leapt all our dreams piled and crumbling beneath our feet into the leaping waves below.   Untitled  We're stuck between these ideas of right- boundaries and lines Where are they drawn? And what went wrong?  I would take it back and start over again-  be more careful, more perfect- do anything needed-  and should it be repeated, be better than I ever have- make it better than it ever was.   Was it ever good enough?  Perfectly flawed- but if nothing was wrong,  was it right all along? Life was content, but perfect destructed  and made the same appear worse- this blessing a curse Now today and tomorrow look the same to me- same faces, same places, same sights, and same smells  Does any of it change?   Is this all life has to offer?  Why do I even bother?  We drift farther and farther. Everything is temporal- it dissolves and it falls and reality hits the walls when insanity calls And corners grow darker by the same light- the words become trite and somehow meaningless now-  but how?  when it meant so much then- where should I begin ?Should I reminisce-each spinning moment,  each floating kiss or should I dream and pretend I'm fine this time fall asleep crying but go out with a smile it might last for a while- but only a while  Interrupting my pictures-park benches, adventures rain and darkness and street lights and swings All of it blurry and floating and the feeling falls behind, but sometimes it stings when it brings to mind how beautiful the stars were- Are they the same stars? I could swear they were brighter- the darkness grows lighter  And tonight will soon fade like our perfect charade the curtain falls down-  the applause soon drowns out the silence of our words- or what was heard-  how absurd this script left unwritten and a play with no ending- only room left for mending in infinite scenes to fulfill all our dreams and conduct all our schemes, but do we hear the screams in the overwhelming silence?  -Outplay all the violence  as the colors mesh and fade to gray, the roles we play, the lines we say they all burn and drift away This wasn't in the script Improvise your disguise,  and don't let your eyes betray your feelings, though your mind is reeling, Hands are shaking, insanity prevails,  your thoughts go stale, but somehow you'll manage-  a graceful bow as the curtain falls  and the lines are drawn.  
      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This was a good weekend.&nbsp; Josh and I went to the zoo yesterday and spent the whole day there walking around and seeing all the animals.&nbsp; God, I love the zoo.&nbsp; It was a lot of fun.&nbsp; We walked SOOO much and that sort of kicked my ass.&nbsp; My legs are tight today, but that could be because I drank entirely too much wine last night.&nbsp; lol.&nbsp; But thats ok it was fun.&nbsp;&nbsp; I certainly don't want any dry white wine for awhile now though! Nothing too exciting.&nbsp; Josh and I were lazy this morning.&nbsp; My blood sugar was all kinds of effed up this morning so that was how Josh got the wake up- to me shaking becaise my blood sugar had dropped.&nbsp; Gotta love the blood sugar disease!&nbsp; :)&nbsp; But it is better now.&nbsp; I am going to go eat something soon and that will help a lot. Blayne's grandma died.&nbsp; I feel bad for him and for his family but at the same time I don't know that I want to open up any lines of communication.&nbsp; Actually I know I don't.&nbsp; We are not friends and I doubt we ever can be.&nbsp; He has flat out said that as long as I am with Josh he will not be my friend.&nbsp; And frankly, I don't see that changing any time soon, so...&nbsp; thus is life&nbsp;I suppose. Josh and I are getting ready to plan our vacation.&nbsp; I am super excited.&nbsp; It should be an awesome time!&nbsp; And I can't wait!&nbsp; We are now deciding on a cruise or a trip to Seattle, because I have never been.&nbsp; I told him yesterday that I wanted to go to New Zealand for our honeymoon and he agreed.&nbsp; lol.&nbsp; Likely.&nbsp; And I suppose we should be engaged first too, eh?&nbsp; Details details. it's weird because a part of me thinks that if we were engaged while he was in Iraq I would feel better about him being there.&nbsp; how weird is that?&nbsp; Of course I don't tell him this because we all know that nothing freaks a fella out more than the old talk of marriage.&nbsp; lol.&nbsp; In actuality Josh is super comfortable talking about future stuff.&nbsp; But there is a part of me that still feels weird initiating any kind of serious talk about us.&nbsp; I know it's dumb, but I just have it engraved in my mind that the best way to ruin a relationship is to talk about the future.&nbsp; And the best way to push a guy away is talk about serious stuff like marriage etc.&nbsp;&nbsp; I need to get over it, but I don't know how soon that's going to happen.&nbsp; I guess the biggest thing about us getting engaged is that it's more of a comittment.&nbsp; And with him being gone, I know that there will be times when I am worried and concerned that maybe his feelings are wavering, even though I am sure that they won't.&nbsp; Sometimes I hate being so thoughtful.&nbsp; Grrrr.&nbsp; But I can say with almost 100% that the artist formerly known as kellbobo will have a naked left right finger as she bids her love adios to Iraq.&nbsp; And that's okay.&nbsp; I just don't think that Josh probably really thinks about asking me before he leaves.&nbsp; Which is understandable since he has a lot on his mind with deploying and all.&nbsp; And it's not as if I bring it up.&nbsp; lol.&nbsp; Just something I think about sometimes. Well, I do believe I should go feed myself.&nbsp; More later folks! 
      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Whew!&nbsp; What a long day I have had!&nbsp; Woke up late being Joshua forget to reset the alarm (worthless boy)&nbsp; :)&nbsp; And so I had to rush rush RUSH to get to work on time.&nbsp; Lucky for me I had showered late last night and so I was not in desperate need of another one this morning.&nbsp; Anyways, so then I got to work and began my day of the terrible twos...&nbsp; lol.&nbsp; Actually today was not heinous and I am glad to have the weekend now.  Maybe my voice will come back and I will stop sounding like such a man.&nbsp; I know.&nbsp; I'm a sexy bitch... :) So tonight is Josh and I's go out to eat night!&nbsp; Woo-Hoo.&nbsp; I am excited.&nbsp; I dont know where we will go, but I am sure it will be good stuff.&nbsp; I wish I had my old appetite back.&nbsp; I guess it's good that I don't, but it's just ridiculous how little I eat and feel full.&nbsp; I guess when you stop eating that tends to happen.&nbsp; ha ha ha.&nbsp; Okay, stop hating me all of my friends who hate my eating disorder jokes.&nbsp; :)&nbsp; I will have all of you know that since moving down here I have been, like 3,000 times better.&nbsp; :)&nbsp; Worry not world.&nbsp; I think I have gained weight, but since Josh threw away the scale before I moved in, I have no idea.&nbsp; I weighted myself when I was home for the 4th and I weighed 122 lbs.&nbsp; Pretty sure that has gone back up to being almost 130lbs.&nbsp; Not that I am complaining, just saying.&nbsp; I do wish I could stay in the low 120s or even in the upper teens, but I dont think that will happen.&nbsp; And I guess being 5'6 thats ok.&nbsp; But still sigh.&nbsp; I wish Paris Hilton did not taunt me so!&nbsp; :)&nbsp; lol. Anyways, so we will probably also play RISK tonight and I will probably lose.&nbsp; Like I do.&nbsp; Every time we play.&nbsp; grrrrrrrrrrrrr. &nbsp;We're going to the zoo tomorrow.&nbsp; I can't wait!&nbsp; That is one thing that I miss about DC.&nbsp; Going to the zoo and sitting in the gorilla house.&nbsp; Man.&nbsp; It sounds dumb, but I loved those apes.&nbsp; I would get so annoyed by the people who would come in and bang on the glass and be obnoxious.&nbsp;&nbsp;It was just such a cool place to sit and watch them interract with each other and then eventually with you. &nbsp;They are just such cool animals.&nbsp; But my last trip there was less than pleasant.&nbsp; Most of them were sick, and the rest who were still out, just layed there and barely looked at me.&nbsp; It made me sad.&nbsp; Oh well! Well, that's all I got for now!&nbsp; 
      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I just have to leave a post up about my awesome boyfriend.  I love that when I pick fights with him, he refuses to play my game and in the end there is no fight, just me looking like a fool... :)  lol.  I just was thinking about how much I loooooooooooooooove him.  :)  I also think I might be in trouble, so maybe this will help  :)    I WUV YOU JOYSWA!  :)
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Holy God.  So I just got home from work and I am exhausted!  Man.  I had 14 in my class today and even with another teacher they kicked my ass.  Running around all day long is truly tiring me out.  And part of me would like to say that is is worth it, but that could be a lie!  lol.  In actuality when the kids are being normal and not hitting/kicking/biting/screaming/running/pouting/scratching and just in general being asses I enjoy my job.  lol.  But it does make me think this on a daily basis... I need to go back to school for Psychology.  :) Anyways, so now I am home and we are trying to make sense of the mess that is our fish tank.  We used to have cool fish, but then we found out that they were super aggressive so we got rid of them and got "community fish" for the aquarium.  Guess what sucks?  Community Fish.  All they do is school.  At least with our other ones they were feisty.  :) Well I should be a good little woman and go help my man with the tank.  Or at least lay on the couch and pretend to help.  :) Later world!
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So let's make this quick...  I watching Big Brother last night.  Even got Josh to watch it with me, which was quite a feat in itself...   But anyways, first of all, i SO want to be on that show.  I really feel like I would rule!  And I think I could win.  Second, I hate the boys.  Sure, they might be hotties, but damn, they suck.  THey are so full of themselves!  it annoyed me. And secondly, alli and donnie got voted off the Amazing Race.  I won't lie.  I was sad to see my girl go...  thus is the life of Kellie: Reality Show Addict...
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Does anyone else remember that song?  I know I do.  They used to play on the last night of camp when i was a kid and everyone would cry.  It just sort of popped into my head... Of course it makes sense why.  I certainly have been missing my friends a hell of a lot lately.  I don't necessarily miss being in college, but i miss the atmosphere and the freedom that I felt back then.  Now everything is about money and bills and when we have to be where.  I miss the days of just drifting, not sure where we would end up, but happy to be traveling together.  I guess in a way I am still drifting. I mean, here I am, living in North Carolina, with my amazing boyfriend, working at a job that is not exactly overflowing my creative soul and having no idea what the next year will bring.  I know another move back home, while J is in the lovely warm and sandy beaches of Iraq, but other than that... no clue!  And now suddenly, that same part of me who cherished having no plans and no "for sures" is drowning in this see of uncertainty.  I find myself craving stability.  Craving consistency.  And yet, still wishing I could be around others who bring out my spontaneous nature that I have always embraced and cherished.  I find it so hard to wrap my brain around that we (my friends) are each of us in our own little world, completely removed from one another.  And we are all living these adult lives.  Everyone is working and making money to pay their bills.  We are all trying to survive in this world and the thing that feeds our souls the most is each other.  And sometimes isn't the soul more important than our water or electric bill?  I guess a soul running on empty doesn't seems as bad as a sweltering apartment in mid July! And things here in NC are great.  I love Josh more than I can express on here, but even still, I miss my friends and their companionship that they provide me.  I am thankful that I have someone in my life that is more than just a lover, but is always a friend and that makes all the difference.  He cheers me to no end, and I am sure I don't tell him enough. The ones I love are always on my mind and I think of them often.  My family I miss so much I can't even express it.  And my friends who have filled me with such wonderful memories, I have to archive them and recall them whenever times are rougher than I'd like.  And of course Joshua.  These are the things that make me smile. These are the things warm my soul... If I had a flower for every time I thought of you, I could walk forever in my garden.
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm sorry I can see you for who you truly are.  I see your truth and your soul.  And I don't like it.  I don't know how I ever did.  It frightens me that I can be such a horrible judge of character.  That I could have allowed someone to blind me with the words, with their "love" and with their lies.  Love cannot exist in such a dry and remote desert that is his heart.  love cannot touch him because he shuts it out.    Only when love is gone completely does he show any emotion.  Any feeling.  Any sign of life on that foreign planet that is him.
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1. IF YOU COULD BUILD A HOUSE ANYWHERE--WHERE WOULD IT BE? New Zealand. Or an island that I own. Johnny Depp just bought an island, so I figure I'll give him a call here pretty soon and maybe we can work something out. 2. WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE ARTICLE OF CLOTHING? i do love me some jeans. 3. FAVORITE PHYSICAL FEATURE OF OPPOSITE SEX? a completely symmetrical face. 4. WHAT'S THE LAST MOVIE THAT YOU SAW AT A THEATER? Spiderman 2 5. WHERE'S YOUR FAVORITE PLACE TO BE? I love Maine. I also love being home. 6. WHERE'S YOUR LEAST FAVORITE PLACE TO BE? waiting for the Metro late at night. 7. WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE PLACE TO BE MASSAGED? back, shoulders, and head 8. WHAT'S MOST IMPORTANT, STRONG IN MIND OR STRONG IN BODY? mind. 9. WHAT TIME DO YOU WAKE UP IN THE MORNING? around 7 10. WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE KITCHEN APPLIANCE? the dishwasher. god i love that machine. 11. WHAT MAKES YOU REALLY ANGRY? feeling like people aren't taking me seriously, or treat me like I am stupid.  And being insulted. 12. IF YOU COULD PLAY ANY INSTRUMENT WHAT WOULD IT BE? the guitar. 13. FAVORITE COLORS? Bright Pink 14. WHICH DO YOU PREFER, SPORTS CAR OR SUV? SUV 15. DO YOU BELIEVE IN AN AFTERLIFE? i believe in lots of things... afterlife, reincarnation, Christianity, Islam, ghosts... I'm a whole mess of beliefs! 16. FAVORITE CHILDREN'S BOOK? Where The Sidewalk Ends, Up the Down Staircase, The Giving Tree. 17. WHAT'S YOUR LEAST FAVORITE HOUSEHOLD CHORE? god what to choose... probably taking out the garbage. it goos me out. 18. IF YOU COULD HAVE ONE SUPERPOWER, WHAT WOULD IT BE? Invisibilty. 19. NAME ONE PERSON FROM YOUR PAST YOU WISH YOU COULD GO BACK AND TALK WITH? my dad 20. WHAT'S YOUR FAVORITE DAY? Fridays. I love em. Even though you have to work, they always go fast. Plus I go out every friday... lol. 21. WHAT'S IN THE TRUNK OF YOUR CAR? Katie Pfadt 22. SUSHI OR HAMBURGER? Sushi all the way. I love me some tuna. And by tuna I mean Katie. 23. FROM THE PEOPLE WHO SEE THIS, WHO IS MOST LIKELY TO RESPOND? I dont even know who reads this 24. WHO'S THE LEAST LIKELY? everyone who says "Kellie Harrison? who's that? what a ho." then ignores this. 25. IF YOU COULD PICK WHAT YOU DO FOR A LIVING, WHAT WOULD YOU DO? forensic pychologist for the FBI. not the be specific or anything. Or a famous movie star. 26. ARE YOU HAPPY? I am all kinds of happy. 27. WHAT COLOR UNDERWEAR ARE YOU WEARING? None right now... God I am a porn star.  I am just wearing my boyfriends pants. 28. DO YOU WANT A BABY? Not yet.  Someday though. 29.WHAT IS YOUR PETS NAME?  Spanky.  And Josh of course.  And the School.  30. IF YOU WERE A STRIPPER WHAT WOULD YOUR SONG BE? Criminal by Fiona Apple. 31. WHERE IS YOUR SIGNIFICANT OTHER RIGHT NOW?  Usually I could answer "right next to me" or "sitting in our apartment" but for the next 4 weeks I must say California.  stupid commander.... 32.  DO YOU WANT TO GET MARRIED? Of Course. 33.  WHEN DID YOU LAST CRY AND WHY? eh i cry all the time. lol But I think it was me being sad about Joshua leaving. 34.  PICK 4 WORDS THAT DESCRIBE YOURSELF.... Only 5? well here goes... I can try... Fun, Passionate, Funny, Cute, Smart- and humble. I know thats 6, but it needed to be said. 35. DO YOU BELIEVE IN GOD? Yes. 36.  WHAT IS YOUR MOST UNPLEASANT CHARACTERISTIC?   i can be hurtful when I am mad. I hate that. 37.  WHAT IS YOUR GREATEST FEAR?  "Oh the Fear I've known is that I will reap the praise of strangers and end up on my own."- that lyric describes it better than I ever could. 38,  WHAT FIRST ATTRACTED YOU TO YOUR GIRLFRIEND/BOYFRIEND?  well the fact that I was physically attracted helps.  other than that... how smart he is and how affectionate he is and how he makes me feel like I am the most beautiful woman alive.  And he has gorgeous eyes. 
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So Josh had to leave for Cali this morning.  Both of us are so annoyed by it, but there is not much we can do except suck it up and just hope the next few weeks go by real fast.  lol. So the apartment seems really empty without him here.  I know that we spend all of our time together (literally unless we are at work we are together) and so I am sure that I will lonely at times, but I plan on reading and catching up on movies he wouldn't want to see (case and point tonight i will be watching 13 going on 30)  lol.  And the weeks certainly do go by quickly usually so keep your fingers crossed all. I was hoping with the hurricanes and all that perhaps the weather would get bad fast so that he would not have to leave today, but then again that is just delaying the inevitable.  But still.  one more night would be nice to have.  man.  what am i gonna do when he leaves for Iraq?!  At least then I will have my family to hang out with and be with etc.  I miss them lots.  Wish I could just up and go home for this month with him gone, but it doesnt work that way when you have a job.  Oh well.  Thus is the life of an adult. I was just thinking yesterday when josh and I were driving around in the car how great we are together.  How we are each totally ourselves and never have to pretend or do all the bullshit that other couples do.  I love that.  I am not going to get all sappy, but sometimes I am just reminded how much i love him and how well we fit together.  :)  It's good to have that knowing feeling that things are a-okay and both people are satisfied. :) Also he left his car here and i love it.  I love driving in it.  Jeeps are just so fun.  Well, thats all for now.  It's dark like night here so I am hoping the storms start soon. more later  :) 
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      the five famous people that I am allowed to "have" and Josh can't get mad.  thank you Friends for the entertainment and Steph for posting hers...  here's mine...  1) Dean Cain 2) Joshua Jackson 3) Dave Matthews 4) Brad Pitt 5) Kiefer Sutherland  honorable mentions:  Jerod Leto, Collin Ferrel, Adam Pascall, and Drew from the Big Brother House. 
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm trying to tell you something about my life. maybe give me insight between black and white and the best thing you've ever done for me is to help me take my life less seriously darkness has a hunger that's insatiable and lightness has a call that's hard to hear I wrap my fear around me like a blanket I sailed my ship of safety till I sank it I'm crawling on your shores I went to the doctor, I went to the mountains I looked to the children, I drank from the fountains there's more than one answer to these questions pointing me in a crooked lin eand the less I seek my source for some definitive the closer I am to fine and I went to see the doctor of philosophy with a poster of Rasputin and a beard down to his knee he never did marry or see a b-grade movie he graded my performance, he said he could see through me I spent four years prostrate to the higher mind got my paper and I was free I went to the doctor, I went to the mountains I looked to the children, I drank from the fountains there's more than one answer to these questions pointing me in a crooked line the less I seek my source for some definitive the closer I am to fine the closer I am to fine I stopped by the bar at 3 a.m. to seek solace in a bottle or possibly a friend and I woke up with a headache like my head against a board twice as cloudy as I'd been the night before and I went in seeking clarity. I went to the doctor, I went to the mountains I looked to the children, I drank from the fountains yeah we go to the doctor, we go to the mountains we look to the children, we drink from the fountains yeah we go to the bible, we go through the workout we read up on revival and we stand up for the lookout there's more than one answer to these questions pointing me in a crooked line the less I seek my source for some definitive the closer I am to fine 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So this is going to be short because I have to go to work.  but I am shitty with the commander right now.  Josh comes home yesterday all shitty and says he might have to leave for 6 weeks to go do a training thing with some troops in California.  Which SUCKS.  But nothing was for sure.  and he was supposed to leave this weekend.  give people 4 days to get their fucking life in order?  WTF!  His commander is worthless. so josh goes in this morning to tell him he just doesnt think he can do it because of a million important reasons and his commander laughs and says "well, thats the army."  So he has to go and so we are MAJORLY stressing and needing to get shit together.  i am so shitty.  now i have to go hang out with 2 year olds.  this is an awesome day. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I LOVE MY BOYFRIEND MORE THAN ANYTHING.  JOSHUA DAVID CLARK YOU ARE TRULY THE LOVE OF MY LIFE. :)  It's in all caps because i mean it.... 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So I have been having major troubles getting a good nights sleep.  Not sure the cause of my delima, but it is starting to catch up with me and I am feeling EXHAUSTED in my daily routine.   Especially since I have a classfull of kiddos to keep me up to speed all day and I need my precious energy.  And I am coming down with a cold or something, but it is driving me crazy. Other than that though life is good.  I have Josh's ball on friday night and then saturday Tami invited me to go to a football game, but I dont think that is going to happen.  Beth and I might go shopping and then out on Saturday.  That would be fun.  We are getting anxious for JOsh and Michael to meet.  I really hope they get along as well as Beth and I do.  It would be nice.  :) Well tonight I took some Niquill.  Hopefully that will help with the sleeping,  Also all wrapped up in my favorite blanket and drinking some Sleepytime tea.  Hope all of this adds up to a good and restful slumber. Wish me luck..... 
      
</post>


<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I didn't get the apt.&nbsp; So, I am moving in with friends for $200 cheaper a month.&nbsp; It is an amazing apt. but it is more north than I wanted to go..but I need to learn new neighborhoods anyways.&nbsp; I get my own bathroom, and a free parking spot- amazing now all I need is a car.  I had a bad day yesterday.&nbsp; Everything was just not going right.&nbsp; Funny though that now my bad days really aren't that bad. I love that story.&nbsp; My power went out three times in the morning while&nbsp;I was getting ready.&nbsp; Apparently I can' iron, toast bread, listen to the radio and have my air conditioner on at the same time. News to me.&nbsp; Work was just long and I was all but smacking myself to stay awake, even though I had plenty of work to do.&nbsp; Then I get on an un-airconditioned bus with a first time driver so that added 40 mins to my normal 15 min commute!!!&nbsp; So I had barely any time to change and eat before I had to go to class...and of course the el was 30 mins late and I was 15 mins late to class...but my teacher was like it is ok cause you have a nerd shirt on...??? aparently I was wearing a star wars shirt....I just liked the word on it and got it at a thrift store three years ago.&nbsp; Well, I was doning tribute to a trilogy of movies that I have never seen. Gotta love that.  Class was great though...god I love improv, it makes me happier than I have ever been when I finish with class.&nbsp; I want to marry it.  I am paitently waiting for that call...but paitently hoping it doesn't come because if I don't get involved I can stay in this zen state of hapiness I am in.&nbsp; But if I don't get involved I may miss a chance at something bigger...why do I think so much?  oh there is a sale on burgers at mcdonalds today......my FAVORITE kind of sale  

						
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So I didn't sleep at all last night because I had so many disturbing dreams.&nbsp; First one I didn't even get a chance to get the apt. that I love.&nbsp; They kept saying "no" without doing the credit check and I became homeless.&nbsp; Second, my ex-boyfriend was dating this really small girl and they were so in love and rubbing it in my face.&nbsp; Third, I got kicked out of the Second City Conservatory because I wasn't up to par.&nbsp; All of these dreams going on intermittingly with eachother and me tossing and turning all night.&nbsp; Oh well, they aren't true (well I know two of them aren't) but they put me in a sad frantic mood which combined with monday is not good. &nbsp; My class yesterday was frustrating.&nbsp; We were working on political and social issues going on in Chicago and the world and using our voice to make a statement and how to incorporate that into improv.&nbsp; We were all really frustrated because we weren't getting it and our teacher wasn't communicating what he wanted either.&nbsp; For example, three guys did a scene they thought dealt with the Scott Peterson trial by being three guys that idolized him....WHAT???&nbsp;&nbsp; I have a problem with that being the voice they chose to&nbsp; speak with and the issue that they focused on...but I have to remember it is class and we are learning with each other. &nbsp; I realized this morning on my way to work the major difference between our generation and our parents is our neccesity for music.&nbsp; As I walk amongst corporate America I notice all younger people in the workforce are wearing headphones.&nbsp; We all wear dresses, skirts, suits and ties-but every 20-something has headphones on their commute.&nbsp; I wonder if this will change as we get older or if this is how we are forever....like when we are 90 with our walkers and ipods. &nbsp; hmmm....  

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My show is done and I am spent...what a long, wonderful week.&nbsp; The show was great and the response was great and I love to perform...I am such a whore.&nbsp; After our last show friday night we all went out to my new favorite bar four moons and drank like it was going out of style.&nbsp; We had one tab for like 20 people and we just kept ordering shots and drinks.&nbsp; My artisitic director paid for it but&nbsp; I was determined to write her a check I don't know why and I can only imagine what that check looks like! &nbsp; Sat. I looked at apts.and I found my dream apt.&nbsp; it is totally in my budget and 2 bedrooms in an awesome area...so I can totally live by myself still but if people need to stay for an extended period of time they can! Problem is I don't know if I will get it because a bunch of other people also want it.....keep your fingers crossed. &nbsp; Last night I hung out with two great friends I have known since 7th and 5th grade respectively...both twins and both now married...odd I just realized that!&nbsp; We had a great time and there is something so awesome about reconnecting with people you have known a majority or your life.....It was a good night. &nbsp; I realized friday night as the girls I was with all went to college together, how they were sharing funny drunken moments together...I was jealous because I wanted my college friends to be there to reminsce about our memories...but then I realized I was making new memories.......I have been so busy missing people that used to be constantly in my life that I don't take the time to appreciate those in my life now. &nbsp; 5 days until my much needed vacation!!!  

						
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   SO here I am!  I am pretty sure no one is reading this and that is  kid of the way I like it...I have an office job and I find my time passing by with amazing deep thoughts and no place to put them so here we go.  I realized just now as I brought two executives their water, that as far as  I wanted to get from the restaurant industry I am still a  waitress...difference is here they say thank you and I get insurance...  My opening night is tonight.  I am too worn out to be excited, but hopefully I will pick up later after a few lines of coke.  I am getting too old to dance..everyday I wake up and groan like an 80 year old and saunter out of bed..but I can still do the splits so I guess I am not that old..or maybe I am just a limber oldie..or maybe I am an over-dramatic 23 year old...or maybe I am a giant ball of hotness wrapped in a jogging suit of old.  see what I mean about deep thoughts... 

						
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am so tired and have a blinding headache and my mind keeps going in and out of spanish.  I hope I am not getting sick.  I went to bed at 9:30 last night which has to be a new record but I am still sitting here trying to keep my eyes open.ahghggg...and I have class tonight.  I wish I liked caffeine.  In other news I registered to vote here today which needed to be done since it was hanging over my head.  I normally try to stay out of political issues but this year I can't help but feel the need to get involved.  I don't hate Bush, I don't know him...but I need to do my part to get him out of office.  Lo siento.  

						
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So I have always known that I am extremely blessed in the parent department, and this weekend reaffirmed that.  Not only did my parents drive 6 hours to help me move, they did it in less than a 24 hour time span and helped make my new digs...amazing!! And when all  was said and done they told me how much they loved me and how proud they are...I was like I just had you do hard labor for 24 hrs and now you have to drive back 6 hours after you worked like dogs and you still love me? I can only hope that I can be as amazing to my children some day as they are to me.  By the way I am pregnant. So I was so dog tired last night, but I made plans for Sunday night because I was moving all weekend.  I didn't really want to go because I wasn't in the mood, but I am glad I did....things may be looking up in a certain area.. I love love love my new apt.  It is so big, and by big I mean big for a city apt.  I was in my bedroom and I was talking to my mom and she couldn't hear me because she was in the kitchen!!! That is huge! I am also obsessed with the olympics.  I love every sport and I am so excited for tonight.  I think I was supposed to be an olympian but I liked showtunes too much to concentrate.  There are women competing for Afghanistan for the first time ever and it is 2004.  This made me realize, once again, how fortunate I am to be a woman in America.  We still have a long road ahead but I cannot forget the rights I take for granted everyday. I was asked to do a sketch show in Nov. and Dec. if they get the slot at Donny's Skybox at Second City.  I am so stoked I hope they get the slot I would probably pee my pants...or at least do a little jig. So last night before I crashed I watched 13 going on 30 and although the movie was weak and fluffy I really enjoyed Jennifer Garner, she is quite charming.  Saw Mystic River the other night (finally)....brilliant on so many levels. Well, I think I have wasted enough time at work. By the by I am really not pregnant just naseous....who knew.  

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I want to be doing a job I love I want my friends and family to live here I want to perform in front of thousands I want to eat everything I want I want to love working out I want to be able to do what is right...always I want the battle between my heart and conscious to stop I want the burnt bridges rebuilt I want a pony I want a boyfriend who doesn't speak english so we can't miscommunicate I want someone to rub my back every night and tell me I couldn't be more awesome if I tried I want to stop this train and get off....but just for a weekend, I'll get back on. Is this asking too much?  I am so bored I could die!  This is torture..absolute torture who knew I could waste so much of a day!  God, if I wasn't doing stuff I loved on the side I might have to become a ...I don't know what a .....donkey?? is that possible? they don't do office jobs right? yeah a donkey, if i didn't have the arts I would have to become a donkey....am i going crazy?  this i can say with absolute certainty....  YES!!!!    

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So after me going back and forth and back and forth about whether to move in with friends, I have decided, at the last minute of course, that I shall find my own place. I just can't give up living alone, once you go solo you will never want to go back. So i found the cutest place twice the size of mine with a view! So, I am going today after work to finalize and then moving in next weekend. You know when you know you are moving the place you are in just sucks even more? Well that is the case here. My apt. sucks balls, and it has bugs all the sudden!! I need out!  So needless to say I will be packing this weekend. I am supposed to go to an African party with a friend of mine who spent time in africa for the peace corps. I think I am going to back out since this week has been crazy and I need to get packing. Plus I think he will want to make out and I don't know how I am going to handle that yet without losing his friendship...why can't boys just be friends sometimes?  I got an email from another friend who said "playing hard to get already? real nice." Ummmm.. anyone who knows me can attest to the fact that I don't call people but it kind of irritated me. Like, dude you don't know me and don't assume that I am sitting around thinking of ways to make you covet me. Once again, is there a decent guy in chicago cause I am losing hope. I have not heard from the ex and it only proves that guys can't be friends afterwards. I am three for the last three. I know it is half my fault but it sucks when someone is so important to you and then non-exsistent. It has happened my last three relationships and I think that is why I am just not in the mood to give it another go. AND to top it off I have no good gays here. Improv is all alpha males and no fun loving guys who love the penis. I need me some loving from a man who has no desire to get laid.(by me that is ) Oh I miss you my homo friends of my past.  In the onion it had an article that George W. Bush is being asked to stop his blog for security reasons. It was hilarious. Imagine, and he would be just the prez to do it.  So now I lay to rest my rant.    

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So my vacation was absolutely wonderful!! How much fun did my family and I have?  SoOoooo much!  Today is horrible though....I am done with this job.  I need to find something else.  Why do I become so impatient...maybe because none of them have been what  I really want to do. ahhh well...I am so close and something big is brewing I can feel it.  Is that weird?  I am now getting nervous about the apt. thing.  I love living by myself and I really don't want to give that up.  Plus the new apt. will be really far north and not that close to transportation.  But I don't want to disappoint.  Maybe I should just move to Ireland so I can meet my husband already and raise sheep.  Is it odd that I am serious?  I went to the grocery store yesterday...I love coming home to a full fridge.  I am doing good on the diet.  Big deal since it has been two days but still kudos to me!!! hehehe  I feel like there is so much more on my mind but I can't place the words correctly.  That is why I feel like something is a brewing.  I got nervous this morning to come to work this morning for the first time since I started working at the Sears Tower.  I think the upped terror warning has gotten in my head.  There is nothing we can really do though and I refuse to live in fear because that is what they want.  Instead I choose to live well.  Miss you kell if you read this ...but I might not get over that pic of jeff and I!! could my face be any fatter?    

						
</post>


</Blog>