<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      actually, no. im busy pretending i am busy, when i really should&nbsp;be busy, actually.   i wish i could be as prolific as my friend joelle. she has blocks and blocks of text on her blogspot.   right now, i really should&nbsp;continue working on this 68.8M-peso marketing plan. ang hirap mag-drowing.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i've downloaded picasa hello,&nbsp;but all "bloggerbot" is giving me is the http 425 error page. jeez,&nbsp; i'm supposed to be tech-ier than this. :S   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i was going to write about something that irked me&nbsp; yesterday on friendster, and i wanted to quote it as it was written by this geek who still, apparently, likes to display his bitterness about me online. knowing very well that i am on his friendster&nbsp; list too,&nbsp;among&nbsp;80 or so common friends&nbsp;of ours who sort of know the story.&nbsp;that catholic boy is just so full of web-based&nbsp;malice that doesn't suit him.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;  my parents were high, therefore i am. i mean,&nbsp; they were&nbsp;both really stoned out of their minds when they conceived me. they weren't&nbsp;really lovers. i'm sure they weren't even friends. it was just that my mother, one time during&nbsp;her years&nbsp;of&nbsp;delayed rebelliousness, happened to tag along with a group of drug users to&nbsp;some place in Nueva Ecija.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;   she never fell in love with the guy, ever. and for good reason: there was nothing attractive about him. considering this, i&nbsp;am extremely&nbsp;lucky to have my mug after all. sometimes, just for the fun of it, i try to convince myself that someone else must have gotten my mother pregnant before that fateful night when she&nbsp;got stoned out of her mind. i go&nbsp;thinking: maybe my mother got raped before that...by a chinoy who kinda looked like me...and who happens to be filthy rich now. then i begin to imagine when and how i am supposed to claim my inheritance. these are the stuff of my more positive musings.     &nbsp;   anyway, the lesson here is not that drugs are bad. it's just that getting married, just because you got knocked up is&nbsp;oftentimes not a good idea (yes, they were that medieval back in 1978). i still hold this as &nbsp;the wisest thing i have ever been taught. &nbsp;     
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       due to the lack of interesting occurrences in my own life, let's  just go pop culture today, ok?  sheryl cruz is back. so i heard from a couple of other people. i didn't even get to see her on tv. and why is this a big deal? it's not.  but you gotta admit--that girl (i suppose we can rightly call her a woman now) is a fucking ICON.  i mean, sinong pinoy ang hindi kilala si SHERYL CRUZ and her signature pa-cute wave to her fans? who doesn't know by heart the lyrics or at least the refrain to such classics as "mr. dream boy" and "sabi ko na nga ba?"  so let's play a little game, shall we?   ililibre ko ng dessert (kahit anong resto) ang magpo-post ng sheryl cruz lyrics dito!* wee-hoo! the more the many-er! wee-hoo! oi, seryosong contest 'to!   *Per DTI Permit No. 070709, Series of 2004.       
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it  just occurred to me now that it's been a while since i last used a floppy disk. it's just that the pc i'm using today has faulty network connection, and i had to use one to transfer a file i needed. while doing the transfer, i realized that the floppy disk is such an icky storage device.  di ba para shang call-boy? so prone to viruses and virtual std, hehe. yuck. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pagbigyan niyo na 'to. Last song na nag-stick sa utak ko before I fell asleep. Partially dedicated to my friend A, who's a writer for a soap with the same title:        Di ba... ako'y tao lang na nadadarang at natutukso rin....   Maiaalis mo ba sa 'kin na matutunan kang mahalin   sa bawat sandaling... hiram natin?      tuloy, mejo soap din tuloy yung story line ng panaginip ko kagabi. about that married guy i mentioned in a previous entry. let us call his character "local papa," kasi he's within my local intranet, hehe.  ang drama sa panaginip ko: nagka-amnesia daw ako (hu-waaat!!!) at sakto naman na deadringer pala ako ng wife ni local papa who just died in an accident na hindi pa nababalitaan ng asawa niya. since may amnesia nga ako, yun daw yung identity na binigay sa kin nung common na kakilala namin (who was my relative in the dream--let us call him "gabby") and, in short, ginawa akong subsitute (o-ha). at feel ko naman daw ang role (shempre! sabi nga ng officemate ko, na-translate sa dream ang desire!) until mambabae ang local papa during our house party. ang chuva kasi, may konting "ilang" between us since i was feeling weird because i had amnesia nga and i didn't really remember him, though i was content in the role-playing. nung nagkaasaran nga lang because of this other woman, inamin na daw sa kin ni uncle gabby ang totoo.  sa galit ko about the whole thing, sinugod ko daw si local papa during the party at pinangsampal ko daw sa kanya yung nanguya ko nang chewing gum (a bit of slapstick here, haha). at ang pamatay na linya ko:   Ako si _________. Hindi mo ko asawa!!!  (delivered with very strong feelings)  and the dream ended there. bongga!  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       feeling ko lang appropriate sha i-post ngayon:     TEKSTO   Salaysay ng kasaysayan ang ating katawan:  laman nito ang bawat pagsilang at kamatayan,  bawat hiyaw ng pagsuko't kalayaan,  bawat latay ng pagkagapos at paghulagpos.    (Ngunit paano ipauunawa  ang pangungusap ng alindog na pinipi?  Paano ipababasa ang mga ala-alang  pilit na pinalabo ng sebo de macho?)    Sapagkat usapin pa rin ng pananakop   at pang-aari ang bawat pagsiping,  markang ililimbag ang bawat pagdantay  sa diskurso ng pakikipagtunggali.    At ikaw--isa lamang pangalan--  dagdag na bilang sa talaan  ng mga nabihag, nakitil at nasalanta  ng patuloy kong pakikidigma.   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       for days now, i've been preparing to write an entry titled "no sex and the fucking city." basically, just a lament on what it's like to be SINGLE and commuting home in the sad, sad rain from an office job in Makati, while the rest of your officemates are on their way to their usual Friday night gimmicks with their dates. While some of these people are not completely happy about their love lives, i still think they're better off than moi, standing on the wet sidewalk of Buendia, un-glamorously unable to get any form of transportation during the rush hour. At least sila may mga sundo.  it sucks having to stand alone in the rain like an old and tired secretary; this city ain't fuckin' new york.  well, last monday, i told my officemates about my pathetic case and thankfully they were very eager to do something about it. So we went out last night, a Wednesday (ladies night), to (dammit) a coyote bar that wasn't at all happening. And all that we found there were cheap women and sleazy men, which is all you can really expect from such a place.  but the night wasn't totally unproductive because they managed to get me a male starlet who said he was there alone "just to drink." at dahil nalolongkot sha at walang makaosap, we picked him up.  so here's something Samantha Jones would have done: I SLEPT WITH THE GUY!   or should i say,   THE VIVA HOT MAN  .     
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        to all the men i could have loved, but who've already been taken even before i got to them...   PANANDALI  Hindi ko man maaaring   yakapin ang iyong kabuuan,  madadaan naman kita   sa kalabit,  sa kiliti,  sa mga panakaw   na sundot ng landi.  Daliri ako ng oras na magwawaglit  ng panahong di niya kayang punan.  Kaya't hayaan mong ako na lang  ang panaglit  na muli't muling lilipas   at muli't muling babalik.  Ako ang patlang, ang pagitan  na di mo nanaising laktawan.  Ang malayang buntong-hininga  ng minsan.  Itatakas kita   mula sa sumpa ng habambuhay,   tungo sa sandaling tutuldok  sa tagal ng paghihintay.    * I wrote this poem during that time I had a fling with the Chen Chang look-alike (Chen Chang is "Dark Cloud" in Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon), kasi he had a girlfriend pala back in Switzerland pero pumayag ako maging "Panandali." A poet friend wanted to re-title this to "Panandaliri." Hehe, pwede din, if you read it another way. Tipong, kung one-way ang action.  Why post this now, after almost 3 years since I wrote it? Because...  i CRUSH this married guy in my new office, and i am so tempted to tempt him. mwahaha.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>