<Blog>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Paul Moss  Who is he?  As A&amp;R Director of ground-breaking record company Positive Tone from it’s inception in 1994 until 2003, Paul oversaw the transformation in Malaysian music that created whole new markets for English language artists and new genres of music. Being responsible for artist signing, artistic direction, recording, production and content development he is justifiably proud of the success of OAG, Too Phat, Innuendo, Poetic Ammo, Ferhad and many others in the Positive Tone family.  Paul is also a multi-award winning Producer/Writer/Arranger. Producing a string of Gold and Platinum releases and AIM (‘Malaysian-Grammy’) winners from OAG, Innuendo, Juliet the Orange and working with everyone from Too Phat to Ella to Nice Stupid Playground. Paul also oversaw the Malaysian production for Taiwanese superstar Elva Hsiao’s phenomenally successful first two albums and added credits with Chinese legend Fei Xiang.  Before settling in Malaysia, Paul was Songwriter and Musical Director for International Pop group 'The Fan Club' (Sony Music NZ 1986-1991) with several Gold albums to its credit and winner of International Artist of the Year at the 1991 NZ Music Awards. , Paul’s pedigree and credibility are unimpeachable. He’s a straight talker who calls a flat note “flat”, not “bluesy”. Ignore his advice at your peril.   Roslan Aziz  Who is he?  A multi-award winning producer-composer, Roslan Aziz is the man behind the unrivaled acts such as Sheila Majid and Zainal Abidin, Amir Yusoff, Prema, Zubir Ali, the recent singing debutante, Atilia and ALI; a duo comprising Roslan Aziz and Mukhlis Nor. Co-founder of the renowned Roslan Aziz Production label (R.A.P), the first local recording label to generate interest from abroad, R.A.P. took the local music industry one step further by not only stirring up the regional music scene, but also the entertainment arenas in Indonesia, Japan, Europe and South America. Although R.A.P. only produced 15 albums in 15 years, they were all booming successes. Commanding quality over quantity in every production, the music house managed to gain favourable recognition and veneration nationwide and beyond, for their uniquely eclectic sounds, tuned to perfection.  Among the numerous awards garnered by Roslan were Best Album award for the album Gamal from AIM in 1995, Best Album award for the album Emosi at BASF Awards, Indonesia in 1987 and in 2002 winning the Most Promising Producer at the Music Producers Awards in the United States. Roslan added,” Malaysian Idol is like an Olympics for young aspiring artists to compete at the world stage and I’m honoured to be chosen as one of the judges for Malaysian Idol.”  Fauziah Latiff  Who is she?  The sweet yet determined Fauziah Latiff, better known as Jee to her adoring fans, first embarked on her singing career quite by chance when she appeared for the first time at a charity concert at Stadium Merdeka in 1987. Her talent did not go unnoticed for Fauziah was “spotted” by recording company Happy Records, and much to her delight, was subsequently offered an audition and later, a recording contract.  Her first single shot to great heights in the local music charts and the song soon was hummed, sung and enjoyed by the young and old alike. The single, Di Gamit Memori, was responsible for bringing the teenager Fauziah into TV shows and stardom.  It was also during that time (1988) that Fauziah was given the honour to represent Malaysia in the 6th Asia Pop Song festival held in the Philippines. The success of this festival was followed by the release of Fauziah’s second album. This time, the slim beauty was paired with composer Manan Ngah. With the release of Kau Merubah Segalanya in 1989, Fauziah Latiff became a household name.  Her presentation in the Kingsway Entertainer’s Fiesta, which saw her crowned as overall winner, also secured Fauziah’s name and reputation as a true entertainer. Success upon success followed and by 1995, Fauziah has represented the country in various song and music festivals such as the Asean Music Festival in Fukuoka, the Asean Music Syndrome in Kyoto, the Asian Pop Queen Festival and the Asian Big Adventure in Osaka, Japan.  By the following year, PAPITA chose Fauziah to represent Malaysia in the Asian Song Festival in Bali, Indonesia. With 15 albums under her belt and numerous awards won throughout her illustrious career, Jee is a bona-fide pop songstress who has been through it all. 
      
</post>


</Blog>