<Blog>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      24 hours a day...for somebody it seem like so short....dont have enough time to sleep, to work, to eat, to watch TV....etc..... whatever....that kind is people which their lives a re fll with so many items in their time schedule. well for the other side...24 hours a day might be so long long day. I guess some of you might happen to watch this American TV series called "24" it's really showed me how much things can really happen in a day. hahaha so cool.. Well.so many reason for this group of people. Some might so lazy don't know what to do in a day. That's why they feel like the day is so long. Somebody might say it so long becuz' I waiting for someone to come back! that's ong for sure....the moment of waiting and long for someone or something... :( well.....all of this thought can come through our mind anytime.....but one true fact that never change is one day still got 24 hours. How we gonna spend it....up 2 U! Time run fast actually see...end of the month again....Let's spend your time fruitfully so that u will never look back and regret...why I never do this..why I never do that...but if u did a mistake today....ya it's too late to correct it...but there is another day that u can live on.....make tomorrow be a better day. Don't give up as long as your breath still not run dry... ;) 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      tODAY...i went to attend one of my friend's wedding.. It's actually quite weird...that this month itself I had 2 weddings to attend. Luv is in the air hahaha....When is my turn?? Still no answer for that...oh no no no.that's not the point. My point is this...every timewhen I attending the wedding ceremony (So far they are all Christian wedding) I can see how God brought 2 different person come to the point of unite 2 become 1. It's such amazing, isn't it? Indeed God is so cool!! Well...I'm glad for my friend that he really blessed by good and passionate wife. Bless ya brother...!!! :) It's reminding me that as we walking in the Lord. Serving Him and walk this journey with Him..sometimes it's gonna be tough, diffcult, etc... but He Himself will be with us...for SURE! And even more than that He will bring someone come along side and walk together with us...It's might be friends, family or even wife/husband!! Well it's really show me that indeed God make marriage to be triangular relationship. God is in between man and woman. I luv the wedding ring That my friend actually designed it himself.It's triangular shape. That's represent himself, his wife and God. They will never seperate from each other...Amen!!! I couldn't wait for my turn honestly... Hhhhhh... :( 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well....Finally I have to write down some of my thought somewhere in cyber space....if not I can't contain God's blessing in my life.....We are blessed to bless, isn't it? Well here it is....It's My Life!! Hopefully that whatever I posted here will encourage all of you guys to walk faithfully in the Lord and be radical for Him..!!!! Alrite.. :p enjoy reading and let's make your own story ok??    
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      this morning I woke up very early to just go out with my dear roommate. Guess what we do in the morning??? Play tennis!!! WoW.....nuts!!!!right? Ya...but it's really great thin i never do here before since i came to Singapore. I once loved tennis....even til now I still love tennis. It's something that come into my life when i was abt 11 years old. So when this morning I went to play, it's really recall the memory when i play tennis seriously as a junior tennis player @ under 12 level.... My best honor in my tennis career (haha) was runner-up of new face junior player under 12 yrs old of Northern region of Thailand. isn't that awesome?? Ya it is...its was one of my good old day that I still remember it. At that time Jimmy Corner was my favourite player. My dad graciously support me to learn tennis and bought a racket. (very expensive at that time for 11 yrs old boy) My coach whom he was an ex-Thailand national representative, he trained me, sent me for competitions. I have no idea whether my future will become pro player or not..?? but ya finally u all know I couldn't make it...U ask me why? I dun know really...I was quit when I enter Sec. school...to busy at school, get caught with new challege Basketball. (I played until become a school representative too) I love sports!!!...I play basketball for school team since sec. school until i moved to another vocational school, i still play for new school...the turning point is here..when I converted....I was a captain of the school team....I suppose to made a decision whether I will continue to play for school or quit becuz' no time to practice..I have to go church!!! I need more time serving in church...also it's last year of my school. I have to think ahead where am i heading neXt?? So it's really hard to laid down everything and say "I'm quit" all my teammate asked "Are u crazy??Why u quit?" Only answer came out from my mouth..."God told me to quit" They all laughed at me.....I really meant that...God told me not to play for school anymore....he has a better things lies ahead for me...I made that decision......I learned to obey God since that....til now....as I obey in what He tell me to do....I never regret...at ALL...So this morning it's just a time that i can flash back to my good old days....and say that "God! all past years that has been through, i have seen U directed my path indeed....Your plan is always the best for me.....Thank You Lord!"    "For I know the plans I have for you," declares the LORD , "plans to prosper you and not to harm you, plans to give you hope and a future. Then you will call upon me and come and pray to me, and I will listen to you. You will seek me and find me when you seek me with all your heart." -Jeremiah 29:11-13 NIV   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    My God given IBM Thinkpad R51&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Blessing of the Lord sometimes so funny....or may be should call it exciting Ya...that's the right word. I am suppose to leave for China in few days.....and I need some money to  top up my budget for the trip....As myself and others pray.....God release the money...The overflowing of God's blessing.....of course blessed to bless! The funny thing is....God always make me excited when I'm waiting for Him to save me in each time that I really need Him. being a full timer rely on God's provisions daily doesn't easy. But one thing I know....I'm still survive! til this day....That's must be a miracle! This is how He being Jehovah-Jireh, God is the provider. He really is...mannn... if i'm about to tell u abt my story after story how God provide for me. It's going to be 3 days 3 nights never finish yet...I tell you. So what is my point?? ok! The conclusion is this...that as we trust in the Lord, He will rain down the drop of blessing upon you! (like heavy rain) Now in Singapore raining is very usual thing here...so hopefully one day when u walk in the rain (esp..heavy rain and can't find shelter) you will remember God's blessings on me are just like rain. PlanetShakers Band sing "Rain down on me Rain down on Me....." I Amen for that!! how about u..?? 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Recently I just recieved very very bad news about one of my friend. He just passed away. I have no idea how all this thing happen. He's a very great guy. Though our freindship is really short time but it's something more than just a time frame that we spent together that bonded us. He's Indian national. First time I met him, he was an ex-drug addict, hopeless soul who try to find the Father's first love. Somehow he came over to Singapore to do DTS again and it happened to be in the school that I'm staffing. Through period of 5 months...isn't that long??? I saw God really do something new in his life. until the graduation day i just realize.....he's totally different from the first moment I picked him up @ the airport. His face is so bright shining with the Father's glory. He look so great and richly in physical, emotional and spiritual. Since I sent him off back to his home....I only heard from him once that he enjoy his new life back home and going for full time ministry.....but somehow......things just change....        i have no word...when i recieved the news about his departure. no tears come out from my eyes...i don't know why? One thing i feel is that....somehow I will meet him again..That's hope I have for now. Sleep in peace bro...til we see each other once again.... 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink      It's my Life!!!!!    urlLink     hehehe...I just try to post some photo on my blog...!! and it's work!! cool!!!! 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>