<Blog>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Hello ok a bit about me.   Im 16 (nearly 17), i go to college and im studying Law, Psychology and English language.    Lets talk about some of my fiends then. If i miss anyone out the im sorry! I will  'go round the group'   ;o)   Jon    ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh Jon he is the most amazing person ever to grace the earth!!! So insecure though even though everyone loves him to bits. And oh my god he makes me laugh, ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME.    Miquel   , the bestest best friend anyone could ever wish for. Has been there for me through everything, so has    Joe    his twin brother who gives me advice that i dont take even though i should do.    Jacqui   , my big breasted buddy. Dont know where i would be without her. Shes my rock&nbsp;and ive known her longest out of all of them.    Becca    dont know about that one. I really like her, she is ver special to me. But im afraid i may have screwed things up completely with her. Me been an arse and messing everything up like always.     Them lot are my closest friends. Ive got loads more, Amy, Ami, Emily, firends from my old school. But i find it hard to trust other people. So i keep within a small circle of friends.    &nbsp;  I have got a FANTATSIC family. Im a daddy's girl, and ive got a fantastic relationship with him, my mother is jst hilarious and the most caring and wndeful woman in the world. Two sisters, Trish (27 pregnant, married to Steve) and Carol (30, married to Dom), who are always there for me and spoil me rotten! Ive got my Grand dad (83 and as mad as a hatter) Grandma, and 6 uncles and 3 aunts and 13 cuzins!!!    &nbsp;  Trisha is been naughty at the moment. Baby is 5days over due. We dont know what sex baby is yet, but i like suprises!!!    &nbsp;  Up until recently i had the most amazing boyfriend in the world. Robert.&nbsp;He was kind, caring, loving and always there for me. Recently i found out that he had cheated on me after we had been going out 2months. It didnt last long, but he lied to me about it till 14months later. I can forgive him for what he did. But can i forgive him for lying???    &nbsp;  Thats the basics on me. More about Robert, updates on the baby and on the relationships i need to salvage later! x-x-x  &nbsp; 
      
</post>


</Blog>