<Blog>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


     

          Yes the main issue today is being single. No hunny bunny's, no loves, no chocolates on V-day...the list goes on. Suddenly everybody wants to belong to someone. I don't know why. I'm single. I have crushes. But I think I'm not longing for a boyfriend...not right now. What do you think is the scientific explanation for this??? Hmmm...I think I know. We all want someone to say "Hey, you look beautiful today!" besides our dear mom. Haha. No offense but maybe it's true don't you think?! Everytime I read a sweet quote, be it from the 'Net, magazines or someone sends it to me on my phone, somehow my  kilig -nerves wake up and flash that red light. Haha.  Kilig  feelings. I like kilig feelings. Only, I don't know to whom I should get kilig. Hehehe. Weird, huh?! But anyway, back to the "single-and-looking" issue...in my opinion, yeah it's great to have someone to hold hands with,  HHWWPSSP (Holding Hands While Walking Pa-Swing-Swing Pa)  but hey! Enjoy life when you're still alone...on your own. Get kilig over your crush, admire that cute guy from afar...savor it because maybe when your Prince Charming comes, you're gonna miss the freedom the "single-life" brings. Hahahaha. Fun discussion. Heeeheee. I honestly enjoyed it...although I'm not an expert or anything...    BEFORE SHE GOES, THE QUEEN OF TALK WOULD LIKE TO SAY:   Being single is fun so I'm just gonna enjoy it. Anyway, patience is a virtue. Let's just all enjoy being a princess and someday, our prince will come...just make sure he's not your best friend's prince too. :)  Adios! Comment, okay?!      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


     

      i may appear so baby-ish in my blog or really even in person. but i tell you, beneath this face is a very, very wild girl with a say on everything she can lay her eyes on.  What's this blog about anyway? This is my small space to express unimportant issues that bugs me in this freakin' life.  Why make a new blog? Well I dont want to bother writing it down in  urlLink my personal blog  because sometimes my opinions just can't stop flowing and it may take up all the space that I allot for stories about the day. Haha. I hope you got that.  So there. Issues, stuff, stories, movies, weird topics...name it, and I would be glad to share my thoughts about it. Comment, okay??? That's what keeps me alive. Haha. 

     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


     

       urlLink Haloscan  commenting and trackback have been added to this blog.

     

    
</post>


<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

             TODAY I    still    FEEL:   bored...but with a little bit of yearning for rain!!! haha...      &nbsp;  it's me again. uuuuhh. why can't i do something?! all i do is watch, eat, blog, watch, eat, blog! haha i'm sick of this...i'm really bored. and to think that i still have  36+ hours  before I can go to school again!!! aaaaahh.  DAYMN.   hate it.  uuuuuhh. This blog is really helpful. Something I can spend my whole boring day with (aside from Friendster). Okay, what am I saying?! I'm outta my mind.    &nbsp;   DIVISORIA.  My mom, titas and lola went to Divisoria today. They bought me DVDs: 13 Going on 30, Ella Enchanted and Along Came Polly. I think I'm going to watch  13 Going on 30  right after blogging. I read somewhere (in the 'Net) that it's a really cool story. I've actually visited the movie's site but I didn't get to play around that long. So that's it. And speaking of Divisoria, I heard (and saw) a video in MTV of a song named DV -- short for Divisoria. Harhar. This country is full of  bargain-hunting-ukay2-lover-shoppaholics.  They even incade the music scene.    &nbsp;   ITSUMO.  Aaaaaaahh!!! That song is driving me nuts!!!  Itsumo kokoro.... please stop it. It's&nbsp;whirling in my head...aaaaahh!!! I can't even understand the chorus part. But my friends say that it's  bastos  daw...something to do with girls or whatever.  Blaaah.  Whatever that freaky song means, it's the tune I'm after. Anyway, even though I don't even know what that song is about (or at least just that chorus part, like what I said) it's okay. Remember the F4 days?! *yuck*Just the same...if you're getting me.     &nbsp;  Okay so what else can we talk about??? Okay maybe just some  UNIMPORTANT  stuff that you  DON'T  need to know, but I'm gonna let you know anyway:    &nbsp;  1.)  Spiderman  is my hero!!!    2.)  Tobey Maguire  is my future husband!!!   3.) I know the title of the  6th Harry Potter book!  (Harry Potter and the Half-blooded Prince...I'm not so sure. Camille just told me...)    4.) I miss school and the things that come with it (yup...the   I-miss-school-syndrome   is still circulating around my system. It does everytime weekends come...)   5.) I haven't memorized a single stanza from the Sabayan piece -- yet. (Oh, I'm so busted!)    &nbsp;  But hey...for the 5th one, I'm gonna do it right after my mind unclogs&nbsp;the boredom it houses right this very minute. I'm still touched by the verse   "To the world, you may be one person. but to one person, you may be the world..."   I forgot where I came across that. I think somewhere in this web...but I think it's really beautiful. Don't you think so?! Haha... senti.  I miss my senti days when I was still in Grade 6...kelan lang yun?! January or February lang, I think...hekhek. Oh well. So much for driving down to memory lane.     &nbsp;  And this girl, the girl with a very unstoppable mind...has nothing more to say.    'nuff said.          
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

            TODAY I FEEL:   b-o-r-e-d...but I don't really know... &nbsp;    &nbsp;  I really feel bored. that's why I blogged again. So what? I just promoted (is that the righ term for it?!) this in Friendster.&nbsp; I want people to comment! To know if they really...like (?) the blog. I know I'm gonna make this blog for keeps. So right now, I'm listening to the song  Iris ...the best song ever! *sings*  And I don't want the world to see me, coz I don't think that they'll understand. When everything's meant to be broken, I just want you to know who I am.  *wink* My voice really sounds like a croaking frog! I wish I could go to school and see my friends there. I wish they would call. Oh I miss them -- real bad!     &nbsp;  &nbsp; Question: Bakit kapag school days, you look forward to weekends. But when weekends come, you yearn for school days???  I have no idea. I feel so bored during weekends (except when we go out or watch movies), but I feel so tired during the school days. Everything's so...misunderstood. I just don't get it.  Basta, right now, I just wanna see my friends . Talk to them, text them or whatever...as long as I'm in touch with them. Part of teen-hood, I think. When you really want your friends so much. Haha.  This conversation is going nowhere . Change topic...&nbsp;    &nbsp;   "The Me you wanna see is in the B..."  did you get it?! The B there was for Blog. Hehe. That was so lame. It just popped out of nowhere. This is what happens when I'm so bored. I do lame stuff. Haha. Forgive me for that. Anyway, I think this blog is going to be really looooooong. But hey! It's worth the read and the time (I think). Let's see...Monday? Practice for  Sabayang Pagbigkas  again. Oooohh! I'm so excited with that Sabayan thing. I can't believe I'm an Official Bigkaser! *screeches* It's an honor...a priviledge...something you can really be proud of. That's one thing I love about being a  Paulinian from Paranaque . I don't think any other St. Paul school has Sabayans during Buwan ng Wika. Well, we do. So I'm so...happy!!! Our practices will be puspusan...until 6:00 pm everyday!  Or maybe later pa...But at least, kasabay namin ang dancers for the Centennial ...so all my guy friends will also be there and my Pas De Tous friends (haha you know yourselves!)  High school life is so C-O-O-L pala...hehe .&nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;  I have to go na. I still have to cut out pics of food (THE) and to memorize our Sabayan piece (Isang Dipang Langit) maybe 3 stanzas of it...blog later, i guess?! ciao :)          
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   cute...hehe     &nbsp;  whoot...i'm here in  blogspot  na!  bilis noh ?! it's because i want to experiment all the blog sites...and i decided to just stay here at blogger. i like it so much better eh...hehe. i moved my recent blogs from blog.com right here. so more or less, this one's updated. i'm just gonna post a note there. anyway, today is what -- saturday? oh shucks i wanna go to school...missy and all the guys are practicing for the Centennial dance, right now. I was supposed to join but, it's not my thing. although...i really want to see them. Maybe I'll drop by later on.  Lapit lang naman bahay namin eh . I think our computer got a virus... nahawa sa ken!  When I open another window, the previous one closes! Hate it.     &nbsp;  I watched  Hiram  last night. They were DHs there.  Kakaloka . I think in the end, Beatrice got the kindest employer. Sofia even fed her alaga with dog food! Freaky. I just miss school -- again. (Sorry for this missing school thing. But ever since SPCP became CoEd this year, sa batch namen...basta!)    &nbsp;  Someone just called. And his voice was so scary! He wanted us to meet. But I know he's not a killer or what. I think it's a friend from school. Nagloloko. Pero kahit na. Hate them!!! Prank callers. Whoever that person is, he's gonna be sorry for what he did. whatever...    &nbsp;  Blog later. ciao! :)  

      
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   dizzy...      &nbsp;   today was major blur-ness...i mean first, Cori and I made up (long story -- just don't ask) which is good news, second we had a quiz in Algeb in which I got a 12/17...sucks. maybe for you not, but we've been discussing the lesson for over a week now and I still don't get it!!! maybe it's just because i'm half-sick...that's the third one. fourth, the new Korean guy arrived during Algeb (which maybe distracted me even more...) and everyone was so curious who he is. I just know that his surname is  Park  (uuhh another one of  Sandara-connected  peepz...) He looks like a teddy bear to me. He's so -- white! And all the people are saying that Karl is "laos" na...no! whatever...fifth, the Sabayan. well okay, everything went just fine...but  I JUST FEEL SO DAMN TIRED ...that's why it added to the blur-ness of the day. And it was even raining. Right now, I just hung up with my ka-telebabad  (pare and best frend)... i love talking on the fone today...especially with new friends (NFs!) oh well...i guess that's it for now...talk to you later...ciao!!! :)    

      
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   very very very sick... :(   &nbsp;   durgh ...I hate today! I feel so..yuck! I'm sick, with  colds and fever ...  I think I sound like a croaking frog that ate a sock *uuuhh!* I don't want to go to school tomorrow, if not for that  NutriQuiz  I have to join. A while ago, my nose can be compared to Rudolph's. And I feel really... BAD!  I just wanna lie down and never get out of bed again. Uuuuhhh...I hate this feeling. I've been sniffing the whole day. In GenChem, we had a quiz...I got 3/3 *whoa!* Yeehee! During THE, we were eating choco chips behind Ms. Cullat because we were so BORED!!! And her period was for two long hours! Can you believe it? Good thing in the middle of the period, she let us sing our hearts out with our  fave songs  (Before I Let You Go, So Slow, Grow Old With You, All My Life...haha!) basta...later n lng ha! i feel really sick na eh!    

      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   tired! lolz   "so many things...so little time!"   hey...today was like  SO TIRING!  everything was so hectic...but all the while it was fun! In the morning we had Gen Chem but St. Lorenzo had their class mass so,  Annsterzz dominated!  We checked the papers. I got a 50/50! Woohoo! But only because of a +8...haha! In Cons Math  and we watched a presentation in the IMC, with Lorenzo. Whoot!!! Sir Santos made the presentation, and we had a couple of exercises. But Nica, Missy and I were busy talking about  HIRAM ...you know, the new drama series in ABSCBN. We were pretending that we're them, because we're so DAMN bored. I am  Beatrice  (Mickey Ferriols), the "heartthrob" and the pretty one *I enjoy being that type of girl! Hehe!*, Missy was  Sofia  (Dina Bonnevie) the warfreak *suits her* *peace!* and Nica was  Diana  (Kris Aquino) because obviously she's her idol...erck! But in fairness, the show was quite cool. No matter how jologs you might think it is. In Filipino with Ms. Pioquid, we just talked about love stuff! She was like, the female version of Joe D Mango! Haha! In English...durgh --  BORING ! And in the afternoon, the SC had a meeting that lasted until 6:00 pm! Which was the reason why  Pare  (Tupe) and  Best Friend  (Jeremy) didn't wait for me! grrrr. Anyway, I have colds today. I just hope it would go away tomorrow. gotta go. Leave comments, okay?! :)      

      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

             TODAY I FEEL:   tired but happy!!!  &nbsp;     Sorry I wasn't able to blog lately...schoolwork. Durgh. Sched's so hectic. Everything's moving so fast -- zing! The week's over! But, I don't think  the "I-miss-school" syndrome  is gonna hit me this weekend. I really need to rest... haaaay.  &nbsp;      SCHOOL.  Guess what? We have school today. And it's so unfair! Well anyway, at least I was able to see my friends even during the weekend, so that means only one day of not seeing them *harhar* But, half day lang today. The SCC officers were asked to attend the mass at Andrew's because the new monsignor (was that spelled correctly?) is having his installation thingy...and the sermon was for 45 long minutes!!! I wasn't able to attend my classes and we ate catered food! Hehe. PGs. So far, school's been okay this week. Good scores, great lessons, wonderful times (I think I'm exaggerating!!!) Harhar. Oopsies: Periodic exams in two weeks...sheesh! 8()  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Oh-my-gosh-schoolwork-is-all-over-the-place!" syndrome.  I certainly don't have "me times" anymore. &nbsp;      SABAYAN.  Sabayan practices are getting hotter! Yesterday, we practiced the first stanza, with feelings (yes!!!) It's so cool...it's so grrrrrrr-eat. Haha. Exaggerating again. We're going home kinda late everyday which means: less time for studies and NO TIME FOR BLOG. Argh. But I have no regrets...being a Bigkaser means SO MUCH to moi.  talk about Queen of Exaggeration .  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Oh-man-no-blog-time-because-of-Sabayan-but-it's-okay" syndrome.  &nbsp;     LEADERSHIP TRAINING.  Oh yeah! Oh yeah! This was held last Thursday...and it was so exciting!!! So fun!!! We (all the participants in the Leadership in Dumaguete) were the group guards and we "sort of" facilitated the whole thing :) I'm so&nbsp;proud. I was in charge of Group 1. Mikka, Nica, Ate Miko, Ate Karla (same name!) and Keith (oohh the only thorn among the roses!) were in my group. We played ball pass, treasure hunt (the beeeeeeeeeesst!) and emperor's wish...the excitement is  SO UNEXPLAINABLE . In the Treasure hunt, we were tasked to find items through clues. Then we're gonna cook our lunch with the items we found. So  kalderos, bigas, calamansi, knife, toyo, coal (uling) and kamatis galore ...we were like castaways on a desert island! Funny?! Not quite...because it took forever for the food to be cooked. The fish was  sunog  and the rice was  hilaw.  Talk about w-e-i-r-d. Although, we didn't eat it because we ate the food from the canteen. Plus: I got to wear my PE uniform with my name and class number stamped on it! official high school...yeah!  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Leadership-training-is-so-cool-and-fun" syndrome.  durgh. &nbsp;      MORE STUFF.  What else? Well we learned the Old testament song in CLE (I think the New Testament song is more fun...we learned that when I was in Grade 6), I got good scores in Algebra (I think I'm getting better...haha  ang bigger ko! ), our report in Soc Sci was alright (thanks to Mikka), and the 2nd year pull-out classes were held yesterday (Mt. Makiling...they hiked, trekked and went caving: major Coolness with a capital C!) I think this week was all good, don't yah think? And more people are catching the Love bug...hehe. :) &nbsp;    I'm so looking forward to next week. But I don't know if I can blog everyday. I guess it's gonna take me 4-5 days...darn.  Boo and bullfrogs . I have to study for the perio (although it's still weeks away...) so that I'll not cram. And I have to make reports and reaction papers...told yah everything is so jammed. Everyone is so busy. &nbsp;      SHOUTOUTS:  Cathy for another comment...not much comments lately. hope you comment after reading this...ooh and by the way, if you love my blog you can also e-mail your comments to me:   urlLink  karla_ganda@heartthrob.com    &nbsp;      "Not all great loves last a lifetime. Sometimes, the smallest flame is the one that burns the brightest"  -- the sweetest love quote I ever read. And it's so true! Love bugs? Check out one blog I found:   urlLink  http://lovebugzzz.blogspot.com        Tata for now...ciao! :)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;          
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   so good... :)      &nbsp;   Today is the first official&nbsp;day of the end of  the "I-miss-school" syndrome . I hope you got that one, whatever that means (hehe).  My day is so&nbsp;Hectic with a capital H!  Exagge...everything was so -- busy. I love the scent of busy days (does that even have a smell?) Whatever. I just love school, no matter how weird that&nbsp;sounds.     &nbsp;   So here I am, willing to "take you in" the life&nbsp;I'm so psyched about:     &nbsp;    MARCELINO.  We watched the film  "Marcelino Pan Y Vino"  in CLE together with St. Lorenzo :) It's the story of a little boy who grew up in a priest's convent. The priests forbid him to climb the stairs which led to a huge Crucufix for "there was a man who's gonna take him". But Marcelino, being mischievous still climb the stairs and ended up talking to Jesus. He even fed Him with bread and wine (that's why Jesus named him Marcelino Pan Y Vino) And you know it's so --  nakakakilabot . You can actually see the nails from Jesus' hands suddenly vanishing and Jesus was able to go down the cross to eat with Marcelino. In the end, Jesus took Marcelino and brought him to heaven. It's a sad ending but it's a great miracle, right? I was so freaked out while watching, I even had goosebumps! After watching the film, I think I had a "reality check". Harhar.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "I'm-so-freaked-out-by-that-film-it's-moving-sobra!" syndrome.  Hehehehehe.     &nbsp;    KOREAN GUY.  Okay so this guy is really  FREAKING  everybody out. His name is  Jun Pyo Park  (If I spelled it correctly) and boy, is he a whiz in Math! Well actually, he's not my classmate (I'm in Pullout Fast, he's a Regular) but my friends from Reg said that he was the only one who got the correct answers from the lessons they were discussing for so many weeks now!!! Can you believe it? And I found out he's somewhat related to Jae-yon and Tammy, the Korean sisters who were also new students last year. Why are Koreans invading the country, huh? No offense to them, but I think they're kinda "in" nowadays. I don't know why...maybe because, of Sandara? Harhar. He doesn't know Sandara though (Yes!!! I don't like her *peace*) So is he an official heartthrob now? That is the question. Let's see...if he collects at least 5 crushes just for this week, he can well be compared to Karl. But honestly,  Karl > Jun Pyo . Maybe it's just that Karl is my friend, or we have the same name? Naaaahh. Don't think so. Karl really took us by storm. Whatever. I'm just gonna wait till Friday.  Syndrome of the Moment: The "Who's-gonna-be-the-Year-I-heartthrob?" syndrome.      &nbsp;    SABAYAN.  Whooot! Something I'm really excited about. We had our first official practice (Woohoo!) and  Ate Fhatz &amp; Ate Jona  were there. They're gonna be our trainors. Although we were incomplete (some were also included in the Jingle) we were able to talk about rules,&nbsp;the thrills we were about to experience (harhar!) and of course, voicing ( Domineo, Veniteo...Un-dos-tres-quatro-singko...Ho!Ho!Ho! )  Nga lang, wala pang mga actions.  But that's okay. We can make it.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "First-Year-is-gonna-fight-this-year-Yeah!" syndrome.    &nbsp;    BEA. &nbsp;We saw her!!! Oh we miss her so much! (I hope she doesn't mind being mentioned here) She's studying in  MaSci&nbsp;(Manila Science)  right now. Their&nbsp;uniform is blue as in royal blue. She looks so -- different. I mean, if she's not wearing the  Paulinian uniform , she doesn't look like Bea. Haha. Whatever. I'm so thankful for the Sabayan practices because I was able to see her. She's waiting for her ate  kasi . That was around&nbsp;5:30. I think&nbsp;we're gonna be seeing more of Bea this week...  Syndrome of the Moment: the "I'm-so-happy-I-saw-Bea-again-she-looks-different-but-she's-still-the-same-we-missed-her-a-lot" syndrome  *whew!* That was toug h. &nbsp;    &nbsp;   Today I realized that nothing's better than going back to the place you love second-best: school...and it's so much better when you study in St. Paul! (haha  yabang ! hey, school spirit guys! hope you understand...) Blaaaahh. *shrugs*&nbsp;I meant what I said!     &nbsp;   You might have noticed, I now have  Syndrome of the Moment  in each topic. Well, I think it's gonna be more organized that way,  hindi pakalat-kalat . Haha. So, I really, really hope you're enjoying my blog (and syndromes) Comments, okay?! :)     &nbsp;   Byebye!!! Ü     &nbsp;    &nbsp;    

      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   *yawns* tired &amp; sleepy...      &nbsp;   i just wanted to blog just before I go to sleep.     &nbsp;    GOOD NEWS.  Infrared device working! So I was able to transfer my pics from my phone to the PC then to Photobucket...presto! New pics for Friendster and for the blog! Woohoo! I can't imagine I have over 25+ photos of me, all shot by me! Oh, the wonders you can do when one is really bored.     &nbsp;    NEWS FLASH.  I memorized 3 stanzas of the piece already! Hooray for me! I'm so happy...see, I told you, I can find time for it. I now have  the "I'm-rejoicing-because-I-was-able-to-do-something-I-was-wishing-I-could-do-but-I-didn't-have-the-time-to-do-it-Hooray!" syndrome  *whew!* Three cheers. :) I am so happy.     &nbsp;    STILL RAINING.  Yup. Raining cats and dogs. And that makes me sleepy. So I have to go now. But never worry...I'm leaving a pic right here.  Baka kasi ma-miss mo ko eh!  Hehe. I guess I won't be able to blog na everyday this week because,  voila!,  schooldays again and the syndrome ends but a new one arrives:  the "I-wish-it's-weekend-already" syndrome . Weird. Totally freakin weird. Tata for now. :) &nbsp;           A pic of me. Pretty?! hehe :)       

      
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

            TODAY I FEEL:   cool...and senti.  &nbsp;     &nbsp;   It's raining.  I love rain. The sound of water falling on the ground, on the roof. *drip, drop, drip, drop*&nbsp;The smell of rain fighting the heat. The sight of water falling from the sky. Aaaaahh. So heavenly. Rain. It brings lots of emotions. Hahahahaha. What a senti mood I have today. Weird, huh?!  "My-mood-depends-on-the-weather" syndrome . Argh. I don't know why lots of people hate rain. I love it. Its sound reminds me of busy streets and busy people, of traffic and lights. I don't know why but it gives me that kind of impression. Which is why I blogged -- again. Am I blogging too much? Hope not. But there's nothing wrong in that, I think. I just feel like blogging and blogging. The rain just stopped. Actually, it wasn't even rain. It was just drizzling. Oh well, still the same if you ask me. &nbsp;     &nbsp;   Buhos pa ulan aking mundo'y lunuring tuluyan... &nbsp;        &nbsp;   Rain on me...won't you take this pain from me...  &nbsp;     &nbsp;  Why do people&nbsp;write songs about rain&nbsp;too much? Haha. I sang the first one that's why it rained. Hehe. Sad but true. *wink* &nbsp;     &nbsp;   CORNDOGS.  I officially love corndogs. Just now. I ate four. *whoa* We bought a whole box of them from PriceSmart. You know, the heat-in-the-microwave stuff. In school, I also buy corndogs only it's called "waffle". Freaky. I'm wondering, who invented corndogs? Some freakin man that owned a dog who loves corn? Haha. Or maybe his name was Doug. And he loved hotdogs stuffed in bread on a stick. And his wife's name is CORNelia. This is so stupid. Why should I care about the good man who invented corndogs? I don't freakin care. I just wanna thank him for coming up with the idea...and a hundred years later, one girl loved it. harhar.&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;   BIRTHDAY.  My real birthday is on October 26, 1991 (I'm just turning 13) But I placed 1990 on the blog application form *lier!* Shhh. It's a secret. Whatever. So I'm planning to just have it here in my house. Of course, I'm gonna invite my friends. It's a Tuesday anyway. I hope they come. Or else I'm gonna develop another syndrome: the " My-friends-didn't-come-to-my-birthday-and-I'm-so-sad" syndrome.  But right now, I'm having the  "My-birthday-is-coming-I'm-so-excited-I-can't-wait" syndrome.  Blaaahh. &nbsp;     &nbsp;   THE "SYNDROME-CRAZY" SYNDROME.  You might have noticed, these "syndromes" are driving me nuts. I can't help it. It's so -- fun, making up syndromes, which really happens to me and maybe to you. Well, maybe it's not scientifically proven BUT they do come in our lives and sort of, attack us or whatever you call it. Honestly, I enjoy making them. Haha. Syndrome-maker girl. I hope you're enjoying them as much as I do. Syndromes...syndromes...syndromes....aaaahh it's going wild!  The "I-can't-stop-making-syndromes" syndrome ...totally freakiness.  Freakiness Rating: 10/10. This is totally not me.  &nbsp;     &nbsp;  So...this ends my blog for the moment. Liking my syndromes??? Maybe someday I can make a complete list of all the syndromes I've made.&nbsp;Waaaahh. These syndromes are making me crazy. Think one of these syndromes have infected you? Give me a shout-out and tell me what you have to say. Adios. :) &nbsp;     &nbsp;   Syndromes: Copyrighted ©&nbsp;2004. karlatotz Ü &nbsp;&nbsp;           
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   superb!!!      &nbsp;   Haha. I feel really fantastic today.  The syndrome finally ends. &nbsp;I saw my friends. Yipee! Well, Jeremy is a sacristan and he served for the 10:00 mass. Missy and I decided to attend the mass and *poof* we saw each other there. Now I'm experiencing the "after-syndrome" Hahaha! Basta right now, I just feel really happy :) at least I saw even just the two of them. Life in St. Paul...you just can't resist the  "I-want-to-be-with-my-friends" feeling . Simply amazing (although I'm a Globe user...hehe) Plus, I was wearing my super cool Penshoppe get-up (T-shirt: Beauty, Brains and Attitude. Pants: Denim.)     &nbsp;    LTMs.  Last night, I talked on the phone until 9:00 pm. Actually that was quite early compared to the other nights when I stayed up until 11:00... late night marathons (LTMs) . I can't imagine I can talk about a gazillion things on the phone for hours then end up wanting to talk pa...me and my unstoppable brain (and mouth)  I'm Queen of Daldal . Harhar. How I wish the new directress (Sr. Angele) would announce a free day one of these days. Super saya. *wish, wish* hmph. I bet we're not getting one. Maybe sa Intrams pa, for the practices. Argh!     &nbsp;    LEADERSHIP TRAINING.  Thursday. Yes!!! No classes for all leaders out there! We're gonna be pulled out, I think. And we're gonna have lots of activities. I'm looking forward to it. And the games we're gonna play were the games from Track 2 (Leadership in Dumaguete) and I was only in Track 1 then, so...COOL. Haha. Freakin cool.     &nbsp;    STARGIRL.  This is my all-time favorite book. (All-American Girl is only second) i read it again out of boredom. It is simply the best book ever. It's a story of growing-up and first love's. Stargirl is just a new girl in a high school and Leo fell for her.  Basta , you should read it! The cover is blue with a drawing of a star and a girl (Get it? Star + girl...)  Highly recommended .     &nbsp;    SABAYAN.  I memorized 2 stanzas  pa lang ...haha. At least I did na. Although the 2nd was not too clear yet. Why?! Something weird happens: when I pick up the copy and start reading it, my heart beats faster, my brain goes thumpety-thump (read: Excitement) I can't stop it. Adrenaline rush  pa yata , as some would call it. But it's so weird. I think about the costumes, the actions, the thrill...I think I'm developing another syndrome. It's the   "Bigkaser's Too-much-excitement-can't-concentrate" syndrome  . Oh man. I'm a  Syndrome Girl  -- big time. Aaaaahh!     &nbsp;   And I just want to announce that my 7650 is alive again because may load na ko!!! Woohoo!!! After the long wait...sorry if I wasn't able to reply if you texted me.  The Karlatotz is back . Yeah! :)     &nbsp;     SHOUT-OUTS:   Thanks to Cathe and Jam for the comments. :) Visit their blogs, okay?!&nbsp;   &nbsp;   Ciao, ciao. :)   &nbsp;    This pic was taken during our Grade&nbsp;6 grad (march&nbsp;2004)   :)  &nbsp;    P.S. &nbsp; Holler back!  Leave your comments. I'm dying to know if you like my blog. Hehe.&nbsp;  The "I-wanna-know-if-my-blog-is-cool" Syndrome.   Tssss. :)      

      
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   ready for school! wahaha...       That doesn't exactly mean I'm having the "I-miss-school" syndrome again. Actually, these past few weekends, the syndrome didn't attack me. Harhar. I just feel like today is already a Sunday, and I'm all geared up for Monday. But by Wednesday, we're gonna be having our periodic exams, and that is one thing I'm not perfectly ready for. I've reviewed Integ, Algeb, a little bit of CLE and Music...oh man I hate GenChem! I'm really starting to hate it big time because of that conversion table. Let's just all pray that I'll not fail that test. Oh.       40 DAYS.  No it's not the part two of the GMA-7 show for the  laos (whatta term!) artistas : 30 Days. Today is the 4oth day after the death of my  Lola Madre  (my Lola's sister) We went to the convent and had mass there. Then we went to Loyola after. We even visited the grave of Dorothy Jones aka Nida Blanca. They were neighbors (hehe). The ambience was unexplainable. I don't know if the people around me were sad or happy or what. But honestly, I feel sad when I remember my lola. She's one of my favorite lolas. She was the one who told me that all my talents came from God and that I should always thank Him. I hope she's happy there with Him.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "I-miss-my-lola" syndrome.        BAGS.  I really like Ate Marion's bags.  Ate Marion  (my cousin) makes and designs bags and boy are they cute. I think it started when they have to sell bags and make a thesis about it and poof! I think the people liked it so she keeps on making them and selling them in different colors. Right now, I just received a cute blue body bag and I'm going to use it on Monday. I think I wanna sell some to my friends. I'll be bringing the color sampes (I forgot what they're called) and they're just gonna place orders. I hope they buy. They're cute and  kikay-ish . Haha. The money I'm gonna earn, well,will be kept and saved for future use. Hehehe.  Syndrome   of the Moment: the "Enterpreneur-in-me-is-oozing-out-of-my-body" syndrome        SCHOOLWORK.  Did I just say a while ago that I'm all geared up for school? I think I take 50% of it back. I haven't finished our Algeb project! Missy e-mailed the problems & puzzles to me and I'm tasked to print it. But I think she forgot to put in the answers so I still have to solve it!  Damn.  I really hate it when projects are made last-minute. But what can I do? The things I was busy about last week were also last-minute, so I guess everything was done in the last-minute. Argh. Hate it. Good thing today is only Saturday and I still have more than 24 hours to go. Argh.       SHOUTOUTS:   Gliza  again! Although she didn't comment here, she commented me in her site! Heehee. Visit her site okay? I promise you, it rocks!   urlLink  www.prinsesa.net    Thanks Ate Gliza! :)      Okay, I think this is for real.  THIS IS THE LAST BLOG I'M GOING TO POST FOR THIS WEEK . Maybe my next blog will be after the perio, which is on Friday. I'm going to miss you guys...(I hope you miss me too! Hehe) Comment, okay?   And wish me luck in my periodic tests...i need all the prayers I can get!   Hehe.       Bye, bye! Ciao! Paalam! luvyah...mwaaaaahh! :)   

      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

       urlLink Haloscan  commenting and trackback have been added to this blog.

      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   extremely good...exagge!      &nbsp;   Haha, contrary to yesterday's blog, today was quite fine...actually it was grr-eat! First, today is Friday. Second, no practices tomorrow...just read on and you'll know more about the girl's day...     &nbsp;    SABAYAN.  Well today I think is the most PRODUCTIVE Sabayan practice. No offense, mehn. Today didn't stink (haha). We had fun, we practiced the actions...everything went well. Although, we really have to make a huge effort to make our voice loud because of 3 things:     &nbsp;   1. The 2nd year and grade 2 field trip-ers (was that the correct term for it? W. Just hope you got my point...) arrived. So everybody were buzzing and talking, blah, blah, blah, blah...    2. The field trip buses were so  NOISY  and so  BLOCKING OUR WAY ...durgh    3. All the other Year levels were practicing so it was like, patagisan at palakasan talaga ng boses. It was so: weird. Another factor for batch rivalries. Everything seems to be moving around...haha. Seriously, everybody was doing their own thing -- for real.     Syndrome of the Moment: the "Sabayan-went-good-bravo!" syndrome      &nbsp;    BOYS.  Okay, weird topic, huh? Haha. I just wanna say, I think I'm getting used to them already. I mean, St. Paul Paranaque was an exclusive girl-school since 1945 and now -- whoa! Boys galore...So I have  pares , best friends , crushes  (Syempre hindi yan mawawala!)  and admirers (Yuck! feeling! as if!) It's as if everything turned upside-down.  Haaaaayy.  I'm telling you -- this is not about me being a flirt or having a boyfriend. It's just an opinion, that well, spells out the T-R-U-T-H about how I (or maybe WE) feel about having the guys around. Haha. 'Nuff said.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Boys-make-the-school-go-crazy" syndrome      &nbsp;    BIRTHDAY BASH:  KITH!!! The guitarist...woohoo! I think he just turned 12? But anyway, he's my friend so he's worth&nbsp;mentioning! :)     I think I should stop for a while...I really need to study...wish me luck in my test! Adios! :) luvyaaaahh...mwaaah! :)     &nbsp;   

      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   bad...this really isn't much of a sunshine-y day...    I feel so disappointed, I don't know what to feel anymore.    JINGLE.  The climax of the day. Well, I wasn't really part of the Jingle contest but I was an extra (hehe) I played the drum thingy just for the signal. The Year I against Year II and Year III against Year IV. The audience loved us (hehe, peace out!!!) and everybody was cheering for the Year IV (Sorry again...) but Year II and Year III won. I guess I'm just so disappointed. We should've won -- but because they recorded the guitar sound, the judges "sort of" took that against us. Hey! We were good. As for the seniors and juniors, the Juniors won because their instrumentalists played better but I think the Yr IV song was cool. Sorry for anything I just typed which you don't approve to...anyway this is my opinion, my side of the story, and my blog. But we congratulated the Year II and Year III anyway. Although, the Year IV and Year I just joined forces:  FORST YEAR . Haha.  FO urth Year and fir ST  year. Hehe.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "We-should've-won-the-jingle" syndrome.    FRESHMEN: ONE BIG FIGHT!!!   Actually, the jingle is stuck in my mind.    SABAYAN.  Oh the never-ending practices. But today was quite better...the other levels thought we were 4th Year students. Goodie! Now we're talking...I think the Freshies have what it takes to be competed against other levels. Not that I'm being boastful or anything, it's just that sometimes, other levels look down to us. Oh well, I honestly enjoyed today's practice. Ate Jona was there...and we all have a crush on *tooooot* Secret!!!  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Sabayan-was-okay-and-we-had-fun" syndrome.       SHOUTOUTS:  Gliza...thanks for commenting!!!!! Visit her site:  urlLink www.prinsesa.net ! Highly recommended...         BIRTHDAY BASH:  Belated Happy Birthday to Pauline (26) and Verna (29, today!) who both turned 13...my birthday's only a few (?) months away...hehe :)  Sorry if my blog is too short...as I've told you, I'm really busy especially this week and next week. Probably  ZERO BLOGS  because of guess what:  Periodic Exams . So, please bear with me (haha). But anyway, I'm still encouraging you to comment...it would be gladly appreciated! Luvyah guys...mwaaaah! :)      

      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   wasted... :) hehe     &nbsp;  I feel really wasted, as in: super-duper tired. My sched's so busy...I can't find time for myself anymore! I'm a having a bad case of  "too-much-school" flu , if ever there is one. Oh man.     &nbsp;   HIGAD.  I have to write this one down even though it's weird&nbsp;in writing (or typing) it down as it is in real life. Yesterday, a  higad  crawled to my sock without me noticing it. While talking to Jeremy, Ray and Melissa, I felt something sticky crawling to my legs and when I looked: aaaaahh!  higad!! !!!! So I immediately removed it but unfortunately, it bit me already. After recess, we had THE and I itched too much that I turned red already and Katrina brought me to the clinic. The nurse asked me to wash the infected parts (arms, head, neck, legs...) and then put on some cream. But I was still itching after that...argh. Now I have higad scars. Argh-er.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "stupid-higad-just-bit-me-and-it-made-my-body-itched-big-time" syndrome.     &nbsp;   SABAYAN.  I'm starting to get bored with Sabayan practices (no offense) We're always incomplete, the Jinglers are not there, Ate Jona and Ate Fhatz are not always there and when they are, we're incomplete, I have to bring my PE everyday but we're not using it and I'm going home super late...which causes some "disagreements" with me and my mom. I just hope practices will be more: productive.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "I'm-too-tired-for-Sabayan" syndrome.  Sad but true.    &nbsp;   Bea and Kathleen went to school a while ago.  Bea (as I've mentioned before) studies at MaSci and Kathleen studies at PaSci (Paranaque Science). We missed them so much!!! Too bad they weren't able to taste the thrill of St. Paul Paranaque High School...hehe.     &nbsp;   SONG OF THE DAY: Old Testament Song. Haha     &nbsp;  Gotta go... bitin ba ang blog? Sorry, takas lang!  Hehe!  

      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

            TODAY I FEEL:   stomach-achy...darn      Yeah and this stomach ache is here since yesterday after that big lunch we had yesterday. We were starving to death then they let us eat big time...so I guess that explains it. Oh man, it really hurts...gastritis? Naaahh don't think so...just a bad case of  kabag . Argh.      BUTTERFLIES.  A butterfly is flying around the window right this very minute. And I know it's my  Lola Madre  (she's the sister of my Lola, and she's a nun) She probably wanted to visit me so she dropped by. Aaaaaww. I wasn't able to go to mass in St. Andrew's because we had a mass here in the chapel (the masses in the Chapel are only held during 4th Sundays) so I wasn't able to see my friends if ever they attended mass at Andrew's. Oh man. But that's okay, few hours to go and voila!  This girl is gonna see her friends again.       INDIANA JONES.  I'm so not interested in this film...but hey can I help it if I have to make a report about it for Integ Sci? When we watched it last week, I wasn't able to understand much of it because all our teacher did was to forward the tape and we were only able to watch for maybe 30 minutes, I think. So...I have to look for synopses in the 'Net. But it's not plagiarism, if that's what you're thinking. I'm just gonna get ideas...and we're supposed to identify the minerals that appeared in the film. HELLO??? How am I supposed to know? And why do we even have to care about the minerals? Aaaaargh. I really hate reaction papers. Syndrome of the Moment: the "I-hate-reaction-papers-and-minerals" syndrome .       SPIDERMAN.  Is it too late to express my love for the movie, the song and the ACTOR (read: Tobey Maguire)? Well, I was always forgetting it last week so...here it is. Haha. We watched Spidey last, last week in Rockwell. It was so amazing. I loved every second of it!!! It is majorly fantastic...and of course  CUTIE SIGHTING!!!  Ohh Tobey Maguire is the best!!! I'm gonna marry him (wish, wish!)...did you know that Michael Buble made a remake of the original Spidey theme? I have a pirated (haha! can't help it...) CD of Michael Buble and it featured the Spidey song. Surprisingly, he made a video...and it's so damn cool. I'm just wondering: why didn't they make Buble's remake the soundtrack for the movie? It's way better than Ordinary by "oops I forgot the name of the artist"...the 3rd part (aka Spiderman 3) will be on 2006 according to   urlLink  www.rottentomatoes.com   . Oh man,  TWO LONG YEARS  of waiting for my one true love. Oh well, patience is a virtue.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Spiderman-found-his-way-to-my-heart" syndrome.   The Amazing Spiderman -- the best!      I just realized something:  Weekends are always jam-packed.  You have to do your assignments and reports, you have to fix your things and prepare yourself for the week ahead. So weekends are not entirely and purely for resting. It's about gearing yourself for the week, which means: everyday is workday for us!!! Darn, darn, darn.     Hmmm...time's up for me. Blog again next time, when sched's become lighter. And one more thing: Comment! Comment! Comment!&nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;   ciao, ciao! :) mwaaaaahh!     &nbsp;               
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   too lazy to even know what I am feeling right this very moment...   i just changed my template... GREEN . Hehehehehe. I just like to experiment. But I tell you guys, pink is still my thing. Just don't mind the Haloscan post. Well since everytime I change the template, all the content goes away too so I have to re-install my commenting system...argh. But anyway, your comments are still there so it's okay.   BHEZ.  I'm making a site for me and my best friend,  Katrina . Actually everybody in school these days began calling her Hope since it's her second name. But I still feel like calling her Kat so, there. We just had a phone convo and I came up with the idea of us having a site. We thought it would be cool. We're gonna have it in Bravenet. When it's done I'll let you know. Visit it, okay?   SEND MY LOVE TO HEAVEN.  It's raining. And I'm loving it...ooh the soothing sound of the rain falling down makes me want to sleep. But I'm not sleepy. Haha. I suddenly remembered the story  "Send My Love To Heaven".  I first learned about that in Grade 4 I think. Missy (my other close, as in super close friend) told me that her cousin told her a story about this guy who fell for his best friend but it was too late when he finally had the guts to say it to her because she died. When he visited her grave, rain poured and he said  "Oh God, send my love to heaven"  I was so touched by the story I wanted to find a copy of it right away. But we didn't know where to get one, so... hanggang dun na lang . Then this summer, as I was surfing my way through the Net, I 'accidentally' found this site named Prinsesa (hehe, Ate Gliza's) and surprisingly, she has Send My Love To Heaven!!! I immediately informed Missy and printed a copy. When school started, I gave her the copy and we were both touched again. Aaaaaww. Maybe I'll post that one in the upcoming site.   SHOUT-OUTS.  Ate Gliza, Cathe and 2 new peepz: Shia and "Anonymous" Thanks guys! Hope you comment again next time...    I think this is it for now. Maybe I'll not be blogging very often so that you can still have time to read the blogs I just posted these last few days. But anyway, if you missed some, you can always check out my archive. Comment, okay? I'm loving my new commenting system (thanks to Haloscan) so tell me what you think and I'll be more than willing to give you a BIG THANK YOU. luv yah!!! :) *mwaaaaaahh*    

      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

       urlLink Haloscan  commenting and trackback have been added to this blog.

      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   so happy and free!!! i'm baaaaack!!! i totally missed sitting by the window, in the comfy black chair, in front of the computer, typing for my blog...woohoo!!!       I missed my blog soooo much!!! Although I didn't get a lot of comments, ok lang...at least new blog again. Did you guys miss me? Haha. I sure hope you did. So here I am, I think I'm gonna be typing a slightly long blog. I just want you to catch up with my crazy, wacky life.       PERIO.   The climax of the blog!!!  This is the entire reason why I wasn't able to blog for one whole week! Can you believe it??? Oh well, it went fine...really fine. I mean, I think I answered well. Ü I just hope I'll pass. From Tuesday night until this morning, my brain was in a major panic-mode. I don't feel the periodic-test ambience. Weird, but true. Anyway, for me the hardest test was THE: Oh shucks. We were supposed to memorize the whole vitamin chart, functions, food sources et al. And guess what? I failed to answer two...haha. I tried but I just can't think of the answers so I just left it blank. For Algebra, I think I answered quite fine! I'm sort of happy because I'm not confused or what. I think the numbers just came flowing down my hands and I just solved it, uhm, peacefully. Ü I'm not being  mayabang , but it's true. That's the way I felt. The subjects for the last day (that is today) were the subjects I'm a little more confident about because I was really able to understand them well especially  GEN CHEM !!! Gosh my mind finally welcomed the idea of changing English units to Metric and vice versa without any fuss!!! Can you believe it? Even the Filipino stuff (ponema, morpema, etc.) and the Cons Math thingies (consumerism, consumer vigilance) blaaaahh...thanks for the prayers, if you ever prayed for me, because generally, I can feel that my 1st perio in high school is going to be just fine. Ü  Syndrome of the Moment: the "I-feel-good-about-the-perio" syndrome        DEBATE.  Guess what? Miraculously, I am going to join the Debate on Aug 12. I don't know who picked me or even mentioned my name, but to her (or him) I don't know what to say. I mean, I would really like to debate (I remember the debate we had in Grade 4 about the American troops coming here for the Balikatan) but not now. I'm only a freshie...haha. Not that I'm underestimating the power within us (naks!) but you know, it's just so unusual. My groupmates are Ate Marianne (coach), Ate Golda (team capt.), Ate Nikki (Beneficiality speaker) and Ate Mae Anne (Necessity speaker).  Obviously, I'm the great scribe.  I'm not going to speak (yes!) but my role I think is one of the most important one. I have to listen to the other team very carefully and write down important points...then the others can make a rebuttal out of my notes. I have to put into my mind that "one wrong word coming from them can make their whole team fall" so I really have to be attentive. The debate is about the "No Permit, No Rally" Policy and we're on the ______ side. Can't tell. Someone from the other team might read it...Ü  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Debate-is-sending-shivers-down-my-spine" syndrome        SABAYAN.  The last thing I wanted to talk about today. Oh damn, like any other day, today was so  walang kwenta . Sorry for the word, but it's so damn true. One thing that is different among the other days is that:  I honestly had so much fun !!! Super!!! As in!!! We only did some vocalizations since Ate Jona was not there (only Ate Fhatz). So  yun , voicing here, voicing there. Then in the singing part (we have to sing the chorus of the APL song... Lapit mga kaibigan... ) we really need to exaggerate our moves so we were like dancing monkeys! Haha. Trixie auctioned P50 again,  ililibre daw niya yung Top 5 na pinaka-OA . P10 each for water. And we called the game  "Quest for Water"  (Quest for Fire? Yuck! I'm so grossed with that film!!!) When we had the break, we bought out own water (except for those who "won") and after that,  nagbasaan kami! As in super saya ...we were all wet and the goal: to wet other people! We were sooooo... WET !!! We were like a group of  basang sisiw's . I had fun, real fun. It was so good to feel the cold water running down your skin, only thing is, I might get sick. Argh.  Anyway, I still had fun.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Sabayan-practice-turned-to-water-disaster" syndrome.        SOME OTHER STUFF I WANT TO BLAB ABOUT::    1. Bea came to school again!!! We were so happy to see her...I hugged her so tightly!!! Hehehe. She's still as cute as ever. I hope she'll visit us more often.   2. Missy and me finally have our song:  The Show !!! It's so C-O-O-L although the meaning's kinda grassy green...but hey: if you don't bring malice to the song, it's just a song. The reason why we chose that song? Secret...it has something to do with *tOooOoOt!* Hehe. Ü   3. Nica and I finally made up. Reason behind the fight? Naaah. Dont need to know.   4. *tOooOooT* is so cute!!! Haha. He's my  Knight in Shining Armor  *uyyy* Durgh. Just kidding. And also  Lee from the Pond's Commercial ...I knew it!!! I knew he was the guy right form the very beginning! I wish I was like Karel...lots of admirers...waaahh.   5. Mom is the parent speaker for homeroom on Monday. Haha. I hope she will make a mark. Naks. I know she will.  She's a Paulinian like me too. And Paulinians always leave a mark . Yes!   6. Recollection on Tuesday! So guys...prepare your reco letters!!! I'm gonna be waiting...Ü      Haaaayy... SORRY FOR THIS ULTRA LONG BLOG . I just missed blogging...1 week of not blogging is total torture for me! Haha. Exagge. Comment okay? I'll be expecting them... Luv yah! Ü  

      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

            TODAY I FEEL:   sexy...I think the song of the day is "Naughty Girl" hehehe.   I wore a mini-skirt to school today. Hehe. So that's why I feel sexy. Plus, I wore my supah cool Celine step-in that is __ inches long each which made me taller...hehe. But anyway, I changed to my work clothes after arriving, so no problemo.   THE DAY BEFORE TODAY.  Modified form of the word yesterday. I just felt like changing boring old words to exciting ones. Anyway, yesterday was finally the end of the ultra long week. (I really think this week is super-mega-totally-long...*sighs*) We were measured for our Sabayan costumes (finally!!!), Ms. Pepito and our class made up (we didn't actually have a fight...but hey, she got mad at us) and we celebrated Mrs. Fragante's birthday (she is our Year Level Coordinator [YLC]). For the last one, we surprised Mrs. F with flowers and gifts during lunch. She was so shocked because she thought that our gift in our Algeb class was the "surprise" but then we gathered all the Year I officers and advisers in the Learning Station and surprised her again. She's so young...only 27 but she has a husband already, Mr. Fragante (obviously) who was a former Paulinian teacher and is now teaching at ADMU.  W.   Syndrome of the Moment: the "Thank-God-for-the-weekend" syndrome. I need to rest.    FROM THE MOUTH OF THE BIGKASER.   OUR PRACTICE IS SO COOL, PRODUCTIVE, HOT GREAT, GOOD, BETTER, BEST!!!!!  This was definitely the coolest. We practiced for the whole day...7:00-4:00. The commercial thing is stuck on my mind:        Say Cheese! Cheddar!     Say Cheese! Garlic!     Say Cheese! Bacon!     Say Cheese! Pimiento!    This is I think the shortest entry about Sabayan. Oh well: More is Less. Hehe. 'Nuff said.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Best-sabayan-practice-was-made" syndrome    SORRY.  I'm really sorry if I wasn't able to blog very, very, very often. TOTALLY BUSY SCHED. I told you, I don't even have me times or phone convos or Friendster...so it's really -- sad. But anyway, I promise when everything unclogs, I will try to blog as often as I can. Thanks for the commentors!!! I'll comment back: PROMISE!!!   BIRTHDAY BASH.  Mrs. Fragante (today, 14, but we greeted her yesterday) and Kristine (tomorrow, 15) Happy Bday guys! :D   SHOUT-OUTS.  I've been missing the shout-outs also. Anyway, thanks to   urlLink  Shari   ,   urlLink  Jam   ,   urlLink  Gliza   ,   urlLink  Cathe    and Deejaie. Thanks guys! :) Luv y'all! Ciao, ciao! Mwaaahh! ;D          
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

       urlLink Haloscan  commenting and trackback have been added to this blog.

      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

             TODAY I FEEL:   like jumping...don't know why.     I feel like it's been a really long time since I blogged. Well you can guess why and if you get it correctly a kiss for you......... busy sched , I hear you say.  MWAAAAAHH . There it goes. Haha. But anyway I don't feel too exhausted anymore as in freaked-out. I think I adjusted to the ambience already. Whoa...congrats to me.     SR. FIDES.  Yes, yes, yes guys. Sister Fides, our beloved CLE teacher. Before you close this window and yawn your way out from my blog, take time to read even this part because it really is freaky. Yesterday (Wednesday) she gave us a seatwork because she has to attend a Council Meeting. Knowing our attitudes when our teacher is not around, we didn't bother to do it and we just played. (Sorry guys, I have to cut the story short) She caught us and told us to remain standing until she returns. After that, her "assistant" came and told us that we can already go home after 5 minutes (CLE was our last period) which also means that we can go to our Sabayan practices (Sabayan is always involved...) Unfortunately, Sr. Fides wasn't informed that her assistant told us to go so she got mad and told us to go up to our classroom again. We tried to say sorry but she thought we were escaping from her.  THE WHOLE CLASS OF I - ST. ANN WAS CRYING , one of our classmates even fainted. She then called us to her office and we had a "mini" recollection there. We were all moved by what she said and we all made a promise not do it again. Sounds weird, huh?  But it made me realize one thing: sisters are not "sungit" all over. They're just misunderstood .  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Sister-and-St.-Ann-encounter" syndrome.      DEBATE.  We lost. Haha. But that's okay. I feel totally fine with it. We fought against the positive side for the "No Permit, No Rally Policy". (Obviously, we were on the negative side) It was a great experience for me. Totally fun. Not the typical shouting debate we see on TV. But real action and real stuff. I'm never gonna forget this debate, it's my first serious one. See I told you, the "I'm gonna be a lawyer someday" statement might have a chance.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Debate-is-totally-cool-even-if-we-lost" syndrome.      BIGKASER UPD8.  Sabayan. We call the Sabayan participants  "Bigkasers"  (Sabayang Pag BIGKAS -- get it?) I just want to change the title for this section coz you might grow tired of it. Anyway, practices today are really getting  COOLER and HOTTE R (uhm?! Haha! Whatta weird statement...) Cooler in a way that it's not plain boring anymore and hotter because we're doing more and more stuff besides the usual vocalization...We have the Say Cheez commercial in it and lotsa other cool stuff. I'm really loving it now. As in! By the way, the competition is on August 26. Wish us luck!!!  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Cool-and-hot-Sabayan" syndrome     I still have to finish my English book report and it's what -- 9:16 pm. Ciao, ciao guys! Mwaaahh!            
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   alright... :)       Yup. I feel totally alright. It's been raining all day but it didn't ruin my day. Actually, it made it much more, uhm, challenging. I think today is not a total waste. I was able to accomplish lots of things. And I think I'm geared up to face the week ahead. Sounds weird? Accept it. It's real.       MASS.  We had mass at St. Andrew's, 8:00. All Year I students were there. We were the sponsors and we were also the choir. Heehee. See? Paulinians really are religious. How can we NOT be religious? The Cathedral is only a few steps across the school. Oh and by the way, our recollection is on Tuesday. Don't forget to make me a reco-letter, huh?  Syndrome of the Moment: the "I-am-a-total-angel" Syndrome        DEBATE.  After the mass, we (Ate Marianne, Ate Golda, Ate Nikki and I) had a meeting about Thursday's debate. We stressed our points and prepared to "block" whatever the other team's points may be. Ate Mae Anne didn't attend the meeting and I thought I was going to take her place (as the Necessity speaker), good thing I didn't.  My powers are only reserved for scribe-material as of now.  Hahaha. Wish us luck.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Debate-is-only-a-few-days-away" Syndrome          SABAYAN.  I think this topic is in almost all of my blogs, didn't you notice? I think it's becoming a real part of me already, not just an extra-curricular activity. Whoa men, it's growing in my veins. Harhar. So...about today's practice (okay, don't be shocked but yes, a Sunday and we had a practice) It went good. Actually, I think it has been the best practice ever. Not ordinary vocalizations and polishing, but  real action . Talk about exciting. We changed the first stanza and made it so much cooler. Then we practiced the intro. It's  kee-yut ! Hehe. I enjoyed it. Some are going to be "activists" and the others will be the "Ate Charo's". I'm one of the Charo's...the  aktibista  role is just not my thing. Well, it rained, yes, but the Bigkasers still rocked the day.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Today-was-so-far-the-best-Sabayan-practice" Syndrome        GARFIELD.  We watched Garfield yester day!!! It's so cool. Although I freaked out for some scenes (FYI, I'm afraid of cats. Weird? Hehe.) but the film was cute. I honestly enjoyed it.    --  Watch out for:  Garfield's dance moves and all his other wacky pranks!!!   --  I watched it at:  Festival Mall, last night   --  Rating: ( 5 stars as the highest) **** - I could've given it a 5 but the fear factor is there...hehe       NOT YOUR TYPICAL BABY.  It's my new blog. It's where I'm gonna talk about issues and stuff that I don't wanna place in this blog because they're not "related" to my life, but it kinda bugs me anyway. Haha. Hope you got that.  Basta , visit it, just click   urlLink  this   . Tell me what you think of it okay?      Gotta go now, I still need to make reco letters...luv yah! and don't forget:  COMMENT!!!!!!!         

      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       

        TODAY I FEEL:   loved...teehee     EAR CANDY:   she will be loved...        I don't mind spending everyday     Out on your corner in the pouring rain     Look for the girl with the broken smile     Ask her if she wants to stay awhile     And she will be loved...she will be loved       Oh it's stuck in my mind. But the question is: who will be loved? Me -- with a huge question mark? Honestly, I feel loved right now...loved by you. Haha. I LOVE this feeling. But not love as in boyfriend-girlfriend love, but the "I-can-feel-the-world" feeling. It's nice. Love is loving me right now.       BOOK FAIR.  We went to the World Trade Center Book Fair today, and boy am I overwhelmed!!! As you all know, I'm a total book-anaconda! But I'm no nerd, mind you. I just love the smell of books and the thought every page brings. It's awesome. I can't believe how people take books for granted...they don't even dare read a book or two. They're missing a huge part of their life. We bought the 5th installment of the Princess Diaries: Princess in Pink. It's so -- PINK. Kee-yut.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "Books-are-cool-and-so-am-I" syndrome        ROSITA.  My second name, as all of you know is something I'm really proud of. Yeah it sounds weird but it sounds wonderful next to my name.  Maria Karla Rosita.  Heavenly *wink* So for our assignment in Soc Sci, we have to research the meaning and heritage of our names. Rosita is an Italian word for small rose. Rose (Rosa) means pink. So sort of like "small pink rose". Cool, huh? I guess that explains my pink addiction.  Syndrome of the Moment: the "My-name-is-so-pink-and-rosy" syndrome.        HEARTTHROB.  I changed the title of the blog. I really like the word. Think it suits me? Naaahh. You judge. Basta, I think it fits this blog. Tell me watcha think, okay?!      Comments guys! Keep it coming! Luv yah, mwaaahh!!! :)  

      
</post>


</Blog>