<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      I have a new found respect for mothers. Yes, after spending 2 nights with a new mother and a 2 month old, I decided I don't know that I ever really want kids. I mean, I probably do, but geez...getting up in the middle of the night,feeding, changing, rocking them to sleep...it's a lot of work. Even me, just as an innocent bystander needed a night out on the town tonight to recover from it. Granted I'll probably need a whole day to recover from my lack of sleep from tonight, but yeah, I don't know where I was going with that. I just think Mothers deserve more Kudos than they get...and I suppose fathers too, if they bother to get up with the kids.  I do have to say though, that making a baby laugh and smile at you, is one of the coolest things in the world. Especially if it's not even your kid. It's like, hey, this kid actually knows you and thinks you are funny for sticking your tongue out or whatever it is you are doing. But it is nice when it's other people's kids and you can just send them on their way and continue your normal life. Something like that. This whole post is pointless, its just 2:30 AM and I felt the need to say something.



     







    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      So I think I'm finally happy with my new blog page, for the most part anyway. Now I need to move all the other blog pages over to this one...that will be a task. Anyway, I hope to have the changes made soon. 



     







    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      Yes, I'm still trying to find a Blogger that I like. This one lets people add comments, so I think I'll like it better.  -mf  



     







    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      So I downloaded a new CD today (legally thank you very much). I actually just was going to get 1 or 2 songs, but the more I sampled the rest, I wanted the whole CD. I must say, it's the best $10 I've spent in a very long time. The CD is The Beautiful Letdown by Switchfoot. I've been a Switchfoot listener for about a year, but after listening to this whole CD, I'm definately a fan now. I've already listened to it several times through today without skipping songs.  I will say, my favorite song on the CD, which I just heard today, is a song called "Twenty-four." If you get a chance to hear it, you should. If you want to see the lyrics (the best part of it) then go  urlLink here .



     







    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      Of course I do, why even bother to ask. Its my only pleasure in spending money at a coffee shop. If I'm going to get a grown-up drink (coffee or something like that, that is) of course I want whip cream so at least I can still feel like a kid and not a crazy Starbucks drinking Californian. But this blog isn't really about Starbucks. It's about whipped cream. More specifically, Cool-Whip. And a certain unnamed friend (see Blog below) and about half a dozen 13 year olds. I must say, if you've never had a cool-whip fight, or haven't had one for a while, you must try it. It's quiet amusing to see all this white poofy stuff go flying across the room and hit people smack in the face, even if it's you. It's even more amusing when you realize that it was probably the grown-ups that started it, but you can ask my friend about her fascination with throwing food (like whipped cream and green beans). What kind of role models are we?   I suppose it's only fair 



     







    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      Yes, two blogs in one day. I've had a busy and blog-worthy week, what can I say? Anyway, on to it. My crazy Starbucks loving friend is up to no good. Not only has she got her husband addcited to Starbucks now (which I find quiet amusing), but she's giving me cravings for it too. And she is feeding these cravings of Strawberries and Creme drinks. I think about it, and presto!, she's at my house or office with one. I think she's just tired of me picking on her, so now her goal in life is to convert everyone to be a crazy Starbucks drinking Californian. Right now she's 2 for 2 *sigh* 



     







    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      So, I guess I should tell you how wonderful the production of The Sound of Music was. It really was. It was at the Forest Theatre in Carmel, which is outdoors, and it was just awesome. The cast did a great job. The lady who played Maria did wonderful too. But (you knew this was coming, didn't you...) my only complaint is that she's no Julie Andrews...haha! Seriously though, she was a great singer, and who am I to criticize anyone's singing abilities, but what I mean is that she didn't have the gracefulness of Julie Andrews while singing. I mean, I obviously don't except her to be Julie Andrews (no, really, I don't). All I'm saying is that there is a difference. Some people are more graceful and flowing when they sing. And some people are just good singers. You need different styles for different times...the character of Maria just needs to be one of those graceful styles. And don't get me wrong, I've known a lot of good singers, and I've known a lot of graceful singers. I wouldn't say one is better than the other. The lady that played Maria was just a good singer. That's all I'm saying. And for all of you who would like to send me hate mail over my mere observations about something I know nothing about, please feel free to send it  here .



     







    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      4 states,  2 Buddy Holly planes, 2 sodas, 2 airlines, 12.5 hours, 1 failed engine, 1 special security screening, and 0 Starbucks...what a day!  It started with me knocking on my friend Sarah's window at 5:30am, praying that it wasn't one of her roomates' window. A quick trip to the Monterey Airport where I hit the long line of people waiting for their early Thursday morning flight. And of all those people, it was me, little ol' me, who is just trying to get to a funeral, that gets "specially selected" for extra security screening and informed I need to go straight to security (as if I had anywhere else to go when my flight leaves in 10 minutes). I still think that I was selected because of my "Pitch to Barry" San Francisco Giants shirt and was headed toward DogerLand. They must have figured I was on a suicide mission, either that, or my blond hair and blue eyes makes me totally look like a terrorist.  Arrive in L.A.--I barely remember this, except I was given the wrong departing gate, and only because I chose to find a seat away from people that happened to be facing away, did I realize that MY flight was boring across the way. Then, off to Denver...which I didn't realize I was going to, until I woke up, looked out the window and decided it was too brown to be Houston and then the flight attendant welcomed us to the "Mile High City." Talk about panic. Next time I'll listen when they do the  beginning announcements before going to sleep and read my flight agenda better. From there, it was off to Houston, which I was happy about. I like the Houston airport, even if it is named after one of them right-winged Republicans (haha!). I'm comfortable there, and of course, there is my all-time favorite, Chili's Margarita Bar. Except paying $8.50 for a margarita is NEVER going to happen again. It was more than my meal. No matter how good it may have been, totally not worth it.  Then we get to the fun part of the trip...one more buddy holly plane from Houston to Lake Charles (plane #4). We get on the plane and apparently the engine shut itself off. 20 minutes later, after mechanics whom I never saw, looked at the plane, we restarted it up, and took off. Talk about paranoid. You hear every little noise on those plane, especially when you are sitting in the very rear. Luckily it was only a 30 minute flight, so not too long to fear for your life I suppose. After that, I'm greeted by my step-siblings and off on an hour long drive to B.F.E., the Cajun version of it, alligators and all (if you don't know what B.F.E., I'll explain later). All and all, I made all my flights, arrived on time, and didn't have a plane crash or get hijacked. I got lots of compliments on my San Fran shirt AFTER I left L.A. (I got a few evil stares too, but I chose to ignore them).  Ready to do it all again on Tuesday! 



     







    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      Yeah, I say I'm not a big fan, but I have to admit, this summer I have been glued to my television for Last Comic Standing (and actually was glued to my TV for The Apprentice in the spring). I even stopped The Sound of Music last night so I could watch Last Comic. I think I like this even better than The Apprentice. In fact, I think now, I want to attempt a stand-up comic career (ok, not really, but what fun would that be!). But yeah, I have no reason for this post except to say I LOVE this show. It's the best show I've seen in a long time. In fact, I would choose to see an episode of that over Friends right now (pick up your jaws). So, yeah, if you haven't seen it, the Finals are next Tuesday and the result on Thursday...watch it.



     







    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      I realized tonight that I had lost something. I lost it and didn't even realize it until just now. I'm sitting here, waiting on midnight to roll around, and thought to myself  wow, I'd love to go for a drive . And granted, I do have my car back and ready to go and have had it for a few weeks now, maybe a month, but it's still in my driveway, waiting on stupid County Attorneys in stupid little counties in Kentucky to help me settle my little car problem (it's a long story, you don't wanna know). So being the good citizen that I am, I leave my car sitting in my driveway day after day, til I can legally drive it again.   Now, that may not seem like that big of deal to some of you people, at least I have a car you may say. But you have to understand something about me.   I love to drive . I always have. I've been known to get in my car and drive a few counties away, just because I was bored. One of my friends even wrote a poem about it. I can easily put over 100 miles on my car just joy riding in the country. All that being said, I realized tonight I haven't done that in a while. And when I say a while, I don't mean since my car was stolen and all the other stuff going on. I mean, in years. I seemed to have lost my thrill of driving. It was kind of a sad realization because driving, in the past, was my way to clear my head, to ease my mind, and to help me just not go completely insane. Maybe that explains why I've had a harder time over the past few years of controlling my "mental state." Maybe I've not been joy riding enough. At any rate, you can bet, as soon as this little problem is solved, driving is going to be my favorite pasttime again. I don't care how much the gas costs, its going to happen. Even if I have to give up little liberties like food to put gas in my car, it's got to be done. You have to do what you have to do. After all, my sanity depends on it.



     







    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      So, I went to the Farmer's Market last night. It's so strange, hundreds of people, wandering out on the streetlike that. I can only recall one time I went to a Farmer's Market (purposely) before I moved here. But it's so different back in Kentucky. They actually have vegetables and fruit and that's about it. Here, I probably spent $5 or so on stupid little bracelets and rings that I would have wore when I was 13. It's okay though, it was rather fun. I haven't been in a while actually. I also got to stop at one of my favorite places here in Monterey, The Britania Arms (aka, The Brit) and have some dinner. I don't know what it is about this place I like so much. The food and drinks are only average and generally overpriced. It gets kinda crowded sometimes. They do have that big screen TV, and Karokee on Wednesdays though. I think mostly, I just like the familiarity of it. I like going in, seeing the same waitresses still there that were working there when we would frequent the place every night just a few short months ago. It's almost like "Cheers" for me. Not really, but it's at least my one "go to" place on the peninsula. Yeah, not everyone knows my name, but they probably vaguely remember our faces. That's not the point. The point is, I like The Brit. I like the Brit, and I miss hanging out and doing things in general. 



     







    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>




	 



      Why is it, on the days that you just want to sleep in a little bit, it never happens? I went to bed at like midnight, kinda sad thinking of only the 6 hours and 45 minutes of sleep I was going to get after a very long weekend. But instead of getting every ounce of that time in, my body decides it wants up at like 5am or 5:30am, something like that. It's nuts. But I mean, there is only so long you can lay there in bed without getting up on mornings like this. Maybe my body just feels relieved Summer Camp is over and I won't have to see any kids until at least 2:30 this afternoon, maybe it knows all the stuff I have to do that I was honestly going to put off a few days and it's saying "wake up, wake up! you have too many things to do." I can't promise, but hopefully my will of wanting to relax will win over my body's natural reaction to want to bombard myself today. I also don't feel a bit guilty over that (okay, maybe just a little). In all honesty, I think that whole "Cycle of Vista Life" is starting to set in on me. I'm not sure what is supposed to be happening at the 5-6 month point, but I'm totally jumping on the "I work for less than minium wage and  you want me to do what? " bandwagon. Yeah yeah, I know, it's a good thought,  volunteering  for a year and all, serving my country, blah blah blah, and I'm really and truely one of the few Vista who can honestly say without cracking up that   I really like my job   and would venture to say that as far as Vista positions go, I got it made. I have a great position, I get to do fun things at work, and work with a great staff and supervisor. So yeah, for the most part, I come to work, ready to work because I love what I do and where I work. So what am I complaining for? I just want to sleep, thats all. That's all I've wanted since Day One in California. I want sleep until my alarm clock goes off on work days, I want to sleep past 10am on weekends. I'm tired of this getting up with the birds on the EAST COAST thing. Anyway, thats just how I feel this morning.



     







    
</post>


</Blog>