<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've had a couple of these dreams in the last few years, I'm not sure what they mean yet. Last night I dreamt that I was working in the California Department of Forestry again. The station was different. I worked at the Colfax station, but this one was not the Colfax station. One of my Captains was there, Miller was his name. He seems to be the predominant avatar from my CDF past in my dreams. The station was also suffering from my indoor/outdoor laws of dream-physics. Everything was indoors and outdoors at the same time. So there were huge redwoods that were also support columns for a room that had a roof but didn't.   So the dream consisted mostly of maintenace around the station this time. There were newbies that were just sitting around while we had some serious work cut out for us. I grabbed a broom and suggested that everyone start cleaning up before the brass walked in on us. Alpa was also a firefighter in my dream. She was a high achieving grad student at SFSU. Everyone was just ignoring my suggestion. Alpa agreed with me and grabbed a broom, then walked to another part of the station to clean. There were a couple of the newbies that were under my supervision. I ordered them to help me clean the apparatus bay and then went to the dining area to get more cleaning supplies. Alpa was in there just sitting. I was a little irritated and surprised, but I respected her so I didn't say anything.  The brass showed up. Among them a woman that I had worked for; an engineer. Her name escapes me but I know she's a batallion chief now. She didn't have very high ethical standards back then, was the 'claw-your-way to the top' kind of person. She walked over to me and grabbed my broom. Then she handed me another one and told me to get to work. As I went back to the apparatus bay I saw that everyone was just sitting around chatting with the brass (2 captains and one engineer). I started to try to sweep a thick layer of duff off the floor and my broom fell apart. The handle consisted of half of a 2x4 ripped down the center, and the broom head looked like an abused toothbrush. What little bristles were left were mangled and pushed out flat. I kept working but resented the fact that nobody was helping.
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in a junkyard, a really big one. I have two other friends living with me in this junk yard. It is laid out like the floorplan of a house, except that the walls are 20' tall chain-linked fences. My chores consist of doing laundry and taking care of these lego space men. If I find them in pieces I've got to put them back together and find missing parts to make them whole. Arms, heads, helmets. I clean them up, put them in working condition.   My two 'room-mates' are an older guy. A big guy who seems to own the property and run the junk-yard aspect, and another who at different times in the dream is either a man or a woman. s/he doesn't like that I get to take care of the lego-men and doesn't approve of my way of doing things in general, but we are generally cordial for the sake of the big-guy. I don't really understand why s/he feels that way, and want to try to find a way that we can work together better, have more mutual respect, but I'm not feeling upset about it. The big-guy and I really get along well, and respect one-another's path.  At one point the big-guy asks for our help. We drop what we are doing and follow him to help. With a wave of his arms, more chain link fences spring up on this adjacent property. It doubles the size of our junk yard. Interestingly, as the fences go up, they fill&nbsp;to the tops with more junk.   Walking back to my laundry/lego man tasks, I see a dog running up to me. She's pregnant. 'Hey doggy' I say with&nbsp;a playful tone, and with that she turns and playfully runs off to my left. She leaps over a barbed wire fence and gets caught in it. Then untangles herself and runs off. I feel responsible, as if I were a jinx of some sort.  Once again, there was a lot more to this dream. I think there were even other dreams, but this is&nbsp;all I can remember.&nbsp;&nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I got a better night's sleep last night. I know it takes more than one night to get caught up, but I feel a little better than yesterday.  My dream is not fully accessible. I remember that much of it was conversational, it didn't feel like it was frightening, but I have a vague memory that it involved 'processing' with another. Visually I remember being in a dark room at a light table with other people around the table. I had a test tray in front of me and took a scalpel to one of my fingers. I held my finger over each grid on the test tray and the blood very slowly dripped out. It almost seemed too slow, as if I was dehydrated.   [ I wonder if the metaphor was realted to thinking about camels during the day. Camels store their water in their digestive tract and when in need, they extract it from there. We store our water in our blood stream (limits on how much water we can store) and as we get dehydrated, our blood agglutinates until pretty soon we can't push the sludge through our body.]  So after filling each grid with a drop, I began to discuss the blood. It almost seemed as if I was giving a lecture, but talking about me. I moved the tray around the table so that different parts of light would shine through the drops of blood. I was looking for a change in the blood, different changes for each square in the grid. I think there was supposed to be different reactants in each grid. There were no visible changes.  There was much more to the dream that I can't remember. I wish I could. One part involved my driving something somewhere, another part that involved yet more conversation, but I'm not able to access it.  The part that I could remember (the light table lecture) might be seen as metaphor for this blog, but I think it is more related to having a conversation with someone yesterday which involved an attempt to access my feelings. It felt like an intervention from someone I hardly know. In my attempt to keep safe limits, to pull away from the emotions and discuss observations, the conversation seemed to go awry. She called me on my being too intellectual about what I was saying, but in a manner that was very aggressive. I felt like I knew that I was doing it, and in another space with another person I would access my feeligs more, but I'm private about my feelings.   The manifestation of this in my dream could be interpreted in various ways. It could be an illustration of &nbsp;my being too intellectual, or it could be that the 'blood' is my vulnerability. That I am dehydrated and need something to replenish my 'blood', yet I share it with others in order to understand it. Remember I too was 'testing' it, so I don't think I am fully decided on the right action. Maybe it means something completely different. 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      He died last year at the age of twenty. He didn't have the old-man zombie thing going until the last two years. Even then he'd be really happy to see me very affectionate. He'd just forget that he had just seen me 30 seconds ago and it hadn't actually been years since we'd seen one another. He was a large Abby/Tabby mix. Sort-of looked as if he wandered out of a wild-animal park with his puma composition. In his youth he also had quite a dog-like personality. Happy to play fetch, he came when we called, etc. Bob was cool.   In my dreams when Bob was there, he generally hung out and was a spectator for at least part of the dream. Watching me as I interacted with others or as I made decisions. Many times in the dream I would eventually have to defend him from other territorial cats. I would hang on to him, hide him in my jacket, or try to get him away from them. These cats would come from out of the dark and attack him as I held him.   I came to figure out that in my dreams, Bob either represented unconditional love or self-love. He either made me feel reassured, or recognized me as who I was. The times when he was attacked by other cats coincided with my dealing with those I loved deeply during some time of ego struggle or discord. It seemed to me that I was protecting myself when I was protecting Bob in my dreams. 
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...and yet I got 7 hours of sleep last night. I even saw Farenheit 911 last night. It was fraught with dream fodder like conspiracy theories, shocking images, and very emotionally charged moments. Nothing. Dang.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so the insomnia is getting to me. I didn't get to sleep until 3 AM, though through some fault of my own. Having little, restful sleep, I am not remembering the little things which make life so important...like keys. I left my keys in my mother's car and she drove one hundred miles away. I had to borrow another's car to get them back. Thus, 3AM bedtime.   Still, I often have small stints of more surreal dreams when I only get 2-3 hours sleep, and I'm not remembering much of any of them. I'm wondering if the reason is my processing them through this blog. So, I've also noticed that there have been more views of my profile than the number of people I have told of this blog. I should clarify for those who do not know me and are reading this stuff.  Dreams have most often been intense for me, intensely good or bad. It all depends on whether I am addressing stressful stuff in my waking life. As it is, I am not, so it manifests in my dreams. To clarify, I have just graduated and was recently engaged. My search for a job has not yet born fruit and it's been 6 weeks. I'm skimming the proverbial financial treetops, and time is ticking away with regard to my grace-period. Also, I am no longer engaged; not by choice. Nor am I now seeing this person, that was my choice. So I have gone from a very successful and rewarding academic life and personal life, to sudden deceleration.   As for the graphic nature of my dreams...well I can't fully explain why. I know that the boogey-man dreams stopped scaring me after the age of about 6. I just turned around and faced the boogey-man. That worked for a long time. In-fact, for the most part until I was about 21. From the age of 17-20 and on and off until now, I have had some experience with vehicular and other trauma. Mostly working as a firefighter and/or EMT, sometimes through happening upon an accident. The happenstance stuff is more common for me than for most.   I am quite aware of what happens to the human body when it suffers from various types of trauma, so this manifests in my dreams when I suffer this trauma. It may be that my brain is still trying to process this stuff. Maybe an unconscious empathy thing, though I do not feel traumatized by it consciously. So when my dreams get sketchy, they can either be the mental stress stuff like 'The Big Event' ( which BTW was benign in comparison to others that I have had) or graphic like 'Cats and Mice' though this too is not the worst. It may not have been so evident but 'Dream with Dan and Car' was a combination of the two and probably affected me more than I may have imparted in type.   As for me and who I am. I am oft seen as an optimist. I think I am more a philanthrope. I want good things and seek to make it happen myself. I've worked through hard stuff in my life and take my grandmother's advice. ("If this is the worst thing that happens to you in your whole life, you'll be lucky.") Very stoic Sicilian grandma, but had been through a lot. I try to be honest in who I am and what I do. FWIW.  So even though much of what you might read here may be interpreted as mirk, I am not seen as mirky by my friends. Maybe the dreams are like my Id Bilge and it pumps out at night. Maybe.
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got about 3.5 hours sleep last night altogether; waking up and taking a while to get back to sleep. I had several dreams that I can't recall except for enigmatic feelings and/or knowing intuitively that they involved family members, friends or representations therein. I know that none of these vignettes were nightmares; though they challenged me in some manner or another. I'll try to search my memory...no guarantees.
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was parousing the other Blog profiles just now and saw that someone put dogfighting in their interests. I think people who support dogfighting should be gathered together for a six month stint in a small room. Give them a daily dose of steroids, crack, methamphetamines, shock collars (with of course the occasional shock), and feed them nothing but grapenuts. Just a thought.
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just saw a post on Craig's List entitled 'Sleep is for the Damned' .....hmm.
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't get to sleep until about 4AM. I think the neighbors had their television volume set to eleven ; )  In the dream I'm in an apartment with my mother. She asks me to get something. I open a hatch in the ceiling, a small attic ladder folds down from the hatch and mice start flooding in like Tribbles. They're running around everywhere. 'Paula? What were you thinking?' says mom. 'I'll just let the cats in mom.' I open the sliding glass door and in come about 30 cats. Suddenly I'm holding a big pile of mice and the cats leap on me. 'Whoa, wait, the cat's are going to -kill- the mice...what was I thinking.' I thought to myself. For some reason I felt a need to protect the mice. The cats sink their razor sharp claws in to my flesh, trying to get the mice. The mice squirm and bite. I can feel and see the claws peircing through the skin in my hands, tearing it away.   I'll try to elaborate, as I wake up, if I remember any more.
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [This is more an explanation than a dream but for future information]   I have had a few common recurring metaphors in my dreams; one of them being spiders. They're always the hard, smooth exo-skeleton, fat abdomened type, like Black Widows or Garden Spiders. They are often lowering themselves down from ceilings, getting into my shirt, running up my pant-leg. Of course eventually biting me, envenoming me, etc.  I have found that the common denominator is that these little avatars of chaos pop up during a time that in my waking life I am worried about losing stability, or not having control of my own destiny. Something may be happening that is preventing me from keeping it all together.  Once, I was dreaming that I was at the Exploratorium, looking at the standard exhibits, like the photosensitive wall or the tornado generator. I noticed a side door open and a man sitting at a desk gestured for me to come in. I entered the room, it was dark and I couldn't see the ceiling. He gave me some sort of headset, which I eagerly put on with great curiosity. He said 'They can read your feelings.' 'Who?' I asked.'  'Shh' he pointed upward. I looked up and there were hundreds of these spiders with abdomens the size of hamsters. I gasped, my heart jumped. 'Oh no, don't do that. They can read that. Spiders are all predators y'know. You're in their territory.' I start to take off the headset. 'No! Not that, you'll frighten them.' At that point one of them lowered itself down into my shirt through my collar and began to run around inside my shirt. 'Um..' '-Sshh!' it started biting me. 'It's biting me...' He then began to ignore me and attend to his monitors. Then another spider and another until I began trying to crush them inside my shirt, missing. With each swat another spider would get disturbed above me. I don't remember the end of that dream.  I went through a period of nightmares involving spiders almost every night for months during a time of turmoil in my life and I became so phobic of spiders in my waking life that even fake spiders, knowing they were fake, would cause anxiety. I never really understood that nightmares could affect a person's waking life that heavily even well into the day. 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We were all getting ready for a big event. The guest was a VIP. All of our 'rooms' were divided up with fabric walls like that of the Samurai camps (think Christo's Running Fence, but rooms) and I had to share my space with someone else. All of my worldly possessions were in that space. It was set up in a park across from the venue. Performers were all running around in a panic, getting ready.  The organizers were not organized. They told me I had to prepare for the event. I asked them how. They wouldn't tell me. My family was also going to be there. So proud that I would be performing for the VIP. They were all in line, dressed in their best, craning their necks to get a glimpse of me preparing, hoping to give me a signal of approval...of pride.  Every time I looked away from my posessions to ask what to do, to look at my loved-ones, I would lose a little more space. The person sharing it with me had partitioned off a little more.   "I have to take a bath now. I have to get ready, but I don't know what I'm getting ready for. Can you please let me know?" "Just get ready, hurry, we're late." (space gets smaller)"What? I don't understand what do I need to do?" (smaller) "Wait I'll get back to you, but hurry up and get ready, everyone is waiting on you." (but they were all as unprepared as me.) "What am I preparing for?" "What clothes do I wear?" "What task do you want of me?" "Just do it, and don't screw it up, we're all counting on you."  (This went on and on and on.)  My space started out as about 5'X8' and now is about the size of a footlocker, the person sharing my space giving me an honest smile of support. I get into the tub to bathe, it's the only thing I know I must do.   The moment I get out, everything is gone, even the tub. I am naked and alone in the park. I look over to the line of people across the street at the venue. My loved ones still with looks of approval and pride in me. With them is an old boss; BJ. I ask him where all of my stuff was. "I loaded it up already, you don't need it now, you're on and everyone's waiting." "Jesus Christ! I've got nothing and you expect me do do whatever it is that nobody is telling me to do with nothing?!" "Well I didn't know..." he replied. "I was just doing what I thought you wanted me to do, and it's too late anyway." I scream, it shocks my loved ones, they're all uncomfortable with my outburst. They can't understand why I am overreacting. The dream ends.
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So Dan and I were out driving at night, I can't remember why. We stopped for gas. In the dream, we had to feed the hose through the back window and put the nossle in the dashboard. Dan was outside, I was inside. The moment I thought to myself 'Is the brake set?' the car began to roll backward. Dan just looked at me concerned. The car picked up speed and careened down a cravass. I was violently tossed around inside. I could feel my ribs breaking, the muscles in my neck tearing, the lumps on my head.   The torn hose was gushing out gas. When the car settled at the bottom, Dan came running up to me. I climbed out of the demolished car. "I'm sorry Dan." "It's okay..." he said "...but you better get out of here before they find you." I knew that fumble got me in trouble with the law. (Dream Logic) Every breath was seriously painful, I could feel my stomach becoming more and more rigid (internal bleeding), my neck getting stiffer, one of my eyes swelling shut. I was still soaked in gas. It was cold and dark, and I was stuck, run from the Law? Stay with my friend Dan and take responsibility for the car? Medical attention was out of the question because I had nothing to pay for it. How is that going to help Dan?
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So Wednesday morning my mother called me and told me that it was time to put my dog down. She was 15 and no longer completely with us. Morgan was her name, a blue merle australian shepherd. My first dog. We used to have a lot of fun together. morgan w also a very considerate, nurturing, and gentle dog. She would only enter a room if invited, we never taught her that, she just caught on that some rooms were territory, and she would wait at the threshold.  She lost her eyesight a few years ago and in the last year or two, her hearing. Still she was happy. In the last year she started to lose her mind. She spent some of her waking hours pacing around the house, bumping into walls and furniture with a loud thud, stumble and try to readjust. In the last few weeks it has been pretty much constant. Not a fun life to live. So my mother called me up to say "It's time." I gathered my thoughts and tried to tie up loose ends here before making the 120 mile trek to get back to my dog and be with her in her last moments.  When I got there I walked up to Morgan and put my hands in front her nose. She recognized me and began to wiggle with appreciation of my visit. Her fur was so soft, she blinked rapidly with affection and gave out a few subtle grunts as I scratched her neck and behind her ears. She pushed her head in to my lap.   I wondered at the time if it was really time, but it felt clear quickly that the moment of lucidity seemed right because she would know her loved ones in this moment rather than wondering who the strangers were that were around her.  Mom and I discussed her state of being. She mentioned that Morgan had pushed herself through the bannister on the stairs one day while mom was gone and had fallen on the television, table, and then floor. When mom came home she saw the evidence of Morgan's fall and after excaiming 'oh no...' Morgan I guess detected the tone with what little and lowered her head in guilt. Mom sat down and Morgan put her head in mom's lap and let out a few stressful sighs. mom worried what else could happen and was thankful that Morgan didn't snap any brittle bones.  ...more to come...
    
</post>


</Blog>