<Blog>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (Bellevue, WA)— "The only way that I could walk any reasonable distance at all was with a cane. I dreaded going into those big warehouse stores. It took forever to get to where I was going and it hurt the whole time," says Bellevue, WA resident, Roger Lewis Posey, who’s suffered from bursitis in both heels for more than 10 years. " I hated using those electric scooters that the stores offered because I knew that I might be using one when someone who needed it worse would be without. I could walk; it just hurt…a lot."  Millions of people like Roger suffer from chronic and debilitating pain in their feet, legs and back, even after years of trying everything from cortisone shots to surgery. His relief came after trying on a pair of funny-looking shoes with a large steel spring in the heel, called Z-CoiL® Pain Relief Footwear™.  "I am now walking much farther now without the pain that I previously endured. I also noticed that I‘m not suffering as much back pain as I did in the past with "normal" shoes," Roger says. "It’s hard to believe that something so simple would change my life so much. I now strongly urge anyone who suffers from foot or back pain to try these shoes."  This revolutionary line of shoes is now available at a store called Feel Good Footwear! located 13281 NE 20th in Bellevue. Open since April 5, dozens of Z-CoiL customers are already experiencing pain-reduction and increased mobility. On June 14, owner Dr. Timothy Young and store manager Jeremy Brock will be having the store’s official Grand Opening!  Specially engineered to alleviate foot, leg and back pain, Z-CoiL Footwear features a unique conical coil steel spring in the heel, which acts as a shock absorber, greatly reducing the impact to the body that typically causes pain and injury. This spring suspension system, combined with a rigid built-in orthotic support and extra forefoot cushioning, cradle the foot in comfort. People suffering from such conditions as plantar fasciitis, heel spurs, lower back pain, and arthritis, report either complete relief or a significant reduction in pain when wearing Z-CoiL Footwear.  Getting over the initial look of Z-CoiLs is well worth the pain-relief. "They looked a little strange to me. They felt strange too," Roger says. "What I mean by feeling "strange" is that they were so comfortable."  The first Z-CoiL® prototype was designed in 1989, when founder Al Gallegos embarked on a quest to build himself a better running shoe. He wanted to reduce the pain caused by years of impact from running. After seven years of designing, testing and patenting, Z-CoiL® Footwear officially opened its doors in January 1996. Since then, Z-CoiL® Footwear has achieved popularity with people in pain and the number of dealers across the country reached more than 220.  Many podiatrists and orthopedic specialists are starting to recognize the amazing results Z-CoiLs are bringing. Dr. Timothy Young of Bellevue began selling the footwear originally through his podiatry clinic because of their wonderful benefits.  "I found that Z-CoiL shoes are most effective for people who do a lot of standing or walking on hard surfaces, such as concrete slabs or a warehouse type of environment," Timothy says. "This could include virtually any position with a weight-bearing job function in health-care or retail."  This amazing line of footwear is available in Bellevue —only at Feel Good Footwear! For more information about Z-CoiLs go to the website at  urlLink www.feel-goodfootwear.com , or contact Jeremy at (425) 614-3668. For general information about the Z-CoiL company, call 800.268.6239 or visit the company’s website at  urlLink www.zcoil.com . 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>