<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've just lost a whole post because I tried to correct a spelling mistake. Arse.   The basic gist o it was this. I don't have high cholesterol or high blood pressure. This is a good thing™. This I know from my visit to the doctor this morning.   I'm probably&nbsp;clinically depressed. This I also know from my visit to the doctor this morning. Also arse. What a lovely month for it. I said that this wouldn't become my personal bile tanker, and that it won't. At least now I have a reason for not finding positive things to say. It explains a lot, like RocKWerchter and&nbsp;Ashton Court.   I haven’t had an awfully interesting week on the food front. Since its been low fat and low salt that sort of precludes tasty. Unless someone wants to correct me...   I've started running again after my 2 month layoff. Which, fundamentally, means I'm starting for almost scratch. I managed 2.5 miles in about 24 minutes a bit of a poor show but that’s quite a bit faster than I was running when I stopped. So that’s something positive.   Well I'll update this later this week when my iPod has arrived and/or I've been on my friend Shaun's stag do (bachelor party if your reading this across the pond (that’s the Atlantic ocean))   Now I think I'll lead you in song....   "Always look on the bright side of life........"   :-)   Tim.   P.S. Keep your pecker up sport, I haven't started listening to Nick Cave yet, it could be worse.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I went to the Ashton Court festival last weekend. I'd love to say that I really enjoyed it, but the best I can say is it was alright. Saturday and Sunday&nbsp;were both disappointing. Not because of the line-up, I was rather expecting some of the bands&nbsp;to be crap, but because the bands I did want to see weren't on top form ( urlLink 3ho'stwomexicansandatinofspanners ), or they didn't get a good crowd reaction ( urlLink The New Grand Smoking Palace ).&nbsp;  &nbsp;  Still I got to eat some dirty festival food. It was probably worth a tenner.&nbsp;  &nbsp;        &nbsp;  This is a picture of the crowd on the way up mount ashton :-)        This is a mentalist     Later,     Tim      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Its seems that I only have time to post very early in the morning, not an auspicious start.  I'll post a more thorough accounting of my actions on a later post.&nbsp;This is&nbsp;just a quick one to say I've just seen The Cooper Temple Clause at the Fleece&nbsp;on a warm up for their&nbsp;American tour.&nbsp;Suffice it to say, they ROCKED! It was they first gig I've been to without earplugs in ages, I left them in Bridgwater, and my ears are ringing like Big Ben. Buggeration.  I suggest that anyone who listens to a lot of live music get some. They are called ER20s you should be able to find them for about £12.  Beddybyes.  Tim 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is a big hello to anyone lucky enough to find themselves here, in my world. It’s not crazy, or mad, or particularly lively. It is however, mine and that’s enough for me.  &nbsp;  I’m hopping that I’ll keep this up dated, and I’m doubtlessly not the first to say that. I’m also that it won’t turn into another bad Bridget Jones’ Diary rip off, or a pit which I pour my bile into every day. That wouldn’t be very nice, there’s far too much of it.  &nbsp;  Mostly I’m hoping to put up chronicles of fun things I’ve done. Fun things you should do to. Like see bands live and cook, thought not at the same time. Obviously.  &nbsp;  And now Batman?  &nbsp;  To bed. I have along day ahead of me, its Bristol’s Ashton court festival, and I want to make it to the end and see Goldie Looking Chain. I think I’ll write a review.  &nbsp;  Tim
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I keep you hanging on with promises of a post.  I couldn't bring myself to write about the stag do. It was painful. Really painful.  My iPod arrived. It’s great and it’s worth every penny. I've used it so much already; I would suggest that everyone gets one.  There is a lot of news to post and I don't have time to do it now, I'm off to see the Bourne Supremacy curse my hectic life.  One thing can't wait. After a few false starts, I'd just like to say congratulations to my good friends Shaun Warren and Sarah May on their wedding yesterday.  Next time someone wants me to wear a suit in that weather I'll tell them where to stick it.  Tim  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>