<Blog>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Wee! Was due to hand in my group report before 530pm today. It was only the second lab and we needa churn out the whole software process report! Yucks! Hate all that writing, cutting, pasting and re-formatting. Cant understand why the lecturers have to torture us this way. Cant they just leave us some memorable memories of NTU before we leave. kekeke..    &nbsp;  The whole report turned out to be over 70 pages (Wah! amazing for just lab 2). As I went to hand it in, another guy from the other group came too. You should have seen his SHOCKED faced at our report. His is barely a 1/4 of ours! ahahha was so amused by his reaction when he compared the thickness and handed in reluctantly.    &nbsp;  No. I'm not gloating about his report being so thin, its just the expression that tickled me. Who knows if his group had more quality compared to ours. Nevertheless, he kinda made my day. At least it keep me amused for a while.    &nbsp;  Mind's abit in a daze mode now. Slept early this morning to wake up early this morning again. haahhaha...I'm losing my beauty sleep recently neh. No wonder pimples are proliferating on my face.. Anyway, my consolation is that I must be still young enough to have qing chun tou. hohoho...    &nbsp;  Making a point to sleep earlier than usual today. Need to rejuvenate myself after all that "busying" and rushing about in school. Nitez and Sweet dreams to me.....   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Decided to walk home from yishun station. Not a long journey really, just a 5 mins walk normally. I took 10.    Didnt know why I chose to re-route from my normal bus route, somehow I just felt like walking....    The way home was a long straight path flanked by trees. The air was humid and cars rushed past, lifting up swirls of dust in my face. I felt surprising calm and ignorant of the dusty air. I was alone, lost in my own world...    I enjoyed the slow walk. There were no obstacles in my way, just that straight road ahead... I walked slowly but steadily, only to stop at a traffic junction. Didnt know how long I stood there, but the red man seemed to stay there for ages, when the green man finally took over.    I was halfway home when I passed by the big field. I looked up at the canopy above me hoping that it'll rain leaves on me. There was not even a trickle to be seen. Without a trace of dissapointment, I continued my walk.    A big tree stood in the middle of the field. I seem to be like it, away from the crowd and alone. I somehow enjoyed this loneliness.    My mind was a blank. I felt peace and contentment.     It was until I crossed the second junction near to my neighbourhood that I started to retract from my isolation state and snapped back into reality. Started to feel the ache in my feet (I was wearing my new slippers) and back (Hahahaa I didnt exercise for a long while already). I was happy and light-hearted nevertheless.    I smiled at familiar faces as I went on, till my feet took me to my door step. The smell of home was ever so welcoming..     I shud take more walks home next time. That long road to home is beaconing me to set foot on it again. Wish to re-visit my world again.. =) Hm.. Wonder how I would feel to walk down that path on a rainy day? Perhaps I better prepare an umbrella for my next journey. =P    
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I'm so touched by wen. I sent her my life journal link. And she msn me back almost instantly to tell me that she's reading and playing the song as well......   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I love music alot. Since young, my life has revolved around music. From learning dance to singing and organ, all involves music.I must say that it is an integral part of my life already. Cant imagine a life without music....I start to appreciate that I have my ears to hear the melodious sounds around me.     &nbsp;   As I grew older, I found that I can have diff songs to represent me everyday.. Each song describes how I felt each day. I believe everyone has a song to represent him/herself. What is my song today...? I think its "Journey". This is the song I first thot of when I woke up this morning... Quite a funny song to start of the day as its kinda a slow and melodrama song. =P     &nbsp;   Well, I'm do feel a little slow and dazed today.. (Could be that I slept late this morning at 3 hohohoho).. Now, I'm starting to hum that song... It goes like this      START   Its a long long journey... Till I know where I'm supposed to be.    Its a long long journey... and I dun know if i can believe..    When shadows fall and block my eyes, I am almost lost and know that I must hide.    Its a long long journey.. Till I find way home to you.     &nbsp;   Many days I've spent, Drifting on through empty shores.    Wondering wat's my purpose, Wondering how to make me strong.    I know I will falter I know I will cry. I know you'll be standing by my side.    Its a long long journey, and I need u to be close to you.     &nbsp;   Sometimes it feels on one understand. I dun even know why I do the things I do.    When pride builds me up till I cant see my soul.    Will you break down these walls and pull me through?     &nbsp;   Cos it's a long long journey. Till I feel that I am wortth the price.    You paid for me on calvary. Beneath those stormy skies    When satan mocks and friends turn foes,    It feels like everything is out to make me lose control.    Cos its a long, long journey. Till I find my way home to you ~ to you....... &nbsp;  END &nbsp;   If you are following me through till the end of my song, I supposed u must have felt like this before dun you? Thanks for hearing it (or i should say reading the lyrics) with me.    Well, its really a nice song, if any of you wish to have it, please msn me. =)    
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Kekeke, I must say that I'm kinda hooked to this journal writing... (Just like I'm hooked to gunbound... =P).     &nbsp;  There are really alot of other stuffs to do, but somehow, my time management really suckz... Oh man, an organiser is of no help esp when its owner doesnt follow the planned tasks. hahahaha... Anyway, I still found some time to update my journal.     &nbsp;  Tomorrow is a free day (",) Yeah! Fyp is my constant nightmare.. Can imagine Mr Wolf (my fyp sup) shaking his head and wagging his index finger in my face... hahaha.. I'm keeping my fingers crossed now... Oh, btw, Mr Wolf really got nice eyes... Wish i had mine like his... *~~~So green with envy~~*   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Check out this link   urlLink  http://www.pathways-to-peace.com/   &nbsp;  Nice music, pictures and quotes to start off a not very interesting sunday.. kekeke its already noon time though.    &nbsp;  A close friend intro me to this site. I fell in love with it straight. Kinda nice to view the presentation when u feel bored or lost.. Well, I'm viewing it now as I write. Feel like jumping into those beautiful scenes neh..!!    &nbsp;  Some of my favourite quotes from this site:    &nbsp;  "Kindness is the language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see."- Mark Twain    &nbsp;  "Faith is the strength by which a shattered world shall emerge into the light."- Helen Keller    &nbsp;  "Hope is faith holding out its hand in the dark."- George Iles    &nbsp;  "We must come to see that peace is not merely a distant goal we seek, but it is a means by which we arrive at that goal. We must pursue peaceful ends through peaceful means."- Martin Luther King, Jr.    &nbsp;  and lastly this one:"I have found the paradox that if I love until it hurts, then there is no hurt, but only more love."- Mother Teresa    &nbsp;  *humming....* My sunday seems brighter already... =)   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       It seems like William Hung is fast getting recognition everywhere. Didnt like the way he potray himself until recently when I watched American Idol. I admit that the way he answers questions modestly do look kinda cute. hahahaha Even cheryl agrees on that doesnt she.     &nbsp;   Was writing a testimonal for my cousin in friendster. Can find traces of William's influence from it. ahhaha I wrote in my cousin's testimonial that He BANGS! It tickled my brother and the rest of them so much so that all of them started to add me into their friendster's list. Guess they want some Hung's "action" in their testimonials as well.     &nbsp;   Even my lecturer could not resist his charm. He's forever mentioning him and forever telling me to be hung's gal friend. AH... irritating man. I replied "Why not? But how am I supposed to break the news to Dave!" Hahaha Opps.. Dave.. Hope u are reading this!! =P     &nbsp;   So much so about Hung. There's something that I thought I should write down. I met up with cheryl last Sat at Causeway point just to talk and shop for a while, after which I took the mrt to my aunt's house for a family gathering. It was a nice surprise to see both my grandparents standing at the platform waiting for the same train.     &nbsp;   My grandparents are a cute pair. Why do I say so? Well, ever since the day I was born, they have already been squabbling all their life. It kept me wondering how they could live with each other for so long.     &nbsp;   I&nbsp;offered to help granddad hold his groceries. Given his stubborn nature, he kept insisting that it was alrite and so. Seeing these 2 old folks, some nice pple offered them seats. My stubborn as ever granddad sweetly declined once again to the kind gestures.     &nbsp;   While walking towards aunt's house, grandma kept complaining that granddad was so slow (Gram fell the week before. Hence, Granddad said that he would walk with her in case she falls again). Its kinda amusing cos we were really ahead of granddad by a good distance. While she kepting complaining, I kept trying hard not to smile cos beyond that sharp razor words, I could sense the underlying warmth as she spoke. I looked back at my granddad. He does walk real slow, but he looked so cute to me! Carrying 2 loads of grocery and dragging his foot, it dawned on me that grandma is so fortunate! Though she's always walking ahead, granddad will always be behind her, looking out for her and carrying her stuff.     &nbsp;   I think she knows that, but pride prevented her from acknowledging it verbally. =)    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       A group of frogs were traveling through the woods and two of them fell into a deep pit. All the other frogs gathered around the pit. When they saw how deep the pit was, they told the two frogs that they were as good as dead. The two frogs ignored the comments and tried to jump up out of the pit with all of their might. The other frogs kept telling them to stop, that they were as good as dead. Finally, one of the frogs took heed to what the other frogs were saying and gave up. He fell down and died.The other frog continued to jump as hard as he could. Once again, the crowd of frogs yelled at him to stop the pain and just die. He jumped even harder and finally made it out.When he got out, the other frogs said, "Did you not hear us?" The frog explained to them that he was deaf. He thought they were encouraging him the entire time.    &nbsp;  This story teaches two lessons:    &nbsp;  There is power of life and death in the tongue. An encouraging word to someone who is down can lift them up and help them make it through the day.     &nbsp;  A destructive word to someone who is down can be what it takes to kill them. Be careful of what you say.     &nbsp;  Speak life to those who cross your path. The power of words....it is sometimes hard to understand that an encouraging word can go such a long way. Anyone can speak words that tend to rob another of the spirit to continue in difficult times.Special is the individual who will take the time to encourage another.Be special to others.    &nbsp;  I'm not the kinda that gets angry easily I think, but there were times when I let anger get the better of me and said nasty things like those froggies above. I speak without giving it a thought and found my words hurtful. Remorseful I may be, but once the words are shot out, no amount of topic changing or nicer comments could alleviate the situation cos the harm has been inflicted. So sorry if it happen to any of u with my sharp words, I really mean no harm. Will learn to exercise some anger restraining techniques. ahahaha    &nbsp;  I&nbsp;must really salute those people who are slow in letting their anger take control over them. Before they could get upset or mad, their anger vanishes as fast as it came. Dun say that u dun believe cos I do have friends who are like that. Its a blessing to have met them. Must bai them as shi fu!! =P   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Just this afternoon, cheryl mentioned that we are neglecting our journals. hahaha I agree cos I'm really busy with the upcoming fyp report. Well, happpen to chance upon a nice poem online, I thot why not just share with all of ya. The title is "The Most Beautiful Flower"     &nbsp;   The park bench was deserted as I sat down to read    Beneath the weeping branches of an old willow tree,    Disillusioned by life with good reason to frown,    For the world was intent on dragging me down.     &nbsp;   And as if to ruin my rare quiet day,    A young boy approached me, all tired from play.    He stood right before me with his head tilted down    And said with excitement, "Look what I found!"     &nbsp;   In his hand was a flower, and what a pitiful sight,    With its petals all faded, from no rain or light.    Wanting him to take his dead flower and go play,    I faked a small smile and then shifted away.     &nbsp;   But instead of retreating he sat by my side    And sniffed at the flower and declared with surprise,    "It sure smells pretty and it's beautiful, too.    That's why I picked it; here, it's for you."     &nbsp;   The poor weed before me was dying or dead,    No bright vibrant colors, no yellow or red.    But I knew I must take it, or he might never leave.    So I reached out my hand and said, "Just what I need."     &nbsp;   But instead of him placing the flower in my hand,    He held it mid-air without reason or plan.    It was then that I noticed for the very first time    That weed-toting boy could not see, he was blind.     &nbsp;   I heard my voice quiver, tears shone like the sun    As I thanked him for picking the very best one.    "You're welcome," he smiled, and then ran off to play,    Unaware of the impact he'd had on my day.     &nbsp;   I sat there and wondered how he managed to see    A self-pitying woman beneath an old tree.    How did he know of my self-indulged plight?    Perhaps in his heart, he'd been blessed with true sight.     &nbsp;   Through the eyes of a blind child, at last I could see    The problem was not with the world, it was me.    And for all of those times I myself had been blind    I vowed to see beauty, and appreciate what's mine.     &nbsp;   I held that wilted flower up to my nose    And breathed in the fragrance of a beautiful rose,    And smiled as the boy, another weed in his hand,    Went to change the life of an unsuspecting old man.     &nbsp;   Nice! In case u wanna know where I got it from, check out this link :   urlLink  http://www.quickinspirations.com/poems.asp       
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Had an eventful day...! Had been at Young Musicians Auditorium since 4pm this afternoon till almost 10:30pm. Was kinda glad that Cheryl invited me to join her in her Hall's cultural nite.     &nbsp;  Both of us performed the song "有你真好" with Zeewei's accompliment (keyboardist). Despite many stage experiences, I still find myself nervous as the nite approached. hahahaha~~! Though during the song, there were glitches, it was still fun in the end. A little dissapointed to say that we did not do as well as during the rehearsals. haahhaha~~! Anyway, its over! Phew... Can finally heave a sigh of relieve.     &nbsp;  Now, its back to FYP FYP FYP ... (chanting..). God bless me! I've got another angmo lecturer as my final year examiner. Hope he is as kind as Wolfee..! Pray hard...   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       My friend just smsed me in the afternoon to bring happy news of a new addition into his family. I bet he must be beaming with pride now that he has rose up to the rank of a father.    Kinda heart warming and excited to receive the good news. Even Wenxin who was going home with me today could feel my excitement cos I was super chatty and grinning away along the way. ahahaha!    Today's also a nice and easy date to remember. 3/3 seems to be a lucky no in cantonese i think.    Hope the blessed child will grow up well, healthy and be like his father. =)    Congrats Weng! (If u see this entry of cos) I know u'll be a great father. =)   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Someone read my journal and told me tat I am dreaming too much a few days ago. Those words did not make must an impact until today.    &nbsp;  Sigh... Woke up this morning and realised that I really am dreaming too much...There are lotsa stuff awaiting me to touch them. Well, guess I shouldnt be running away from my responsibilities. Time for me to buck up and face all the undone work!    &nbsp;  Must learn to love all these tasks. ahahhaha   
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Gonna sleep soon, but before that thot of just updating my journal. Had a fruitful day slacking hahahaha....    My fyp progress is still as slow (crawling pace). I bet many people are either wrapping up their projects or starting on their report. Oh man.. I hope I'm not a goner! eeks wat a scary thought.    Writing in the wee hours of the morning is fast becoming my norm. In a terrible shape lately with large prominent eye bags and droopy eyes. hahaha Hope I dun scare anyone when school re-opens!    The one week March holidays have just started, kinda envy those who are enjoying themselves while I bury myself in my project and school work. Hump! Will bao(4) chou(2) when I graduate man. haahhaha... Will play very hard then... If I can!    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
        The Mysterious thing called "LOVE"....   If you find yourself in love with someone who does not love you, be gentle with yourself.There is nothing wrong with you. Love just didn't choose to rest in the other person's heart.    &nbsp;  If you find someone else in love with you and you don't love him/her, feel honored that love came and called at your door, but gently refuse the gift you cannot return.Do not take advantage,do not cause pain.    &nbsp;  How you deal with love is how you deal with you, and all our hearts feel the same pains and joys,even if our lives and ways are different.    &nbsp;  If you fall in love with another, and he/she falls in love with you, and then love chooses to leave,do not try to reclaim it or to assess blame, let it go.There is a reason and there is a meaning.You will know in time.    &nbsp;  Remember that you don't choose love. Love chooses you. All you can really do is accept it for all its mystery when it comes into your life. Feel the way it fills you to overflowing, then reach out and give it away.    &nbsp;  Give it back to the person who brought it alive in you.Give it to others who deem it poor in spirit. Give it to the world around you in anyway you can.There is where many lovers go wrong. Having been so long without love, they understand love only as a need. They see their hearts as empty places that will be filled by love, and they begin to look at love as something that flows to them rather than from them.    &nbsp;  The first blush of new love is filled to overflowing, but as their love cools, they revert to seeing their love as need. They cease to be someone who generates love and instead become someonewho seeks love.    &nbsp;  They forget that the secret of love is that it is a gift, and that it can be made to grow only by giving it away.   Remember this, and keep it to your heart. Love has its own time, its own seasons, and its own reason for coming and going. You cannot bribe it or coerce it, or reason it into staying.You can only embrace it when it arrives and give it away when it comes to you.But if it chooses to leave from your heart or from the heart of your lover, there is nothing you can do and there is nothing you should do.    &nbsp;  Love always has been and always will be a mystery.Be glad that it came to live for a moment in your life.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Went to check out this website   urlLink  http://www.myhome.com.sg/homeimprovement/interior_design/personality_finder/personality_finder.shtml    that helps individuals look for an ideal home. Well my results are:     &nbsp;   You are an Artisan-Adventurer     &nbsp;   Famous Artisan-Adventurers: Elvis Presley, Madonna, Ernest Hemingway, Clint Eastwood, Winston Churchill,     &nbsp;   You are spontaneous, and a genius at thinking on your feet. You are daring and confident of yourself; and happiest when expressing yourself in some form of artistic or athletic endeavour.     &nbsp;   You are extremely “in touch” with the physical world.     &nbsp;   The design style which suits you best is the Contemporary look. You are knowledgeable about culture and do not like to be led by any one particular trend.     &nbsp;   Therefore, you are comfortable in a home with other influences, like Mediterranean, or Classical.Your look is modern, yet not stark or cold. You enjoy seeing clean lines in furniture but do not mind a mix of styles in accessories or furnishings.     &nbsp;   The part of the analysis about me being the happiest when expressing myself in some form of artistic endeavour is so true!! It reminded me of how accomplished I felt after every performance I engaged in last time. The applause from the audience made every effort put in worthwhile. Especially when I danced with my friends last time on stage, I can get lost in my own world. I'm quite a natural stage fright kinda person, but when it comes to dance, I'm usually comfortable during every performance.     &nbsp;   Erm.. Talking about dance, I'm getting a bit out of form lately. Hopefully after graduation, I'll have time to continue my dance lessons at the Singapore Dance Theatre! =P     
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       This day finally came. I awoke with anticipation early in the morn. Despite my fitful sleep last nite, I'm fully sane and excited about the upcoming results. Without even washing up, I headed for the pc expecting the results to be posted. Nah! I was disappointed. Its still in hiding.....     &nbsp;   I wonder wat's wrong since our results normally come out a day in advance. I was already disappointed the whole of yesterday. ahahahaha     &nbsp;   Well, the results finally showed itself in the later half of the day after much speculations and msn msging.    Was alittle surprised by my final year project result. I've actually got an A??? Wow how unexpected and surprising.    And the fact that I've got second uppers hons. Wee... Life cannot be any better!     &nbsp;   I've expected myself to get second lower so this was a pleasant surprise for me. My 4th year results were quite good. No Cs or Ds, just As and Bs. I've done well for my law paper and my software testing module. They were more or less expected. Got Bs for Imaging and Mobile communications. Interesting subs but i failed to score on them. Guess that's the&nbsp;dilema in wanting to score well or studying something you are interested in for many of us.     &nbsp;   Anyway, I'm glad to have done well and this calls for a celebration of cuz! Tata     &nbsp;    &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Innocence&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    My sleeping quaters&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        My Adventure Begins....      &nbsp;   During the Jun holiday period, I left for Cambodia for almost a month. I was there to do some voluntary work at a little village called Prey Klar.     &nbsp;    Day 1: 15/06/2004      &nbsp;   Eveything started off smoothly. Though there were glitches here and there, everyone's mood were rather high and filled with anticipation at Changi Airport. The flight to Phnom Penh (Capital of Cambodia) took only 2 hours.     At Phnom Penh International Airport, everything was a hustle. The custom queues were short but the wait so damn long. Everything seem to just slow down significantly. By then, I couldnt wait to go to the hotel!    Asia Hotel was our destination for the night. After going through the gates, we expected a big bus to be shuttling us to the hotel. Was a little surprise&nbsp;to see 3 small tiny&nbsp;vans waiting. Had a hard time trying to get everyone's backpack into a single van. We had so much luggage. So much that the van was over packed and some of the cargos had to&nbsp;be placed on top of the van. Was quite a funny sight actually.    When we finally arrived at the hotel, it was way pass our schedule.&nbsp;One good thing was the hotel wasnt as bad as expected as&nbsp;there was&nbsp;at least hot water. Phew!    Slept with Elizabeth and Regina that night.      Toul Sleng Museum    urlLink        Lei, Me and Fang&nbsp;  urlLink        &nbsp;  This is a shot of me, Qinglei and Huifang just outside Toul Sleng museum, Cambodia's most famous museum.  Quite a sad place actually. We see pictures of people being tortured and the terrible conditions they were subjected to, cant help but feel sad and heavy.    urlLink     Torture room&nbsp; urlLink           
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Angel wings&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hahaha my title looks alittle disillusioned, but hell no..! I'm kinda enjoying life now that I'm free and able to slack around.   Well, I did try to put in some effort in looking for a job but guess the sense of urgency is still not there. Was hoping wolf would give me an answer today on whether the job offer can be finalised.   Great his door was shut, an indication that he's away. Well 劉貝(liu2 bei4) had to knock on zhui1 ge3 liang4's door 3 times. I hope I dun have to 步 his 後塵 (bu4 hou4 chen2) hahahaha.   Well went to san ba with meehae instead. Talked mostly on my Cambodia trip and her new collection of jeans.   Wanted to find Sourav to chit chat, but the poor man was so busy to meet his cute student. hahaha Will try to catch him the next time I fly down to NTU.   I ended up in Sub Dean's office after seeing his clock face on the door indicating that he's in. It reminds me of Harry Potter's Ron's family clock.  He was entertaining someone else when I entered. Had to excused myself and station outside.   It wasnt a long wait till i get to see him. He was very fast in knowing my motive there. hahaha He said "無事不登三寶殿 (wu2 shi4 bu4 deng1 san1 bao3 dian4), na" and passed me the vcd of NTU's 20th anniversary concert. Hehehe so smart! Well, I stayed in his office for a while and san ba. Told me to address him by KC, (something that we called him by when we were working on the 20th anniversary concert). I did went into a little dilema that time cos I dunno whether to address him Prof Yow or KC. hahaha Now that he said it himself, I'm not going to 客氣 (ke4 qi4).   I told him if I 無事 also 登三寶殿 then he'll get headache cos I'll be looking for him to chat everytime till he gets sick of me. hahaha   Poor sub dean... He has to face pple's complaints as well as pple kneeling outside his door. That poor guy who knelt flung too many subjects and was fated to be footed out of SCE came to find KC for help. Guess KC was also in a dilema man...! lolz     
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Finally I will get to wear my convocation gown on this supposedly special day for all the graduates. It was a mad rush to school today since we had to be seated by 140pm. The rest were telling me that they'll be in school by 2pm.     &nbsp;   Thanks to sp who informed me that we have to register by 130pm or miss our ceremony.&nbsp; I turned out to be the earliest one in my grp.     &nbsp;   I arrived to see many happy and elated faces from the earlier ceremony batch. Dunno wat school they were from but I suddenly picked out one face among the vast sea of mortar hats. Oh man...! MRS LEONG!!! That must be her son with her in his gown.. Being the nice person I am hahaha I went up front to greet&nbsp;as well as congratulate her. She was just as surprise to see me there. Didnt stayed very long, I excused myself to the gown robing room.     &nbsp;   Expected to see someone in the room helping us robe, but I realised it was just a room for us to change. Wat a nice name ha. Thank goodness Ailing arrived hence I had help pining my gown. Her friends and relatives were fusing around her adjusting this and tat. It was funny but nevertheless an envious scene too. There I was alone trying to HELP myself into my robe while others had pple to fuse over them. STOP! Thats it, I am an independant gal. Get that into your head gal! lolz     &nbsp;   Well I got nicely into my gown and went to stationed myself at the stairs in case my friends arrive. I half expected David to march in any moment but he turned out to be the last of the lot. Damnit! Made me worried for him. Nevertheless, we were all in time for the ceremony registration at 130pm. Great! I was alot more patient and less anxious waiting for them hahaha It could be my Cambodia training. I was so used to everything being slow over there.     &nbsp;   The ceremony was boring.... Not that spectacular like I've always imagine. But still its MY ceremony. I tried to look excited and awake hahaha since I was in the front second row. The lecturers could jolly well see me. Could see the diverse emotions on those on the stage. Some lecturers were beaming at us while some just simply looked like they would like to leave the stage.     &nbsp;   Got a pict with Dr Yow (Sub dean) in his nice nice gown. Wonder which uni he was from. Glad that he still remember me and my name. He even told me that he has our 20th anniversary tape in his office and I could always pick it up as I like. Yipee!!! Sub dean so nice......... lolz     &nbsp;  &nbsp;         
     
    
</post>


</Blog>