<Blog>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sam and laura&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hildas 6th form formal&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      faye & jen @ hildas 6th formal&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sam and laura at hildas 6th formal&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i had to put this on cos its fuckin funny&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      formal&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me grem and ginga 5th form camp&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      phoebe grant dane jane and ?? @ kings formal last year&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      kate me and jane at formal last year&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dane sent me this i think&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is funny too...&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Funny carrot... i just had to put this on! lol&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me chillin @ cricket in Q'town&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Queens chicks Hayley and Rachel&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      emma kean and her ex (i think)&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      andrew grant and me before st hildas 5th form formal 2003&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me and buzz aldrin (2nd man on moon) warbird 2004&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      columba 5th formal 2004&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      st hildas 5 form formal 2003&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>


<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      lol..........&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eric me and my corres demi or julien chez moi&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the mountain-top town of meudon&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      veryemabarrasing foto of me and kat a la place&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nat & Andrew at Pizzeria in Cannes. We wnt here for lunch during our first day in Cannes while the stupid frenchies went of to maccas...&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      voila... mon drapeau francais... sorry but the picture not very good&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this foto has nothing to do with france but its funny anyway...&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me and flo&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me and gemma on the beach at cannes... very romantic lol&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me and my "pink lady" charlie at the cafette at the civ. &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is a very sexual pic of anna. lol if u dont like it tell me and i will take it off. i think it very sexy though... ; )&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      flo dressed up as a post box for the carnavla last year...&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is a pic of my very good russian friend, yulya. u r a legend et je t'aime bcoup!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is a photo of me passed out in a broom cupboard on new years eve lol&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is my mate emma kean. she didnt actually go to france but i put a photo of her on anyway cos i love her! lol r u happy now?&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me and snowman thingy at xmas village&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      flo, the up and coming jimi hendrix. flo u r awesome and me love you! lol&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me and gemma... gemma u asked for it lol&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      view of yaughts at cannes&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      monte carlo city, monaco&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      negresco htel in nice at night&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      jenny andrew and veronica a la place&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      me and laetitia going for another beer at the bistro after enjoying our monday afternoon vodka!!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      laetitia after enjoying her cheap afternoon vodka...&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      laetitia enjoying her cheap afternoon vodka&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      laetitia me and caro on our last drinking day au ferme&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Veronika Vaugn, u r a legend... haha&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      april and a intoxicated looking me at the queens pub in cannes&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tristan and me outside the carlton, cannes' most expensive hotel&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nat and a dutch chick that i cant remember the name of, at the beach in Cannes (if anyone knows her name email me..&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      helen me and cockie in the caffette at the civ&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ice skating at the xmas village in nice on xmas eve&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Laetitia, me and caro after a spot of drinking on a monday afternoon au ferme. and no we are not alcohloics!!&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me and Caro outside le petit café a la place. Good times&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunset in Nice&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this foto was taken at the palais du festivals in cannes. we were travelling round like tourists in a big group of people from the civ who are from all over the world..&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this is laura and me (outside the pub on my 16th i think..) very sexual foto of us... lol&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>