<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           I'm pretty pissed about two things now, so let me start. first. this is addressed to  all ssc graduates. MAMANSIN NAMAN KAYO!!! KALA NYO KUNG SINO KAYO!!!! ANAK**&$!!!!! tayo na nga lang magkakasama sa walang kwentang skul na to kala nyo kung sino kayo. yung mga iba naman namamansin sila at nakikipagkuwentuhan pero yung iba nakakaloko na. parang gusto ko silang hagisan ng mga silya. E=mc2.      Second. "...: gaya gaya naman talaga itong tag board na ito eh.. ive seen this site before... wala naman.. mr pocholo henson.. ive seen your site.. and it looks exactly like this... yeah.. only blue.. yeah" "plaigarism? holy crap... your blog looks like mine! only, it's blue!...that says a lot about you..."  GAGO. ooohhh.... my site has a tagboard... cool... has a graphic of the week too... awesome dude... give me a freaking break. what's next, "cadaver of the week?" DumbASS.  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
            Just finished watching "Big Fish", a film by Tim Burton... very good, highly  recommended... also saw jackass the movie... no comment. Can't believe this.... i'm actually spending all my prepaid internet time on this blog... Question... required ba sa mga IT at MassComm students sa AUF na magsuot ng make-up na parang si minney mouse at ng mga skirt na kakasya lang sa isang 9-month old na baby? Halos nanlalaki ang mga mata ng mga male species kapag uupo ang mga babae sa mga bench sa quad a... o quad b? di ko alam... o kaya sa pag-akyat nila sa mataas na mga hagdan sa library? o pag nag-tricycle sila papunta sa au? how do i know all these things? courtesy of a classmate na nag-enroll sa auf para lang makaboso. (name ommitted for protection) hahaha.... not really true. sheeeeiit. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Forget the thing about the damn revamp. sheeit. napakawalang kwenta ng auf. ung section  namin walang unity, maraming sipsip, backstabbers, plastik(pareho lang ba yun?) at napaka INGAY. dammit. parang isang litrong kape ang iniinom nila araw-araw. may teacher na eh sige pa pagbubuladas ng walang kakwenta-kwentang bagay. isa pa- may mga makakapal ang mukha na nag-aastang lider. mga sasa kayong lahat. tangna, kaya nga walang unity eh! pangalawa! napakaliit na bagay, pinapalaki!! ano ba yan? mukhang mga retard sila na kailangan pang palakihin ang usapan para maintindihan ng mga kukote nila. I can almost imagine myself sa ust, taking up journalism, major in social climbing. o kaya naman sa up, taking up psycho... buti pa dun, sa tingin ko, dun ako babagay. IM A PSYCHO STUDENT!!! hahaha.... seriously, i admire psych students, mga iskolar ng bayan, for that matter. i can almost imagine myself sitting beside t.. that didn't come out right.... chatting w/ people who share my interests- books, politics, people who have understandable opinion. di tulad sa puro video games at porn cd's ang pinag-uusapan. for your hate mail, send all death threats to choii214@yahoo.com. add nyo rin ako sa friendster kung gusto nyo... :-)  
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For the gifted few of you members of the human race, who care about american imperialism, i recommend you watch fahrenheit 9/11 by michael moore. Good film.. Currently showing at all pirated CD stalls in Angeles. Near Jollibee, to be specific. While youre at it, send me a porn CD. Be discreet. :-)   Oh yeah, fuck you Ely Buendia for leaving Eraserheads the greatest band ever formed. goddamn you to hell. Hmmm.... Itsumo = STUPID. Nakaboso na naman ako kanina. Yey....  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
             
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       bakit ang daming magagandang babae sa u.p.? sa au maganda nga, puro panlalalake at make-up naman pinag-uusapan. paksyet. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       will revamp blog soon, too lazy.................. daming units ng mga bsn students... do they want us to die before we earn thousands of dollllllllllaaaaaaaaaaaaaaarrrrrrrrrrrrssssssssss!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       there's so much hype over that person. even his kids now have educational plans. para pa nga balatuan nya yung mga nang-hostage  sa kanya. dammit.   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           who will win? hope kerry does, bush is an asshole.   
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       paksyet. nakakapagod..........   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
              Sa wakas. may blog na. tenkyu karl sampang    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         You Won't Like Me When I'm Angry. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Go Team Philippines! (flashes sarcastic smile.)     
    
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       At the end of the first part, the tribe of dipshits residing in room 315 died, were killed by the infamous Mr. Pocholo Henson. Unfortunately, their cadavers absorbed liquid nitrogen reacting with plutonium. So they roamed the fucking room.              Part 2.  Anthropology. So there was this project. It was like a magazine. Logically, every magazine has its editor. I being the genius that I am, was appointed one of the five editors.        The class was divided into five, for the five magazines.         For the meantime, there was peace and harmony.  Then, some DIPSHITS changed the freaking groupings. the deal was, rearrangements were approved, provided that the editor approved..         Since I had no fucking idea what the hell was happening, it means that I did not approve.  I complained, got angry, cursed, destroyed a chair, (the usual ranting) tapos, ako pa ngayon ang masama. Eh mga gago pala kayo eh! Kahit na binigay nyo saken mga bobong mga ka-group i don't GIVE A FLYING FUCK! Just ask for my consent Dipshits!! is that too hard to understand!!        Dipshit is the theme for this blog, so leave now if you don't want profanity, because there's more to come.         There's gonna be some serious ass-kicking.         (insert part 3 here)               
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
            Ever noticed the camera phone, music phone, n-gage, phone bomb, nuclear phone, etc? What the hell? Nokia and Others are capitalizing on the sheer stupidity of  Filipinos. A cellphone will always be a cellphone. that is, to CALL people. However, because Filipinos are naturally DUMB, (remember the water-powered car by Daniel Dingel which could have ended our dependency on oil but the fucking government lacked the political will?) these gadgets are happily consumed by the populace, mainly the social climbers and techno-geeks. Though i don't see a camera phone as an evil invention, using this phone to capture nude pics of female species isn't very morally gratifying. Just buy a 3310 and a camera!  Much, much cheaper.  75 million Filipinos think that Nokia Phones are cool. (Stole this idea from www.maddox.xmission.com since I am a plagiaristic bastard)  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
                 Dipshits. I hate you all. except for some handpicked people, i hate you all. kala nyo kung sino kayo.          1. Classmate1: POCHOLO? ano bang pangalan yan?  fuck you. paayos mo itsura mo.       2. Classmate2: Grade Conscious!  gago. mukha kang manika. go back to the preschool where you came from. baka ma-devirginize ka ng mga  dipshit na  lalake. Mukha kang teacher's pet.       3. poch:  f u all. ANG INGAY NYO!!! DIPSHITS!!         4 .  here is the story of bsn 1-2:             [insert poch w/ swiss army knife]  stab! stab! stab! mwahaha!!!!! (releases machine gun and kills all bastards in the room) oh! the grade conscious one! you look so good w/ your brains splattered against the wall!!! oh! here's the stupid one/forty-five! now you're brains out! hahaha! oh shit! now i know blood looks like red wine! only red! oh! the bitches! mwahaha!!! oi yung mga plastik! karne na sila ngayon!!!! hahaha!!! (throws up and kills the damn lazy filipino teacher then reloads... yes, di pa tapos.) pray for mercy from... nevermind! wahaha!!! (beheads the remaining people covered with blood). Dipshits. yes, to be continued. mabubuhay pa sila. Unfortunately.    
    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
                 I've been thinking about a few ideas to publish, and i came up with some, so here i go:           1. prelims- over. here are my grades:               Cultural Anthropology -92               English- 91               Christian Formation- teacher too pregnant.               Chem- teacher too busy.               Filipino- teacher too lazy, retarded, whatever.               College Algebra- ?               PE- no comment.               Psych- NO COMMENT.                            that's nice first-rate education.         2.  girls and cars: an objective analysis.   girls                                                   cars                     presents/gifts                   that usually means a huge speaker with huge subwoofers                                                              that costs your allowance for 5 years                      hatid-sundo                          full tank- refill                      posessive                           "hands off tha hood pal."                    "You're too fat"                              oil change.            empty backside, flat-chested    "shit! na-flat ang gulong!!!"   " you don't see me enough anymore!"              "call insurance."                     Bling-bling                                                       19-inch silver rims        "you deserve someone better"    BMW 386i 2.0 L 2004 model, X-Chassis w/ missile launchers.                "I think we need some time off"                             "sell your stinking car, man"            "Please, I'm not ready yet...."                              "You REALLY need to sell that car!!!"              3. Henson-Sampang para Malacanang.. Giving you your everyday dose of social injustice since 1987.             "Our fifth agenda on this campaign is 'putting education first'."        4. I still love you Khaye Manialung. please break up with your boyfriend. i BEG of you. ( i'm going to write about that)        5. I HATE POP STARS. nuff said.        6. Still thinking.        7.  Still waiting for a death threat.        8. Still waiting to get a girlfriend.        9. Still waiting to get laid.        10. Still waiting to die. I hate Dipshits. Like You.    
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
            haha....     
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       www.maddox.xmission.com.... mad... really mad.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1. eraserheads 2. rivermaya 3. rizal underground 4. siakol 5. parokya ni edgar 6. yung kumanta ng santong kabayo.  *salbakuta, slapshock and dice & k9 were excluded because they had "dipshits" written all over them.   p.s. - para akong nagpepenitensya kapag umaakyat ng lib. 28.8 kbps internet? give me a fucking break. 31,000/sem?   
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1. NAME? >> Poch  2. SINGLE OR ATTACHED? >> Single  3. ARE YOU IN LOVE? >> no.  4. DOES SOMEONE HAVE A CRUSH ON  YOU? >> definitely not.  5. HAVE YOU EVER BEEN HEARTBROKEN? >> constantly.  6. HOW MANY EX(ES)? >> 000,000  7. HOW LONG WAS YOUR LONGEST RELATIONSHIP? >> 16 nanoseconds  8. HOW SHORT WAS UR SHORTEST RELATIONSHIP? >> uhm... 2 nanoseconds?  9. HAVE YOU CHEATED ON SOMEONE BEFORE? >> only in quizzes and exams.  10. HAVE YOU BEEN CHEATED / TWO- TIMED ON BEFORE? >> no.  11. IF YOU ARE SINGLE, DO YOU WANT TO FALL IN LOVE AND GET ATTACHED? >> no. but if she's rich, no.  12. IF YOU ARE ATTACHED, DO YOU LOVE YOUR GIRLFRIEND / BOYFRIEND? >> maybe, dumbass.  13. HAVE YOU EVER PLAYED WITH SOMEONE`S FEELINGS? >> too tiresome to play. sleep only.  14. HAVE YOU EVER BEEN FORCED/DARED TO GO WITH SOMEONE? >> i force myslelf  constantly, but no.  15. HAVE YOU CRIED OVER SOMEONE YOU THOUGHT YOU LOVED/LIKED? >> 366 and 2 nanoseconds days a year.  16. HUGS OR KISSES? >> text messages  17. DO YOU THINK IT IS ALRIGHT FOR PEOPLE OF THE SAME SEX TO LOVE EACH OTHER? >> yes.  18. HAS ANYONE EVER TOLD YOU THAT  YOU WERE 2 YOUNG FOR LOVE? >> no..  19. WHAT DO YOU THINK OF LONG  DISTANCE RELATIONSHIPS? >> no time for play. get it?  20. WOULD YOU EVER GO WITH SOMEONE OVERSEAS? >> if she pays the tickets, yes.  21. HAVE YOU THOUGHT YOU LOVED SOMEONE BUT THE FEELING WENT AWAY AFTER A FEW DAYS? >> i takes 4 years.  22. DO LOOKS MATTER TO YOU? >> yes.  23. WHAT IS THE MOST IMPORTANT THING  IN A RELATIONSHIP? >> money and cars, based on personal experience.  24. FOR GIRLS: HOW DO YOU FEEL IF  YOUR BOYFRIEND IS YOUNGER THAN YOU? >> im going to ignore this.  FOR GUYS: HOW DO YOU FEEL IF YOUR GIRLFRIEND IS OLDER THAN YOU? >> kaya mo ba to?  25. FOR GIRLS: HOW DO YOU FEEL IF  YOUR BOYFRIEND IS SHORTER THAN YOU? >>ignore.  26. for GUYS: HOW DO YOU FEEL IF YOUR GIRLFRIEND IS TALLER THAN YOU? >> ashamed, suicidal.  26. DO YOU TELL YOUR CRUSHES YOU  LIKE HIM / HER? >> no, but, no.  27. ARE YOU ROMANTIC? >> ............  28. WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ONE NIGHT STANDS? >> it's a bastardized version of love at first sight.  29. WHAT DO YOU THINK OF COUPLES  WHO BREAK UP AND PATCH BACK AFTER A FEW DAYS? >>shit. fuck them.  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Damn them. Ngayon lang ako nakakita ng trabaho na nagpapakita ng kanilang boobs para kumita. Nagpaparetoke pa sila, parang di pa sapat ang Cup Z nilang duyan. Kaya nga dumarami ang rape cases diyan eh! I'm hope i'm not offending anybody, its just that kahit sinong matinong tao ay alam ang kagaguhan na ginagawa nila. Wala man silang katalent-talent eh binibigyan ng breaks, mas deserving pa sa kanila ang mga underground bands.(no rappers please) Then there's the damn novelty song craze. Fuck it! Sinasamantala nila ang pagiging tanga ng mga Pilipino. Ginagaya pa nila ang pananamit ng mga sexbomb dipshits. ang bata-bata pa lang e mukha nang nilaspag ng singkwentang hapon.(no malice intended) Putchang Lito Camo. FU2hELL.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
            Eraserheads.... I think i missed half of my life because I didn't get to know their  songs till i was in high school. NO, I'M NOT TALKING ABOUT LOVE ON THIS BLOG. too boring for the average people's intellects. now i'm going to rank their best songs according to depressing content..... 1 = highest          9 = lowest  1. Ang Huling El Bimbo 2. Pare Ko 3. Magasin 4  Torpedo 5. Julie Tearjerky 6. Harana 7. Toyang 8. Tindahan Ni Aling Nena   9. Alapaap       This is my opinion so i don't care if you think that Toyang is not depressing. why is it that i don't talk about love, well, there was this girl......  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>