<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hello my visitors. I knew you would come. Oh I see, you ask how. Silly, look at the title of this article. Ah yes, if you were gifted with "other-worldly" abilities, you'd have known.  Now... I know that this quest you have conducted to find my blog is because you need an answer. You are mystified, anxious, curious, hurt, happy, conflicted or confused - I know, remember (describes my first 7 visitors - note the number seven as having good chi associated with it).        Do you have issues you need to resolve?       Do you want to have advice on the best path to take?       Do you want a birds-eye-view on that cheating spouse, that wayward teen, that new job, how to handle your future, or how to deal with your sordid past?    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      test
      
</post>


<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Survivor  , the Original and Still Champion of "reality" TV shows, is again leading the way in network programming.    By Mark Connolly   Temporary Movie Critic    Mark Burnett, acknowledging that he has many imitators, the most egregious   of which are foisted upon the viewing public by rival studios, knows   that reality shows have just about run their course. "It is clearly   obvious that most of the reality tripe being served to the viewing   public is entirely staged, and even the minutest of interactions are scripted.   Actors playing 'normal' poeple is the latest twist. However, this is a   one time fix, unless I underestimate the stupidity of the American   people... well.. strike that. Anyway, I refuse to lower my   standards. I will continue to serve up reality   menudo  .    "Just about all the possible permutations have been tried. Fake reality, Real   fakery, double blind who's playing and who's acting, etc. The next step   is to really fake out everyone, even Jeff Probst, and of course the   discerning audience."    Burnett of course refused to comment further, stating that surprise is the only thing he has going for the show. But, disgruntled insider   Jeri Manthey,   in her hatred of all things Survivor immediately dropped a dime on Burnett as soon as she heard The Glob was on the trail.    "Ok, here's the deal. Since I refused their offers to be on the show yet   again, they have had to resort to the cheapest and least imaginative of   premises. They are going to have a real celebrity that no one   recognizes anymore crash the campsite."    Right about the time she was about to reveal that celebrity, she said she wanted to leave, and ran off.    The Glob doesn't need much of a lead though. We were on it like cowbirds on   cows. Now, we don't want to give away anything, but, she had instant   fame as a singer songwriter, then went on to play   God herself   in   Dogma  .   (Really, by the way, you should see this movie.) We have a picture of   her in full Survivor regalia, you can just about see her   buff  .    Woo hoo. As Jay would say "I'm getting half a   censored  ."         I can hardly wait for next season!! Ψ 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       By Mark Connolly    Editor, Dallas Bureau      Lots of "facts" get posted on the internet, and lots of them are just read and responded to as if they are the real deal. Mostly because the poster uses the psychological tactic of adding scientific sounding statistics to foster uncritical acceptance of what is being said.       The following post starts with an appeal to authority and antiquity, with flavor notes of patriotism (the founding of the USA) and then goes into a bunch of stats which are probably verifiable, but which I have not bothered to verify. Then it leads to a conclusion without stating it, an insidious tactic.     But, since I like what is being said, I forthwith post without any attempt to verify!     I don't remember where I got this, and am unable to attribute it appropriately, beyond what is in the letter itself.         Subject: A History Lesson      At about the time our original 13 states adopted their new constitution, in the year 1787, Alexander Tyler (a Scottish history professor at The University of Edinborough) had this to say about "The Fall of The Athenian Republic" some 2,000 years prior.      "A democracy is always temporary in nature; it simply cannot exist as a permanent form of government. A democracy will continue to exist up until the time that voters discover that they can vote themselves generous gifts from the public treasury. From that moment on, the majority always votes for the candidates who promise the most benefits from the public treasury, with the result that every democracy will finally collapse due to loose fiscal policy, (which is) always followed by a dictatorship."       "The average age of the worlds greatest civilizations from the beginning of history, has been about 200 years. During those 200 years, these nations always progressed through the following sequence:      From Bondage to spiritual faith;       From spiritual faith to great courage;       From courage to liberty;       From liberty to abundance;       From abundance to complacency;       From complacency to apathy;       From apathy to dependence;       From dependence back into bondage."      Professor Joseph Olson of Hamline University School of Law, St. Paul, Minnesota, points out some interesting facts concerning the most recent Presidential election:      Population of counties won by:       Gore=127 million (Note from editor, this post conveniently ignores the popular vote count, implying as it does that these are the numbers of people that voted for each candidate...)      Bush=143 million      Square miles of land won by:       Gore=580,000       Bush=2,2427,000      States won by:       Gore=19       Bush=29      Murder rate per 100,000 residents in counties won by:       Gore=13.2       Bush=2.1      Professor Olson adds:      "In aggregate, the map of the territory Bush won was mostly the land owned by the tax-paying citizens of this great country. Gore's territory   encompassed those citizens living in government-owned tenements and  living off government welfare..."      Olson believes the U.S. is now somewhere between the "apathy" and "complacency" phase of Professor Tyler's definition of democracy; with some 40 percent of the nation's population already having reached the "governmental dependency" phase.     ************************    Ignore all the above non-verified stats if you like. The progression reportedly listed by Alexander Tyler seems plausible to me. Which can kind of lead to a discussion of fiscal policy and responsibility, and one, possibly two future articles:   The Haves and the Have-nots, the only barrier/stereotype that will not be overcome  , and   Democrats vs Republicans, who really believes in Human Potential? 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Stop the insanity   By Mark Connolly Editor, Dallas Bureau  We caught up with Racial Profiling in a dark alleyway, where he was hiding. RP as he is known, was reluctant to talk, but once apprised of the credentials of The Global Exclaimer, agreed to this exclusive interview.   The Glob:   How did this happen? You hiding in an alley, living off scraps, reviled by all?    RP:  Pull up a crate, this is going to take awhile. (Pauses while I find a reasonably sturdy crate…) Ok. As you probably know, I was once a valued resource, a time tested tool, if you will, of various law enforcement agencies. Cool under pressure, efficient, sometimes downright indispensable in tight situations. But, a tool is only as good as the person using it.   The Glob:   What do you mean?    RP:  You’ve heard the phrase “guns don’t kill people, people kill people”?   The Glob:   Yeah, but…    RP:  I know, guns do kill people, and sometimes people that kill people wouldn’t succeed if they had to use their bare hands. But, the idea, that a tool can be misused, that’s what I’m getting at.   The Glob:   I’ll give you that. But, misused? Come on. What is a legitimate use for you, RP?    RP:  It’s like when you need to screw in a screw. There are screw drivers and drills and hammers…   The Glob:   Hammers!?    RP:  Yeah, hammers. Think about it, if you had to, you could probably connect two pieces of wood together with a screw and a hammer. Granted, it’s not the best or right way, but regardless, in a pinch it would work. You could, if you had to, use a drill to pound nails, right? Basically, where there’s a will, there’s a… What’s that?? (Siren in the background… RP looking all about, a hunted and haunted look in his eye…) Jeez. I can’t used to that. Where was I? Oh, where there’s a will there’s a way.  Ideally, you use the right tool for the right job. But, some people will get lazy, and become reliant on a specific tool. And use it for everything, beyond its intended purpose. Or even just because they can, or due to some kind of character flaw. Musashi warned against this. He said you should have no preferred weapon, as even a high level of proficiency can become a dependence.   The Glob:   Who? Wasn’t he some kinda samurai or something?    RP:  (Looking very disgusted) He’s MUSASHI, urlLink  the Japanese Sword Saint  Jeez. Do they teach nothing in school? Never mind. (Takes deep breath)  OK, anyway, let’s say there is a robbery of a local convenience store, and someone is shot and killed and some are wounded. The survivors say “It was a tall Swarthy Male, with some sort of scarring on his forehead.” What do the police do? They put out an APB for a tall swarthy male with scarring on his head, and put me on the job looking for anyone fitting the description. So, in the resulting sweep, some recently arrived Ethiopian tribesman two streets over gets arrested, along with a couple of other likely folks. He’s innocent, and can prove it, and is released several hours later. Is he a victim of me? I suppose. But, the police have to do something, right? And if the culprits are caught, then I, Racial Profiling did my job. The temporary inconvenience to a few vs the safety of many is considered to be a valid trade off. By the way, that also works as, "It was a tall blonde with  urlLink fake breasts ." I would go looking for her, and the Ethiopian tribesman is not picked up in the sweep.   The Glob:   Well that seems to make sense. So, what happened?    RP:  Simple. Some people got lazy and misused me. For example, let’s say that there seems to be a disproportionate number of one particular ethnic group involved in burglary of a habitat. Someone lazy, and or wanting to make a name for himself figures out that if he just pulls over every one in that ethnic group, he will accidentally find someone doing something they are not supposed to do. So, he’s not trying to solve a particular current crime, and he’s not bothering to narrow the focus by asking any questions. He just puts me on the job with the slimmest of criteria. “Hey RP, find me some Mexicans.” So, I do. I’m a tool remember. From there, it is a slippery slope. And people are being stopped for absolutely no reason aside from they fit what I am looking for.   The Glob:   Wow. So then what happened then?    RP:  Well several things happened along the way, and I became associated with prejudice. And God knows, you can’t be prejudiced, at least not in public. I became almost a cuss word. All anyone has to do is mention my name, and whoever was employing me is assumed to be evil. All thinking has stopped. Just overwrought reaction.   The Glob:   Ok, but what drove you underground?    RP:  911.   The Glob:   The World Trade Center, etc.?!?    RP:  Yep. Just try to defend looking extra hard at someone just because they are middle eastern or muslim. You can’t. You simply can’t. It is not allowed. So, we will stop someone’s grandma at the airport for a full body cavity search, but smugly decline searching through someone else’s luggage because they kind of look like they might be muslim or middle eastern, and, well, that would be prejudiced. For any law enforcement agency to have any credibility, they had to boot me out. (Hangs head, tear falls.)  And (snif) I’m really good. I can be very effective when used intelligently. I, I, … (voice trails off, RP stands and shuffles off.)   The Glob:   Eh, good luck, OK? Bye?   Ψ 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        And their failure in Drug Education   By Mark Connolly Editor, Dallas Bureau  I am outraged. Our public schools are not doing their duty and ensuring the safety of our children. Everyone knows that AIDS is a severe problem, and that the primary method for getting this disease is through intravenous drug use with used/dirty needles. But is this fact being addressed adequately in our schools? No!  We all know that it is not feasible to simply tell our children to avoid drugs. Kids are kids, and they are going to experiment. There is nothing you can do about human nature. God knows we can’t stifle their minds or future creativity by setting arbitrary barriers. Who’s got time to police all this anyway? No, this is a job best handled by our school systems.  Our children should be taught that when they shoot up heroin, be sure to use a clean needle. In fact sterile syringes should be handed out at our schools. Possibly even pharmaceutical grade heroin. It’s the responsible thing to do.  Now, I can sense that some of you more straitlaced people may be raising an eyebrow, wondering if this is such a good idea.  Hey, get with the program! After all, this is the same approach used to such good effect in the prevention of teen pregnancy in our elementary and high schools! Ψ
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The following is very personal. It involves people that I know, and friends of theirs. It affected me, and I think rightly so. I share here on the Glob as these things matter, and should be thought about. This is not intended to be political in any way. It is intended to be Human.  I have hidden or changed the names involved. I deleted a line or two. The rest is as I received it.  To clarify, the Original Message is from someone I know from The Hunt. In his message he tells briefly about someone he knows, and then relays the email he received from that person.  Finally I have included reaction from Uncle Buck.  -----Original Message-----  Subject: Marine that was killed in Iraq  When I was growing up, one of  my friend's brother-n-law was like a big brother to all of us.  He and his wife had a  little baby when I was about 17.   He grew up and enlisted in the Marines as an 0311 grunt.       This is the email just sent me.    To:        HIDDEN   cc:         HIDDEN  Subject:            How is it  going? We just found out that Johhny was killed Monday. Bob   ***********************************************************************   I was unable to respond to the person that sent me the above.         However, Uncle Buck finally had a response, which follows:   Well I've been stewing for a week trying to come up with something worthwhile to say, but nothing that comes to my  mind is really worthy of a life lost in service to our country..  Young guys and girls join the service, and they have their own reasons for doing so. These might include a vague  notion of "service to country", but that's normally not the main reason. Most young folks are beyond fear of death,  they don't think about death at all. Yet their service and sacrifice is greater than they know.  "All give some, some  give all" sounds like a cliché, but it's the real deal. Those that serve give up part of their lives, and maybe more,  for us.   My son's high school graduated 400 in 2003, about a dozen enlisted. So a few serve so we can all sleep safer at night.  Say what you want about the wisdom of going to Iraq, or Afghanistan, or Yugoslavia or anyplace else...but those  willing to serve stand in the gap for us. John Stuart Mill had this to say at the close of the War between the States:  "War is an ugly thing, but not the ugliest of things. The decayed and degraded state of moral and patriotic feelings  which thinks that nothing is worth war is much worse. The person who has nothing for which he is willing to fight,  nothing which is more important than his own personal safety, is a miserable creature and has no chance of being free  unless made and kept so by the exertions of better men than himself."  My heart and prayers go out to Bob's family and to the memory of Johnny, one of the "better men". We owe them a debt of  gratitude that cannot be repaid  We're on the eve of Independence Day. Most of us will cook out and drink beer and watch fireworks. As part of your  celebration, take a minute to think of and be thankful for those who can't, either because they're in some God- forsaken corner of the world or no longer among us.   Freedom is not free.   Uncle Buck
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Celebration Shuts down The Glob   By Mark Connolly Editor, Dallas Bureau  The 5th Edition Gala Celebration was apparently conducted on an alternate plane of existence, as it resulted in the total shut down of The Global Exclaimer and all publishing. The lead story planned for this edition, originally scheduled for Aug/Sept of 2003 and once relevant, is not.  Most of the Aug/Sept edition was lost in the catastrophe. New equipment had to be purchased and the format of the paper recreated. Thankfully, Daver maintains his files in a mobious cube, and he is largely to thank for there being any paper at all this quickly. That and this blogging thing, since I went to Windows 2000, and for some reason the high tech features of my Deskjet 722C are unavailable in W2k (although they worked find in W98, like duplex printing for example.)  We forge on. I ask for letters and questions to be sent via: theglob@comcast.net. Or, you can post comments in the commenting section available at the end of each post to the Glob Blog.  You can also send your own creative submissions, i.e. prose, poetry, opinions, whatever. Anything to fill this rag with print. And any of which become the property of The Global Exclaimer to be used solely for our own financial gain.  Meanwhile, I have to say I am pleased with the new equipment purchased by The Glob. It’s a much faster computer, and is running Windows 2000 professional, at the moment. The old computer hard drive died, but Erik replaced it, and so I will soon have a network of computers working tirelessly to further my ego-maniacal publication empire designs. (Actually what that really means is that Rosie and Leon will have an alternate computer to use while I am consumed with creative passion.)  We MAY attempt to continue to do a bi-monthly newsletter, and to server our readers the unique blend of reporting and retorting that you have grown to love. Or we may just do this blog thing.  I'm still not sure if Web Logs are the way to go for the newspaper. There are things I think I can do which I haven't figured out yet, like bundle all this into one edition, so as to maybe have the front page of this blog have an article or two then links to the editions. Maybe they have to be separate blogs or something. Dunno yet. But, the Glob is not dead, perhaps metamorphed, and we shall continue the struggle for whatever, blah blah.  I'm also trying to figure out how there can be a letters to the editor section or something for people to post questions to the Spiritual Advocate and etc. Until next time. Ψ 
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As a devout Liberal ;-p, I found the following article most concerning:  urlLink Blogging Conservatives! 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      useful intro to the web logs. I like this site. You can find out about all kinds of stuff here:  urlLink Link me off  
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Interesting. I enabled being told when a person commented an article, and  received these emails.  I confess I don't really know how all this works. It is sort of like a  purpose built website, specifically for journaling or logging your thoughts on  the web, or web logging, or blogging, you see.  I am sending this to you of course, but I will also cause it to appear as  the latest post on the Glob Blog.  Meanwhile, what you wrote was supposedly posted but I don't know where.  Daver wrote a self promoting comment congratulating the author of the cage match  article, and that comment showed up.  Perhaps you can tell me what article you commented, or whatever. Meanwhile, this is not intended to replace the Global Exclaimer, but rather  to be an adjunct to it. How that may work remains to be seen.  I've noticed also, that things seem to post slowly, which I'm sure is  affected to some degree by the fact this blogspot is free.  Ciao dude.  FB  &gt;&gt;&gt; Uncle Buck &lt;noreply-comment@blogger.com&gt;  12-Jul-04 10:39:17 AM &gt;&gt;&gt; OK, i guess it worked.   i'm only  here because of the similarity of GLOB and BLOG, which seems significant  somehow. has this replaced the exclaimer? is this better than a website like  that of the HUNT? do these things go on forever or do they end someday?    --  Posted by Uncle Buck to  The Glob Blog  at 7/12/2004  10:43:54 AM 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The Eye is Open  Dear Spirit Dude, What did you learn from the whole Janet Jackson Boob Incident? - Wondering   Dear Wondering, What I learned is that in the United States a white man can forcibly rip the clothing from a black woman, and the black woman will be reviled and scorned and the white man will suffer no consequences whatsoever.   Dear Spiritual Advocate, What did you learn from the Matrix movies? - Neowannabe   Dear Neowannabe, I learned that sometimes, no matter how badly a movie seems to scream for a sequel, it should not be made. Especially twice.   Yo, Eyeball dude person, can societies be immoral or moral? - Pontious   Dear Pontious, No soundbite answers available here. This requires some set up and some sort of starting point that we can agree upon.  First we need to determine what is meant by society and what is meant by moral or immoral. You may find it odd that I shall choose to use circular definitions as it may be most beneficial to view the two concepts as being interrelated and codependent. One problem with Western thought is the tendency to strip things down and attempt to isolate them from anything else in order to gain insight into their ‘true’ essence. Ignoring the fact that some sort of interrelatedness is part of, or perhaps in fact is, our true essence.  Society being a word used to describe the actions and purposes of multiple persons, definitions of society involve how society is ordered towards individuals. It is therefore written: “Society ensures social justice when it provides the conditions that allow associations or individuals to obtain what is their due, according to their nature and their vocation. Social justice is linked to the common good and the exercise of authority.” But, what is ‘the common good’? And what is this about the ‘exercise of authority’? It is written: “By ‘authority’ one means the quality by virtue of which persons or institutions make laws and give orders to men and expect obedience to them.  “Every human community needs an authority to govern it. The foundation of such authority lies in human nature. It is necessary for the unity of the state. Its role is to ensure as far as possible the common good of the society.”  Common good again.  And so it is written further: “A society is a group of persons bound together organically by a principle of unity that goes beyond each one of them. As an assembly that is at once visible and spiritual, a society endures through time: it gathers up the past and prepares for the future. By means of society, each man is established as an ‘heir’ and receives certain ‘talents’ that enrich his identity and whose fruits he must develop. He rightly owes loyalty to the communities of which he is part and respect to those in authority who have charge of the common good.”  Hmmm. Authority and common good again.   We shall leave this for now and allow some digestion and some questioning. We shall take this up in the next issue.   Ψ 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      By Jim Bob Jones  Guest columnist and  damn fine dent puller at the body shop   So I’m waiting for a couple of months for this stinking Texas Cage Match between Opie and that little piss-ant Daver. I have been so excited about Daver’s upcoming butt stomping that I haven’t been able to focus on my work down at Bubba’s Bumper Bungalow. Luckily, most of my customers are at least one enchilada short of a combo platter down at Taco Loco, so they rarely notice my crappy work.  I get to the arena early to stake out a good seat, maybe get close enough to get splattered with a little blood as Opie beats the Jedi crap out of Daver. I make my way down close to the ring and find all these hoity-toity, fairy looking men in tuxedos sitting in seats marked “Reserved” down close. What the hell is that? I was about to get really upset when I noticed that each of these lucky bastards was sitting next to some chick with some serious knockers. I mean, they were barely contained in a low-cut gown. Maybe I should call them lucky stiffs, if you know what I mean. I should have known that this would be a weird event if the society crowd was here. Little was I to know that those snotty society geeks would be a part of a life changing experience.  Finally, the house fills up and ass-kicking time arrives. The air was hot and humid and began to smell of testosterone and sweat as the pre-match entertainment wound down. I knew it was time to start when a very serious hotty entered the ring and introduced herself as Paddy. Damn! Made me forget about the hooters on the front two rows. That chick was so hot, I’d drink her bath water! She began the introductions with that little know-it-all bastard Daver. Who the hell does he think he is? Does he think I give a rat’s ass about his opinion? I can’t wait to see him get killed tonight. Anyway, after she introduces him, he comes out in some dark satin robe with a hood, trying to look all bad-ass or something. Then they start playing that Darth Vader song from Star Wars, gimme a break. Go ahead Daver, just a few more minutes and BAM, your ass is gonna be grass, you little freak!  Finally, I am drawn back to Paddy and her rockin’ bod. Damn! Hell, I’d even listen to the phone book if she was reading it. She introduces Opie and begins to jump up and down excitedly. Damn again! Paddy is, as my friend Jam Master Tyrone would say, one “fly-ass cootchie!”  My attention is pulled away from my libido-induced Nirvana as I look back to find Opie enter wearing a red, white & blue robe, looking like Rocky Balboa about to kill that arrogant bastard Mr. T. I even hear the music from Rocky. This is gonna be great! Go get’em dude!  The conqueror and victim enter the ring and stare each other down. Daver has to be on a step-stool, just to be able to see Opie’s eyes. Little pip-squeak! Loud music blasting, lights flashing, knockers on my left, hooters on my right, Paddy in the ring; it just don’t get much better than this. I am ready for some serious bloodshed!  Paddy exits the ring just as a hush falls over the massive crowd. Opie and Daver are still in the center of the ring in a stare-fest as the cage comes down around them. The lights dim. Still staring. You can almost hear the pulse of the crowd, waiting for the beating to start. Still staring. Just then that loud-mouthed announcer dude steps up to the microphone and belts out “Lllllllllettttt’s get ready to rhumbaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa!”    Wait, what did he say? Rhumba? What the hell is that? It’s rumble! I WANNA SEE A RUMBLE! The combatants drop their robes as Daver motions toward the roof and a freakin’ mirrored ball drops from above the ring. Now Daver has on a little miniature tuxedo, looks like he got it from Barbie’s gay pal Ken. Opie, no, say it ain’t so, man! Opie has on a pink chiffon, sequined floor-length ball gown slit high on the side, with delightful, understated red rose accoutrements on the shoulders. AAAAAGGGGHHH! Oh, the humanity! Wait, how did I miss this? There is a full symphony orchestra off to my right. The orchestra begins to play some kind of weird ballroom dance music – I still can’t describe it, but those society geeks in the front seemed to know it. Oh, man, I need a drink. Where is the beer dude when you need him?  There is no sound from the audience as we watch in stunned amazement as Opie and Daver look like Fred and Ginger gliding across the mat. Oh my lord, what is happening? Somehow, despite the height difference, Daver manages to “dip” Opie in a surprisingly graceful move. The crowd begins to sense something really special occurring here. After a few minutes, I myself am transformed by the sheer beauty of the dance. I begin to see that the dance has brought two enemies together. They move as one across the ring as we stare in awe of the grace and elegance on display before us. If Daver and Opie can put aside their differences, I should be able to lay down my old ways and appreciate my fellow man. I come upon the realization that it was wrong for me to lust after the delightful young society ladies and their low-cut gowns, and I am suddenly ashamed that I never wondered what kind of brilliant mind resides within the lovely Paddy.  The dance ends! Daver bows, Opie curtsies gracefully. We all clap politely, yet enthusiastically. I notice that, instead of a beer dude, a waiter with wine and cheese has appeared. How refreshing! Suddenly, without any prompting, every member of the audience turns to their neighbor and gives them a big hug as we begin to sing “We are the World.”  I make friends with a tall, turbaned man from the Middle East and apologize for my improper judgment that he was just a towel-headed terrorist. He smiles back, accepts my apology, announces that he loves America, and offers me a ride in his cab. It was positively the most uplifting, mind-altering event of my life.  Sure, a part of me was bummed that there was no bloodshed, but I think everyone there came away a little more enlightened and tolerant of others as a result of being present for “The Dance.” Ψ 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      By Daver the Raver Staff Political Poet  Hello loyal readers. After a 1 issue break for Cage Match training, I am back with another opinion about the world that revolves around me. But first, if you haven’t read the report about my Cage Match with Opie, please stop this article and read the account now. I’ll wait.  No really, I’m serious, I’ll wait. Go on, I’ll be here when you get back.  (softly humming “Bad to the Bone” now)  As you can see, some rather amazing events unfolded. I determined that Opie is just a young, impressionable young man who had made the mistake of following the dark path sent forth by our editor. I have decided to take young Opie into my tutelage and instruct him in the ways of The Farce. The Ffarce is quite strong in him. As part of his training, I have given him a new name; he is now Opie Juan Canoli. I shall provide occasional updates on his progress.  As for my rant – I have had an overabundance of crap to rant about since I last spouted my thoughts about the world, but just recently I saw something totally ridiculous that really got my blood boiling.  I saw a news story out of Southlake, Texas that really hacked me off. For those of you who do not live in the great state of Texas, Southlake is a small town between Dallas and Fort Worth, on the Fort Worth side. It seems that Homeowner’s Associations are big in Southlake, as the town has enjoyed pretty good growth in the past decade and many people bought nice homes in these little Utopian neighborhoods.  You’re probably wondering what the problem might be, aren’t you? Well, here it is; a totally over-zealous Homeowner’s Association, hereafter referred to as Communist Dictator Bastards, has informed a brave war veteran of our United States Armed Services that he may not fly Old Glory everyday in front of his home. The evil Communist Dictator Bastards have told the entire community that the flag of the United States of America may only be flown on designated holidays. America, what a country!  Am I alone in thinking this is an outrage? How about the irony here? This man risks his life to join the military, go overseas and do his duty, not knowing if he will ever set foot on American soil again, and then returns home to be told he can’t fly the very symbol of freedom that gave the Communist Dictator Bastards the right to make that decision. How must this guy feel? I’ll bet he wants to go down to the next board meeting and go all Rambo on their ass.  As I see it, the real problem is Homeowner’s Associations in general. I have never liked them, and I never will. I agree with the concept that they should work to maintain property values, but most of them overdo it. Does anyone want their neighbor painting his house neon-green? I would hope not. That is what the Communist Dictator Bastards should be doing, keeping the local hippy pot-heads from screwing up the neighborhood. That being said, I don’t need some power-hungry, pencil-pushing geek on my neighborhood Politburo making me submit landscaping plans because I want to plant roses in my fenced-in backyard. No one but my stereotypical American family will ever see the roses anyway, so why the hell should little Junior Stalin and his comrades care? If they want to tell me what to do with my house, then they can damn well make a few of those 360 freaking mortgage payments!  You should have seen the size of the Communist Dictator Bastard’s rule book in that news story! The book was so big that Seabiscuit couldn’t have jumped over it. The thing was obviously written by people with too much time on their hands. I’ll bet some of them were even lawyers!   Bastards!  If I were in charge, and I should be, I would make that evil Communist Dictator Bastard board get down on their knees on live television and kiss our brave soldier’s ass in thanks for his service. Then I would have them castrated so they could breed more little Communist Dictator Bastards. Without our brave hero, they might actually be answering to real Communist Bastards. Let the man fly his flag whenever the hell he wants, it’s his right. I think he’s earned it!  Just think about it. Does the fact that he is flying his flag everyday lower the property values in their little Xanadu? Could this situation be more ridiculous? God Bless America, God bless our President, and God bless our armed forces!  On an unrelated note - Did anyone who saw the Cage Match think that Opie looked a little too comfortable in that floor length gown? It kind of freaked me out, but that’s another rant for another time. Ψ 
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Glob Staff Mourns The Departure Of The Retail Republican (1984-2004)  Unbeknownst to many Glob readers, the Retail Republican was an inspiration to The Glob’s editorial staff.  Many staff meetings were spent discussing current events with the Retail Republican, and even more staff meetings were spent discussing additional ways the resident conservative could contribute to the publication.  Now, after almost 20 years in the retail sector, The Retail Republican has decided to move on and pursue other interests.  We here at the Glob wish him the best of luck, while simultaneously hoping that it was not our actions that caused this major life change in our former colleague.  Perhaps the introduction of the “drive-by” interview at our last staff meeting was not as successful as we had hoped.  In order to fill the void left by the Retail Republican’s retirement (say that 5 times fast), the staff at the Glob has already been in talks with possible replacements.  Daver has been appointed to head the search team and has vowed to leave no stone un-levitated in his search for the most qualified journalist (patsy) to join the staff.  Anyone interested in filling the void left by the Retail Republican should think really hard about it and send a telepathic message to Daver personally.  Daver will respond in a suitable manner.  Daver the Raver
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a practicing Roman Catholic. I make this announcement because I am not going to pretend that I don’t have some bias or predilection regarding this movie or the subject matter.  However, I think religious affiliation is almost irrelevant. The movie is the movie, and you should really go to see it and pay little or no attention to reviewers and what they have to say. Including me. We all have our agendas.  I have decided to rail against some of the crap I’ve read in other reviews, then offer my review.    Mel as Anti-Semite   I note that to date, there has been no pogrom against the Jew. Nor will there be, in my opinion. The film’s message is not one of hate. The statements that he and his father are worse than the Germans (Howard Stern) or that the movie is ‘virulently anti-Semitic’ as quoted by some rabbi whose name I can’t recall seem specious and inflammatory, and driven by hate.  “Worse than the Germans…” would imply that Mel and his dad have been directly responsible for more than 6 million Jew Deaths. “Virulently anti-Semitic” would imply a specific and unmistakable Hate message to be conveyed, along with specific direction of how to deal with the Jew Threat, such as murder, extortion, violence, seizing of property, etc.  Clearly the sewage of rhetoric emptying from 4 ft. diameter pipes into the rivers of our collective conscious requires capping.    Mel as Discipline Fetishest   I’ve seen 4 different reviewers , apparently dipping from the same sewage contaminated well, describe the flagellation as being handled with a “fetishist's eye” and turning the movie into some sort of nearly X-rated bondage and discipline flick.  A quick glance in my American Heritage Dictionary provided three meanings for ‘fetish’.  “1. An object superstitiously believed to have magical powers, esp. of protection.  2. An object of unreasonably excessive attention or reverence. 3. Something, such as a material or object or an often non-sexual part of the body that aroused or gratifies sexual desire.”  I will grant that definition 2 might apply in this case, from a skewed perspective. However, given the prurient nature of our society, and the tendency to write for sound-bites rather than for understanding, I assume that the reviewers are referring to sex.  One of these was a Presbyterian minister! I am not sure what that says about that man’s theology, or his personal life.    Mel as Action/Adventure Actor/Director   Several reviewer’s wrote things such as “...it is not surprising that Mel, an action/adventure movie star and director, made an action/adventure Jesus movie.”  I don’t even know what that means. Reference to a “big strapping Jesus…” and “blood and guts Jesus hero in the action/adventure tradition…” leave me scratching my head.  Perhaps Bruce Willis should have been cast as Jesus in  Die Hard, The Passion .    Mel as Director with a Vision   One potential interpretation of this movie is that of Mel as someone wanting to make a movie about something personally important to him, and financing it himself because it was that important to him.  Yeah, I know it’s more exciting to critique a movie about some mouth-breathing thugs being transported into sexual ecstasy by scourging some big strapping man. But, as boring as it may sound, I think the simple truth is: This movie is about the last 12 hours of Jesus’ life as reported in the Bible. Note I did not say it was The Gospel. It is after all a movie. There are things in this movie not directly in The Bible, and vice a versa. Still, it is what it is, and what it is is one man’s vision of the events recounted in the 4 Gospels.  The scourging, which is painful to watch, doesn’t have anything on the Friday the 13th, Freddy Krueger or Halloween movies.  No one has lined up to question the need for the blood and gore in those movies. What fascinates me is that the violence in those movies is for no reason other than to horrify/titillate the viewer. The violence in  The Passion  is an integral part of His-story, and there is a reason for it. Yet people were quick to fault Mel for “unnecessary violence.”  As if the artistic merits of Freddy Krueger killing semi nude nubile teenagers warrants gallons of indiscriminately spilled blood while the scourging and crucifixion of Jesus to save all of humanity doesn’t? Oy vey.  Look up the word “scourge”. Ok, I’ll look it up for you: “1. A whip used to inflict punishment. 2. A means of inflicting severe suffering, vengeance or punishment.”  You read something that says that someone was “scourged” and what kind of mental image does it bring up? For me, prior to this movie, it was a clearly painful but survivable punishment designed to chastise someone. I was not afraid of being scourged.  Now I am. The movie portrays a scourging at the hands of professionals. For me, anyway, the brutality of a scourging could not be adequately conveyed in mere words. So, what was all that about then anyway? Well, to really answer that you have to get into the religious aspect of this movie, and the purpose of Jesus Christ.  That topic is off limits for most movie reviewers because it requires of them to delve into areas thought to be somehow incorrect in these extremely odd politically correct days. And, they may find themselves expressing ideas that are perhaps unpopular, and maybe dangerous to their careers. And that may be why most of the reviews I have seen have been truly shallow, and of very little substance. This is a religious movie with no agenda beyond a portrayal of the last 12 hours of Jesus’ life. No conclusions are drawn. The story is just told, in Homeric fashion. The conclusions are left to the audience to draw for themselves.  Some questions that a person might ask, regardless of background and upbringing:  Who was this person? Did this really happen? Why? Why did anyone want him dead? Why was it so horrible? What’s the deal with the water when they poked him in the side? What’s up with the end of the movie? Wasn’t he dead?  Look it up! Go read the context of this story. There is a reason for why it happened, every bit of it. You may not like what you read or think it is all some childish fairy tale. But, you might be surprised. The story is remarkably simple and self-consistent. When’s the last time you thought seriously about God, or talked with anyone about God?   You may find Psalm 22 interesting. It’s the same in the Tanakh as well.  Ψ  
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To the loyal readers of The Glob (The Global Exclaimer) I give you this blog. More to come.
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I am showing my mother-in-law about blogs. She may possibly use this to publish her newspaper, Navarretadas.  What do you think, Antipentheus??
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Nuke the Moon   Submitted for your perusal without comment.
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink How we play in the neighborhood   Ok, this was just funny to me.
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Syrian Bandwagon   I stumbled across this blog, and after wading through the "I blog for Kerry" button and the democrat symbol button, I read the above linked post.  I find myself agreeing with pretty much the whole article. A very refreshing and lucid post. I had emailed her (being new to this blogging thing) and asked her OK to link to this article. Here is her response:    Hi Mark--thanks, feel free to link. I agree we need more humane communication between people whose viewpoints  differ. Have fun blogging! I have some libertarian/conservative friends on my blogroll: Gary Farber, Chris Markum,  and Jay McCarthy. Me, I'm a build-up-the-social-safety-net kinda Democrat.   Betsy   http://BetsyDevine.weblogger.com "Making trouble today for a better tomorrow."   So, I was inspired to create a list: Blogs I Have Known, and she's the first entry!
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        RJ Reynolds in a Panic   Mark Connolly Editor, Dallas Bureau  Dateline: RJ Reynolds Situation Room  The announcement caused the same type of panic reaction that "Core Meltdown" would cause in a nuclear power plant. "Madame Boverie has succeeded in avoiding cigarettes for one full week!" Klaxons sounding, rotating beacons rotating, the executives were briefed.  "The first sign was a precipitous drop in sales for the week" stated the Chief Investigator. "Investigators were mobilized to the local 7-Elevens to ascertain the cause. It became immediately evident. Cigarette stock was literally flowing out the front doors. The managers were at a loss. They had simply ordered the usual amount, but they were not purchased."  He went on to say, "This precipitated a search of credit card activity in the three affected stores for the past month. The reports, 10 pages long per day for the first three weeks, dropped off to a page and a half a week. From there it was easy to determine what had happened."  Agents were mobilized for a quick visit to Madame Boverie's place of Business, Rosie Palm Reading and Tarock Tournament Townhouse. They confirmed what was becoming dreadfully obvious.  She had quit smoking.  "Oh, the humanity. The large numbers of humanity we have to get hooked on smoking to make up for this loss" one executive was quoted as saying. A lucky strike team was sent to India the next day to get the hitherto untapped 6 and 7 year old prospects introduced to the coolness of smoking. Ψ
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a theory is based on the assertion that “the stock market/economy does better under democratic presidents”. Now I don’t know if this is true, but it seems to be widely believed and reported (I’m struck by what I see as an apparent inconsistency in this belief!). None-the-less, for my purposes if it’s believed to be true, it’s the same effect as being true.   Take this to a logical conclusion…Republicans are about foreign policy and defending the nation and such. Worthy goals to be sure, but what about MY JOB? What about MY 401K? What about MY MUTUAL FUNDS? Do intangibles like national security mean anything if my standard of living has to suffer? With all the pretense and rhetoric stripped away these ideals sound greedier than republican ones (this is all weird backwards-land stuff).   Practical working folk can sign up for this. Forget about all the rest: Republican morality or Democratic social reform…who cares? All I care about is MY STUFF…which will fare better with a democratic prez in charge than the other. It is a solution unto itself, no plan or justification is needed beyond this simple cause-and-effect.   Keep in mind I’m not talking about what’s best, or the value of right-and-wrong. I’m just talking about ME. I think this shameful little secret is how the “left wing whackos” have taken over the voice of the Democratic party. In their own self-importance they don’t realize they don’t matter. What matters is that on Election Day millions of individuals quietly vote for themselves, and they don’t have to admit it. They can keep their mouths shut, or hide behind some smokescreen issue.   What stronger motivation to vote is there than a vote for yourself?   
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Truth Hurts!   Hah!!  I find the last part of this little trailer pretty interesting.  Ψ
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Reuters | Latest Financial News / Death threat just free expression   Read that little article real quick, if'n you don't mind.  Ok, I'm not really wanting to get into a discussion of free speech. What I'm extremely confused about is this line of the poem contrasted with this quote from Justice Carlos Moreno:   Poem extract: "...For I can be the next kid to bring guns to kill students at school..."  Judge quote: "Of course, exactly what the poem means is open to varying interpretations because a poem may mean different things to different readers. As a medium of expression, a poem is inherently ambiguous."   Huh?  Ψ
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Click on that title to read the article on Reuters.  Very interesting. This guy probably recognizes propaganda when he sees it.  Ψ
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A brief thought about Carlos Delgado of the Toronto Blue Jays.&nbsp; He has publicly stated that he is against our on-going war with Iraq and, as a result, he refuses to stand and be present when “God Bless America” is played during the seventh-inning stretch. &nbsp;Many people are up-in-arms over his blatant anti-American attitude.  &nbsp;  Big Freaking Deal!!  &nbsp;  This is America and you have the right to protest if you wish.&nbsp; Good for him!&nbsp; He has an opinion, has made a public protest, and has not changed his mind because of some bad press.&nbsp; How refreshing!&nbsp; Maybe the Dems could learn from him.  &nbsp;  Mainly, however, it is ridiculous that we care what Carlos Delgado does or thinks.&nbsp; He’s a damn overpaid, overgrown kid playing a game for a living!&nbsp; Maybe we should concentrate on keeping terrorists from attacking us again or maybe focus our attention on the upcoming election.&nbsp; Hmmm…  &nbsp;  That’s it for now – Daver out! 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, OK, First Base  The following link will take you to some hot news about a sports figure and his protest against the USA in Iraq. If you haven't read this, then good. Don't bother. It's a non-issue. But, if you feel you must, I'll wait a bit.  urlLink Taking a stand: Delgado does not stand for `God Bless America'   God Bless America is not the National Anthem. As far as I have experienced in my life, no one is expected to leap erect when it plays.  The seventh inning stretch traditionally was a time when everyone stood up and stretched while singing "Take Me Out to the Ballgame." In New York, after 9/11 they swapped songs, understandable and patriotic in my mind. But people were already standing to stretch anyway.  Delgado plays for the Toronto Blue Jays. They're from Canada. Although, that is also America.  Hmmm. Well, anyway...  I haven't checked this assumption, but I don't believe Delgado is a citizen or even a resident of the USA (not that it matters regardless.)  He simply chooses not to stand, a very understated form of protest, well considered and even respectful. He didn't go and advertise this.  Someone seeking a story in NY sought him out . Otherwise, we wouldn't know. But he is abiding by something that means something to him, while acknowledging that others disagree with him. Very mature.  By the way, he stands during the National Anthem. Not that that matters, as many ball players I see are groping their crotches and spitting during the National Anthem.  I sincerely hope he doesn't get a bunch of flack over this, and if he does, I hope he continues his protest. It is important that he is doing this, and that it be tolerated. That is a sign of health for our country.  This mostly caught my mind's eye because of some of the silliness being said about free speech. Whoopi Goldberg is ranting about her right to free speech being abrogated by the Bush Administration. It astonishes me what people will say, and feel they can say, without feeling any need to support it.  First of all, the thing called freedom of speech is specifically referring to the right of people to speak out without the Government taking hostile action against them. It does not mean that you are protected against employers deciding they want another spokesperson. To those of you that may want to salivate over some conspiracy theory where SlimFast is owned by Halliburton, I can only say, if Whoopi's rights are being violated, she has legal recourse. So, sue or shut up.  She won't do either of course, but she will be tuned out quickly. It's like that catchy tune that you really wanted to hear all the time that makes you jab frantically at the tuner button every time you hear it now. It gets old fast.  That makes me think, for the first time in months, about The Dixie Chicks. Haven't heard from them lately. You'd think if that girl had any conviction in what she was saying, she'd still be saying it. But, no, as soon as it interfered with the very capitalistic endeavor of making scads of money, she shut up.  Oddly, I want Whoopi to shut up, I'm glad the Dixie Chick shut up, but I don't want Delgado to stand up.  Go figure.  Ψ
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In an attempt to give this something more of a newspaper feel, I have created a separate blog for one of the posts that will have regular follow up, The Spiritual Advocate. If I ever learn some HTML I'll make it pretty. But for now, the link is up there at the top. The plan is to update that blog weekly.  I copied the previous post from down yonder to its new home. I left the one down yonder 'cause it had some comments, and I can't figure out how to get the comments directly over there. But future SA posts will all go to the link above.  It's supposed to be like its own column. Let me know what you think, please.
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Mind Control   By Mark Connolly Editor, Dallas Bureau  A plan has been in the works for years. Spawned in the creative minds of a desperate Democratic Party during the Reagan/Bush years, and appealing to unholy powers while tinkering with knowledge beyond our ken, It now comes to fruition.  This is mind control; control of the minds of the populace, and control of the minds of the politicians. This is not the Manchurian Candidate, though that could be the inspiration. No, it is Stepford Politician. To what end is not clear yet. Perhaps, just THE end.  The first signs were evident during Bill Clinton's initial campaign for president. When he was giving speeches and really trying to seem earnest, he would punctuate his speeches with a kind of affected "thumbs up" gesture. I know you've seen it. Fist extended with the thumb kind of poking up, almost like you might have a piece of paper pinched between your thumb and the side of the first phalange of your forefinger. Somewhere it was presented that he was doing this in imitation of General Eisenhower, from a famous photo taken during World War II. This picture was taken just prior to D-Day, and reportedly was captioned to the effect that Eisenhower was giving the troops a 'thumbs up'.  There is something comforting about the picture, and inspiring, especially taking into account how horrific D-Day turned out to be while still signaling the beginning of the end of German aggression.   urlLink     The beginning of the thumb   Clinton deliberately used a gesture that psychologically instilled in the populace a feeling of trust and a belief in his competence. It was a calculated gesture, and it worked. What is funny/sad about this is something I saw on the History channel the other day. It was one of many specials marking the anniversary of D-Day, and it was from one of the survivors. He's apparently in that picture. Dwight, he says, was talking with the men about fly-fishing, and showing how you hold the rod.  The question in my mind is, how smart is Clinton anyway? Is he really that calculating, or does he take direction from some other source? No one knows for sure, though the rumors fly about Hillary's control. But I think it may be even more sinister, if not provable. I simply present the following photo taken by Russian Parapsychologist Investigators using special purpose built cameras.   urlLink    The author of this diabolical plan  This is concerning because his calculated earnestness managed to land him the Presidency, not once, but twice. And that is appalling when you realize his real attitude towards the American People.  urlLink    "Yeah, I got your American People right here..."  Clinton's alarming success could not be repeated by Gore, the first prototype Stepford politician. He simply had no emotion, and could not form a bond with the voters.  urlLink    Vice President Al Gore  So, the next step was to simply build a viable Presidential candidate from scratch.    How it works   Take a politician, and strip him down to his constituent parts. Remove all sense of self respect and replace with unbridled ego. Excise any actual sense of compassion and fill the void with naked ambition. D&C the conscience and replace with a waffle iron. Perform a continuityectomy, and replace with expediency. This procedure also requires that a Jarvik 7 Memory Loss module be implanted to deal with any inconvenient recollection that might lead to a sense of shame. The result is a  Whatever it Takes  approach to getting elected, without the annoyance of scruples.   urlLink    How it works  It is perhaps not surprising that the party of abortion and stem cell research is leading the way in the creation of "life" that will simply follow orders and appeal to the lowest common denominator without having any pesky traits like individual thought or a sense of right and wrong.  If you watch the physical behavior of any Democratic speaker, you will see this fly-fishing thumbs up gesture used during any speech where they begin to make up something that they want the populace to accept uncritically. It is a visible clue intended to set your mind at ease (or turn it off) while they spout something preposterous.  All kidding aside, if you do watch for this, you will see it over and over. Evidently they all have the same handler/speech coach. Or, it must be perceived as a gesture that works, and it has crept into their mannerisms in the same way that teen age kids imitate the words and actions of the current hot rap star. They don't know why they are doing it, they just do it because it is the thing to do. I've seen Kerry do it, and I've seen Edwards do it. It is used while stating things like "I will be a president that seeks to unite, rather than divide" or some other substanceless cotton candy of a sound bite.  I would really like to know what Kerry stands for. I've talked to some Kerry supporters. I've asked them what his plans are for dealing with terrorism. Not one of them has an articulable understanding of Kerry's plans. All I get is "Whatever it is, it will be better than Bush." These are reasonably intelligent people! I don't understand.  It must be the thumb. Ψ
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Which party has the greatest faith in human potential?   By Mark Connolly Editor, Dallas Bureau  My nephew asked me last night what the differences were between Republicans and Democrats on education. I stumbled through an answer. I realized during the attempt that as far as I know, there really is not a huge difference in what is being said by either party. So I had to resort to my perceptions of an overall approach to governance, which in my opinion entails a certain world view regarding individual citizens. And that leads, however indirectly, to the topics of Democrats and Republicans, and Liberals and Conservatives.  When asked whether I am Republican or Democrat, I always say Republican. I am Republican for some perceived general ideological stances, and not because of specific policies or platforms. I have some basic perceptions that may or may not be accurate, which I now hang out to swing in the wind, offering them up as fair game for any commentary.  I would first like to set out one issue that contributes to this debate; the assertion that "all Democrats are Liberals, and all Conservatives are Republicans." Liberal and Conservative are kind of world views, and they do overlap with Democrat and Republican platforms. But even inside one's own skin you will find you are liberal on this issue and conservative on that issue. You shouldn't simply pigeon-hole individuals into one or other group. Nevertheless, I do believe that Republicans  tend  toward a more conservative world view while Democrats  tend  toward a more liberal world view.  I have two quotes that kind of sum up my views on Dems and Reps and Libs and Cons.  Regarding liberal and conservative:   Any man who is under 30 and is not a Liberal has no heart; and any man who is over 30 and not a Conservative has no brains. - Winston Churchill (1874-1965)    And now for Republicans and Democrats:   On God and Santa Claus From P.J. O'Rourke's book Parliament of Whores  I have only one firm belief about the American political system, and that is this: God is a Republican and Santa Claus is a Democrat.  God is an elderly or, at any rate, middle-aged mate, a stern fellow, patriarchal rather than paternal and a great believer in rules and regulations. He holds men strictly accountable for their actions. He has little apparent concern for the material well-being of the disadvantaged. He is politically connected, socially powerful and holds the mortgage on literally everything in the world. God is difficult. God is unsentimental. It is very hard to get into God's heavenly country club.  Santa Claus is another matter. He's cute. He's non-threatening. He's always cheerful. And he loves animals. He may know who's been naughty and who's been nice, but he never does anything about it. He gives everyone everything they want without thought of a quid pro quo. He works hard for charities, and he's famously generous to the poor. Santa Claus is preferable to God in every way but one: There is no such thing as Santa Claus.    I use these two quotes to introduce a core question:   Are people responsible for their own actions, or is society responsible for the actions of its people?   What's so core about that? Well consider in the above debate regarding education. One thing that is not touched by either party is the role of the parent in education. That is a taboo topic and nobody wants to go there. In my opinion that has made both parties default into the premise that society is responsible for the education of its citizenry. That may be a no-brainer to some. But, if you will honestly look at some of the "failures" in our educational system, I think you would have to acknowledge contributory failures in parenting. An involved parent will cause a child to study, whether or not the classroom has computers. An involved parent will expect a level of behavior by their child. An involved parent will communicate to their child the importance of education, and that the child will have a good education whether said child wants one or not.  This is why you can have an individual parent triumph over the (documented) failure of a particular school system. An involved parent will always outperform a school that has had a child handed over to it for rearing. (It is not really fair to expect schools to do what we are expecting them to do.) I speak from personal experience as a child and a parent. I and my child did not go to school in a vacuum. I succeeded where others failed, and my child succeeded where others failed. I know first hand in my case, and anecdotally in my child's case, that our successes are attributable to parenting, NOT to the school (if it was just the school, everyone would have succeeded). And most certainly, the presence or lack of money in the school system had nothing to do with our education.  Based on this, in my opinion, both parties act liberal regarding education. They act as if they believe society is the answer to the problem, not individual parenting.   Human Potential   Let's look at the old saw,  If you give a man a fish, you feed him for an hour, if you teach a man to fish, you feed him for a lifetime.   That is only true if the man will actually go and fish. And whether he will go and fish depends on the quality of the character of that man. If his character is of one sort, even if you teach him to fish if someone will still give him a fish, he won't fish. And if his character is of another sort, he will walk past free fish stands and go and catch his own.  The issue then becomes, do you expect him to fish, or do you decide to give him a daily fish? If you are pragmatic, and you are looking long term, you know that he can fish. But you also know that he may or may not fish depending on if he is hungry and if he thinks he can get a fish without effort.  1. If you believe in the potential of that human being, you will expect him to fish. If he does not, he can go hungry. When he is hungry enough, he will go and fish, and find out maybe that he kind of enjoys being self-sufficient. And he becomes a productive member of society and society is better off. (Or he might steal, and if he gets caught, he'll be put in jail.)  2. If you do not believe in the potential of that man, you may teach him to fish, but you really won't expect him to. Meanwhile, he's got to eat. The only right thing to do is feed him. Hopefully, you can encourage him to get up and face the world again, after he is fed. But we are a wealthy society, so feed the man, already! (And, he won't need to steal if we take care of his basic needs.)  The first example is seen as cold hearted and unfeeling. The second example is seen as caring and just and good.  If you have kids, do they all have the ability to clean their own rooms? If the answer is yes, will they clean their rooms if you don't tell them to? Some will, and some won't. A parent has two basic approaches:  1. They are made to clean their rooms, whether they want to or not. You believe they will learn life lessons that will help them as they get older. As in 'One day you'll thank me'. You know they can do it, and you are not going to let laziness or other priorities keep them from doing basic things they have to do. It doesn't matter if they are happy or not. It matters that they do it. Happy and unhappy are temporary states of affairs. They'll get over it. Meanwhile, the room needs cleaning.  2. Some kids will clean their rooms on their own, and some won't. Hey, they're kids! Who wants to clean rooms? I've got time, I'll clean it for them. Some day they will see what I've done for them, and they will thank me. Meanwhile, the room gets cleaned, and all my kid's friends think I'm really cool. Besides, it makes me feel good. Not like those other bastard task master parents that force their will on their kids. Why can't they see it my way? It's all so obvious. (condescending sigh)  To me, the examples marked "1." expect individuals to do what they are supposed to do, or face consequences. The examples marked "2." expect nothing, hope for everything, and wonder why everyone else can't see the light.  In the sets of examples above, the ones marked "1" are conservative world views. The ones marked "2" are liberal. You will note that the liberal world view also wonders why everyone doesn't feel like they do. Meanwhile the conservative world view doesn't care if you agree or not. They are going to do what they think is right, and expect you to do what you think is right.  And so it goes in the political party system. The Republicans expect people to take care of themselves. They believe that they can. The Democrats believes that society should take care of everyone. They believe some people can't get by on their own, and that a civilized society should take care of them. Republicans believe that the percentage of people who  really  can't get by on their own is smaller by several orders of magnitude than what Democrats are hoping for at election time.  Republicans believe in individual human potential, and expect people to live up to their potential. They don't want people to suffer, but see a lot of suffering as self inflicted. This is perceived as haughty and uncaring by liberals.  Democrats believe in collective societal potential, and expect people to sign up for that belief. They don't believe people should ever suffer, and that it is a failure of society when people do suffer, regardless of the reason. And they feel good about believing that. This is perceived as elitist and condescending by conservatives.  Personally, I believe in human potential, and I believe there should be consequences for your actions, if only as object lessons for other individuals to learn from. You should learn from your own mistakes, but I can't make you. I don't want you to suffer, but that is largely up to you, since I believe you have the wherewithal to make better decisions. Ψ
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Submitted for your approval: The introduction of a new verb into the common blogosphere vernacular.  To michaelmoore is much more than to simply take things out of context. To michaelmoore is to take someone's comments or story or post and create a fiction from that post and present it as fact attributed to that person.  Example post:   Such  is life! First I went to  my  car and discovered I had a flat tire. Then I had to deal with the spare being flat. I called Triple A and some guy came out named  Dick . Now, I know this is a version of Richard. But given the various other possible meanings for that name, I can't help but wonder why people name their kids that. One day at work we were processing a new hire. His social security card said "Richard Head." I looked at him and said, "You go by Richard, don't you." He sighed and said "Yes." I mentioned this story to the Triple A guy. He laughed and we had a pretty good conversation about names we give our children. What started as a bad day gave me a great idea for my next post!   Example post after being michaelmoored:   Elsewhere, Frater Bovious wrote: "Such(sic) my Dick."   See, the genius part of michaelmooring is the creation of an alternate "reality." The above is made more effective by the masterful addition of "(sic)." That parenthetical word, from the Latin for "Thus; so", is used when quoting someone else and indicates "...that a surprising or paradoxical word, phrase, or fact is not a mistake and is to be read as it stands..." However, over time, it has also been used to indicate when quoting misspelled words from the original, to prevent the impression that the person doing the quoting actually misspelled the word.  Of course, in my original post the word was not misspelled; therein lies the genius. Not only do I have my words completely misrepresented, I appear uncouth. I also look like I can't type and that I don't bother to spellcheck my posts. Yet, it can be factually stated that I wrote those words. Diabolical!  Whenever you have some faux reality twisted out of one or your posts, you can simply reply, "Whatever. I was michaelmoored. Here's the link to what I really said."  The potential uses for this new verb are limitless.  Ψ
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blog blog blog blog. Lovely blog! Wonderful blog! Blog blo-o-o-o-o-og blog blo-o-o-o-o-og blog. Lovely blog! Lovely blog! Lovely blog! Lovely blog! Lovely blog! Blog blog blog blog! 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Offered as a sort of sanity/reality check to Fahrenheit Blair Witch 9/11 Project.   I think one very interesting excerpt from  urlLink this article  is this:   Clarke's tenure as America's top counterterrorism official is essentially contemporaneous with the Clinton administration. Before Bill Clinton took office, it was assumed that major terrorist attacks against the United States were state sponsored. Clinton turned a national security issue, focused on punishing terrorist states, into a law enforcement issue, focused on arresting and convicting individual perpetrators.  This fundamental policy shift was fundamentally flawed. People with nothing to lose aren't afraid of anything. Nations, and national leaders, have a self interest that cannot be denied. However, our voting populace prefers flash and dash to boring substance.  (Which explains why movie and rock stars are successful in speaking to the young and liberal. There is no there, there, and it does not matter to the fawning idolators, since what they are attracted to is style and a certain experience of closeness to an untouchable benevolent aristocracy; a giddiness at rubbing virtual elbows with the high and mighty.)   Anyway, if this article by Laurie Mylroie, a former adviser on Iraq to the 1992 Clinton campaign, can be given any credence, the Iraq - al Qaeda connection seems to have substance.  Which, by the way, neither Bush, nor anyone in his top administration, ever stated that Saddam was part of 9/11. I'm really tired of hearing that. Ψ  
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       If you haven't seen this, well, you have to. Go now. It is a long time loading, but it is definitely worth the wait. Ψ    urlLink JibJab 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Political Affiliation and Demographics              Republican/Democrat Party Affiliation and Conservative/Liberal Identification    I've scoured the Web for interesting polls, studies, and opinions (Click title above and see excerpts below) detailing the personal and socio-economic characteristics that may predict a person's ideological leanings or party affiliation.     Some generally accepted political stereotypes are validated by statistical tendencies: Republicans/conservatives are more likely to have higher incomes, members of minority groups are more likely to be Democrats/liberals, etc.      Statistically, you're more likely to be a Republican and/or conservative if you're:   a man   a college graduate   in the top income bracket   an evangelical Christian   living in a rural area   a Thinker-Sensor     Statistically, you're more likely to be a Democrat and/or liberal if you're:   a woman   a senior citizen   gay   nonwhite   living in an urban area   a Feeler-Intuitor 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink       It has started already.&nbsp; I managed to catch part of Bill Clinton's bullshit (speech) at the Democratic National Crapfest and almost lost my damn supper.&nbsp; Why doesn't anyone question the Dem's assertions? &nbsp;According to Bill, who has an impeccable record of honesty, the GOP is going to do away with Social Security to line the coffers of the rich.&nbsp; What the hell is that?&nbsp; Of course, there is a significant portion of America that believes that crap!   My favorite ruse is when Bill, Al, and John F. Kerry claim to be for the common man and against the wealthy.&nbsp; Did anyone ever notice that all of them have money coming out their ass?   I guess they must be okay though, since all of those celebrities are on their side.   It's only day one - more to come!     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So, uh, what was that all about?    (Click on above title. Read carefully. Ask yourself what does it all mean?)  Those kwazy Democrats!  Take Hillary, for example. I just finished listening to her introduce her husband. The praise she heaped on Bill was matched only by her minimal acknowlegement of Kerry. What could her goal be? I believe  urlLink this person  may know.  Ψ  
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Screams outrageous headline in vain attempt by obscure blogger to drive traffic to his blog.   Attempting to capitalize on the prurient nature of humanity, he also offered a link to  a graphic depiction of a  urlLink clam  being cleaned and trimmed without even mentioning the Madonna/Brittany kiss.  Then, sadly, he tried to redeem himself through a sort of public service announcement by linking to an  urlLink Actual Clambake Synopsis.   The obscure blogger's significant other raised an eyebrow, fearing that this sexing up of the Glob Blog would compromise the journalistic integrity of the Glob.  "Bwaaaaaaaaaa-ha-ha-hahahahah!" was his reply. Ψ
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In these trying times, it is important to have some sort of respite, some escape, where one can relax and enjoy the company of good people and lively conversation. Yet, these days, even simple relaxation becomes a chore as we fret over the various health aspects of what we are drinking. Well, first of all "Phooey" on that. Secondly, "Slainte" and please note the following facts.    GUINNESS® DRAUGHT   196 CALORIES PER PINT Semi-skimmed milk             260 CALORIES PER PINT	 Orange juice                         220 CALORIES PER PINT     Raise A Pint Of Guinness To Your Good Health  By KEVIN HUNT Hartford Courant  Source: The Milwaukee Journal Sentinel   A man walks into a bar, orders a 12-ounce bottle of Corona Extra. Another man walks in, orders a 12-ounce Guinness draft. The two men turn to each other; raise their glasses and say, "Here's to your health."   Question: Whose dietary and health interests are better served by the 12-ounce beer?   If the guidelines are less alcohol, fewer calories, fewer carbohydrates -- and, to top it off, protection against heart attacks, blindness and maybe even impotence -- then it's the Guinness drinker, hands down.   No joke.   Guinness, in fact, is lower in alcohol, calories and carbohydrates than Samuel Adams, Budweiser, Heineken and almost every other major-brand beer not classified as light or low-carb. It has fewer calories and carbohydrates than low-fat milk and orange juice, too. Could this be the same Irish stout that looks like a still-life root beer float and tastes about as filling as a Quarter Pounder with cheese? Yes, the same Guinness that beer expert Michael Jackson (the British king of hops) calls the world's classic dry stout. It's a favorite of Bono (obviously), Madonna (with a good cigar) and Matt Damon (no, Guinness does not make teeth unnaturally white).     Low in alcohol   This tastes-great, more-filling formula defies nutritional expectations because Guinness is so low in alcohol, a source of empty calories. Guinness is 4.2% alcohol by volume, the same as Coors Light. Budweiser and Heineken check in at 5%.   "That surprised me," says Joseph Brennan, a Yale-New Haven Hospital cardiologist of Irish heritage and a confirmed Guinness drinker. "I could never understand why one or two wouldn't leave me light-headed." Brennan, like many cardiologists, recommends a drink a day for his cardiac patients. Red wine, in particular, has been shown to help prevent heart attacks. Now, maybe it's beer's turn. A University of Wisconsin study last fall found that moderate consumption of Guinness worked like aspirin to prevent clots that increase the risk of heart attacks.      Take, er, drink your vitamins   In the study, Guinness proved twice as effective as Heineken at preventing blood clots. Guinness is loaded with flavonoids, anti- oxidants that give the dark color to many fruits and vegetables. These anti-oxidants are better than vitamins C and E, the study found, at keeping bad LDL cholesterol from clogging arteries. Blocked arteries also contribute to erectile dysfunction, as does overindulgence in alcohol. Guinness has a higher concentration than lighter beers of vitamin B, which lowers levels of homocysteine, linked to clogged arteries. And researchers have found that anti-oxidants from the moderate use of stout might reduce the incidence of cataracts by as much as 50%.   In Ireland, where the slogan "Guinness Is Good for You" was born, the stout's medicinal uses are the stuff of legend. Diageo, the U.S. distributor of Guinness, makes no claims about its medical benefits, spokeswoman Beth Davies says from the company's offices in Stamford, Conn. But a visitor to Ireland might hear accounts (most no longer, if ever, true) of Guinness administered to nursing mothers, blood donors, stomach and intestinal post-operative patients and mothers recovering from childbirth. "Pregnant women and racehorses, one a day," says Michael Foley of Wethersfield, Conn., standing over a pint of Guinness in the subterranean bar at the Irish American Home Society in Glastonbury, Conn. Racehorses? Foley, who left Castlemaine, County Kerry, 43 years ago but retains a Guinness-thick brogue, returns a cocked-head glance that says, loosely translated from Gaelic, "Duh."    "It's made from barley, you know," he says.   (C) 2004 The Milwaukee Journal Sentinel. via ProQuest Information and Learning Company; All Rights Reserved  Thanks to Blake for this important health article.
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Last Rafter Leaves Cuba
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a note to introduce myself since Frater Bovious asked me to feel free to post here. He can fill you in on other details, but basically I am here because I know personally many of the bloggers here and I have a different point of view on many issues, and I am willing to listen to reason and think you are too.   I will not be a rabid blogger with daily posts and challenges. I will probably comment on some posts, and sometimes present a link to something I found interesting or educative.   I'm happy for the hospitality offered and I created my own little blog with no big plans to do anything with it, so visit if you wish.   A toast to reason, friends!
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        The only barrier/sterotype that will not be overcome   By Mark Connolly Editor, Dallas Bureau  I wish to posit that virtually all struggles between peoples can be reduced to real or perceived differences between those that see themselves as having, and those that see themselves as having not. This cannot be oversimplified into a generic all-encompassing statement about anyone or any society however. Just like a man ‘Jim’ can at once be both Father and Son, each person or group or society can at one time be among the Haves, and at another time be among the Have-nots as those are defined within relationships. There are the rich that have plenty to eat everyday, as compared to those that do not. There are the rich that drive BMW’s as compared to those that drive an old jeep bought at auction from the Post Office. There are the rich that own Gulf Stream business jets as compared to those that can only afford LearJets.  There are those that are Christian as opposed to Pagans. Those that are Moslems as compared to the Infidels. One supposes to have the truth while the other are supposed to have not. There are those that have light skin and those that have not. There are those that have freedom as compared to those that have not.  And reverse all of those depending on your personal situation. Today in Iraq there is no doubt that there are those people that preferred the (in retrospect) stability and safety of the old dictatorship as compared to the (current) utter chaos of ‘freedom.’  On the global stage, (I think) America is largely perceived as having, and much of the world is perceived as having not. But what America is perceived as having varies widely. We have wealth, we have debauchery. We have freedom, we have arrogance. We have charity, we have unbridled greed. We have the best intentions, we have the worst intentions. (Hmmmm, that sounds familiar somehow… best times worst times, perhaps a novel in there somewhere?)  All of this wouldn’t matter much if it didn’t engender hatred as a collateral effect of noticing these differences. And that is the part of this that I don’t understand, and wonder if it can be dealt with. Even among my own family differences of opinion can flash into anger. And we are all from the same basic socio-economic-religious background!  I believe People tend to think in a collage of future probababilities that range from downright fantastic to very pragmatic. But we emote in the now, often in a very disconnected way, and then use the awesome power of our minds to validate the emotion of the moment. That can become exhausting, physically and emotionally, hence the phenomenon “Birds of a feather flock together.”  Are we, should we, can we, be a global flock? I’m not sure there is enough common ground for determining the basic issues. So, I wonder if that is a realistic concept. And I don't believe it feasible to simply distribute everything equally and  Oila! , no problems. You'll not get any agreement on what is important and what needs to be distributed equally. Because someone will see themselves as having the right to distribute and someone else as not being equipped to decide.  The reason I think all this matters is because I believe that it is only in consideration of these concepts that the issue of Terrorism can be dealt with or resolved. Who or what is a terrorist? Well, among other things a terrorist is also a mother, father, brother, sister, son, daughter. They may or may not belong to this or that branch of some religion or race. They may be 'disenfranchised' in reality or in their minds. Or someone else's mind.  We focus on Arab/Muslim today, due to current events. But there are terrorists in Japan, Ireland, America, etc. It is pretty clear to me that the motives and methods of a "terrorist" in Ireland are not identical to those in Iraq. So, the class of  Terrorist  is insufficiently defined, and consequently oversimplified at the moment to someone in a turban.  People often rush to Answers without considering the Questions. Some questions I have been asking myself are:  What is the source of terrorist behavior? Is there common ground for dialog? Is there potential for common dialog? If not, what then? Why 'terrorism' instead of some other avenue? Would someone recognize another potential avenue even if presented?   And then, what if the motive is simply extermination of Infidels? What is the civilized response? Historically, it has been kill or be killed. Can we move beyond that?   What is to be done about it in a world that will perennially be populated by Haves and Have-nots?  Genocide or Religicide cannot be the answer.  Ψ
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Most of staff on vacation on the coast of Texas  Riding in car: Frater Bovius, Madame Boverie, Froggy, and two more people yet to be determined.  Stowed in back of Global Exclaimer Suburban: beach wear, alcohol, fishing gear, food stuffs, travel humidor, Barista Espresso Machine for espresso and cappucinos.  Alcohol acoutrements: Bombay Sapphire Gin, Vermouth, Travel Martini glasses, martini shaker, blender, vodka, Mudslide mix, Pina Colada fixins, olives.  Contents of Humidor: Perdomo Cabinet Series S; JR Alternate Padrons; JR Alternate Monte Cristo #2s; Cuban Cohibas, Romeo y Julietas, Punch Grand Crus. Enough for three a day for the duration (though, being a man of moderate appetite, two a day is probable.)  Contents of beach house: Two grandmothers for cooking. 8 couples. 3 unattached children.  Daily agenda: Wake up at some point. Eat something. Recline on the beach. Drink and smoke and swim and fish. Eat at sporadic intervals. Nap. Sleep. Contemplate the serene majesty of ocean and sky. Recall Spanish saying: "How beautiful to do nothing and to rest after."  Alternate activities: Read, stroll on beach, turn over and bronze other side.  Side attractions: Cell phones inoperative. No house phone. No newspaper. TV will mysteriously fail for duration, unless someone really really needs to play Grand Theft Auto.  Posting to continue upon return.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am going to use this space to shamelessly plug my own blog! For a while now, I have been documenting some of the funny, bizarre, and downright sad events that have occurred while I was on duty in my previous life as an Assistant Manager in a grocery store.  I invite everyone to visit ( urlLink www.grocerytales.blogspot.com ) and comment as you see fit. Granted, my blog may not be as thought-provoking as the Glob Blog, but there may be something there you might find interesting.  I will try to post at least once or twice per week.  Daver 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What ever happened to the days when the President of the United States was our president?  It seems that those days are gone.  Nowadays, you hear all kinds of people claiming “He’s not my president!”  More disturbing than that, however, is the venom with which people speak of our current Commander-in-Chief.  In a good portion of America, there is downright hatred for the man.  I can’t believe some of the things I hear people say.  I have heard President Bush compared to Adolf Hitler, he has been likened to being a terrorist, he has been called a liar, and some people are claiming that he knew the September 11 attacks were coming and did nothing to stop them, supposedly for personal gain.  Come on!  How ludicrous are some of those accusations?  The man lives in this country, his family and friends live in this country, etc.  You folks in the GOP don’t get out of this one easy, either.  Remember some of the awful things said about President Clinton?  How he supposedly sent troops to Kosovo to cover up his sexual indiscretions, etc.?  I will admit that I have been guilty of calling him the “Commander-in-Heat” on more than one occasion.  The nation is becoming more polarized almost every day.  We are so focused on name calling and party bashing that we are creating more hatred, rather than focusing on the issues.  How about focusing on the issues and hearing what they have to say, instead of hating either one of them?  I don’t know about you, but I don’t know either one of them personally, so I don’t feel like I have the right to hate them.  I can only agree or disagree with their record or their ideology and vote accordingly.  I urge everyone to get educated on the serious issues of this campaign and make an informed choice this November! 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is how Madame Boverie travels.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink MY WAR - Fear And Loathing In Iraq: One Enemy K.I.A.   Sometimes you need a teaser to get you interested. So, here's a teaser, if you will forgive the choice of words.  After you absorb the post, read the comments. I especially would like to point out the comment by "this we'll defend". This is real shit, and two men talking and dealing with real shit. We have a unique window into a world probably only protrayed in the past through stories by the likes of Hemingway. Read the current Hemingways live.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I have an interesting question.  At least interesting to me.  If most Vietnam vets smoked pot, then most of them probably did it because they liked how they felt when they were high. If smoking the pot (ganga, wacky weed, thaistick, sinsemilla, red hair) did not create a high, I deduce they would not have continued smoking pot. Keep following me here. Now, I am certain that you can only get high by smoking it yourself. However, you can either smoke it right, the way you do it to achieve the desired results, which is inhaling; or you can not inhale it and never get high, rather than waste your time smoking it for no reason.  Which brings me to my question. If  'nam vets got high, what are the odds Kerry did? And, did he inhale? Did he ever smoke a Cheech and Chong joint? Think of all the pot he can buy with Teresa's money? Wow, he can even sell it and gain revenues... tax free. Wait, I think I might be onto something. Maybe Bush's plan cuts into his ability to make money on the side selling dope to other countries... blowing his cover and making him broke and potless. Finally, another reason for this lifetime politician to run for President.  Did you ever hear the story about one of the band members from Pink Floyd who did a hit of acid and never came back down from his trip? I wonder if that is possible with pot? I wonder if that is Kerry's excuse for all his flip flopping? Yo dude, I forgot I voted for that.   
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Uncle Buck wrote:  Very interesting!   Did you know the 9/11 commission report is free on line? There is an exec summary that you can get through pretty quickly (24 pages). The full report is available as well. I have my opinions, look at this and give me yours    urlLink 9/11 report     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    How the Spiritual Advocate gets around.
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       In Plano, Texas, Lisa Diaz drowned her two children, ages 7 and 3. She admitted she did it, there was evidence that she did it. Her defense team never tried to refute that she did it. She was found  not guilty  by reason of insanity.  While it may be true that this woman is truly insane, how can she be found not guilty? This is my problem with the system. She did it – she is guilty. End of story.  I am not saying that her insanity should not be an issue. I believe it is a very real issue, but it is an issue for the punishment phase, not the trial phase. I don’t believe that a truly insane person should be put in the general population at the big house. They should be confined to a mental hospital and receive the appropriate care for however long is appropriate.  The fact that she murdered her two innocent children needs to be permanently attached to her record. What if the shrinks and the judge decide that her insanity was a temporary situation and release her into the world? Oh, you say, she isn’t really a danger to anyone else, why shouldn’t she go free? I’ll tell you.  My wife and I have recently signed up to teach pre-schoolers in Sunday School every week. As part of the process, we filled out a questionnaire so that the church could make sure we don’t pose a danger to the little ones. One of the questions on the questionnaire was “Have you ever been convicted of a crime?”  Now, imagine that your child is attending Sunday School and Lisa Diaz is signed up to help. She could truthfully answer “No” to the conviction question. Do you not think it is important that you, as a parent, know that she held her two beautiful girls under the water in the bathtub until they were dead?  I think it is pretty damn important. She should have been found guilty and then her sanity could have been assessed and addressed later.  I am not condemning the jury. They did their job. It is the legal system that didn’t do it’s job!  
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "... Tremendous breakthrough", says ACLU spokes-person. "This case represents a giant leap in the right direction."   Dateline: Massachusetts  Exact details are sketchy, but what is known is that a woman, known only as "Jane Doe" gradually fed her two day old baby into a food processor.  In arguments before the court, Ms. Doe's lawyer, Mr. Sharq, argued that the alleged murder was in fact an abortion. Mr. Sharq noted that Ms. Doe had not wanted the pregnancy, but didn't know that federally funded abortions were her right as a woman. As she did not have enough money to pay for an abortion, she had been forced to bear an unwanted child. The lawyer then focused on the legality of abortions, centering on the viability of the fetus.  Noting that in the  Roe v Wade  decision the Supreme Court had left the ultimate determination of the viability of the fetus up to the doctor, Mr. Sharq then called in a pediatrician as expert witness. The pediatrician, responding to Mr. Sharq's pointed questions, admitted that a new born baby was just as helpless as a fetus. Elaborating, he acknowledged that a new born was just as dependent on the mother for survival immediately after birth, as before. With the term "viability" hinging on survivability outside the womb, the pediatrician commented that a baby wasn't able to survive "on its own..." until it was able to feed itself. A newborn, not being able to feed itself, would not survive outside the womb on its own, and was therefore not viable. In summation, Mr. Sharq said, "So, a new born is in actuality simply a post-uterine fetus, and a non-viable one at that." Turning to the judge, he continued, "A non-viable fetus is subject to abortion, under the laws of this land."  The court then focused on the grisly manner in which Jane Doe had disposed of her baby. In testimony, Ms. Doe asserted that she had only heard of two methods of abortion, suction and D&C. When vacuuming the baby did not have the desired result, she resorted to D&C, or chopping the baby into little pieces.  The court dismissed the charges. The judge, in the written opinion, noted that "in court case after court case the right of a woman to terminate an unwanted pregnancy has been upheld as an interpreted constitutional right. As the natural result of pregnancy is a child, it can be argued that the prevention of an unwanted child is implied. Further the Supreme Court has rejected the notion that a fetus is a human being entitled to protection under the Constitution. It has been here established that a new born is simply a post-uterine fetus. As such it has no standing under the law, and no crime has been committed. May God help us all."   In a related story, you will no doubt be fascinated to learn that in  Santa Clara County v The Southern Pacific Railroad (1886) the Supreme Court ruled that a corporation was a "person" under the meaning of the Fourteenth Amendment. It is Unconstitutional to pass laws applied specifically to corporations and not to flesh and blood persons, as such laws deny corporate "persons" civic equality. (Conlin, The American Past, A Brief History. Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Copyright 1991)
    
</post>


</Blog>