<Blog>


<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     Check out my photoblog at     urlLink GreatestCities  .  urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        In a quick turnabout, the   urlLink Sudan Tribune   reports that UNSG Kofi Annan said yesterday that a US resolution in the Security Council could be approved if presented soon. The draft resolution would give the Sudanese government 30 days to disarm the Janjaweed and impose am immediate arms embargo on the Darfur region. The change in circumstance leaves one to assume that Russia and China have dropped objections that seemed to make any resolution against Sudan a non-starter. A draft of the new UN resolution is available   urlLink here  .  The resolution does not speak to the possible need for a no-fly zone in Darfur due to the fact that aerial bombardments by government planes of villages has often preceded attacks by the Janjaweed according to refugee accounts nor does it make any statement concerning whether genocide is occuring in Darfur.  Matters on the UNSC resolution vote are complicated by some recent developments…the delivery of Russian MiG fighter planes to Sudan ahead of schedule and the connection of Chinese oil companies and interests in Western Sudan.    
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Although there is a similarity in name to John Garang's Sudanese Peoples Liberation Army or Movement SPLA/M operating out of Southern Sudan, it should be noted that according to all the news sites that I am reading and the reports, there is no coalition between the SLA/JEM organizations operating in the provinces of Northern and Southern Darfur and the SPLA/M. But, Garang did acknowledge that he does support the aims of the SLA while simultaneously denying any ties. To add onto the confusion here, the Sudanese Liberation Army was formerly known as the Darfur Liberation Front.    Well, it all seemed to start sometime in February 2003 according to the   urlLink Sudan Tribune  ...here's an early timeline of the crisis in Darfur:    "February 26: Khartoum says a rebel movement, the Darfur Liberation Front (DLF), has taken control of the town of Gulu, capital of Jebel Marrah province.    March 14: Rebels claiming to belong to the Sudan Liberation Movement/Army (SLM/A), the renamed DLF, demand that Khartoum step up economic development in the region and better distribute the wealth.    March 26: Rebels say they have taken Tine on the border with Chad.    April 12: Sudanese President Omar al-Bashir and his Chadian counterpart Idriss Deby pledge to restore stability along their common border."    The goals of the SLA and JEM have been stated by several different sources as (1) reform of the central government in so far as it currently favors those that live in Northern Sudan and (2) greater autonomy for all of Darfur. More precise aims can be found in examining the   urlLink 2003 Political Declaration of the SLA   which states: "The objective of SLM/A is to create a united democratic Sudan on a new basis of equality, complete restructuring and devolution of power, even development, cultural and political pluralism and moral and material prosperity for all Sudanese." The SLA is the largest rebel group in the nation with around 13,000 members and when working with the JEM, the Darfurian rebel groups number a little over 20,000.    Unlike the SLA, the Justice and Equality Movement has signed cooperative agreements with other organizations, one such example was within the last week and is detailed by the   urlLink Overseas Security Advisory Council  :    "...The agreement [was] signed last week between the Free Lions Movement (FLM), and the Sudan Justice and Equality Movement (JEM). The FLM is based in Eastern Sudan most of its members belong to Beja tribes, the JEM is one of two acting rebel movements in Western Sudan. This agreement was signed in Asmara on Thursday July 15, by Khalil Ibrahim for the JEM and Mabrook Mubark Salim for the FLM."    The Free Lions Movement is an Eastern Sudanese rebel group asking for greater political autonomy for the Beja tribe living in Northeast Sudan.    The Leader of the Justice and Equality Movement is Khalil Ibrahim.   The Leader of the Sudanese Liberation Army is Abdel Wahid Mohamed Ahmed Nur.    For more information on the Sudanese Liberation Army and the Justice and Equality Movement, please see the following links:   urlLink  Information on the SLA/JEM      urlLink  Justice and Equality Movement/JEM Homepage  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I wanted to pull from a couple of sources in an honest attempt to understand as much as possible concerning just who the Janjaweed are. I want to begin my entry with one possible reason for Khartoum's quasi-sponsorship of the Janjaweed's genocidal campaign in Darfur because it has been mentioned twice in stories I have read....an oil pipeline that would pass through the region. Once I have more information, I will hopefully elaborate.   While Darfur has been the site of conflict between the more than 80 different ethnic groups that reside there over wells and other natural resources since the 1980's due to the effects of prolonged desertification, conflict has escalated in magnitude to its present proportions only recently. The current level of conflict in Darfur began in February 2003.    This is part of an interesting article from David Hoile of the European-Sudanese Public Affairs Council in the   urlLink Media Monitors Network   summarizing a nuanced answer to the question:    Who are the "Janjaweed"?         "The term "Janjaweed" has been used as a blanket term to describe most of the "Arab" gunmen active in Darfur today. The UN has described the "Janjaweed" as being made up of "Sudanese and Chadian horse and camel- riding Arab nomads, opportunists and 'criminals'" (1) There can be no simple analysis of the issue. (2) Darfur is an ecologically-fragile area and had already been subject to growing - and often armed - conflict over access to water and pastures. The war has greatly exacerbated previously-existing tensions. In perhaps the most objective reading of the crisis in Darfur, the UN media service observed: "The conflict pits farming communities against nomads who have aligned themselves with the militia groups - for whom the raids are a way of life - in stiff competition for land and resources. The militias, known as the Janjaweed, attack in large numbers on horseback and camels and are driving the farmers from their land, often pushing them towards town centres." (3) There is also no doubt that these militias, and criminal gangs, have exploited the security gap which opened up in Darfur following the murder by rebels of over 400 policemen and the destruction of dozens of police stations in a region the size of France or California in which law enforcement infrastructure was already badly stretched.   The UN media service has reported "that there was nothing new about tribal clashes between nomads of Arabic extraction and village farmers belonging to local African tribes in Darfur, but these days they have become much more deadly because the raiders were better armed." A foreign diplomat noted: "The Janjawid have kept their traditional values and ways of living. They do the same as they used to: they steal to get. Only this time, their weapons are more sophisticated". (4)    "It has also become apparent that the Darfur issue has been caught up in the sort of propaganda and misinformation that has characterised previous coverage of Sudan. Several commentators appear to have opted for a partisan or lazy analysis of events in Darfur, seemingly unable to resist projecting the image of government-supported "Arab" - "Janjaweed" - militias attacking "African" villagers (and in doing so often merely echoing questionable rebel claims). This has been done despite the scarcity of reliable information. United Nations media sources, for example, have noted "a lack of accurate information on the conflict" (5) and Reuters has also stated that "it is hard to independently verify claims by government or rebels in Darfur." (6) Commentators have consistently reported - and attributed - human rights abuses within Darfur in circumstances in which independent confirmation of such assertions is impossible. The New York Times, while echoing many of these allegations of human rights abuses, was candid enough to admit that "it is impossible to travel in Darfur to verify these claims". (7)"    urlLink Wikipedia entry on the Janjaweed    urlLink Information on Musa Hilal, leader of the Janjaweed    The `why' and `when' of the Janjaweed    Julie Flint writing in   urlLink `The Tablet'   does an excellent job of describing one of the myriad reasons why conflict has escalated and when it began:   "The reason the Sudanese Government is targeting the Masalit - and two other African tribes, the Zaghawa and the Fur - is that these three ethnic groups form the backbone of the rebel movements that took up arms in Darfur last year to protect their communities against a 20-year campaign by government-backed militias. Calling for groups of "Arab background" to join forces with them to prevent ethnicity being used as a weapon of war, the rebels demanded "a united democratic Sudan" and an end to political and economic marginalisation.   The rebels attacked at first military and government targets with surprising success. In April 2003, a few hundred fighters succeeded in briefly occupying El-Fasher, the capital of North Darfur state, and destroyed several military aircraft. In May, they briefly occupied Mellit, the second largest town in northern Darfur.   At the end of August 2003, the Janjaweed took over from the police and the army in manning checkpoints in much of Dar Masalit. This could not have happened, nor would it continue to happen, without the full agreement and compliance of the Sudanese Government.   Civilians and rebels I interviewed in the course of 25 days in and around Darfur said the Government had responded to the rebels' successes by fighting along- side the Janjaweed and targeting civilians. Investigations by Human Rights Watch uncovered large-scale killings in 14 incidents in the Masalit area between November 2003 and April 2004. In these 14 incidents, when there were coordinated attacks by the army and Janjaweed, almost 800 civilians died."      
    
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Greg Austin and Ben Koppelman of the London-based Foreign Policy Center in the Globe and Mail   discuss exactly how the atrocities in Darfur can be stopped:     “To end the violence, the UN, the major powers and countries such as Canada must understand that the government they are dealing with is a dictatorship that has directly sponsored terrorist attacks and harboured Osama bin Laden. This government has been subjected several times, usually unsuccessfully, to UN sanctions or unilateral U.S. sanctions. Ultimately, it is government officials who are responsible for the murderous campaigns in Darfur. Until their calculus of political gain is specifically targeted, the violence will not stop. These officials should be publicly named and shamed, and be subjected to personal sanctions, such as freezing bank accounts or banning international travel. Simultaneously, the major powers or the UN should form a working group to document and publicize the war crimes in Darfur quickly and authoritatively.     First, the AU ceasefire monitoring team must be more robust in terms of troops as well as logistical support, especially transport and satellite communications. Darfur is a vast and remote region (as big as France), has a low population density (one-10th that in Rwanda), and has few transport links.   Second, the mandate of the AU troops to protect the monitors should be extended. Their duties must go beyond observing to include protecting refugees and disarming militias, a measure that Mr. Annan identified in 2001 as a necessary adjunct to any UN peacekeeping deployment.   But a necessary condition for diplomacy to succeed is the threat of international military action, especially since the sanctions against Sudan in the late 1990s were not effective. The only way to demonstrate the seriousness of such resolve would be through the contribution of troops from non-Western countries, particularly African and Arab states. A force led by, or even containing troops from, the U.S. or Britain may be out of the question.   Along with threats, there must be incentives. An effective way to end attacks by the militias and their opponents may be to offer cash incentives to them, or communities that support them, to stop fighting. (This worked in Mozambique.) The international community should also provide emergency funds for quick-effect projects to revamp the regional infrastructure.”    urlLink Daniel Wolfe describes how the Janjaweed and Sudanese government cooperate in a Washington Post editorial:    “On the morning of July 12, hell descended on the village of Donki Dereisa. Shortly before sunrise, Fatima Ibrahim, 28, awoke to the deafening sound of exploding ordnance falling from the sky. As she emerged from her mud hut with her 10-year-old daughter, she saw fires blazing all around and scores of heavily armed men on horseback attacking from every direction. With bullets whistling past, Ibrahim and her daughter ran for their lives, ducking into a nearby ravine, where they hid without food or water for the next two days. From the ditch, Ibrahim witnessed a horrific avalanche of violence that will haunt her for life. With Sudanese foot soldiers at their side, the mounted attackers shot the panicked and unarmed villagers in cold blood. Approximately 150 people, including 10 women, were killed. But the worst was to come.”     Concerning humanitarian assistance developments , the Associated Press has compiled a timeline from statistics at the United Nations, here’s a snippet:     About 1.1 million people in Darfur have been forced from their homes and fled to other parts of the region. Another 150,000-200,000 people from Darfur have fled into neighboring Chad, according to the Office for Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs. The population of the three-state region before the conflict was 6 million.      The 17-month-long conflict has led to 30,000 deaths in the region, U.S. Ambassador John C. Danforth has said.      Half a million children are among those forced to flee their homes, according to the U.N. Children's Fund.      Lack of protection from violence is the greatest threat to the population driven from their homes, OCHA says.     Aid workers have been unable to reach 29 of the 137 settlements for internally displaced people because of bad weather, poor infrastructure, insecurity or other reasons.   urlLink French soldiers are participating in airlifts of humanitarian aid to the Chad-Sudan border.   Aid workers and the UNHCR complimented France on the much needed assistance but…“some aid workers in the town said it was frustrating that France, with a military base on their doorstep, had not provided more logistical support earlier in the crisis.”   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Maine delegates at the Democratic National Convention gave Kerry’s acceptance speech glowing reviews according to the   urlLink  Portland Press Herald   :   "It was a great speech," said Ball, who had been pledged to former Vermont Gov. Howard Dean and was looking to Kerry to sound the right themes for the Nov. 2 contest against President Bush. Maine delegates uniformly praised the speech as red, white and blue balloons and confetti fell around them to the floor of the FleetCenter. "It was terrific," said Betty Johnson of Lincolnville. "That was the greatest speech he's ever given." Elaine Makas of Lewiston said she most appreciated one of Kerry's references to his service in Vietnam, where he led a swift boat while earning a Silver Star, a Bronze Star and three Purple Hearts. "He told about us all being together - we're all in the same boat," Makas said. "We're already together."       
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink  The fourth draft of a resolution on Sudan passed with 13 affirmative votes and 2 abstentions coming from the representatives of Pakistan and China.        “China abstained because it felt the measures were unnecessary because it said it believed the Sudanese government has been cooperating and would continue to do so. China hopes and believes that the government of Sudan will continue to actively honor its commitments," including disarming the militias known as the Janjaweed, Ambassador Wang Guangya said.”    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        According to an   urlLink  article on International Law and Genocide    in the Economist, there are ways to get around the obstinacy of China and Russia in the Security Council:    “One way round a possible veto would be to invoke the UN's “uniting for peace” resolution, put forward by the United States in 1950 to overcome the Soviet veto on military intervention in Korea. Under it, the UN's General Assembly may “recommend” measures, including the use of force, to counter a threat to peace, if the Security Council is unable to act…Another possible tack would be to persuade Chad, across whose borders tens of thousands of Sudanese refugees are streaming, to initiate an intervention in Darfur under its right to self-defence. This would obviate the need for a Security Council vote and thereby the threat of a veto. But could Chad be persuaded?”    A muslim force for Iraq and more time of impunity for Darfur   Don’t you find it more than a little ironic to read in the news that US and other countries are considering a ‘muslim force’ for Iraq to replace allies that have withdrawn while refusing to do anything about Sudan? It’s surreal that these two situations can be happening parallel to one another. Pakistan which is determined to allow Khartoum to act with impunity against its own civilians   urlLink  are now ready and willing to send troops to Iraq   .   New draft res is panned     urlLink  The fourth and further watered down version of the resolution on Sudan has been given a big thumbs down by humanitarian assistance groups.    “The key criticism being that it relies too heavily on government actions.”        
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink What is the difference between the third draft resolution that the US and Britain were considering and the fourth draft that was submitted yesterday? Not much according to US Ambassador to the UN John Danforth.   The direct reference to "sanctions" might have been removed but apparently the new draft cites Article 41 of the UN Charter which allows for actions not excluding sanctions in the 'event of noncompliance', so now it is implied.     We will now have to wait and see if this even more diluted of an already diluted resolution The resolution would give the Government of Sudan thirty days to comply with a July 3rd agreement which calls for the GoS to disarm militias and provide relief and protection to internally displaced people and refugees after which the Secretary-General would give a report. Thirty days seems like a long time for a government that has spent 18 months in outright complicity and when 1 000 people are dying per day. Furthermore, hasn't the 'event of noncompliance' already passed a long time ago?     In any event, all eyes are watching the desks of the representatives of Pakistan, China and Russia at the Security Council.   
    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I went to an event during the Bates Dance Festival which is happening until August 14th. And I think that the program I saw counts as a   personal discovery   for myself, the program   urlLink "Dance for the Camera"   presented by Victoria Marks consisted of four short dance films. All four were dazzingly sensual and communicated a sense of warmth and reassurance. The first was called "Touch"   urlLink which depicts four different real-life couples who explore the way touching is experienced.   Victoria Marks in some comments after the showing said that her intent in the film's choreography was to show how the same kind of touching is experience differently for each couple. This first film and another short film called "Mothers and Daughters" which depicted through dance of course, the tumultous yet timeless bond that exists between a mother and her daughter. It was a beautiful thing to behold.    urlLink For more information   on the powerful talent that is Victoria Marks.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Does anyone have some kleenex cause I think I am going to cry. It was very heartening to see in the news that   urlLink  the American Psychological Association has backed gay marriage   . The group has over 150,000 members and will hopefully be able to bring whatever influence it possesses to bear in the fight for full equality for GLBT relationships across the country. The resolution is available   urlLink  here   .   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Barbara Ehrenreich writes a very interesting op-ed piece in today's   urlLink  New York Times    talking about the need for Kerry and the Democratic Party to put some sense in our policies toward improving human rights for women. One of the first steps she recommends is for Congress to ratify the   urlLink  UN Convention on Discrimination against Women   , Ehrenreich points out that it is currently stalled the in Senate while 169 nations around the world have already ratified it.       Recalling that discrimination against women violates the principles of equality of rights and respect for human dignity, is an obstacle to the participation of women, on equal terms with men, in the political, social, economic and cultural life of their countries, hampers the growth of the prosperity of society and the family and makes more difficult the full development of the potentialities of women in the service of their countries and of humanity,   Concerned that in situations of poverty women have the least access to food, health, education, training and opportunities for employment and other needs,   Convinced that the establishment of the new international economic order based on equity and justice will contribute significantly towards the promotion of equality between men and women...      What is the holdup in the Senate? Why would they not taking immediate steps toward affirming the goals of the Convention and toward making these goals a reality for the many women around the world for which these goals are merely a dream right now...       
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        It's 4:42p and I was just watching Rep. Joe Hoeffel speak at the DNC. Some of his first words were prescient: "The fierce urgency of now...demands that we act to stop the genocidal rape and killing in Sudan..." There was a little applause from the crowd..even though these were some pressing words for us to consider...  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Suleia is the latest site of Janjaweed atrocities according to reports from   urlLink AU observers   in Darfur.    The Peace and Security Council of the African Union is pondering the creation of a   urlLink “full-fledged peacekeeping mission”  .    The Washington Post editorial page nails it once more when they ask the question   urlLink “How many more deaths?”    BBC Monitoring summarizes the   urlLink Kenyan press’ coverage    of the crisis in Darfur.    Finally, a blog called the   urlLink “Passion of the Present”   is just incredible in disseminating the latest information about Darfur.      
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I have felt compelled on a daily basis to closely follow developments concerning the ongoing crisis in Darfur, Sudan ever since reading a book on our country's indifference to genocide over the past century. I have also struggled with what exactly is my individual ability to contribute in helping to end such horrendous atrocities. In looking at the news coverage today, I found the following news stories particularly illuminating:    urlLink Sudan conflict coverage from Reuters AlertNet    urlLink Ethnic cleansing campaign unabated    urlLink US, Sudan trade accusations   urlLink  Majority of Americans believe genocide occurring in Sudan    urlLink PBS Lehrer Newshour coverage on Sudan     Yesterday, I talked with someone about Sudan as I have been doing constantly for almost a month to my colleagues and friends and this person told me `that people do not want to hear about this'. It was the most pristine vision of indifference that I have seen in a long time. Others I have talked to said that they feel powerless. A determined and vigilant person is never powerless.    Write your leaders.   It might not be much but yesterday I sent out at least 10 letters to my representative and senators in Congress and Assistant Secretary of State for African Affairs Constance Newman and Secretary of State Colin Powell along with President Bush. You can do this too at   urlLink Congress.com  .      Donate.   You can also donate money to humanitarian and human rights agencies that are working to get aid to the 1,000,000+ people that have been internally displaced and the 200,000+ people that are refugees straddling the Chad-Sudan border.    urlLink World Vision   urlLink CareUSA   urlLink MercyCorps   urlLink USA for UNHCR    The men of Darfur who are being murdered, women of Darfur who are being raped and the children of Darfur who are starving need more than our angst-ridden concern they need our money and they our conscience-driven will to take substantive action that will force Khartoum to end its campaign there.    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        For the first time in its history, the Holocaust Memorial Museum’s Committee on Conscience has declared a   urlLink  Genocide Emergency   …and it is happening in Darfur. On August 2nd, the Museum will open a display entitled “Who Will Survive Today? Genocide Emergency: Darfur” in order to help viewers understand what is happening in Darfur.     
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        In a   urlLink  Rasmussen State Poll    released on July 8th for Maine, the race for the Presidency is as close as can be expected. Kerry 46%, Bush 45% with a ‘mysterious and presumably Nader’ other getting around 5%. Rasmussen’s other conclusions for Maine…Rasmussen has moved the state to the ‘toss-up’ category based on this new information. It also notes that Kerry has less of his base locked up than Bush. (Bush has 86% support among Maine Republicans and Kerry 76% among Maine Democrats.)   A Strategic Marketing Services poll of Maine voters assessed it similarly. Kerry has 43% to Bush’s 41% with Nader taking a 4% cut. That is awfully high for Nader in such a close race, I wonder if that percentage will fall as voting day nears?   Finally according to the   urlLink  Atlas of US Presidential Elections   , voter confidence is leaning Democratic in 3 of Maine’s 4 congressional districts with the other a close ‘toss-up’.     
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         “  urlLink  The United States    said Monday that security in Darfur was Khartoum's responsibility, ruling out for the moment calls for an international peacekeeping force even as it piled more pressure on the Sudanese government for immediate action.  Washington last Thursday put forward a draft UN Security Council resolution authorizing sanctions against Sudan if militia leaders are not brought to justice, while the US Congress unanimously labeled the situation a "genocide".”     Meanwhile…ditto from the White House.   America is currently operating in a conflicted way when attempting to provide some kind of leadership in pressuring Khartoum to rein in the Janjaweed and bring relief to the millions in need in Darfur. The White House, State Department and US Congress seem to each be in different dimensions. President Bush is completely silent, Secretary Powell refuses to call the situation in Sudan anything more than a ‘humanitarian disaster’ and Congress in uncharacteristically unanimous fashion labeled it ‘genocide’. So far, I like the direction in which our legislators are headed, I just wish that Bush and Powell would heed the lesson in leadership that is before them.   Stop shifting the responsibility to act onto Khartoum when the last 15 months have been proof enough that it is not the intent of al-Bashir’s government to stop Hilal and the Janjaweed. Responsibility now lies with the international community.      
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I sent this letter on hearing that he had visited the UN yesterday concerning Darfur and ahead of the possible UNSC vote on a resolution that may 'threaten sanctions':     Hello Representative Payne,  I wanted to tell you that I was pleased to read on the internet that you recently made a visit to UN Secretary-General Kofi Annan concerning the ever-worsening situation in Darfur.   I wanted to ask you a question which I am not all too sure I will receive an answer to: "What was the general sense on the next course of action for the UN with respect to Darfur that you were able to discern?" Do you think that Secretary Annan supports a strong UNSC resolution that might actually influence Khartoum to end the attacks of the Janjaweed and restore some sense of security to the millions of IDPs and refugees?   Finally, I wanted to tell you that I was happy to see in the news that Congress had unanimously agreed that genocide is occurring in Darfur and must be stopped by international intervention.  Thank you.     Oh...props also to Representative Jan Schakowsky who was also at the UN lobbying for an international force in cooperation with an African Union contingent.     
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        First, we must really know what exactly is a swing state or battleground state. According to the glorious   urlLink Wikipedia  :     A swing state is a state full of…yes, swing voters. Which are: “…voters who’re undecided about how they will vote (sometimes, they're called undecideds or simply undecided voters)…they might be dissatisfied Republicans or Democrats who are open to vote for other parties, or people who have never had a strong party affiliation. Others might be people who have not voted before, such as voters just reaching voting age. Because the votes of swing voters are "up for grabs", candidates direct much campaign effort toward them, although they must also be concerned with voter turnout among their political base.”    I’ve only lived in Maine for a little over 7 months but that is probably long enough to realize that Mainers have an independent and quirky streak that is as long as the Appalachian Trail especially when it comes to state and national politics. In   urlLink the 2000 presidential election  , Gore won the state by five percent with Nader taking a six percent cut of the vote. The close margin of victory for Gore here in 2000 along with its unusual but more equitable distribution of electors by congressional district—Nebraska is the only other state that does this—and the fact that   urlLink voter turnout   here is among the highest in the country and the fact that analysts predict this to be the closest elections in more than a half-century makes little ol’Maine one of 17 states that will be crucial to the outcome of the 2004 presidential race.    More ‘politics in the pine tree state’ specifics sometime soon…I presume    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The death toll from conflict in Darfur was once 10 000, then 30 000, and now according to the UN’s news service   urlLink  IRIN   , it may stand at 50 000. 1 000 people are dying per day. Meanwhile, there are 1 500 000 internally displaced people (IDP) who are stuck in and out of refugee camps on the Chad-Sudan border without much assistance and protection from attack by the Janjaweed. The UN has dispatched its special envoy for IDP’s, Francis Deng, to assess their situation. 50 000 dead, 170 000 in refugee camps in Eastern Chad and 1 500 000 who are internally displaced in Darfur.     urlLink  Russia and China    stand accused of blocking efforts to pass a Security Council resolution which would threaten sanctions on the Sudanese government if it did not disarm the Janjaweed.   urlLink  The Netherlands    has also rejected calls for even sanctions. Germany, Japan and France stand accused of an inadequate humanitarian response to the crisis. UN Secretary-General and the World Food Programme called for greater aid to Darfur months ago and apparently the response was paltry as it is still currently. The UN stated today&nbsp;that $200 000 000 more is urgently needed, so far   urlLink  UN agencies    have received only “145 million of the 349 million requested” for humanitarian assistance.   On the peace talks front, the rebel groups ‘Justice and Equality Movement’ and ‘Sudan Liberation Army’ stand accused of obstructing the peace process with Khartoum in an effort to prompt intervention from the international community. This is a new but not too surprising twist. The leader of the Sudanese Liberation Army, Abdel Wahel Mohammed El-Nur said in the   urlLink  New Zealand Herald    today,  “Khalil Ibrahim, head of the rebels' Justice and Equality Movement, said: "JEM will not have any direct contact with the Government and will not start any political negotiations ... until the Government meets preconditions which are the terms of the ceasefire."    So, the JEM and SLA would like to see foreign intervention for the purpose of enforcing the ceasefire, protecting civilians and channeling humanitarian aid to refugees and IDPs. Unfortunately, the grand total of nations ready to oblige stands at only three, yes three…New Zealand, Australia and Britain which have each stated that they would be willing to contribute some 6,000 troops to a UN peacekeeping force that would work towards achieving the three above-mentioned objectives. This is occurring with the backdrop of the impending rainy season and the subsequent inaccessibility of refugee camps without food, medicine or adequate shelter….a macabre recipe for a catastrophe that Khartoum and the Janjaweed may have wanted all along.   A UN peacekeeping force would probably arrive by the end of the year and operate under a mandate justified by   urlLink  Chapter VII of the UN Charter   .      
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Sudan's government has attacked civilians with helicopter gunships. It has armed a militia that burns villages, slaughtering the men and raping the women. It has spent months obstructing humanitarian access to the resulting refugee camps, denying aid workers visas and impounding their equipment in customs, condemning tens of thousands of people to die for lack of food and medicine. Even the recent ramping up of diplomatic pressure, which has allowed relief to flow more freely, has not distracted Sudan's government from its purpose. Its commandants have been closing down refugee camps and sending inhabitants off into the torched countryside, where there is no food, no protection and no foreign witnesses.     This excerpt from a Sunday editorial in the   urlLink  Washington Post    seems to say perfectly what the Sudanese government is guilty of. Why is it that so many nations are unwilling to stop such inhumanity? Don’t we realize that our failure to stop such injustice makes us nothing less than silent accomplices?   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I was watching a talk show on one of the cable news channels when they started talking about some website where you can publicly apologize for practically anything....it's sounded amusing and might be somewhat cleansing...so, I tried it out...my first apology was for not getting back to a friend of mine about accompanying a group down to Boston for the local social forum.       The site is called   urlLink The Apologist   and it is really research for an interesting book titled   urlLink "Eating Crow"  . I don't think its out yet but it is on my 'to read' list now.      On another mundane note: I went $9 over for groceries...Not good but better than last week when I was $24 in the red...yikes    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The world outside of my living room window  urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Today has been pretty uneventful...just not much happening on the mighty Androscoggin. This coming Wednesday, I have to help give the transportation part of a newcomer orientation program...so I have been preparing for that...and cleaning the house...dishes, laundry, bath and bedroom....My little sis', Dominique is heading back to Newport News with little Caden (born on July 6th) in tow and expecting Andy back from his tour out at sea anytime now.          Discoveries:   While volunteering at   urlLink Pepperill Books   yesterday, I found another Carl Sagan book and decided to try it,   urlLink Broca's Brain   is about science and human reason and so far I think it'll be as interesting as the last Sagan book I read. Also, check out the divine sound of   urlLink Jamie Cullum  , from what I have heard so far he is incredible.          On this sunny Sunday in Maine, a friendly reminder: if you are lactose intolerant don't add milk to your oatmeal...otherwise the day could look much like picture above...      
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Slate has a good article on the roots of the 21st century’s first genocide and one of the men who upon whom the architecture of this genocide may be owed. The country’s former attorney-general, Hassan al-Turabi. Incredibly, a man who was responsible for inviting Osama bin-Ladin into Sudan to live and was a longtime ally of al-Beshir’s National Islamic Front has now become the ‘spiritual guide’ of rebel groups in Darfur.  The article by Lee Smith concerning  urlLink “Sudan’s Osama”  is pretty informative.  While reading this article, I was also fascinated by the case of Mahmoud Muhammad Taha. He apparently was executed by the Sudanese government in 1985 for apostasy because he advocated a form of Shari’a that respected human rights. A backgrounder can be found  urlLink here . Now can you guess which form of Shari’a was put into place in 1985?  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Josh Keefe an intern at the   urlLink  Bangor Daily News    has written an engaging op-ed piece on US-Sudan relations. Sometimes, nations would like to avoid looking in the mirror. It is good that there are people at every opportunity holding the mirror high and forcing us not only to remain informed on world affairs but to also forcefully question our foreign policy and envision the nightmarish consequences. Keefe has some particular venom for the Clinton administration bombing of the Al-Shifa pharmaceuticals plant.  Here’s a chunk:     "Where does the blame fall? The Washington Post recently said, “Darfur is a tragedy with many authors,” but the media have ignored one author’s participation. That author is the United States of America, a nation that, on Aug. 20, 1998, used cruise missiles to destroy a pharmaceutical plant in southern Sudan. Then President Clinton said the strike was ordered because the “the factory was involved in the production of materials for chemical weapons.” U.S officials also believed the plant had links to Osama bin Laden, who had ordered the bombing of U.S embassies the week before. Investigators later found no evidence of any sinister operations at the factory.  The incomparable Noam Chomsky discussed the bombing at length in a 2001 interview, citing many articles illustrating the horrific costs of the strike. The factory, named Al-Shifa, “produced 90 percent of Sudan’s major pharmaceutical products,” The Boston Globe’s Jonathan Belke reported a year after the strike. Germany’s ambassador to Sudan wrote in the Summer 2001 edition of the Harvard International Review that “it is difficult to assess how many people in this poor African country died as a consequence of the destruction of the Al-Shifa factory, but several tens of thousands seems a reasonable guess.” James Astill of The Guardian reported that the Al-Shifa factory was the “only one [in Sudan] producing TB drugs — for more than 100,000 patients, at about 1 British pound a month.” Costlier imported drugs were too expensive for an impoverished nation trying to pull itself out of a then 15-year-old civil war.”    
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Now look, I don’t agree with conservatives very often but I was awestruck to read this article in today’s edition of the   urlLink  Guardian   . The statements of the Conservatives’ shadow international development secretary, John Bercow, in this article should be like thunderclaps to those that currently reside in an incorrigible stupor concerning Sudan and the Darfur genocide. He labeled the UN resolution an “essay in timidity”. I think he is right and a little too generous.     Some snippets below.  “John Bercow, the shadow international development secretary, said diplomatic efforts were "too little ... too late" and intervention would be needed.    Tis’ too true, Monsieur Bercow. The article continues:    Asked how soon UK forces should be deployed, Mr Bercow told the BBC:   "I think within a matter of days, if there is not demonstrable evidence of improvement, if we cannot see that there has been a large-scale round-up and arrest of militia leaders."      A “matter of days indeed”. He continues:    "Unless there is evidence of real change, I believe that international action in the name of humanity is needed. All the evidence shows that the government of Sudan responds only to pressure, pressure, pressure and more pressure. There has been too little, and it is too late.    Oy. The article goes on:    Mr. Bercow said he had met Sudanese ministers on a visit to the country last month. "They were in denial about the fact of the atrocities, the scale of the atrocities and the collaboration of the Janjaweed in the commission of the atrocities, so I have no serious hope that they are likely to respect the wishes of the UN security council."   In my lazy lingo: This ain’t no sly meshugganah talk by Bercow. No diplomatic jiving with dictators either as it seems many Western governments are intent on participating in, just an unvarnished but difficult reality.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink  According to Darfuri rebels say that as many as 24 villages have come under attack from the Janjaweed in recent days or weeks:       "On Friday ... a group of Janjaweed attacked four villages 60 kilometers (35 miles) southeast of Nyaya," the capital of South Darfur province, Colonel Abdallah Abdel Kerim told AFP in Libreville by telephone. "The ceasefire commission has been able to verify (the attack) in the first village, Baraka, where the Janjaweed killed 13 people and took cattle and cereals," Abdul Kerim added, saying he had no details regarding the three other villages. The rebel spokesman was referring to a commission set up by the rival sides in Darfur and including Chadian mediators and members of the international community under a peace accord signed for the region in April.   The Organization of Islamic Conferences (OIC) is seeking to convene a foreign ministers meeting concerning Darfur early next week in Cairo. Several nations have agreed to attend. The meeting was requested by the Sudanese foreign minister to develop some ideas on how to deal with the UN resolution. http://www.washtimes.com/upi-breaking/20040802-105344-7061r.htm   urlLink  A truce between the Darfuri rebel groups and the Sudanese government originally signed on April 8th has been extended    after neither side raised any objections. Both sides have accused the other of ceasefire agreement violations. In the   urlLink  Guardian   , Simon Jeffrey provides some background on Darfur with particular overview of what the international community is doing.  Concerning humanitarian assistance, Japan has donated 3 million to the Government of Sudan for the purchase of sorghum for Darfuri refugees and IDPs. Due to the start of the rainy season in Darfur some refugees are inaccessible by road, therefore the World Food Program has begun airlifts of food parcels into areas affected by heavy rains.   urlLink  Four cargo planes are now en route to Sudan from Egypt with medical and structural supplies for Darfuri refugees funded by the Egyptian Red Crescent and government ministries.        
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink The Passion of the Present  continues to cover the actions of the Sudanese government vis-a-vis the meek UN resolution. The operations of the French military on the Chad-Sudan border are also highlighted by some press outlets.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        On Friday night, our interesting adventure in Lewiston began shakily in indecision. We could not decide whether to go see a social commentary on technological progress littered with eye candy of violence (I, Robot) or a political commentary with its usual twists and bends. We ended up seeing Jonathan Demme's remake of a classic political thriller (The Manchurian Candidate). I am probably reading into it what I want to see, but I think most directors don't mind viewers doing that as long as you pay your $8...lol. The movie had four situations, I guess, or comments on contemporary society as it is currently and what its future may be that I though notable.       First, I must say that although Washington, Streep, and Scheiber are superb, I haven't seen the original so I cannot compare them with Lansbury and Sinatra.      On to this movie's commentary threads:    The first thing that I noticed was the complete blending of news and entertainment in the movie's media networks.The runaway trend of 'Infotainment' was an accepted presence and it yielded a formidable influence on the level of debate it seemed. Of course, this is already occurring in what some term the "Fox News" effect. Why can't more American news broadcasts be like the BBC?    Second, the almost scientific targeting of specific areas and specific groups of people by the political parties shallows general debate on major issues. I made this conclusion personally after comparing the increased presence of security with the lack of debate between the political figures in the movie.    Thirdly, speaking of the constant presence of cameras, armed guards and checkpoints at places like schools, libraries and public political events and the presence of an atmosphere where a domestic culture of fear was constantly cultivated and war or close-to-war hostility was engendered created a society where the personally fulfilling exercised of civil liberties was restricted and sometimes completely abated.    Finally, the extraordinary growth in political clout and general audacity for multinational corporations was strolling and probably the most frightening aspect of the movie. Although some have said that this was the most unbelievable aspect of the movie.      Oncemore, these are simple things that I read into the movie. Feel free to disagree. After the movie, Athena* and I went to a local diner for coffee talk. It was good conversation of the eclectic and somewhat eccentric kind. Issues discussed varied from African human rights and politics to collegiate experiences along with a smidge of other topics. Athena is very good at expressing her sentiments and pulling out the subtext of what you are not saying when you talk, which many times is more important than what actually comes out of your mouth.  *Names have been changed.    
    
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        First, I will start with my odd dream this morning. Feel free to analyze cause I remember a lot of details in weird dreams like this one. Well, the place I was in was filled with a pale light as though the sun was farther away in a sky with high clouds. I dreamed that I had a child and was running from some unknown force which wanted some information that I had in my head. I end up hiding in some kind of church on an upper floor with some kind of priest behind some kind of rectangular pew, the child has disappeared and I see a spherical object with some lines wriggling underneath it come near the door with some person(oid) next to it. I feel that they are not good. These things sense where I am and I hear the priest say something to the effect of "don't think about what they want to know..." So the wriggly things float over above me and puncture my head, I can sense them searching for something in my memories and thoughts cause it is playing before my eyes with subtitles (oddly enough) and I actually feel stinging at the top of my head! I woke myself up at that point and for a few seconds the tingling was still there. It was a very odd. I am not even trying to decipher any possible meaning to it.    OK, now on to more sane things. Wow. Last night while watching the opening ceremonies of the Olympics, I was amazed by Bjork's performance of a song on her upcoming CD, Medulla. The song was called Oceania and it's absolutely beautiful. If I have the money, I will definitely be buying Medulla on August 30th when it is released. She is a fascinating woman too, here is a   urlLink brief unofficial biography  . Dancer in the Dark is also now on my list of movies to see soon along with Behind the Sun (again) and Burnt Money (oncemore).    I went to a farewell party for Athena thrown by a local community organization. She is one of the few people I have met in my life who actually exudes more love than she absorbs. She is just incredible and I am going to miss her more than I can express currently. She has an open heart and an open mind that seems to really yearn for opportunites to experiences difference and the subsequent growth in self-knowledge. If I were straight, I would be crushing right about now.   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Exhibit A from a recent Associated Press article on Sudan:    urlLink  …offered to host the talks on what has been called the ‘world's worst humanitarian crisis’…      The international press must stop its complicity as the Sudanese government attempts to label genocide as anything but. As I sift through news articles on a daily basis I am continually reading a sentence that goes as such: “what is being called the ‘world’s worst humanitarian crisis”. No, it is not necessary to go through the 1948 Convention on Genocide with a fine-tooth comb to realize that 'genocide' is exactly what is occurring nor is it hard to see why the international community is avoiding the term like the plague. Human rights agencies, humanitarian assistance agencies and independent observers have all clearly stated that what is occurring in Darfur is nothing less than a systematic and genocidal campaign by the Sudanese government through its proxy, the Janjaweed. The media needs to call it what is and thereby put an ever-increasing and simply unyielding pressure on the international community to act decisively.   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Maine ballot access deadline is looming for Nader’s presidential bid hopes. The Nader/Camejo campaign “needs to collect 4,000 valid signatures by August 9, 2004.” Nader/Camejo hope to collect around 6,000 signatures. His most recent failure to get on the 2004 California ballot and his loss of Arizona ballot access may not indicate his possible fortunes in Maine. This battleground state has what some may agree to be one of the strongest Green parties of any state in the country. The 20 year-old party of  urlLink Maine Green Independents  is pretty well organized and despite the reluctance of the national Greens to support Nader/Camejo some of the state parties are sympathetic to his candidacy.  Also in a  urlLink press watch  of those that are covering Maine presidential politics. A CBS News reporter took a tour of Maine’s coast through the towns of Wells and York and randomly conversed with prospective voters. Yes of course, many of the people are undecided but a common trend is that most don’t view Bush’s performance over the past 4 years very highly indubitably leading me to conclude that the likelihood of their vote being for Bush being similarly placed.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        At work and listening to NPR, nothing unusual there. Dick Gordon's show, The Connection, is doing an entire hour on the politics of humanitarian intervention in Sudan. I was wondering when his show would begin to focus on the situation in Darfur and it appears that it has begun. Thank goodness.  On the internet, I usually listen via   urlLink  90.1 WBUR    
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       My notes for the day:  Icarus, I am avoiding your phone calls tonight because I almost flew too close to the sun and feared falling into the ocean. I will not burn my waxen wings in the fiery hot sun of your own pain. I can only go so far for you. Meet me halfway in the shade of a calmer day and I will give you everything that I have.   Demeter you know the acrid smoke of those ciggies you loved so much before your pregnancy are pretty good...I think that I may be hooked unfortunately. But just one day for now...lol  Persephone is quiet and has been for some time. I don't know what to make of this, perhaps she has lost some respect for the vulnerable Daedelus. Anyhow, the coming week should be trying probably one of the busiest in some time. A meeting every day of the week and a volunteer opportunity in almost as many days. Night.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I received two copies of the "Song for Sudan" yesterday and hope to get them to some local press outlets soon. Any suggestions on exactly who I should send it to in Maine?  Here are the lyrics, I received in the mail from fishweasel:  i asked her to tell me her story she started by looking away – gazing back into that darkness when she knelt to pray. the planes dropped the bombs before daybreak - the janjaweed stormed with the dawn. those who could fled to the forest to hide till they’d gone.                                 returning to ruins by moonlight she found she was orphaned and then - there they began their exodus out of sudan.  her husband, ali, gently warned her “if worse comes, don’t try to save me.” you must survive with the children, so hide quietly. the next day the janjaweed raiders caught up and took all of the men she watched herself widowed while guarding their sleeping children  - then into the infinite star skies mother and children took flight through storming sands they crossed into chad from sudan  (bridge) his love for her keeps her going while her love for him keeps her calm - smiling when she says his name. like a prayer for sudan.  now as i write you her story - magboula rocks under the tree no food for the child she cradles – staring at me. what will it take to remember - what we said we’d never forget. never again,  is now, once again in sudan. never again, is now, once again in sudan.  – like a prayer for sudan   [bamanankan background vocals]  let’s pray to get out of the dark. some people made a plan and dropped a bomb. let’s take the children and run away. woman gets scared by a lot of bad things. woman, let’s hid your children. fighting, fighting, stop fighting, stop fighting. people get up from sleeping oh suda, sudan it will never happen again god will not make it happen again it will never happen again let’s pray for sudan never happen again stop fighting stop fighting fighting ruins everything.    Song copyright 2004 fishweasel music, ASCAP  Note: you can hear the song in its entirety at the Passion of the Present  urlLink blog  or Jim Moore's blog  urlLink here . It is an MP3 file.  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       To intervene or not to intervene…  A good  urlLink New York Times  editorial by Sam Dealey of the Asian Wall Street Journal attempts to discourage an simplification of circumstances in Darfur. Dealey discusses some of the economic, racial and political complexities that perplex Western decision-makers and public opinion which seeks to make sweeping generalizations about what is happening there and what needs to be done. I don’t agree with his conclusion namely that foreign intervention is not necessary but his debunking of generalizations is much needed.  Speaking of intervention…  There is an incredible editorial on why foreign intervention under the aegis of the Arab League or attributions to the African Union force is needed. The editorial is written from the perspective of an anonymous aid worker in Darfur. The piece in today’s edition of the  urlLink Independent  debunks some of the major points of objection to intervention. More coverage from the  urlLink Independent  documents how government forces may be forcing refugees out of the camps only to be attacked by the Janjaweed.  The President of Chad, Idriss Deby, had a powerful statement for U.S. Senator Bill Frist as he visited with Darfuri refugees this week. "It will be a catastrophe. In our minds, we have what happened in Rwanda…The international community has to act. Time is against us." Also over at  urlLink AlertNet , an article by Evelyn Leopold asks “Does Iraq invasion inhibit intervention in Sudan?” Seems like a good question, right?  More talks…  The African Union has stated that talks between the Sudanese government and Darfuri rebel groups will resume on August 23 in Nigeria. Meanwhile, in a recent meeting of Arab League foreign ministers, the head of Human Rights Watch Africa division, Peter Takirambudde, accused Sudan of attempting to  urlLink “manipulate opinion in the Arab world to hide the massive crimes it has committed against Sudanese citizens…and allowing the Sudanese government to hide its crimes behind Arab solidarity would be an insult to more than 1 million Muslim victims in Darfur," Takirambudde continued to say that “the Arab League should stand behind the victims in Darfur and take concrete steps to ensure that civilians are protected from further crimes."    Not only does it appear that the Sudanese government is attempting to manipulate Arab governments and public opinion by trying to keep the Organization of Islamic Conferences (OIC) and Arab League from acting, but it is also trying to scapegoat Israel for its rebel insurgency in the South and West. According to AlertNet, Sudan has accused the Darfuri rebel groups of having ties to Israel. One of the groups the Justice and Equality Movement (JEM) has denied this…"There is no relationship between the movement and Israel and I have no knowledge of any intention that there should be a relationship. It is lies on the part of the government,"  Finally, the  urlLink Washington Post  has an article telling how the Sudanese government in another about face has decided to allow African Union peacekeeping forces in all but name only. “Sudan will allow African troops to protect observers in the country's troubled western region of Darfur, Foreign Minister Mustafa Osman Ismail said Saturday, but he stressed that any peacekeeping role would be limited to Sudanese forces.  "We have to make a distinction between three categories. The presence of observers, the presence of protection forces for those observers and the presence of peacekeeping forces," Ismail said in Khartoum, the capital, when asked whether Sudan would accept African peacekeepers. "We don't have a problem with either the first or the second categories. As far as the third category is concerned . . . this is the responsibility of the Sudanese forces.”  
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here is what Maine’s presidential ballot will look like this November:  John Kerry 		Democrat George W. Bush	        Republican David Cobb		Green Independent Michael Badnarik	Libertarian Michael Paroutka	Constitution Ralph Nader		Better Life  Not all of the above parties are actually recognized in Maine. (Ex: Constitution party) But each of the people above had enough petition signatures for ballot access.   Yes, the  urlLink Lewiston SunJournal  reports today that Nader’s petition signatures were certified by the Secretary of State on Monday. A total of just over 4100 were received which was just over the minimum needed. So, what is the Better Life Party? I have no idea. I searched and so far have found nothing. Nada. Zilch. That’s a little odd isn’t it? Well, I am not a political pro so perhaps not.  Earlier, I had speculated that the Maine Green Independent party here in Maine might assist Nader because of some residual goodwill. I am not so sure of that now. The party accuses the Nader/Camejo campaign of attempting to split the party in its efforts in California to replaced David Cobb with Ralph Nader under the Green ticket before the August 26th deadline.  From today’s Bangor Daily News:   "I find it despicable," Nancy Allen of the Maine Green Independent party said. "It's an issue for people who thought Nader supported the Green Party. He gave us his word he wouldn't do what he's doing."  Meanwhile in New Hampshire, it seems that while the Nader campaign is confident about its chances, some suspect chicanery abounds.  Again from today’s  urlLink Bangor Daily News :   “Aaron Rizzio, Nader's New Hampshire coordinator, said Tuesday the campaign has collected more than the 3,000 signatures needed to get on the ballot. The signatures are due to town clerks for verification on Wednesday. But some of the signatures in New Hampshire were gathered last week during President Bush's appearance in Stratham - a move that had Democrats in an uproar. A consulting firm owned by Republican David Carney hired 10 to 15 people to approach Bush supporters at last Friday's picnic. The company, Norway Hill Associates of Hancock, N.H., also hired about 30 people to gather signatures at malls, fairs and other events. Emily Sawka, 25, of Kittery heard about the $12-an-hour job through a temporary employment agency, but decided not to take it after learning what it involved.”   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I looked in the mirror this morning... Is my hairline receding? I hope not.      I once wanted gray hair but not a receding hairline...  This I know for sure, Hope is receding. What does 'hope carrion' look like?            --Daedelus   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
                             Introverted (I) 54.55% Extroverted (E) 45.45%    Imaginative (N) 58.97% Realistic (S) 41.03%    Emotional (F) 56.1% Intellectual (T) 43.9%    Organized (J) 53.13% Easygoing (P) 46.88%  
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I walked in the chilly pouring rain tonight, it was fun. No seriously, it was invigorating....then I came back and baked some biscuits for the second time in as many days. Ask me tomorrow, if I still recommend a nice rain walk. After researching Bjork somemore (I plan on buying Vespertine first), I ran into some webpages on  urlLink Sigur Ros  and began to listen to their music. Agaetis Byrjun, while almost indecipherable to me, was also impossibly mournful and brought tears to my ears very quickly. So, I am well on my way on Icelandic music. Bjork. Check. Sigur Ros. Check.    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I opened my email box this afternoon and saw that I had been inundated by responses to my recent flurry of emails concerning human rights sent to my congressional representative,   urlLink Michael Michaud  . I found out some interesting things. I did not know that Congressman Michaud is a member of the House Human Rights Caucus. I was also pleasantly surprised to learn that he is a co-sponsor of H.Con.Res. 330, the International Human Rights Equality Resolution (for more information see below). I was even more pleased to find that some of the resolutions have already passed over the course of the summer.     Here is a sampling of the email responses I have received on some issues today.     DARFUR   Thank you for contacting me regarding your concern about attacks against innocent civilians in the impoverished Darfur region of western Sudan. I appreciate hearing from you.    As you are aware, since early 2003 a conflict between forces of the Government of the Republic of the Sudan and rebel forces in Darfur has resulted in attacks by Sudanese Government ground and air forces against innocent civilians and undefended villages in the region. Over 700,000 civilians from Darfur have been forced to leave their homes due to what United Nations Undersecretary General for Humanitarian Affairs has called probably "the world's worst humanitarian catastrophe."     I remain deeply troubled by the Government of Sudan's efforts to restrict desperately needed humanitarian assistance to the people of Darfur. Nearly 3,000,000 people affected by the conflict remain beyond the reach of aid agencies. I am a supporter of H. Con. Res. 403. This resolution condemns the Government of Sudan for its attacks against innocent civilians and demands that the Government immediately cease these attacks. Furthermore, it urges the Government of Sudan to allow the delivery of humanitarian assistance for the people in the Darfur region.   Finally, you may be interested to learn that I am also a supporter of a motion in the House which calls for the highest possible level of funding for responding to the current crisis in the Darfur region.     DR CONGO   Thank you for contacting me regarding human rights abuses being committed in the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC). I appreciate hearing from you.    As you are aware, ongoing human rights abuses in the DRC, including ethnically-based conflict in Ituri province, threaten the integrity and viability of the Congolese peace process.   It is the policy of the United States Government to support efforts aimed at accounting for these crimes against humanity. You may be interested to learn that funding support for Central African States was recently included in the Foreign Assistance Authorization Act of 2004. This funding will be used be used to support the development of responsible justice and reconciliation mechanisms in the DRC and other African nations. Additional funding will also be made available to enhance the capacity of African militaries to participate in peace support operations.    As a member state of the United Nations and of the world community, we must take a leadership role in ensuring human rights for all people. I will certainly keep your comments in mind as I work with my colleagues in the House to achieve this end.    BURMA   Thank you for contacting me regarding H.R. 2330, the Burmese Freedom and Democracy Act of 2003. I appreciate hearing from you.    As you know, Burma is governed by a military junta that took power in September, 1988. The junta, the State Peace and Development Council (SPDC), violently suppressed pro-democracy demonstrators in September 1988. It changed the country's official name from Burma to Myanmar. (The United States officially does not use "Myanmar.") The junta allowed elections to a National Assembly in 1990, but it nullified the results when the opposition National League for Democracy (NLD) won most of the seats. Since then, the government has suppressed political liberties and jailed thousands. The forced draft of civilians into military service has been another abhorrent policy of the dictatorship.    H.R. 2330, introduced by Representative Tom Lantos, sanctions the ruling Burmese military junta, strengthens Burma's democratic forces and supports and recognizes the National League of Democracy as the legitimate representative of the Burmese people.   As a member of the Human Rights Caucus, I was proud to support this legislation when it came before the House of Representatives on July 14, 2003, passing by an overwhelming vote of 418-2.     On July 16, this measure passed the Senate by a vote of 94-1, and was signed into law by President Bush on July 28.    SEXUAL MINORITIES AND HUMAN RIGHTS   Thank you for contacting me regarding H.Con.Res. 330.  I appreciate hearing from you and welcome the opportunity to respond.    I entirely agree with you that the United States should recognize and condemn human rights violations that are perpetrated on the basis of someone's perceived sexual orientation. This is why I am a cosponsor of H.Con.Res. 330, the International Human Rights Equality Resolution. As you know, this resolution seeks to commend the United Nations and non-governmental human rights organizations for their documentation of human rights violations on the basis of sexual orientation and gender identity. Also, it urges the US State Department to improve its own documentation of these violations and pursue these incidents with the same vigor with which it considers other human rights issues.     As a member state of the United Nations and of the world community, we must consider human rights violations with an equal hand. We must also recognize that human rights are possessed by all human beings regardless of their sexual orientation or gender identity.   For these reasons, I will continue to work to see that H.Con.Res. 330 is passed by the House.    CHILDREN AND IMMIGRATION   Thank you for contacting me regarding H.R. 3361, the Unaccompanied Child Protection Act of 2003. I appreciate hearing from you.    As you may know, the Unaccompanied Child Protection Act would enact several reforms in how our nation deals with foreign-born children who find themselves alone and in federal custody. This bill has been referred to the House Committee on the Judiciary's Subcommittee on Immigration, Border Security, and Claims where no further action has been taken. I share your view that our country must do what is in the best interest of the child and I will be sure to keep your strong support and thoughtful views in mind as this bill continues through the legislative process.   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Saw grass shimmering this morning   It was the first time in a while   I'd seen beauty        in a different place        other than a human face   It made me smile        for the first time in a while                    --Daedelus   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Gandhi once said that he felt pain "from the temporal accident" of his existence. I think that describes how I feel right now and have felt for about the past two weeks. Perhaps this dream that I have been living is an accident, some kind of bizarre mistake and will be corrected in the near future.  There is an unbearable 'heaviness' of being right now...and something within is cracking...  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I locked myself out of the apartment AGAIN! LOL. It was the second time in less than two weeks. I had to call my landlord again and this time it wasnt as much an amusing aside to a busy day. It was an unwelcome interruption to an otherwise relaxing Sunday. Well after about 20 minutes my door was unlocked and my wallet was twenty dollars lighter and I was on my way to Portland to see a friend, Ichthyus. It was fun, he basically gave me a tour of Portland, the Old Port is beautiful, and then we went and had some sushi. I doubt that I made an indelible impression.    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        The rate of death in Darfur has risen from 1000 per day just a few weeks ago to 1500 per day. This is expected to increase dramatically in almost as few weeks due to disease, famine and continued attacks by the Janjaweed.     There is a good editorial over at   urlLink allAfrica.com   about the failure of the African Union to adequately respond the crisis in Darfur, here is a snippet:    “Either way, the world must hold Khartoun responsible for the despicable happenings in Darfur. El-Bashir's attempt to whip up Arab opposition to the UN for threatening sanctions is contemptible. The ultimatum by the UN is imperative despite the objections by the Sudanese authorities. Why, for instance, would it seem impossible for the government to ensure security in Darfur within 30 days as the UN has mandated? President El-Bashir says he needs 90 days. If he is really determined to rout the Janjaweed in a fortnight he can do it. The truth, however, is that he seems to lack the pluck and commitment to do so. Which is why he's asking for 90 days. He clearly does not need it. Now that the AU has been aroused from inertia, it must move at double quick pace to stop further escalation of the Darfur humanitarian tragedy. President Obasanjo may have realised that the Union whose leadership he took over only recently, had not acted with sufficient dispatch on the crisis. This perhaps explains the flurry of diplomatic activities he has set in motion in the past fortnight to restore peace in the region. That is how it ought to be. Human life should not be treated as though it is worth nothing. Darfur didn't have to lose 35,000 residents. It bears restating that Africa's image as a hopeless continent derives mainly from the irresponsibility of its leaders. Until fairly recently the continent was replete with brutes and knaves who derived sadistic pleasure from tormenting their subjects and turning them into beasts of burden. A good number of the civil wars fought in Africa in the past 40 years were the result of callous leadership. The Darfur killings ought not to have occurred if Omar E-Bashir had learnt from the mistakes of his predecessor, the late Jafar el-Nimeiry. Since President el-Bashir does not appear keen on taming the Janjaweed, the UN and AU must help do the job in order to restore peace in Darfur. This calls for sacrifice. More African nations must volunteer troops to join the 900 already pledged by Nigeria, South Africa and Rwanda. It is noteworthy that Rwanda is among the very first nations to volunteer troops. Its experience in 1994 during which nearly one million Tutsis were exterminated by a Hutu-instigated genocide, possibly accounts for this. Its example ought to challenge other African nations sitting on the fence.”    Disease is spreading across the refugee camps of Darfur and Eastern Chad as the rainy season begins.   urlLink Gulf News   reports that “at the clinic run by the ICRC in Abshok camp, the most recurrent diagnoses are malaria (20 per cent) ... and respiratory infections (13 per cent) ...," and “the main illnesses affecting the displaced population are diarrhoea, malaria and acute respiratory infections…cholera, a deadly and extreme form of watery diarrhoea, is also feared in the teeming camps.”   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>