<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok we got webspace off abp for bgs but of course as always my ftp wont workwith it grrrr, and abp ftp wont work  about spelling well ill try 2 improve but theres no point changing previous posts cause no1 gonna look through them again probs  The signature aint there cause im using google bar's blogger 2 do it and the signature doesnt appear with it grrr  just finished starwars 4 aint on site yet still want ppl 2 look at it incase theres ne problems    urlLink http://homepage.ntlworld.com/robertcbeckett/starwars3.html   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Note to Beckett: Post your name underneath each post and freakin' c heck your posts before you post 'em , most of them have at least one typo! Can you go through your last posts and edit teh typos! :P lol  Anyways, heres a progress report of my flash anim:   Graphics:  Scene 1 preloader: 100% Scene 2 introduction [40 secs]: 0% Scene 3 meeting: [20 secs]: 0% Scene 4 road: [66 secs]: 100% Scene 5 shrine: [60 secs]: 60% Scene 6 Credits: [10 secs]: 0%  Total: aprox: 3 mins 6 secs and 260/600 [43%]    Sound:  All scenes: 0%  Total: 0/600 [0%]    ETA: August 2004   Yes I know, its pretty late, but its gonna be damn good... Well at least I'm gonna try to make it as good as I can, and if it turns out okay, I'll submit it to newsgrounds. Well, maybe :P      Jamie   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff    
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sheshkerli nomads have declared war on me...lovely.  Right, I'm just gonna make my own custom preloader, then Episode 1, the Way will be ready. But being ambitious, i'm starting Episode 2, A Saviour from the Way. I'll just say that Rhue teams up with "Red Hair" to save a lady who was taken hostage by Blue Scarves, notorious bandits.  *Yawn* Goodnight, Shecklers.  Tull,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff    
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i could have conquered it butn i got really pissed off with the story line, ill try and get the ending sorted out and i should get mine finished by tonight
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      But... er... Will Be... Eventually...  But fret not, I shall have it done...  Soon...    Over and out         &nbsp;    James   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Right, this is a broadcast on Shecklevision.  I have completed my movie, Wanderers One. Approx. 80 secs of stuff, excluding the titles and 'BGS Presents' etc etc. I'll send it to Jamie when he comes on...I SAID when he comes on...Grrrr...  So that's the deadline conquered, I shall finish my articles, and get ready for Episode 2!  Tull,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      if u want i can nick the code, using this program i have, ill gte ya the scripting and send ya it
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bleh...  Found quite a nice tutorial on  urlLink Flash and shaking browser windows   Slightly over excited, but anyway,  Now to find some way to integrate it into my flash...   Over and out     James   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And my Sheckolollies are tasting good today! And news that David Blunkett is getting ready for one of his crackdowns, this time against bad language on British TV!   Deadline, I should be able to meet it. Have&nbsp; screenie here ^^  http://img66.exs.cx/img66/8246/Wanderers1Screen.jpg Proof that I am working and almost done. Let's see...let's take a picture of the workplace too. The library's huge though :/&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; http://img66.exs.cx/img66/6782/Wanderers1Workspace.jpg  THESE STUPID F-BEEP-ING TAGS! Right, screw this direct linking, it's f-BEEP-ing up the toolbar thing on the side.  &nbsp;  Note that the three Lyns aka Assassins who are not being slaughtered are still in the same place as in the movie screenshot above. This is merely due to the fact that I haven't done their fighting bit yet.   But I shall be back...with my movie next time...at least I hope i will...meh...   Tull, &nbsp; urlLink Black Ghost Staff        
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      testing out google blog thing lol can everyone meet the deadline you dont have to be ready till thursday but i would recommend to finish them on wednesday, if you cant hand them in on time dont worry but try and hand them in before saturday
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok sent every1 an email witha&nbsp; preloader in it, plz put it in the first frame of your movie.  just started my movie today lol but as long as i dont go anywhere tomorrow or thursday it should be ready on time, pretty rubbish graphics, made a room and the walls looked like they were about to fall in lol, the spaceship is like a palace  made  urlLink http://homepage.ntlworld.com/robertcbeckett/PENALTY.html &nbsp;earlier, tutorial was in a flash magazine and just followed instructions, not gonna put it on bg site though cause i never really made it     Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I sent you an email recently, sould tell you about the deal. You know the terms about the email. Hopefully, the deal will be finished, and be successful. Until then, keep up the good work lads. I have every bit of faith in you (well, ermm, maybe :P)     Jamie   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bleh...  Okies Becket, problem is though, I don't have any decent pics I can use, I ain't at home, so all my stuff is unavailible...  :/  Where is our board anyway?   Over and out     James   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok i wont make whiffy then just alot easier cuase i have the story already written but i must admit the story is 2 boring!!! and so is my movie most ppl will just close the window before its finished no action really but if i make like 20 seconds per each chapter and put in the most exciting bits then it should be ok, but since james dont want it then i wont do it, gonna make starwars 3 can ppl please go to forums for sum ideals, thanks  i was talking to fish about the webspace supposidly we need a link to abp on every page at the bottom, jonny want a banner but fish says a text link will be ok (gonna put it in as small as i can like 1pt well ill send him a tet page and hopefully he'll allow it if hes in a good mood)  James if you want the picture on the site changed email me, dont really think you want a pic of a guy out of tekken for you, but maybe you do, email me  &nbsp;    Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bleh...  DEAR HOLY FUCKING MOTHER&nbsp;OF GOD NO,    NO, NEVER, NOT THAT STUPID DOG AGAIN     Got it?   Over and out        James   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey does anyone think i should redo whiffy, theres way 2 much text in it that u dont need and just takes up loads of time plus i may add in chapter 2 and 3 riefly not gonan go into much detail just gonna do basics so what do ya think or should i just do starwars     Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And a call to all you graduates of Sheckingversity.  I'm slowly progressing on my movie. Don't expect it to be the best...i should be able to make the deadline. Jamie, me, you and Fish need to talk on msn in a convo, most likely Monday to decide on the forums? Fish is considering quite seriously. I'll stick in a pound a month instead of 50p. Call me generous ^^. The reason i wasn't on today was because i was working at mum's takeaway. Don't expect me on tomorrow either. I'll just be working on Friday for this week...normally just Sat. 3Fusion sounds good and l33t i must say and uhmm...i shall visit Sheckington now. So goodnight. Or goodmorning i should say...(geez...four in the f-BEEP- morning.)  Tull ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok take it not much work has been done today? han hasnt been on msna dn neither has dragontail so it is only me doing work and i havent started nething new, all ive dont was change the name on all my flash to bg studios and add blood and sounds to in agfa2 (screams)  gonna send jamie the zip with all the webpage files in it now, if possibl can ppl use the forums and give me ideals for iagfa3 (in a galaxy far away) really need more ideals and i dont have the best imagination     Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      was talking 2 fish he said  perhaps you should tell him if he reduced dragontail, to the standard that i am now thinking for as a standard of about 25MB.... i would definately agree to give him 200mb for free  which would be with him getting 225 in total&nbsp;and also, he would have to agree to the new use policy for both accounts which would account to sooner for him than when i intend to fully bring it in though he could be assured that i couldnt be assed with the copyright thing   and&nbsp;you can probaly&nbsp;get jonny 2 increase it after u reduce it   Forums      the forum i made wasnt for the public its just for us to use cause i want ideals for my new movie and using the blog means it will get relaly crowded with posts so thats why i used the forum        Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff     
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Got a chance to post before I go and play footie with some friends. For the site, I ask Beckett to send me all the .html files in a zip to my gmail, I want to make a few minor changes, such as font consistency, parts of the writing, and some other shit. Dont expect&nbsp;it returned soon, though,&nbsp;maybe in&nbsp;1 or&nbsp;2 days maybe. I'll spend&nbsp;5 minutes a day trying to fix&nbsp;that all up. Also, all the PCs are the QUB computational PCs my dad has, and he has decided to replace his old networking/try out a new one, with a new&nbsp;switch, so&nbsp;he told me&nbsp;(phoned from China) to look at possible configs. I also decided&nbsp;to reformat the other old athlon 600 pc and install a fresh copy of XP for no reason.   Anyways, theres a slight problem with the forum business. The forum was suppose&nbsp;to be for all 3 sites,  dragon-tail.tk, blackghoststudios.tk  and  dbeckett.co.uk , so it cant be just called " Black Ghost Studios Forum ". It has to be for a name for all three sites' forum. Maybe like " 3Fusion " and the motto " Synthesis of Dragontail's Lair dbeckett.co.uk Black Ghost Studios " or something like that. Go to our current forum mentioned by Beckett below and post ideas. I also think if we combine the news/improvements/general talk section of all three sites into each main section, so instead of 3 news, 3 general talk, etc, we have 1 news, 1 general talk, etc and each section is for all 3 sites then we can get more posts in each section, thus making it more busy than each seperate one. Get me? Anyways, the forum needs to be split into boards and sub-boards like the following:    News ->  Whats new?, Future updates  General ->  General chat, Flameyard (ie spam can, no rulez), Recycle Bin (ie, all moved topics gets put into here temporarily)  3Fusion chat&nbsp;->  Suggestions 'n' Comments, Content&nbsp;(talk about content, ie flash, games etc), Affiliation (sorta like where ppl post to affiliate)  What do yers think? Anyway, I'll email fish now for the forum and the extra webspace in a new account for "bgs" with a password which i will send to you via email. I'll ask for 200MB (which is well enough, considering an avg flash anim is around 1-2MB, thats like 200/10 anims), and I'll pay him a fiver for that and the new forum, if he is a bit unhappy. Unless you are&nbsp;all meanies, everyone pays a measily&nbsp;50p and I'll pay £3.50, in the senario. actaully, I'll email him when I get back. Easier. Respond here with your ideas,      Jamie  ,     urlLink Black Ghost Staff   
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
               Next Wednesday eh?    I will have to cut my movie short, but okay, I've done it in the form of Kill Bill, which means chapters, which means everything is fairly short and compartmented, so it won't be all that difficult for me to finish for next Wednesday, can't promise anything all that long though, its sort of a prelude, I still need to think up a proper storyline for the main thing, :/     &nbsp;   final verdict: deadline is no problem for me    Just don't expect uber.swf that's all     Over and out     James,     urlLink Black Ghost Staff    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      what about you james can you meet it?? if james cant meet it either then ill put it back till the following wednesday plus why does jamie have to network 30 pcs why does ur dad need that many networked or are u doing them for his work heres some sites for good sound effects, the 3rd one u can download xaio sounds and stuff  urlLink http://www.flashkit.com/soundfx/    urlLink http://www.findsounds.com/    urlLink http://www.stickslaughter.com/site/downloads.php   i just need sumthing to motivate me 2 make starwars 3 thats why the deadline is there plus we need content and gett he site up and running, jamie can u get 50mb space for monday off fish for the time being and if u can get the qub webspace then we can use that isntead then, and if u can get forums cause i will have to change all the forum links on all the pages (3 per page) to that address.  ive made a forum at  urlLink http://dbeckett.fragism.com/gl-bin/forum/ &nbsp;which i want us to use temporary till we get abp forums, dont want the link on the site just forums for the admins of bg studios so we can discuss our current movies and stuff     Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry my friends, I will defianately not get my flash finished by then. Seeing that its somthing like 2 minutes, most of it which is total co-ordinated sword fighting. I want something to be quality, not a rushed piece of crap. As you can see, I haven't been&nbsp;on the net&nbsp;recenty due to the fact I didnt have time, having a job, then the CDRW drivers failing and crashing as I watched The Matrix: Reloaded in the drive, and then to find out the flopply drive had done a kari-kari and died on me, randomly. So I had to get a new floppy,&nbsp;try to fix the problem unsucessfully with the CDRW, etc etc. I wont be on the next few days either as I have to work out&nbsp;the optimum&nbsp;method of networking my dads 30+ pcs which includes PIII500s, P4 1.4s, P4 1.7s, 2.4, 2.8, and many more, some on linux (different versions), some on windows 2k, some on XP!!!And then I have to build my dads new PC when it comes,&nbsp;which is good :) At the moment,&nbsp;the deadline is far too unreasonable for me, sorry folks, though if you really want, I'll send you what I have. I want it to be good, and I do not want any work rushed to achieve the deadline, though I do admit it is not a bad idea. I'm glad Beckett did this to motive the team.     Jamie ,    urlLink Black Ghost Staff      
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is a warning issued to all sufferers of Shecklerscholosis. Do NOT expose yourself to the face of Tony Blair, even on television, as it may trigger a very bad reaction. *Cue dead ringers music*  Right...deadline...I'm working on my flash, Wanderers, Episode 1. Finished the first half of it, which is nothing but music, movement and random talk. But the latter half is full of fighting. Rhue against four Lyn...who will win? Well...programming the fighting's gonna be hard...so many sound effects to add in as well as blood splatter. Meh...but if I can't get it done, well, my article will have to do.  I shall now beam myself back to my comphy computer chair...peace.  Tull,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok every1 has to handin a piece of work by thursday but the work has to be finished on the wednesday to give you time to add finishing touches after that you can relax for a week or do some work then we will set a deadline for around the 10th of august or sumthing  i will try and get the preloader for flash to every1 by around monday     Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bleh...  Thanks for the comments Beckett, it was just me doing something different for a change, plus I get to use some AS I'd just learnt, You're prolly right that it's not the best for the format of the site.   Do we actually have a deadline? ie. Next Tuesday?  Just checking, cuz I'm gonna be away during the weekend, will still try and make it though  That's me for now,   Over and out     James   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Currently having a homemade milkshilk made by me, pretty good considering i have never made one before and no1 told me how to plus i had 2 stir the icecream for ages by hand to make it soft and turn it into chocolate flavour... really nice   Now done to work we need content, the only way this can go wrong is if nobody make anything and there aint&nbsp;any comunication.&nbsp;I think we should set a deadline that everyone has to submit a good piece of work, eg around next tuesday so we can get content and start to get hits and have something to talk about. so what do you think everyone has to submit a piece of work article/flash between monday and thursday plus it will make me actually start about making flash, couldnt be bothered at sec   Done no work today cuase went to see spiderman2 during afternoon and evening was installing new wireless phones that my dad had just bought and was watching tv.   James design doesnt suit the site enough ok i can see youve spent alot of time at it but you dont want the navigation to stand out and using flash makes things stand out, plus the current&nbsp;navigation is better, its&nbsp;a bit smaller and in your one&nbsp;clicking for the navigatin to appear isnt very proffessional, i like it the way it is small, simple, easily fixed and quick to download      Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bleh... &nbsp; Hold yer horses there Beckett, I am indeed in Canada, so there's no reason to celebrate yet. &nbsp; Anyway, didn't get that much time on the computer today, so I decided to make some buttons for the site instead of my usual project, they look okay to me, but will probably need refining for the particular colour scheme of the site. &nbsp; I'll send them to Jamie, and he can decide what to do with them.     James   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok just put counter on and so far weve had 3 visitor me, a person from CANDADA and sum1 else. (is james in canda if so that could be him) &nbsp; Don't want to make any more pages on site since when we get the forums i have to change every page's forum link (3 links on every page) and more pages there are more work needed so i couldnt be bothered. Havent&nbsp;done much today just fixed the roblems james noted and changed contact page form's colours and added my bin laden game not much     Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lo to all the residents of Sheckington. &nbsp; I'm inclined to join James in giving the one-fingered salute to Jamie...but decided that the Grand One isn't worth the "honour." &nbsp; As for Beckett's post...what about capital letters in the title? ^^ &nbsp; I've done my first ever sprite flash (13seconds) and when I finish those articles, I shall get to work with the latest Wanderers flash movie, featuring Rhue aka Mr Blue. Just need time...and some morale to get to that 1 min+ requirement for each movie ;_;... &nbsp; And I shall close with the remark, "Change is inevitable...except from vending machines."  Tull, &nbsp; urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok all those mistakes well mine since i done 95% of content, never had a chance to check over it all. Its good that you like the design.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;I never knew if you wanted your blog pic on the site, you know your actual pic, do you???  just&nbsp;incase you dont want it on&nbsp;i put a random pic in.  &nbsp;  There aint enough content so i dont want people to go to&nbsp;the site yet so i&nbsp;put the logo in and done under construction to make them think you cant view the site yet, gonna take all that page out when i get a bit more content and everything working.  &nbsp;  Can we also get a proper logo for the site, that we can put on all our presentations cause i need to change all my good flash to bg studios.  &nbsp; If you want to add content to the staff site i.e comment or any other page then send an email to me  urlLink davidc_beckett@hotmail.com &nbsp; &nbsp;  thanks,  p.s if you havent noticed i put capital letters in (just to please han)      Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bleh...  &nbsp;  In respect of Jamie's various purchases, I have this for him:  &nbsp;  *One finger salute*  &nbsp;  *mutters* lucky b******  &nbsp;  Ah well, I'm not to argue, the fat mess has returned, so if all else fails I have a new guy to get sheesh kebabed in my flash :)  &nbsp;  I think I'd better go back to my own blog now, need to get the formatting fixed, and for Jamie's benefit I've changed the layout back :/  &nbsp;  Hmm, this is the first time I've tried something that isn't Trebuchet, but I can't say much  &nbsp;  Never trust a font that can't do colon forward slash properly...  &nbsp;  Also (pay attention now Jamie) I've had a look at the site, and it looks pretty good, just a coupla points though    On the front page it says " company " and since when were we a company exactly?  Ummm, you guys left out the apostrophe in " we've " on the front page, just point out that spelling mistakes look pretty random...  WHAT THE FUCK IS WITH THE PICTURE OF A SURFER? (self explanatory really)  The logo at the start looks random, just a thought...  Can we please remove the "Site under construction" banner thingy? Since I'm&nbsp;thinking the site will always be under construction as we're adding things to it...   I know that was quite a few points, but just some stuff for our "Glorious Leader" to consider in his free time...  And when he has more free time he can go see wtf is wrong with the formatting in Life Eh?... :/    Over and out       James     urlLink Black Ghost Staff     
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can almost say  urlLink www.blackghoststudios.tk  is finished! Me and Beckett (mainly Beckett) have worked on it for a long afternoon and evening, and its looking pretty l33t! All credit goes to Beckett who adapted the layout, and design most of the site, while I suggested this and that, and did some of the table layouts.  &nbsp;  Everybody is working:    Jamie - Working on the site, pages, and&nbsp;ads&nbsp;and his Flash movie evil.swf (not the final name, btw)  Beckett - Working on the site, pages, logos, layout... etc (a lot of work here)  Han - working on his articles, and his Flash animation, still unnamed right now, though its suppose to be a sprite animation  James - Not sure, but think he is working on his Flash animation, a parody of Kill Bill?   Good work done today, pretty happy with all the progress.      Jamie   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lo all you Shecklers out there. &nbsp; I have finished my first ever 13 second flash!&nbsp; Well, 13 seconds of animations. And my smilie collection is constantly growing for the *cough* inevitable *cough cough* invisionpower board. As for articles...they've been put on a temporary halt as I did my first flash, but now that that's done, I'm back on track. I've decided to put 20 points in the Too much C'n'C one, so not much left to do.&nbsp; Random Thoughts...need two more thoughts to write about before that's finished. &nbsp; So I end this blog post thingie with a quote from...Wilde. &nbsp; "America is the only country that went from barbarism to decadence without civilization in between." -Oscar Wilde.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Lovely quote describing one of my favourite countries, America. *Retches* &nbsp; Tull,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The sites template is around 96% completed, now for content if u have content email me  urlLink davidc_beckett@hotmail.com , ill probaly add most of the stupid stuff that ive made for  urlLink www.useless-flash.tk   &nbsp; just added movies page     Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff       
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey site template up go to  urlLink www.blackghoststudios.tk  and click on the logo, still aint that good, want it 2 look alot better&nbsp;      Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff     
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My dad ordered all his stuff today, for you who don't know, he had £2000 [up from 1500 I said before] to spend on various stuff.&nbsp;He let me decide what to order. I&nbsp;may have posted before what&nbsp;I  wanted  to order, but that has changed now,&nbsp;this is what he  has  ordered:  &nbsp;   (btw, if you don't understand, just ignore and move on:/)   &nbsp;     2x Opteron 242 1.6ghz 1MB cache 64bit  1x Dual Socket 940 MSI EXT-ATX motherboard  2x WD Raptor 36.7GB 10,000RPM&nbsp; SATA&nbsp; Hard drives  1x RAID controller  2x 1GB PC3200 ECC RAM (yes, 2GB of RAM, muwahaha)  1x Inwin 7010 tower case (very nice, has an intergrated fan controller)  1x 550W Meridian Power supply (uber power)  1x Samsung black DVD-ROM and Sony black Floppy  1x Gainward Geforce 6800 GT *Golden Sample* (pre-o/c, xtra cooling)  1x Microsoft wireless desktop set   Pretty good, no? Plus hes gonna use the 19" Sony TFT he had bought earlier. Ever better, is the fact that I get to swap my crappy Geforce4 Ti4600 with his Geforce6 6800GT! Thing is, I could have got a 6800 Ultra! It was only £20 more, so my dad agreed, but then I realized that my power supply&nbsp;only had&nbsp;1&nbsp;more molex connection free, while 2&nbsp;molex connections were&nbsp;needed by the 6800 ultra (a molex connection is the thing you power your optical drives/hard drvies with) 1 F£%ing molex connection away from&nbsp;a 6800 ultra! Son of a b#$&amp;h!  otherwise, I'm getting a DAH-1000 512MB MP3 player:        and a Dita V3KC (Korean Curve) hockey stick:        Heheheheh, any time soon, I will buy. Kinda need to work on my Flash anim again.      Jamie   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Whoever invited Beckett is indeed very smart. Good thinking :) Just a bit retarded for not doing it myself, lol. I changed the link, so Black Ghost Staff indeed goes to the new URL :) I'll alos work on a small logo hopefully less than 500k, to stick in front of projects, and such like. I also&nbsp;gave Beckett admin access like everyone else. I sent beckett an lengthy email describling several topics we were discussing, and everything looks well. So i'm happy :) &nbsp; Han's doing work on his articles, Becketts working on the site, I'm working on my flash, and james on his (which is quite a bonus) All I can say is good good good :) &nbsp; Hopefully something will become of this, but theres a 99% chance of everything becoming like Hiroshima '45, ie: everything F$%ked up. As long as people are prepared to work, I think It will become the 1% chance of a success. Maybe I should be less optimisitc and look at the defination of ghostanomics:  [2] miserable failure...      &nbsp;    Jamie   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      G'day to all you shecks out there. &nbsp; I'm taking up flash...but until I figure out how to even open the application,&nbsp;I shan't be contributing anything in  that  field. But onto the articles...two articles currently active. They are: &nbsp; 1. Random Thoughts, Collection 1 2. You know when you've played too much C'n'C &nbsp; Cheers to Jamie for the second one :). Now, down to discussion as to whether the things on Jamie's katana action thriller (j/k) are eggs or blobs. IMHO, eggs generally do not go around decapitating, dismembering and disembowling (my 3Ds) each other, unless they're in flash movies...on the other hand, blobs IMO don't have a regular shape, they resemble the things which inhabitate the bottom of a cesspit. So let's all just say that those 3D-ers are blobby eggs. &nbsp; ~Tull,   Black Ghost Studios staff   
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey never knew about this till today, just to let you know in one of the other posts it said beckett.co.uk well its actually dbeckett.co.uk, &nbsp; i havent started on the site yet but will start on it tomorrow shouldnt take me too long, black ghost aint up and running until you get a site, ive registered BLACKGHOSTSTUDIOS.TK.  &nbsp; site should be up soon and can sum1 get webspace &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;   Beckett  ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff    
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Bleh...    &nbsp;  This is wingdings, try that for minimalist :P    &nbsp;  Props to you if you can read that without pasting it onto Word and changing the font to something normal...    &nbsp;  After an hour of work, I've got about 20 seconds of bugger all... that's the bad news, the good news is that I've got a storyline, and I can now work on it properly...    &nbsp;  Jamie is soooo lucky he can just do his randomly coloured background, I actually have to make my own in Photoshop, which can be a pain in the neck when the damn computer freezes every 2 seconds, even you open something like ****ing notepad...    &nbsp;  I'm moving into rant now aren't I...    &nbsp;  Btw Jamie, you can help me with this... How badly will having 1Gb of RAM cripple a Chinese version of Win 98?    &nbsp;  until next time...    &nbsp;   Over and out   &nbsp;   James  &nbsp; urlLink Black Ghost Staff    
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hmm, Blogger seemed to have updated the GUI once again. Now I don't need to look up the "img src =" for images HTML tag again, woohoo! Also, you can change font, but the funny thing is, the default font is Georgia which is my preferred font, so no changes there! I see James has changed to a smaller lighter font, being minimalist again >_>  &nbsp;  &nbsp;Haven't got any Flash done today, just couldn't be&nbsp;bothered.&nbsp;I hear James is actually working on hid Flash project... That's good news, no?&nbsp;Note to James: They are NOT eggs! They are  blobs  :) Also noticed the gif image stretched out which screws up the layout. In the future, don't do that, notice that James. Thing is, although I have published the whole blog a million times over, I don't see the changes for at least an hour or two, unlike Life Eh? Which does it immediately :I've actually&nbsp;got 1700 frames in the Flash of the movie in the 1st scene. There will be 1 more full scene, and a credits scene and a preloader scene. I also have the basic storylines for the sequels, parts 2  and  3 of the Flash. Pretty l33t, huh?  &nbsp;  I'm also thinking for running a Invision board jacked up with some nice cosmetic hacks with Han&nbsp;admining it, running for&nbsp;3 sites, Black Ghost Studios [run by Beckett and me], Dragontail's Lair (Build II) [run by Han and me]&nbsp;and dbeckett.co.uk [run by Beckett]. At the moment I'm trying to persuade Fish aka Daniel to do it. He hasn't responded yet&nbsp;):/Once that happens, I'll try to get all 3 sites on a webring. Heheheh }:]  &nbsp;  Gotta make most of the l33t idea before Fish says no. Probably. Heh, must plead some more.      Jamie  ,   urlLink Black Ghost Staff    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Bleh...    Works begins on my idea of flash version of Kill Bill (I still have to name the movie, but plenty of time for that), or Jamie's gonna want my ass on a silver platter.&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;  I&nbsp;currently face the problem of figures, I have a choice of stickmen or the eggs like in Jamie's katana dudes.&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;  2 problems, the stickmen will require a lot more work as their various body parts will have to move... Eggs have the opposite problem, they don't show enough movement, how the hell am I supposed to show a kick? Eggs going in with their bottoms???&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Bah...&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;  I'll try and get a trailer up soon for you to look over...&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;  (Just so it'll look pr0, as Jamie likes to say)&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;  Over and out...     &nbsp;  James &nbsp;  urlLink  Black Ghost Staff       
     

    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      'sup folks,          [EDIT:]  -  i'll explain why i removed the image    urlLink click here to view     Well, rather large, but still, pretty neat, no?    Waiting to see what James comes up with :/ Maybe hes working on something? Or maybe hes doing nothing (99% more likely) >: Meanwhile I continue to wokr on the Flash (I've shown Han already 2/3 of it)     Jamie  ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff     
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Nothing really to contribute in this post, except to tie up some loose ends.  Preferably make the forums Invision, as I have the most (N.B. all) experience in it. I'll need some webspace allocated for Invision for custom skins and custom buttons(Reply, New Topic etc etc...)  Also, I've reached what is known as a "writer's block" for my articles. Absolutely no ideas...except for some articles including collections of random thoughts...which seem to allocate themselves the larger portion of my brain...ster-ange.  -Tull
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Part of the movie:    Look at all the motion tween in the layers! Arghh    More on this later? maybe? :/    Jamie  ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Worked on some Flash today. The result is 31.3 seconds of pure kantana action :) At 24 fps, this little flick is rocking, with kantanas, dai-kanatanas, throwing knifes, shrunkiens(might remove this later on), short swords and axes mixing with blood and little dudes. Theres like 24+ layers, so I had to switch resolution to 1280x1024 to get more stuff on screen. I will post a screenie later.   I wonder how Beckett is getting on with the site? Also, I have decided to have a full forum (invision prob), and I also putt Tull in charge. I also advice him to look at  urlLink this skin resource site . Its pretty l33t for Invision boards :) James better start to create some stuff in Flash, his wee exuse of no access resources is rubbish >:|  I produce 0% resource content Flash, with 100% of my own work, all drawn inside Flash.   Have to go to work tomorrow, must earn cash for l33t hockey stick and mp3 player.   Have fun the rest of you,   Jamie  ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *Ahem* Under pressure from certain groups to make a post, I have put together a small and not so detailed message to add to this Black Ghost blog thing.  Testing...1...2...3  Right, the name "Blog" is about as random as this post is. The term, "Blog" generally makes me think of a mess, in particular mashed potatoes. This is *probably* what this blog is about, mashed potatoes, perhaps some of the games Black Ghost is making will include a mashed potatoe fight.  But I shall be writing articles, possibly reviews if James can get a decent flash game/movie up :P. Oh, and RPG designing, my specialty, ripping gfx from other games. Oh, and surfing the large large net for useful things to add to the site. Oh yeah, I'm the master of Invisionpower Board forums, giving me admin powers means you get the most out of your forum, trust me :D  "It is equally offensive to speed a guest who would like to stay and to detain one who is anxious to leave." -Homer. (Which I've experience before.)  -Tull,   Black Ghost Studios staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Long time no post :/ Mainly cos of Morrowind. Anyways, Beckett should be back soon and us two will try to work out a site for Black Ghost. I decided the blog can be related to anything, so it doesnt have to be with Black Ghost. Hopefully, that adds freedom :) Added Tull a long time ago, but he hasnt posted. His time is short. I mean it!  Dads got a £1500 to spend randomly on PCs. I have convinced him to spend it on a PC which I will build. Here are the the specs:  Pentium 4 3.2ghz | 1gb cosair PC4000 memory | 2 x 120gb Hard disks in RAID 0 | 875P Albatron motherboard >:) | geforce 6800 GT | 19" TFT Sharp  time to overclock it to 3.7ghz muwhahaha  Meanwhile must go back to messing around with Flash :)    Jamie  ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Set up, well tried to set up Apache on my computer. It works, but there's a slight problem. My router seems to stop all incoming traffic, even though I open port 80, enable DMZ on my IP and disable the hardware SPI firewall. Meaning everyone part from me get a 404 error. Its enough to make me throw it out the window. I even registered http://dragontail.serverbox.org, which directs all traffic to my IP. Shame it all gets blocked though >:(  Me and Beckett have agreed to develop a template site for Black Ghost, while James is continuing to fiddle about with Flash trying to create his pr0 movie. Only problem is he is on a 56k, and hes never gonna get the right resources. Well, thats his excuse. Han is, well, not doing much. Great. I'm having some doubts to see what he is willing to produce. Better late than never I suppose.  I swear, this stupid router is gonna piss me off till I throw my ultra heavy goldfish bowl 17" monitor at it. What else can I do?    Jamie  ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Did a small change to the template. See if you can spot it :) Also give James admin control, dunno if thats smart, but I trust him... :/  On a side note, kinda expect this sorta crap to pop up now on my old laptop since we got win98 installed :)      Tribute to thy l33tn3$$,    Jamie  ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Meh...  Tis me... again...in all my bleh and meh glory... :P  Yes... I appear to be on the payroll (in expression only unfortunately) of this Black Ghost Studios...  I'll be doing random VB proggies and Flash... Flash being more likely for the time being considering my Aunt (whom I'm staying with over most for the summer) has no VB... ah well, tis an opportunity to brush up on Action Script... assuming the cousin doesn't scream too much...  *sigh*  Bleh...    James  ,   urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dear Lord, asked some friends if they wanted to join Black Ghost Studios, providing that *insert huge list of details here*, and so far a pretty +ve response. Quality, quality.  James is added as a member in this blog, but it will take him another couple of hours before he realises, cos he is kinda like 5+ hours behind the GMT time in Canada. Grrreat!  More later. Maybe.   Tribute to thy l33tn3$$,    Jamie  ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The 1st post is always the hardest one. It is my job to make it less hard for myself. First, you may be wondering: [side note:  you , like, someone else apart from me is readings this?]    what is the purpose of this blog?  The simple answer to that is to act as a jotpad for ideas and thoughts for the staff and friends of  Black Ghost Studios .   Erm, Black Ghost Studios?  Yeh, Black Ghost Studios is a Studio dedicated in indie development, by indie developers. It started as a hobby for me, and it still is. I have to wait and see how far the rest of my friends are willing to stay with  Black Ghost Studios .   Yeh whatever, you're just a bunch of losers!  Thanks, just read the meaning of Ghostanomics :)  James won't be the most happy man in the world when he sees this, but I promise to him this is just occasional postings, I will still post in  urlLink Life eh?  Meanwhile, to find out a little more, why not check out my  urlLink website ? View the forums, and you should see a new template for it. Should be cool B), see you there.    Tribute to thy l33tn3$$,    Jamie  ,  urlLink Black Ghost Admin  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hi again abp site is down, should be back up when fish comes back from holiday and he doesnt know when that will be he says he should be back by monday but may be later, started work on agfa4, not much content yet,  take it jamie has been doing alot with his job and his new pc, oh well lol  can james maybe submit some content by the thursday 26th, can be a movie download thing nething we need something from anyone, i know youve got ur holiday so dont worry if u cant.  same for jamie but i know u ahev a lot of work so dont worry if u cant     Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Bleh...      I'm stuck for something to do... >      And the massive amounts of Homework my parents have set me isn't helping...      Anyone any ideas? Or am I stuck with tutorials?     Over and out         James   ,   urlLink  Black Ghost Staff   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Graphics:  Scene 1 preloader: 100% Scene 2 introduction [60 secs]: 17% Scene 3 meeting: [20 secs]: 0% Scene 4 road: [66 secs]: 100% Scene 5 shrine: [80 secs]: 83% Scene 6 Credits: [10 secs]: 0%  Total: aprox: 3 mins+ and 300/600 [50%]    Sound:  All scenes: 0%  Total: 0/600 [0%]        well, the last scene is longer than I thought, but worked a good 3 hours on the flash today... :/     Jamie   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I done the logo. At 20fps, and 400x300 dimension, I think it came out pretty well. I really like the font, Can't remember what it is though :/ I gonna start the banner and then the ads plus the 88x31 buttons like the ones I'd done for DL. Wonder what name to use, BlackGhostStudios is kinda long... maybe just Black Ghost...  Well on another note, most of the components for the PC has arrived. Just the Gainward geforce 6800GT *Golden Sample* hasn't arrived yet. The manufacter don't know when they can get the board produced and sent to us, LOL cos its so rare. So, the ppl at XFX are ever better at selling rare graphics cards. The Geforce 6800 Ultra Ultimate Edition (LOL @ the name already) is so rare that potenial buyers must enter into a ballot to be drawn to even buy the card...  at an cost of $600  X-D     -=ROFLMAO=-  Only 100 cards have ever been sold. Its only ever faster than the normal 6800 ultra in extreme situations, like Far Cry 1600x1200, ultra high settings, 4x antialiasing 8x anistrophic filtering and Unreal II 3200x2400 (LOLOL @ that res) max details and 4XAA and 8x AF. But its $100 more expensive.  I also have a 486 chip and 16MB EDO memory stick in my bedroom randomly, and I compared it to the opteron 64 242 and a 1GB ECC DDR PC4000 stick. 10 years of technology side by side... Not much difference in terms of shape and colour and stuff...:/     Jamie   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok can every1 try to post in forums as much as they can cause we need as many posts as possible, just added a wallpaper to the downlaods seciton aint that good but it takes up room which is good :):)   if u want 2 help me wiht storyline for part 4 of agfa talk to me in msn  beckett
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink http://abpni.serverbox.org/bgs-forums  forums are now up  Han has released wanderers part 2 it is now on the site   urlLink http://abpni.serverbox.org/bgs/secure  - u can get to it another way by going to site and on news page click on the title Black Ghost Studios  on the secure-downloads up the new flash intro is ready to be downloaded and be put on all your flash movies  i just added an invisible counter 2 every page so we cna see whta movies are the most popular   JAMES AND HAN AGREE TO TH BGS TERMS AND CONDITIONS BY REPLYING TO JAMIE   every1 register in the forums, have fun do some flash and talk to ya soon  BECKETT 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ok what terms and conditions??? do we really want ppl coming to this blog, this is really just for us 2 joke around and talk about stuff, not sure if i would want the public seeing this (and my spelling mistakes  :P)  ADDED FORUMS just added forums to the site its just temporary till fish can be bothered 2 get us forums, whenever that will be lol  PROJECTS ok the projects page has now got info, still havent done new layout for the projects page, done a tiny bit of it, can jamie and james give me more info for their section  MY PROJECT does anyone think i should amke a flash game instead of agfa, we really need more games and downloads can jamie if he has time make a download of some sort, nething really  thanks!    Beckett   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Again, everything seems to go very well so far for BGS. Beckett's being doing some good work on the site, while Han's working hard on his flash anims. Unfortunately, I haven't been able to finish my animation on time for the new deadline. However, the movie is still going very strong and I plan to finish it before August 20th. The temp. frums will have to do for the meantime, till we get our new invision one from ABP. One of the affiliates on the site should be BGS offical blog which would like to this! I also need to create a new 33x81 button for BGS and BGS Ofical Blog and some banners, plus a new logo :/ Hopefully, that will be soon. I will also create a new revision of BGS terms and conditions and a doc with Future Info as soon as I have free time. Otherwise, thats all from me right now.     Jamie   ,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And Sheckloproduction has ground to a halt...  Right, I'll be releasing a screen of Episode 2 soon, as soon as i get all the graphics i'll be needing ripped.  *Bit about beckett deleted cause beckett didnt like it* - edited by beckett  Changed storyline of Episode 2, got a much better one. I'll just say that there'll be a 'duelling' battle, called the Plunge, where the two opponents run up to each other and jump up, and attack. There'll be blade arts possibly if I can be bothered to grab them, but you'll understand all. Red hair to all!  Tull,  urlLink Black Ghost Staff  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>