<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I woke up and weighed myself and I still weigh 284 pounds.      6:38 AM    I ate two eggs, 2 pieces of sausage, and 3 pieces of bacon again this morning, and that means... yes... you guessed it.. 2.2 carbs!     
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning I woke up and weighed myself and I now weigh 284 pounds.&nbsp; 2 more pounds!!!! woohoo!!!!   6:02 AM &nbsp; I ate two eggs, 2 pieces of sausage, and 3 pieces of bacon again this morning, and that means... yes... you guessed it.. 2.2 carbs!  &nbsp;    6:30 PM     I didn't eat lunch unfortunately, I was very busy.  Last night I had a piece of steak for 0 carbs and then went to pizza place and at a salad and toppings from pizza.  So hopefully that wasn't too bad.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I woked up with some extra energy, and felt better because my back is not hurting today.&nbsp; I can finally stand up straight.&nbsp; I weighed myself and I've lost another 4 pounds and I'm now at 286 this morning. WOW...  &nbsp;   Kinda felt sick to my stomach this morning before eatting, but I think thats because I was hungry. I felt better afterwards.     6:00 AM&nbsp;   This morning for breakfast I had 3 pieces of bacon, and 2 peices of sausage, and 2 eggs for a total of 2.2 carbs again today for breakfast...&nbsp; This might get old soon... :(  &nbsp;  Took chili and jello and turkey to work for lunch.&nbsp; The chili will be 1 carb...  &nbsp;    1:35PM  &nbsp; I ate&nbsp;&nbsp;some&nbsp;Jello and Turkey for lunch today for 0 carbs total.&nbsp; I didn't eat the Chili.&nbsp; That means I've eatten 2.2 carbs TOTAL today.&nbsp; I still have 17.8 left!!!!&nbsp; Sound like a good&nbsp;dinner to me :)  &nbsp;&nbsp;    5:30 PM&nbsp;  For dinner I had some steak with A1&nbsp;sauce for 1.5 grams of carbs.&nbsp; I also had salad with bacon and&nbsp;dressing for 1.75 grams, and some Ice cream and Pork rinds for 0 carbs each.&nbsp; That means I ate 3.75 carbs for dinner and 5.95 total for the day.&nbsp; I have 14.05 carbs left for today :)  &nbsp;            
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        6:00&nbsp; AM&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Today I woke up and weighed myself.&nbsp; Its funny to see I've lost two pounds, I weight 290 today.  Making breakfast now.&nbsp; Going to have 2 eggs (1.2 carbs)&nbsp; 2 peices of sausage (1 carb) and 3 pieces of bacon (0 carbs)&nbsp; So that is a total of 2.2 carbs for breakfast again this morning.&nbsp; Sure beats the Hardees 3-5 carbs for their breakfast bowl (although it is good, and I'll probably have to get it some morning when I'm in a hurry)&nbsp; This means I have 17.8 carbs left for today....  &nbsp;  Today will be interesting.&nbsp; Second day on the diet and I've got to go to work.&nbsp; Work is one of the main reasons I can't diet.&nbsp; I have to be out and about in the Double Kwiks so much and that makes it hard to diet, but hopefully with this one, that won't be the case as fat is not a factor.&nbsp; I can get just chili anywhere, or just a piece of hamburger meat somewhere...&nbsp; So hopefully it will be easier to diet on Atkins while at work.&nbsp; I think I'm going to take some pork rinds, and Chili with me to work.&nbsp; Interesting combination...  &nbsp;    1:15 PM&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For Lunch I had some Chili for 1 carb and pork rinds for .5 cards and ham for 0 carbs and jello for 0 carbs.&nbsp; So for lunch, I ate a total of 1.5 carbs.&nbsp;&nbsp;Total so far I've eatten 3.7 carbs today, and that leaves me 16.3 carbs left for today.  &nbsp;    5:30 PM&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp; For&nbsp;Dinner I had too much. I ate a Hamburger with Cheese and A1 Sauce for a&nbsp;total of 3 carbs.&nbsp; I also had salad and dressing for 1.75 carbs, and some cabbage and meat for 3 cards.&nbsp; I also had some Ice Cream for dessert for 0 carbs.&nbsp; This was a total of 7.75 and so far I have 8.55 left.  &nbsp;    10:00 PM&nbsp;   Later I got hungry and ate another hamburger and cheese for&nbsp;2 carbs.&nbsp; This means I have 6.55 left for the day.  &nbsp;  Total for the Day&nbsp;I ate 13.45 carbs.&nbsp; Not to bad for 13.45 out of 20...  &nbsp;  &nbsp;  &nbsp;           
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        11:15AM&nbsp;   Today I began the Atkins Diet.&nbsp; I am trying to do this with the help of my friend Jeff which has the Atkins book.&nbsp; He knows what things one can and cannot eat since he has read almost the whole book.&nbsp; I hate reading, so he tells me what to do :)&nbsp;My body my react interestingly since yesterday I drank 5 sodas which had 39 carbs each, along with some candy, and other&nbsp;foods that were high in carbs.&nbsp; It will be in carb shock today :)  &nbsp;  I started out today at 292 pounds, so we will see where I end up.  &nbsp;  Today I started the process they call Induction, where you "Induce" your body to use Fat for energy instead of sugars.&nbsp; During this phase, someone can have up to 20 grams of Carbs each day.  &nbsp;  Today for breakfast I ate 2 eggs and 2 pieces of sausage.&nbsp; So far that means I've eatten 2.2 carbs today.&nbsp; (.6 grams&nbsp; for each egg and 1 gram for the 2 pieces of sausage)&nbsp;  &nbsp;  I also went to my old high school and walked about it five times.&nbsp; If I remember right, thats 1.5 miles and I did this in 15 minutes.&nbsp; So far today, I feel good and still have plenty of energy.&nbsp; I went grocery shopping to gather things I need for the diet.&nbsp; I bought about $70 worth of stuff, and still really didn't end up with much at all.&nbsp; I doubt the stuff will last a week.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I've drank 2 cups of Crystal Light so far.  &nbsp;  For now, all is good, lets just hope I can keep doing this....     1:30 PM&nbsp;&nbsp;   For Dinner I had&nbsp;2 cups of&nbsp;salad which was 1 carb for two cups, and some salad dressing that was .75 carbs for 2 Tbps.&nbsp; I also had some pork spare ribs which has 0 carbs, and half a cup of green beans for 2.9 carbs.&nbsp; That means so far today, I've had 2.2 from breakfast and&nbsp;4.65 for lunch for a total of&nbsp;6.85 carbs out of 20 total possible.&nbsp;&nbsp; I have 13.15 left for the rest of the day.     6:57 PM  &nbsp;&nbsp; For Supper I had 1 cup of green beans for a total of 5.8 carbs.&nbsp; I also had some more pork spare ribs with 0 carbs.&nbsp; I&nbsp;also ate some salad and dressing for 1.75 carbs, and some pork rinds for&nbsp;.5 carbs.&nbsp; &nbsp;So far today, that means I've eatten a total of 14.9 so I have&nbsp;5.1 carbs left today :)           
     

    
</post>


</Blog>