<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Panic on the streets of London      Panic on the streets of Birmingham      I wonder to myself      Could life ever be sane again      On the Leeds side-streets that you slip down      I wonder to myself      Hopes may rise on the Grasmeres      But Honey Pie, you're not safe here      So you run down      To the safety of the town      But there's panic on the streets of Carlisle      Dublin, Dundee, Humberside      I wonder to myself        &nbsp;    Burn down the disco      Hang the blessed D.J.      Because the music that they constantly play      IT SAYS NOTHING TO ME ABOUT MY LIFE      Hang the blessed D.J.      Because the music they constantly play        &nbsp;    On the Leeds side-streets that you slip down      On the provincial towns that you jog 'round      Hang the D.J, Hang the D.J, Hang the D.J      Hang the D.J, Hang the D.J, Hang the D.J      Hang the D.J, Hang the D.J, Hang the D.J      HANG THE D.J, HANG THE D.J,       HANG THE D.J, HANG THE D.J...    &nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I don't care if Monday's blue      Tuesday's grey and Wednesday too      Thursday I don't care about you      It's Friday I'm in love        &nbsp;    Monday you can fall apart      Tuesday, Wednesday break my heart      Thursday doesn't even start      It's Friday I'm in love        &nbsp;    Saturday wait!!!      Sunday always comes too late      But Friday never hesitate...        &nbsp;    I don't care if Monday's black      Tuesday, Wednesday heart attack      Thursday never looking back      It's Friday I'm in love        &nbsp;    Monday you can hold your head      Tuesday, Wednesday stay in bed      Or Thursday watch the walls instead      It's Friday I'm in love        &nbsp;    Saturday wait!!!      Sunday always comes too late      But Friday never hesitate...        &nbsp;    Dressed up to the eyes      It's a wonderful surprise      To see your shoes and your spirits rise      Throwing out your frown      And just smiling at the sound      And as sleek as a shriek      Spinning round and round      Always take a big bite      It's such a gorgeous sight      To see you in the middle of the night      You can never get enough      Enough of this stuff      It's fridayI'm in love...    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know what I have to do...the message and the path are clear yet I am not sure I can do it. I have put myself before a difficult situation. I should have guarded my heart, but I couldn't. I should have been cautious, but I was mesmerized by something so grand. Is this just a blinking light that caught my attention? Or is this a star among all the blinking lights? In many ways I think it's the latter. What a fool I was... Now I'm in a state where the decision has to be made and my own weaknesses are stronger than my strengths. One thinks this is strange for me to be in this situation. Another thinks I have to figure out what I really believe. The other thinks it's a great opportunity. The final one thinks I'm foolish for my involvement. I'll run three miles and it won't take me anywhere. I'll fly 500 miles and I'll only be closer. What was I doing here in the first place? Why can't I find a simple path? Why am I always in these complex situations?Are my standards too high? This has brought me here. Finally one meets so many of my conditions and it's the path I ought not take...one condition is not met. I have talked to so many and none strike me. They have not been able to get my attention. They do not fascinate me. They are too simple. They lack so much. I want nothing to do with them. I prefer to have nothing than to have them. Am I lonely? No, I was content. I was even scared that I was content. I had never been fine in that situation and yet for once in my life I was. What is wrong with me? I saw it all before me and I did not react. I knew, yet I did nothing. I kept on. All my sleepless nights and days had finally been filled with ease and yet just as quickly as I am able to rest I am hit by reason, rationale, and religion. This is a wicked game, yet she didn't do it...I played it and I'm sufferring for it...It's strange what desire will make foolish people do. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is so strange that this is the song she said was her favorite...how could she have known?  Without one word or hint, this is what she said.  My jaw hit the floor.  I could not believe that this would continue to happen.  From cars, to music, to baseball, to my brother?   I know I'm setting myself up for destruction.  This ride will eventually end and I'll probably be where I dread being, but I can't get away.  There is just something amazing placed before me and I can't help but view, study, and admire this person. I've lost all sense.  I know there are more than enough reasons to walk away and save myself, yet I have never had my soul touched so quickly, so easily, so gently by someone.  It is so much easier and so much harder to stop when a wall is placed in front of you...
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Flowers and Gardens, abandoned from view.  Cry for their love, like I do. People throw their love to whisper, think of all the girls who've kissed her.  But to me it doesn't matter they, fade away, they fade away. Fade away. When we meet we fell together, now she's gone I can't forget her.  Love is chance but time won't let her, fade away and fade away. Fade away, fade away. Alot of flowers in this world are never seen. I wanna hold you love, I wanna win your love for me. Fade away. For me there was no sunshine, for me there was no rain. For me until I meet you, every day was the same.Fade away, fade away, fade away.   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Late night coffee will never be the same.  A long drive and lost twice...I flew all night alongside an angel.  A trip that shouldn't have ended.  I can't believe I spent 16 straight hours with one person, in constant conversation, laughter, amazement, and completely in heaven...I know how i felt about it, I know how I enjoyed it, I even know she enjoyed it, so much so that she had never been with anyone that long and so much so that she had never enjoyed that flight more than she did with me.  If only you could begin to understand what I have gone through...It was just like heaven, at least for four days...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Cuando veo a travez del vaso  (When I look through glass)  Veo a travez del tiempo  (I look through time)  Donde los sentidos se dislocan  (Where feelings are dislocated)  Donde los temores se evaporan  (Where fears evaporate)  Y aprovecho para desdoblarme  (I take advantage to unfold)  Para salir del vaso  (To escape the glass)  Con las paredes sudo tu rastro  (With the walls i sweat your trace)  Con la memoria busco tu rostro  (With my memory I seek your face)   
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's not that we don't get along...   We get along great...that is the problem...  I am simply baffled...Up is down and left is right?  Does anyone else think this situation is strange?  And I thought all the stuff prior was complex.  I thought figuring things out on knowing when and how to act was hard.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Si pudiera ver   (If I could see)   Una lagrima   (a tear)   Mientra de beso   (while I kissed you)   Entre incendios   (among flames)   Te abrazaria   (I'd hold you)   Para salrinos con el humo   (to escape with the smoke)      Debajo de tu piel hay zafiros conquistados   (Beneath your skin there are conquered emeralds)   Encima de mi piel hay una alfombra entre tus pies   (Upon my skin there's a floor beneath your feet)   Debajo de tu piel yo resucito y me derrito   (Beneath your skin I'm revived and I melt)   Encima de mi piel te guardo el aire que no hace daño   (Upon my skin I save the air that will not harm you)      Ven acércate   (Come near me)   Si pudiéramos   (If we could)   Escupir cometas   (launch comets)   Le ganaríamos al tiempo   (We'd beat time,)   A la magia, al destino   (magic, destiny,)   A la distancia, Al olvido   (distance, the forgotten)      Debajo de tu piel hay zafiros conquistados  (Beneath your skin there are conquered emeralds)  Encima de mi piel hay una alfombra entre tus pies  (Upon my skin there's a floor beneath your feet)  Debajo de tu piel yo resucito y me derrito  (Beneath your skin I'm revived and I melt)  Encima de mi piel te guardo el aire que no hace daño   (Upon my skin I save the air that will not harm you)  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Strange Days, where did you come from? I wasn’t ready for you If I don’t follow you tonight Things will never be the same  We soared a thousand miles Just to be with my dream  But she walked towards the sunset She left me there without a care in the world Alone for weeks, One day I’d return   Strange Days, I knew the end that would find me But you were sweeter than fear And if I follow you tonight Things will never be the same  I soared a thousand miles Just to be with my dream  I flew towards the sunset With wings spread wide and my heart in hand Through the night I searched for my dream  And she leaned across my shoulder She touched my soul, she touched me back to life I awoke with wounded heart in hand        My mirage, my only dream was gone…     
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I've been looking so long at these pictures of you 
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         "Antes de tres lunas volveré por ti,  (Before three nights, I'll return for you)   
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Yesterday things were "great" We drove across the Golden State Together It should have been forever...  Walking piers and touching trees Seizing castles and memories Those days are gone Painful reasons to move along  And I know Tomorrow will find me Through the door and on the floor Forevermore.  Today it hurts, today I cry Today I don't really know why She left me She chose door 2 and I was number 3  And I know Tomorrow will find me Through the door and on the floor Forevermore. And Nevermore  Can I say all these words That I long to say, there is no way You made your choice, I've no regrets Just keep on smiling, I'll be ok.  And I know Tomorrow will find me Through the door and on the floor Forevermore. And Nevermore  Can I say all these words Like you're magnificent, you're wonderful You're interesting You should know all these things  And I know Tomorrow will find me Through the door and on the floor Forevermore. And Nevermore  Can I say All these words Like you're magnificent. You're wonderful. You're interesting. You’re beautiful. You’re marvelous. You’re intelligent. You make me laugh. You make me smile. You make my life glow all the while When you’re by my side.    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So after much thought, I finally came up with something positive to say about my ex...in contrast to thinking I wasted my time, wasted my efforts, I was lied and deceived, etc etc...  So even before I state that "positive" I have to qualify it...except for those times when she put me through hell, she really did help me deal with my emotions, she was great for listening and I can honestly say that for four and a half years (aside from the qualification) my pessimism, bleak outlook, and depression were pretty under control...how great it is to have someone listen...keeps the jar from overflowin' 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...things look and feel better.  There are new songs and the old ones don't mean as much.  It's only a matter of time I'm sure...but what that actually means I'm not sure yet...not sure where I'll end up, but it will be better than before, that much I know.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        "Show me how you do that trick      The one that makes me scream" she said      "The one that makes me laugh" she said      And threw her arms around my neck      "Show me how you do it      And I promise you I promise that      I'll run away with you I'll run away with you"      Spinning on that dizzy edge      I kissed her face and kissed her head      And dreamed of all the different ways      I had To make her glow      "Why are you so far away?" she said      "Why won't you ever know that      I'm in love with you      That I'm in love with you"       You      Soft and only      You      Lost and lonely      You      Strange as angels      Dancing in the deepest oceans      Twisting in the water      You're just like a dream       Daylight licked me into shape      I must have been asleep for days      And moving lips to breathe her name      I opened up my eyes      And found myself alone alone      Alone above a raging sea      That stole the only girl I loved      And drowned her deep inside of me       You      Soft and only      You      Lost and lonely      You      Just like heaven   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>