<Blog>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Never thought I would even consider trying one of these things out, but it's free...what the hell.Lesse, it's saturday morning, I'm on duty and bored to tears. No new S*P cartoon up, just filler art, and the paintball outing for today was postponed til next week. So far a shitty day, with no prostpects for it getting better.Since I'm in the US Navy on shore duty I have like tons of time on my hands throughout the day, because my job has to do primarily with the internet, surfing that is pretty much all I can do to wile away the time.  &nbsp; So I got hooked on web comics. So far the archives I have read completely are: Something Positive - Love it! Dominic Deegan oracle for hire - Loved it, but now it is turning in a dull direction. Usr/bin/w00t - Love it but hate how slow it is going now that I can no longer read it fast like the archives(im very impatient) GPF - Loved it although it is going in a direction that it seems to keep repeating, over and over and over... Sexy Losers - Funny! Love most of it, not really into the whole necrophelia stuff though. Nuklear Power - 8 bit cartoon that is so funny it had me in tears at work. Sore Thumbs - not enough series to really form an opinion, doesn't seem to be going anywhere at the moment, or at least not in the direction of the original storyline. PvPonline - Will always love this one! &nbsp; I'm currently trying trying to get through Real Life, another one that is very funny, specially since it is a Seinfeld sorta life sitcom with the whole "Doncha wish we could do this, oh wait, we can do this!" thrown in.So far S*P and PvPonline are the ones I relate to othe most, an old man gamer with a scewwed view on life...   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I don't know why anyone would be interested in reading these things.&nbsp; I can certainly see why writing them is popular, I can pretty much say what I want here with no real repercussions.&nbsp; I did make a small mistake on the Real Life blog, apparently you pretty much have to explain in detail, every comment you make on these things or people will blow a single sentence or 2 way outta proportion and turn a comment into your entire belief structure.&nbsp; Not only that, they will be able, from 2 sentences mind you, catagorize you as a biggot.&nbsp; Wow, I'm floored at how quick people are today to jump on the negative, and here I thought flames were strictly kept to message boards concerning primarily online roleplaying games.&nbsp; Yes, I know those boards, I'm a 33 year old gamer geek, with a wife that's a 35 year old gamer geek.&nbsp; My kid is going to hate life growing up with me, a forever teenager who will always be able to whip her ass at just about any game imaginable.&nbsp; Actually right now we are playing City of Heroes and having too much fun to powergame.&nbsp; We keep trying to go back to Dark Age of Camelot, but it just isn't the same there anymore, pretty much a ghost town of a game now.&nbsp; We are anxiously awaiting the arrival of EverQuest 2 though, that just may have a little promise.  &nbsp;  Well back to my new addiction...web comics...    
    
    
</post>


</Blog>