<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink           Is has left Wellington this morning and I didnt send him to the airport coz I don't have the guts to watch another of my friends leave. It's already hard to say goodbye but to watch him walk away much more harder. I wish him goodluck in his future undertakings. May he gets what he always wanted. &nbsp;   urlLink               p/s: that's my brother at the back sneaking into the pic   
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Had dinner with&nbsp;fellow&nbsp;Malaysian students in Wellington jst now and man the&nbsp;dinner was superb! everyone was stuffed man. the food was alot and everyone was getting full by the time the last dish arrived.&nbsp;jz now was also the last dinner with Iskandar coz hes going home tomoro for good *goodbye Iskandar* he gave a speech and everyone was listening to his conversation and Jan as usual as a clown, interrupt his speech making his own&nbsp;jokes hehehe newayz was fun to see all the&nbsp;familiar faces again =)&nbsp;  &nbsp;    urlLink      &nbsp;&nbsp;  Me and friends at Satay Kajang sponsored by MSDNZ. From left: Nysha, Christy,&nbsp;Me, Lya, Naz. Jan, Sita. Sit down from left: Nalein, Zahrin, Yusuf, Adnin, Sean and Faz   urlLink         
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Fuh..yesterday was another tiring day of my life.Had the busiest day of the week. 9am-4pm class. I was so tired I didnt even had the guts to visit my dear blog. Sorry blog, had to ignore you for a day but now I am back. Yesterday was fun even tho' I was so damn tired. I met my Prince Charming [bak kata Jhaja]. Finally met him but the sad news is he's bold again.=( He had his hair last week tho and he looked so damn hot!Buat he's still the best looking guy evn tho' he doesn't have any hair *laugh* Anyway, I had fun with my class yesterday coz normally I would sleep the whole lecture. But yesterday was the best man! we talked about the indegeous people in Aoateroa/New Zealand. We were asked about who can claim theirself as a Maori and who can claim theirself as being a Maori as well as who can claim&nbsp;theirself as a Pakeha or being a Pakeha.&nbsp;That questions had make me think till this morning because when we had the debate yesterday, the issues weren't yet been solved. Being a Maori and a Maori have two different meaning. A Maori means you are the Maori that have a Maori descent from your ancestors but being a Maori means you are associates with the Maori itself [e.g relationship]. But the question is who can claim theirself a Maori or being a Maori? A person who has Maori blood but doesn't know the language, the culture what-so-ever still can be known as A Maori but for those who do not have the blood but know the knowledege, are they still consider as Maori or being a Maori? hm..Oh what about being a Pakeha or a Pakeha? Pakeha means you're the white people[European] that live/born in New Zealand and you're not&nbsp;associate&nbsp;with any of the Maoris.&nbsp;Being&nbsp;a Pakeha means&nbsp;you have connections [e.g relationship, grandparents, parents]&nbsp;with the European people&nbsp;here and do not have any connection with the Maori people. It's quite confusing aye? coz the explainations are similiar.&nbsp;But the word Pakeha&nbsp;was given from the Maori people, it means "Pake-Pakeha" which means someone with the fair skin.&nbsp;So not all of the people can claims themselves as a Pakeha even though they were born and educate here.     When I had this discussion yesterday, I have been thinking about my own roots as well. My mind had slipped a little bit from what I was supposed to discuss. I was thinking about my roots. My culture. About my own indegeous people in Malaysia. How many of them can claim themself as a malay, chinese, indian and what-so-over when they have forgotten about their own roots? I am not trying to raise any questions or point out finger or anything, but isnt it we have to know our own roots first before knowing other people roots? isn't it your identity is the one who shape your life? speaking of the identity, I have met few fellow Malaysian who have been brought here but never ever know their descendant or ancestors back home but have claimed themself as a Malaysian. But when I ask, do you know how to speak malay?, they replied " why should I learn the language? I'm not gonna use that language anyway, what is the point of learning it? ". "but you do claim yourself as a Malaysian but you do not speak the language, then why do you have to say you are malaysian anyway when you think the language is not important to you?isn't the language is important too? isn't the language is the thing that can identify you where do you come from? then what language you gonna use when you go back home? your grandparents would not want to speak other languages with you&nbsp;except your own language. It's funny how these days youngsters do not see how important is the mother tongue to them. The language that shape their culture. Without the languge, outsiders would not know where do you come from. They can claim themselves as Pakeha,Maori, European whatsover but what is important is your culture. That is more valuable than anythingelse. I wouldn't claim myself to be Javanese or Chinese or somethingelse, just because I have bits of bloods from&nbsp;each of the categories but I will claim myself as a pure malay because in this these days you will not find any of the purity of the ethnic groups anymore.All of them have been mixed with everything.&nbsp;So what is so proud with your own identity anyway? because that identity is the one that will shape the part of your life. That identity will show where do you come from and where you will be categorize in..and besides there is nothing wrong to know other cultures ae. Is just you have to knw your own roots first coz that is more important..hehehI love my culture heheh [proudly admit]is just in these times like this you tend to think something that you've&nbsp;never thought&nbsp;before..just a thought not to be offensive or something. we live&nbsp;in a free country where thoughts&nbsp;are counted~so do more thinking and who knows&nbsp;you mite learn something from it~~&nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's 6.00am in the morning and I am still awake. Awaken by the books that are all over my bed. I was supposed to sleep by now but how can I sleep when the books are all over my bed!!! Yet I am still awake. UNi&nbsp;has just started but I&nbsp;can almost&nbsp;feel the pressure right now.And guess what, I am already under&nbsp;lots of stress even though UNi&nbsp;just started two weeks ago.&nbsp;Just look at my workloads, it's unbelievable,. I have 3 journals, 5&nbsp;essays, 5 assingments, 1&nbsp;writing editing, 3 writing exercises to complete and 1 seminar presentation. How was that? Amusing?&nbsp;I&nbsp;don't think so!&nbsp;I have to finish all these by the end of October, before UNi close. *long sigh* I hate my subjects sometimes because it&nbsp;"steals" me away from my social actiavities [e.g clubs, gossips, friends] but again, I should not be complaining. I should be thankful because I do not any exams after UNi closes. Lucky Me =)     &nbsp;   I called my fren, Chip before and I admit, I am a bit jealous and admire of him. Jealous because he already complete his degree whereas I am still struggling with my degree *long sigh again* He's wating for his graduation which takes place next month. *lucky him* Now I am&nbsp;starting to feel the presurre again. All friends have finished their study and have found an excellent job and I am still stuck here completing my degree. But why should I be sad because I remember what Chip told me, he said I inspire him somehow. I've insipires him with my confidence to study in overseas whereas he doesn' t have the chance to do so. I took it as a compliment. I never actually seen my self as an inspirer so when a person told me that, it's a big thing for me. Thanks!     &nbsp;   I remember my friends back home told me that I am lucky because I have the opportunity to study at Overseas University. Different Universities than them. I questioned them, what do u mean different Uni? Isn't just an UNi after all except different names and country? They reply, I am in NZ, they are in Msia. That's the different. I have the opportunity to study in different education systems. I totally agree about the diff education systems but what I do not agree is that , education will always be an education no matter where you do learn it. Coz the end of the day, the overseas students will come home and serve their country about what they have learned. Is it? No doubt about that. If only they know what is the truth beyond the eyes they see. I know some of the students here can be helpful, cheery, friendly and nice but do not forget about some students who are selfish, pathetic. egoistic and jeolousy???Oh yeah do not forget abt the fees that increasing every year?that's sux! I have to pay a large amounts of fees whereas they only pay just a bit from us which I think that's no fair. Speaking of the fairness, where is the fairness in the world when you have striked to get&nbsp;the fees decrease&nbsp;but you've been ignore? So fair and square.     &nbsp;   Oh well, I think I better go back to my work. Have to get ready for school * a very long sigh* damn those thinking have distracted me from finishing my work! damn those thinking. Oh Boy, I hope today will be another excitement day of my life. Hope to see my crush today. Haven't see him last week. Kinda missing his smile tho's. Speaking of crush huh! =) &nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             urlLink        Ninie, a great friend and amazing human being with a pure soul. When you're with her, she puts on this tough exterior but she's actually marshamallow soft.   urlLink           I was reading the comment that my friend wrote on friendster. It's kinda touchy and emotional coz he has left NZ last saturday.&nbsp; I was feeling sad and lonely after he left. Not because I do not have any friends besides him or anything but because we are more than friends. He has become a brother to me. We shared secrets and gave advices&nbsp; to each other. But whats more important is that, we trust each other. Dat's more important than antyhingelse. &nbsp; I've realise after living in Wellington, New Zealand, I have made lots of friends here. I have also made some enemies too :p heheh. Well i guess thats what we call the balance of life. You have to balance your life a little bit.&nbsp;It cannot go perfectly&nbsp;through your journey. It has to be ups and downs moments once in a while. Like&nbsp;Ninie told me, my friends feel comfortable to be around me. They feel ease whenever they around me. I take that as a compliment. For me, when&nbsp;my friends need me to help them, I will try my best to help them as much. Isn't&nbsp;that what you are supposed to do, offering a helping hand when they need a help?&nbsp;I guess so. My life has been improving days by days. I have&nbsp;gained lots of experiences by being acquainted with&nbsp;new people. Which I think good basically. Because&nbsp;I&nbsp;have learned how to control my life and not being control by any&nbsp;pathetic humanbeings. I am rebellious when I am being control. I normally do what I want to do at first without want to think what is going to happen&nbsp; and face the future consequences later. Hence,&nbsp;because&nbsp;I think, my heart rules my mind and my body. I always follow my heart. It's like I have this strong instinct inside of me. I try to behave like confident, wordly-wise girl who has a mind of her own. But eventually,it is my mind that takes over.  I&nbsp;have watched my friends come and go. After Ninie left last year, it seems that all my friends have continuously following her steps. Recently was Firdaus and soon will be Iskandar and Jan. God knows how sad it can be, seeing fthe riends you always hang around suddenly make a huge departure in your life.&nbsp; But I guess it won’t be called life, if you keep on receiving happy moments with you. Life is not about equality. Life has never been equaled to me. To me, life is like a tyre. It goes round everyday and it never sticks unless its stop-means you’re dead. Speaking of dead, I just lost my best friend. Ardiana Azrin Iskandar. She was my best friend for 9 years and she died after got hit by a truck. She was on her way to see her wedding dress. She’ going to get marry in about 2 weeks. I was shocked to receive the call from her fiancé, Hazri Irwandi. It was like a drop bomb and there was no word to describe how shocked I was it’s because I was talking to her on the phone just few hours before the whole thing happened. I can still hear the way she saying, “Hey Ike, I am on the way to see my wedding dress. It’s your favorite color, purple. I cannot wait to see it. My tailor said it’s done. I’ll call you when I am trying it on ok? Take care girl”. There, that was the last sentences she said to me. That was the last ever called I am going to received from her.&nbsp; May she rest in peace..Amin  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink        Went to work this morning and it wasn't a bad day for me. Normally I would be complaining and angry towards my customers. Sometimes they are nice but sometimes they can be a pain in the ass. I can see sometimes they look at me without seeing two eyes just because I work at a fast-food restaurant. So they assume people who work at the fast-food restaurant don't have the manners or anything. People do work to gain money or even experiences. People who work at this kinda of places do have feeling. Just because they work at this kind of places, doesn't mean they are low or anything. They just want to get extra pocket money. In the contrary, even though they treat me like that, I feel I am better than them because I have what they do not have [I think]. I've got money every weeks and excel in my studies and also I know how to treat people nicely. Not just judge them by it's cover. Coz I've been there and felt that. So by treating other people they why people deserve, doesn't make me a loser. It makes me a winner. Speaking of that, I was watching the movie "I am Sam" yesterday. It's definitely the best movie so far I've watched. It's definitely a movie that will teach you a lesson about love. There is no difference when it comes to love regardless whether you are normaly or disable. Sam who is a developmentally disabled adult who has been singularly raising her daughter , Lucy for all her seven years. Her daughter was taken by the social worker after they discover the father' disability. I was thinking, how can you question the father's disability of taking care her daughter when he has raised her daughther 7 years by himself? Why they do not question about the mother who is perfectly normal has left her daughter behind just because she felt ashamed being pregnant to a disable person? But they question is, how can they took her away from her after 7 years? and questioned the father tons of questions which they already know the answers? For me personally, you cannot judge what you've seen with being there personally. Sometime they do not know what they cannot see beyond the eyes. People can judge randomly but only us who know the truth.     p/s: that's the picture of my feet-was taken by me when I was in Uni last week =)&nbsp;&nbsp;  urlLink      
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink        WMSO's Party&nbsp;  urlLink      &nbsp;[At the back: Jan, Idzwan, Nal, Johan & Kakera. Front: Christy, Oli, Me &amp; Sita]   I attended the WMSO’s party just now and it was fun to see all the familiar faces again. I was so happy to see Nad again. He just arrived from Malaysia last 2-3 days. I was thinking its like Nad arrival is like replacing Firdaus’s departing. Firdaus left and Nad is here. Kinda sad to lose Firdaus but I am happy to see Nad again. At least I have someone I can talk to when I am down. Oh yeah, it was fun to see KakEra again. She’s finally here. She arrived couple of days before Nad. KakEra is like a big sister to me. With her, I am able to talk anything I want with her. I admit I like to tease her a lot even though she is older than me. At the party, I saw all the pictures that were taken on Bersatu Games. [Bersatu games is a friendly games that unites all the Malaysian students around NZ] Happy to see my friends around New Zealand from Auckland to Christchurch to Dunedin. It reminded me the memories I had with them during the Bersatu Games. But suddenly, my feeling was changed to sad feelings. I realized the Bersatu Games this year was be the last Bersatu Games I will ever joined. I won’t be here anymore when it will be in Auckland next year. I will be finishing my studies end of the year and attending the graduation next year. After that, I will be packing my bags and heading home. I will be sad to leave New Zealand when my memories have been increasing every year.   
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     All Blacks won the rugby against South Africa. It was a great victory thanks to Doug Howlett who was the hero of the day. He made the last try before the games ends. On the other hand, sad to Carlos Spencer, he lost the last kick. But oh well, All Black already WON anyway even though he lost it. All Blacks-23: South African-21&nbsp;&nbsp; urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ...throughout the course of my life, I have learned many  things, not just the basics of living, but also the basics  of living with others - but it is that we are not or won't  be always alone. We are often in the company of one  another, whether we like it or not. My life has always  been most rewarding to me so far, but this not because the  rest are not. But it is the most memorable I have yet  because I started active socialization. I made new  friends, and learnt how and where to get new friends. I  ran... and I fell... I started to realize that I have not    just have to constantly make new friends.... but I also      have to learn how to keep them..I began to see things  differently, from a more grown up point of view - not just  making and keeping any friends, but true friends. People  whom I can trust all my secrets with, people who can  provide listening ear, a shoulder to lean on, and a heart  to care...whenever you need them there...It was only then  did I realised that true friendship is indeed more  precious than all the diamonds in the world. It reaches  beyond time, and the true miracle is in giving, not  receiving. I also realised that we do not know what we  have got until we lose it, but it is also true that what  we have been missing out until it arrives...Once, I closed  my eyes and recalled all my dear friends faces.I realised  that they all all been like one of the shooting stars we  could seldom see in the New Zealand and Malaysia's night sky.      They had streaked across my life and lit up the darkness cos  without friends, our lives would be terribly empty they have    filled up a gaping hole in my life...thanks to all of you,    &nbsp;my friends, for filling up this hole in my life....   urlLink            
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today was a "sial" day for me..everything today was so uneased around me. Uni was arite but once i went to work, most of customers either pervert, bitch and unfriendly..damn! i hate that..When I went home, I got my Adsl Modem for broadband[yey] but yet i still cannot use it coz the telekom ppl hasn't yet connect my internet even tho they told me i can log on anytime today damn!sial betul lar..damnit! geram then when i was on the internet[yes i was using my dial-up, then suddenly blackout!] gerammnyer.......actually byk lagi bad things happend to me today but i dnt want to mention it coz it already past n besides there is no point of talking it      Ive got my extension for my essay til next week friday yey..good for me but i guess i hav to struggle to finish it coz i hav another to due on the same week oh bugger..the upcoming holiday is not going to be a hols for me coz i have essay but what the heck i have to enjoy it anyways..i am going back and that is much much more fun hehehe      this morning was so damn cold wait a sec, the whole day man..bloddy feeezing...it was haling[hope i spell it rite] and it keep continuosly happen heheh and it was so nice i even took picture of my brother on it..heheh its like snow..i hope it snow. i wan snow hehehe...desperatly need it...:)  
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Took me about 20 minutes to log on to the Internet today in Uni ..what the F**k????i am so piss now..i prefer to go home at the mo to check my mails but i cant coz i gotta go to class n go to work later :( damn..oh well      today mite be the last day i update my blog before i hv the access to log on to the net again..il be leaving welly tomoro nite afta skol and taking the plane to Msia on thursday morning yey!!!kewl kewl..i can seem to smell the Msian food now hahhah..missing the food so much now..hehehe cant wait to go home lar..      
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       dear blog   I have been so bz for the past couple of dayz that i didnt even bother to check my mails or update my blog..ive been working for 10 hours straight the whole day yesterday and by the time ive got home, i was damn tired. Today my mother told me that we are going back to Malaysia on thursday, This thursday, so malaysia, here I come..yey!!! newayz, even tho I am happy to go home, but i gotta bring my books wit me because I hav 2 essay to due on mondy and tuesday and i got to send it online :( wat a holiday huh??then i hv another one to due after hols open..damnit      I am gonna miss CHCH malam Malaysia that I have promised Kam to go..Sorry liaw..I am going home much2 better aye..Il promise Il come to Visit u guyz aye..:)      I promise I will try to update my blog when I am in KL..even tho I dont have any internet access at home but I will try my best to go online..:) that is a promise that I will keep aye..:)      I am so happy that I could hardly eat at the moment..I was so happy to go home that the very first person I told was Olivia then I called Ninie in KL..I am so gonna Miss the weather in wellington. I am gonna miss the winter in NZ..wait hang on a second.i am not going back for good..i am out frm NZ for the past few dayz..oh bugger!!      i gotta go blog, if not i couldnot finish the essay that I have to due tomoro..its only 300 words..i can finish it in 1/2 hours coz I am expert [bak kat Olivia]..  
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Happy Birthday to my dearly friend: Kam Weng Yuen. Today is his big day yey! Hope he has a good day today..  I received a bad news from my mother saying my grandfather passed away yesterday morning [Malaysia time] :’( I was shocked but mostly I felt regret coz I didn’t had the chance to visit him when I went home last April. I think that was the most regrettable moment I had in my entire life. I wish I had seen him before so that I don’t have this guilty feeling burden on me now. But someone had told me that there’s nothing to be regret about because it already happened and I got to move on. I hope my grandfather will forgive all the mistakes I have done and I will always love him and I will never going to forget him. Amin to my grandfather:  Abdul Aziz     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink       Bestfriends are like diamons, they are rare but once you found it, you tend to keep it forever [Olivia Thomas, Me, Christy Ngeow]   urlLink         
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        *This song was orignally done by Brian McKnight but Brian (Littrell) sang it as his solo in concert.       ONE LAST CRY      My shattered dreams and broken heart Are mending on the shelf I saw you Holding hands Standing close to someone else Now I sit all alone Wishin? all my feeling was gone Gotta get over you Nothing for me to do But have one last cry  One last cry Before I leave it all behind I've gotta put you out of my mind This time Stop living a lie  I know I got to be strong, But around me Life goes on And on And on And on  I'm gonna dry my eyes Right after I have one last cry  One last cry Before I leave it all behind I've gotta put you out of my mind For the very last time Quit living a lie  I guess I'm down I guess I'm down I guess I'm down To my last cry  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Today was not a bad day for me at all. i wen to class as usual in the morning and the evening. i went to morning class and did my presentation. even though the presentation did not go the way that i wanted [technically, it was my mistake coz i was supposed to tell my tutor if i need a projector, laptop etc beforehand, instead but i didnt know abt it and i didnt tell her that] I did my presentation safely and sound. The end of the presentation,my classmates have to ask quetions or reflects on what i have presented. Well it turned out good and luckily my tutor[well she wasnt my tutor actually. my real tutor was sick so she had to replace her for a while till shes feeling better] saved the day. Oh man! the reading was hard to understand and i dun even know what they wanted and i presented the whole passage to the class instead. I felt so ashamed that I wanted to cover my face with something. So embarrasing man. How do u feel that you  have done your work nicely, clean and presentable but u cannot present it and u had to summarize a reading that you dont even get it even though you have read it for almost gizzilian times? Literally I understand the reading but to summarize it and presente it to the whole class [nah i dont think so!] I had to read the sentence that I highligted one by one. Just imagine how embarrasing was that? I felt like a total idiot. I am in my last trimester of uni. I was not supposed to do it but like in a freshman year, I did it anyway. Take Note:    The most embarrasing moment of this trimester.     Later, I went to see Neene and we walked together to go back to her place[coz i parked my car there at her parking space] I had to man coz there was so bloody hard to find a parking space in Uni these days. It even hard to find car parking for 5 minutes.  I remember the other day that I needed to drop my essay in Uni and took me for about 10 minutes to find a "5 minutes parking space". I was so pissed off man. I just needed to drop an essay and it takes less thatn 5 minute to do that. Damn it!    I went to my "Guidance and Counselling" class in the evening and it was totally totally a boring class as usual. When i went there, i didnt see any familiar faces that I normally sit with. I had to wait and praying that those familiar faces come today or else I would be die waiting. Luckily my fren turned up. Today we were learning abt this Pyschoanalytic and Self-Helping family what-so-ever. I had no idea what my lecturer was talking about. Me as usual after finished writing those notes on the OHP, started dreaming and floating in the air as if I was somewherelse. Then afterwards we had to watch a video about the Family problems what-so-ever and yet again, I still I had no clue what was the vid about. I was so boring that I ended up creating something on my piece of paper. Gosh, then what's the point of going to class then? [the reason why I always  have to go class is  because she gives a good note or I am force to go]    I am now actually taking break from doing my essay [yeah I know..how many essay do I have?]. Well lets see how many do I have to finish by the end of this trimester. I have 3 journals, 5 essays, 5 assignments, 3 writing exercises, 1 portfolio, 1 seminar presentation and 1 writing test. Hmm..hows that sound? This is the reason why I alwayz lock myself up in the house. Its not that I dont want to go out and have fun with my friends but look at the amounts of work I have to finish. Each essay can be 2000+ and each week continously I have to hand in essay, so obviously I have not time to hang out. I know my friends have been asking me " Ike where are you? how come never heard from you, blah2 blah2?" Take note guys, its not that i dun want to hang out, I am extremely busy. I have heaps of things to due, that still doesnt count the essay that I hav to rewrite sometimes. Arghh when that happen, I will be totally piss.    Break in another 2 weeks..but still its not going to be a holiday for me..I have 2 to due on the hols and 1 after that * a very long sigh*            
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       dear blog, it's been a while since i've updated my website ;} been so busy lar did not even had time to look at it *silly me* newayz nothing interesting happen to me for the past couple of dayz except today oh bugger! i went to my WRIT 203-Writing for print media class and we had to this peer review thingy and i had to swap my essay with somebodyelse in my class. i swaped my essay with this guy who sat next to me and guess wot? he didnt even do his essay so i said "well, u can read mine then. when u finished we can review it together". So i waited for abt 5 minits for him to finish reading it. After a while, he called me and we reviewd the essay together and guess again what happend? he said MY WRITING SUCKS!!!  he qoute" your writing is bad, ur conclusion n introducation dont flow, u use really bad wordS, ur reading make me confuse, u use repetition, u cannot put present, past n future in one essay, u have a bad structure of essay and blah2" i was like "f--k u man!. who do u think you are? u are not even suppose to say those things. those things are mean man!". While he was saying that, I felt like I want to slap his face and say "well buddy at least i did mine u didnt even do ur homework". Stupid Russian!!!! u were suppose to correct my grammar or some shit like that not gave a bad comment on it...or u can say something bad but not as bad as that!! thats mean, horrible, despise and bad bad opinion..damn those people..i really hate him even tho i only spoke to him once and i will not speak to him nor seat next to him again..  oh well shit stuffs happen but u gotta overcome it then..arghh tomoro is my seminar presentation day and i havnt done anything abt it..and i am totally totally going to die..what am i gonna do it. the presentaion is 20 minute..what am i gonna say what am i gonna do damn damn..*sigh* arghhhhhh tidakkkkkkkkkkkkkk!!  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I want to cry but there are not more tears in my eyes     I want to scream but there are no more voices in me     I want to run but I am scare I mite fall     I want to live but I am afraid to live anymore     I want to love but I am scare to be loved again     I want to hide but I am scare people will find me     What I should do??   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       not in the mood to write anything at the moment, but feeling to jot something down..      dear blog, yesterday was another interesting day of mylife. I have met my old classmates even tho one of them cant seem to remember who I was..am..kinda sad but what the f**k, at least had to the chance to talk to him was great enuff..it was so kewl to know at least some of my frens are still breathing...       dear blog, I was supposed to be in class now but I am so sick at the moment. I feel all my body is itching, my legs are sore, my nose has been sneezing, my throat is sore and so on [all the bad conditions when your body is not feeling well]..I have been having a really bad headache for the past couple of months. The same headache that has been bugging my brain and keep me sick all the times. I wish I could tear this brain up and see what is going on inside of my head..har har..but I know it's impossible. If  I have done that, I would be dead by now..=)      to sum up, I am getting sick. Face the facts Ike!  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       finally..i have finished my essay..wala! but the bad news is my friend had an accident and he wont tell me when did it happen *sob*..well not in the mood to talk abt anything now..  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I was supposed to be doing my essay now but I don't feel like doing it. It's DUE tomoro and I am still playing with it, looks like I am going to hand it in on tuesday..f**k, I have another essay to due on tuesday..and I haven't quite finish yet! lazy me!I dont't know what have happend to me..I can't seem to remember what I have read. I have read the same book 5 times and I still cannot understand it.I have to write a written critique based on what I have read but yet, I am stuck here running out of ideas on what to write.Wait..hang on a second, I have done this essay before *sigh* I know how to write a critque but why my mind still shallow..out of ideas??why?why can't i understand the context?why? thats one question that I cannot find the answer..=) by the way, I have been listening to this song..instead of doing my essay..          Was it something I didn't say?-98 degrees             Spending another night alone     Wondering when I'm ever gonna see you again     Thinking what I would give to get you back baby     I should have told you how I felt then     Instead I kept it to myself     I let my love go unexpressed'     Til it was too late, and you walked away          Chorus :Was it something I didn't say     When I didn't say I love you     Was it words that you've never heard     All those words I should have told you     All those times, all those nights     When I had the chance to     Was it something I didn't say     Always assumed that you'd be there     Couldn't foresee the day that you'd ever be leaving me     How could I let my world slip through my hands baby     I took for granted that you knew     All the love I had for youI guess you never had a clue'     Til it was too late, you walked away          [Chorus]All the words were in my heart, they went unspoken     Baby now my silent heart, is a heart that's broken     Shoulda let you know you're the one I needed near me     But I never let you hear me     [Chorus]   
    
</post>


</Blog>