<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I've been trying to create a link and I just can't do it.&nbsp; I know it's s'posed to be easy.&nbsp; I know I'm s'posed to be able to figure it out but what can I say?&nbsp; Women and machinery. So I'll put the addresses here and you can manually type them in.&nbsp; It wastes precious time but I'm going to have to work on this.&nbsp; I'm the kid in 4th grade math that can't figure out long division and I'm about to give up and raise my hand. Anyhoozlebees-- noneedformeaning.blogspot.com - that's Mangi and she is sassy fun notevenher.blogspot.com - that's Liz whom I used to share a room with, a true party girl absolunacy.blogspot.com - I don't know if these kids are still really using it but it's a comedy troupe I was in at Ball State  Now get going--do as you're told! 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was watching Star Wars last night with my homeslice Liz and of course we all know that Darth Vader is a great villain but I wanted to make a list of other awesome villains besides him because he's too easy. Best Villains Ever (Besides Darth Vader): 5. Jesus (The Big Lebowski) 4. The Monkey (Raiders of the Lost Ark) 3. Count Reugen (The Princess Bride) 2.The Book with the Face in it (Care Bears: the Movie) 1.Ming the Merciless (Flash Gordon) &nbsp; &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A word about my blog name....... A few years ago I was living in Cincinnati and met a band called Ultimate Fake Book.&nbsp; They were fun guys and one of their album titles was Open Up and Say Awesome.&nbsp; I thought it was a fun name and I've been looking for years to find an appropriate way to steal it. This band is also the inspiration for my URL--they told me about a band called the Kids of Widney High.&nbsp; I'm not going to get into it but I found one of their albums at a record store in a section called 'difficult listening'.&nbsp; It's about as difficult as listening can get but their album was called, "Let's Get Busy" and I liked it.&nbsp; So again, I found my chance to steal. I'd say the only thing harder to listen to than the Widney High kids is an album I found near them in a sub-category called "Celebritites at their Worst".&nbsp; It's a 2 disc set of Judy Garland's late night ramblings and&nbsp;I totally bought it.&nbsp; I guess in her twilight years she was trying to put an autobiography together and she thought it would help get her thoughts together if she recorded herself talking about her life.&nbsp; But she would record herself late at night when she was presumably strung out.&nbsp; The results are a bracing study of arguably the greatest entertainer of the 20th Century.&nbsp; My friends are always interested to listen but they can't stand it for more than a few minutes.&nbsp; I reach a threshold too, but there are some real gems in there--like when she talks about trying to get over the rainbow,"...and I couldn't! So WHAT!" Priceless. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since I just turned 25, I figured it was time to join the blog nation.&nbsp; How was my birthday, you ask? Why,&nbsp;it rocked....so....very....hard.&nbsp; The fun really started when I got drunk in the afternoon which is my favorite way to get drunk.&nbsp; Then I went out for some karyoke with my friends--we ruled the school.&nbsp;&nbsp; The best birthday perk has got to be not having to pay for your drinks. &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>