<Blog>


<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My father in law, Eddie,&nbsp;has made it apparent from day one that he doesn't like me and feels that my son, his step grandson, is not part of HIS family. He went as far as to have a sexual relationship with my husbands ex wife.&nbsp;Eddie is constantly telling my hubby that he needs to go back to his "real family and quit playing house" with me. In the 5 years that my husband I have been together Eddie and I have had one civil conversation, not that we have un civil conversations we just don't talk to each other. I am very aware of how he feels about me and I am not going to kiss his butt and he knows how I feel about him. When my hubby found out he was being deployed my wonderful sister in law decided to tell him instead of letting my hubby do it. Eddie comes over acting all concerned and dishearten that his oldest son&nbsp;is being sent off into a combat zone.&nbsp;So dishearten he scheduled a trail ride for the time when hubby was leaving. He is one of those types of people who uses and uses and uses but then wonders why no one wants to talk&nbsp;him. When&nbsp;hubby left he told me to not give out his address to his family, he has their addresses and will&nbsp;write them when he feels he is ready. I&nbsp;respect that totally.&nbsp;  Today Eddie has called 4 times and even came by and rang the door bell for 10 minutes. I know it is chicken to avoid him like this but I don't have any patience to listen to him and his sob story about why his kids don't like him. It would end with me telling him to&nbsp;grow up. If he wants to be family then he should have been trying for the last 5 years. I have a great relationship with my mother in law, Eileen. I have nothing to say to&nbsp;the rest of the&nbsp;members of&nbsp;my husbands family.&nbsp;&nbsp;  I have to say I find it so pathetic that they are now concerned about how he is doing and how much danger he is in. When he had surgery where were they? When his daughter was born where were they? They only want to come around when they feel that they will benefit from the attention. I know that my sister in law tells everyone that her brother is in Afghanistan and oh...Whoa is me....blah blah.  Family should be family no matter what....   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I figured I would start this Blog as a way to keep in touch with my husband who is serving in the US Army in Afghanistan.  In the recent months my life has sucked in massive ways.  My dad, who had cancer for a year, died on May 04, 2004. It was the worst day of my life. The whole process of watching him die has&nbsp;cracked my very being. I think that I will get over it in time...not get over it...bad choice of words...learn to be without him. If that even makes sense. I only have one sibling, David, and he is in the Army as well. He came back from Afghanistan when our dad died. I know this bothers him but we love each other so much that we don't turn to each other to grieve.  Then my husband got the news that he was chosen to spend 18 months in Afghanistan. His military pay will be enough to keep us afloat financially while he is gone, but as a family missing him is hard on all of us. He has two children from a previous marriage and his ex wife goes beyond the call of duty to make life a living hell for us. She has taken a particular offense to me being alive. He and I have one child and then I have one from a previous relationship. Total of 4, but 2 that are with me 24-7. This deployment is harder than I ever expected.  As much negative as there is going on currently I am trying to find ways to keep some positive flow to things.&nbsp; I paid a personal trainer and am trying to get into shape. I am still working on my degree(s). I am spending a lot of time thinking about who I am and what I want my life to mean and be about. Trying to sort out the spiritual side of me.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; This is my first posting, hopefully I will pull it together more and more as time goes on.  &nbsp;  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I dropped my husband off at his barrack and hugged him good bye. I turned away before he got on the bus that would take him off into combat. I cried the entire 6 hour drive home. I am so lost. He has not been home for about 6 weeks but he was in Indiana...now he will be in Afghanistan. I cannot get over the loneliness of the house now. How I know that for months on end I will not catch his smell in the house. I should be grateful that he is going now...in an age when there is almost cosistent phone access and some internet access. In WWI and WWII husbands were gone for years and years with no contact or news. I am sad right now and trying to think through how I am really going to go through this. I am glad that my children are not here. Seeing me break down and cry over nothing would probably scare them. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>