<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Music, how could anyone live without it?? When I think about it, I'm always listening to or thinking about music. Music is a constant thing always following me wherever I go. Most recently, I've been listening to Adore's version of "Your Love O Lord", since it's one of our new songs for Oneighty. I really must say, they did an excellent job at creating a new and much better version of the song. I think all the versions of the songs they play for worship sound better than the originals, there's just something about them. I was kind of bummed this year at Elevate when they didn't play, but Yancy did an excellent job! I also really enjoy her music. It's great to see them live to see what awesome musical talents God has given them. Anyhow, before I bore all of you to death with my bad writing skills, I'll head out. PLEASE make some comments...... things you want me to talk about, questions you have, etc.
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's getting to be that time of year already. School is a little over a month away and there's always planning that needs to be done! Deciding which classes to take and making sure everything adds up to the right credits can be quite confusing. But in a sense it can be fun too. It looks like this school year isn't going to be too bad for me. Only ONE semester of math! No science at all. Sounds pretty good to me. It's going to be very busy at the beginning because of Oneighty opening on September 22nd, but everything will work good.    PS.... It would be nice to have a little feedback from you guys. At least let me know you're taking a look at my blog. Thanks. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We had another great work night at Oneighty. The walls look alot cleaner, as well as the duct work. Carpet was cut and placed along the outside of the auditorium. It's looking great. All of the fabric that's going on the sound panels in the auditorium is cut, and it's ready to be painted. And I think that's about it. If you guys don't like this little section of my blog let me know. I'll probably do it every week if I don't get any comments saying not too. 
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got back a little while ago from visiting a church in Sheboygan called Praise Fellowship. I've been wanting to check it out  for a while to see what their service was like. There were a couple of things that I found rather interesting during the service. Thought I'd share them with you.   //Music.  First of all the music. One of the things I notice right away when I visit a church. (That was one of the driving forces of oneighty that pulled me in.) It wasn't too bad, although I knew only one or two songs. The drummer didn't seem to be keeping a solid beat either. He was just kind of "tinkling" around on the drums. And there was too much guitar. I'm guessing that had to do with the mixing in the soundbooth, which by the way is very cool. It's located on the second floor of the building..... pretty interesting. But all in all the music was good, some great instrumental parts and that kind of thing.   //Presentation.  Secondly is video presentation. This was pretty good too. There weren't too many weird things about it. I liked that the song slides had the title of the song (something to think about at our church). As far as video goes, there were two big pieces of video clips. First, during the announcement part they showed a video, which I wasn't very impressed with. The quality was not real great, and the blue screen before they hit play came up on the screen, not real impressive either. The second piece of video on the other hand was of much better quality. This was the video opener for the message. This was put together by Praise Fellowship, and they did an excellent jorb! Two thumbs up on that one. Another big thing I noticed was the logo, which was nice and crisp looking, and the transition from it to other things was great.  //Message.  Very enjoyable message. Pastor Ed is on a series called "Extreme Makeover". He talked about desires and greed tonight. The opener, like I said up above was excellent. The material shared was good, relevant material. Which always gets a thumbs up.  //Overall feel.  Pretty good. I'm not sure if I would attend every week, it just isn't my style. I like things really loud and peppy. But that's why God brings us to the churches that we're in. Everyone was very friendly, and I enjoyed worshipping with that body of believers.  Interested in learning more about Praise Fellowship? Check out their website, www.praisefellowshipag.com.
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here's a story I wrote for a Creative Writing Assignment (it was also something to do on the car ride up to Gary's Cabin). My aunt liked it, so I thought I'd post it. Enjoy.  	It was a beautiful sunny morning in Tulsa and the Johnson's were getting ready for their yearly trip to Silver Dollar City, an Amusement Park located in Missouri. It's a family tradition for the Johnson's to visit Silver Dollar City every year. Everything was packed and ready to go by 6:00 AM. There was an attitude of excitement running through the house as everyone got ready for what was usually a four to five hour trip. Dad and mom went through the checklist one more time to make sure everything was packed and ready to go. Little did they know, but they missed a whole bag. 	By now it was getting to be 6:30, so everyone jumped in the van, excited to get on the road. They decided to eat their breakfast enroute, which consisted of bagels and strawberry cream cheese. Mom spread the cream cheese on everyone's bagel and passed them through the van. The last bagel almost made it to Johnny, but not quite. He dropped it on the seat and it got all over the place. Then Jenny's orange juice spilt all over her because she was paying too much attention to Johnny while he was dropping his bagel. Luckily mom brought napkins along. 	An hour passed. Everything seemed to be going as planned, dad realized he took a wrong turn. The road signs just didn't look familiar. He had gotten off course only by fifteen minutes, but fifteen minutes was plenty. He turned the van around and got back on the right road.  	The kids slept for an hour, so mom and dad got a chance to talk. In that hour they realized they had forgotten mom's bag of hygiene items at home. Since they were already two hours from home they decided that it would be alright without the hair products, toothbrush, and toothpaste. All of a sudden the van came to a stop and the kids woke up. It was construction! Dad was not happy about this. The roadwork made them take a detour which added an extra half hour from their travel time. Things were just not going well on this car trip from heck. 	It was definitely time for a gas stop. They pulled into a gas station that looked like a good gas station. Dad filled up the tank and everyone else went in to get something to drink and use the bathrooms, which Jimmy found to be rather disgusting. And the clerk was scary-looking. To dad's surprise, gas was $2.15 per gallon. He was not real excited since it cost him about $45.  	They got back on the road, and the rest of the ride went well. No spills, high gas prices, dirty bathrooms, scary clerks, or construction, the weather was beautiful. The hotel finally came into sight, everyone was excited to be finished with the long car trip. This was a hotel that they had never stayed at before, the first impression was not a very good one, which started the trip from heck....
      
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Everything went pretty good tonight at Oneighty. Stuck alot of sticky notes on carpet tiles, and that kind of thing. We also found something fun to do.... ride on the garbage can wheels!! Plenty of good stuff was accomplished tonight and I think it was a great start to alot of great work nights. For those of you who helped out, thanks a bunch! It's gonna be undescribable when it's finished.
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone. I'm extremely bored right now. No worship rehearsal, or oneighty practice tonight at all! It's kind of weird. Hopefully I'll find something to do tonight. Have a good one.
      
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone. Just checking this out. I might add some stuff, I might not. 
      
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone, sorry it's been a couple days again since I've updated my blog. This post is more about you guys my readers, if there are any of you. I'm curious to know what your favorite types of movies are. My favorite types would have to be scary/suspenseful and comedy. There's something about scary movies that catches my attention. I guess I just like being on the edge of my seat. Secondly, I love comedies. I always enjoy having a good laugh. Let me know what your favorites are.... could be one, two, or three, or however many you like! Thanks to those who have given feedback, I hope to hear from more of you.
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know I said I wasn't going to add anything this week, but I just saw The Village and thought I'd comment on it. I would have to say it definitely kept me on the edge of my seat. The title "The Village" really fits the movie well I think. When I read the description of it I didn't really understand what it was about, but after viewing it for about 20 minutes I started to catch on. I don't get scared very often, but this one did me pretty good. If you haven't seen The Village, I recommend it. It was an excellent flick, especially if you're into the scary/suspenseful movies. People who have seen it, let me hear your comments. I'm interested to know what you thought of the movie.
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone, sorry I haven't been updating as much lately. I'm trying to take care of some last minute things before the PGA. And speaking of the PGA, I will not be updating my blog at all next week because of my busy schedule. I've gotta work 5 days out of the week and the other two I'll be taking care of oneighty projects with Mr. Houk since we'll be having oneighty practice the following week at the new building. I'll be back the following week so keep checkin' it out! Have an excellent week.
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          On MSN today in the news flashes I saw a story called "Reality TV makes Amish Stars". I thought it sounded kind of interesting, so I thought I'd check it out. It turned out to be really stupid. Who would make a show like that? I guess with all the reality tv being so popular in the here and now it makes a little sense. But Amish people living in the city, give me a break.       The fun thing about reading that story was that I got to make fun of a friend. Doesn't sound very nice, but it's pretty funny. Somebody he works with thinks he's Amish for some reason...... pretty interesting. If you're interested in checking out the MSN article here's the link......  http://entertainment.msn.com/tv/article.aspx?news=164904      On a side note, there's another great article I had the chance to read from MSN. It's called "How to Jazz Up a Tiny Room". I thought it was an interesting article if you look at it from a creative standpoint. Check it out......  http://houseandhome.msn.com/Decorate/5ColorSchemesforSmallSpaces.aspx  Adios.
      
</post>


</Blog>