<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There has been a lot of debate on marriage lately.&nbsp; I just thought I would share some of mine with you.  You see, to me the act of marriage doesn't stem from something legal, but Godly.&nbsp; It is, as I have already said, a spiritual bond through God and an act of God meant to be holy.&nbsp; The misconception that it is anything different I simply cannot agree with.&nbsp; If you are gay, then I have no problem with being what I have always been...your loving brother.&nbsp; We could argue for centuries and maybe never see eye to eye, but I will never change my mind about the sanctity of the act of marriage.&nbsp; While it may be true that some secs of the organized denominations of the church have had wrong views, that doesn't make them Godly views.&nbsp; The Bible cleary states right for wrong, sin from not sin.&nbsp; As you know, I am not perfect by any stretch of the imagination, nor would I ever claim it.&nbsp; I am just stating that what I base my beliefs on and my faith in, resides in something much deeper than myself.&nbsp; Faith is something given by God, it cannot be boughten, sought, obtained from reading or hearing...it is from God and him alone.&nbsp; I have learned over the 25 years I have been alive that I am wrong a lot.&nbsp; But the thing that has always remained constant is God's promises to me.&nbsp; God's word and his faithfulness are unbroken truths that remain constant and never change.&nbsp; I remember once upon a time someone who believed that too.&nbsp; But time washed away hope and with it came shattered dreams.&nbsp; Blaming God for the unfair circumstances, but I grew to realize that if I was going to question the bad, shouldn't I also question the good.&nbsp; For in God's eyes all have sinned and fall short of his glory...right?&nbsp; Well what could I ever do to make things right between God and myself...long story short....nothing.&nbsp; God loves me no matter what....and I don't deserve it.&nbsp; Decision time right?&nbsp; Well should I get what I don't deserve or get what I think I deserve.&nbsp; I don't deserve eternal life, forgiveness, etc.&nbsp; It's kind of obvious which road I have chosen...at least when I try to stay on it!&nbsp; ;o)&nbsp; However, chosing that road has come with a price...giving up my life for God.&nbsp; Obeying him and doing his will when I have been shown it.&nbsp; That means I am in God, and he is in me and nothing can change that.&nbsp; I pray for you everyday.&nbsp; I hope would do the same for me.&nbsp; God always listens, and answers (in his own time and his own way).&nbsp; Take a moment to listen more and talk less...maybe you'll hear him ;O) 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok so here I go...joining this blog thing!&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>