<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok so i just went shopping with my mom, and i couldn't help but notice that women wearing curlers in public is growing at an alarming rate.  what is it with the curlers ladies? are we REALLY in that much of a hurry to get to the store that we can even make ourselves presentable before we go? is it that important to have curls for tonight? shouldn't we at least cover our heads if we must be out and about with the curlers?  i saw some poor woman today who'd lost a few curlers in her travels. is she going to be a mess tonight or what?  save yourself the trouble ladies - invest in a curling iron for days that, well, you don't feel like running around with plastic cylinders attached to your heads.  that's it. thanks for listening. :) 
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i just have to say that my brother is the shit. he is going to be HUGE one day. he is right on the cusp of falling into the entertainment industry, and i'm soooo proud of him.  he has already had a phenominal year. he's a senior at temple university, he's been to rome, italy to study abroad, we both met our idol janet jackson this year, he's helped produce his first fashion show in philly, and oh yeah, he's been offered jobs at sean john and other ad agencies. my brother is also the king of meeting famous folk. he always calls me like, "i bumped into ellen degeneres today at the mall". huh??  so he calls me today to tell me that he went to an industry party for blender magazine last night in new york city. made all sorts of contacts there. saw de la soul walking down the street. saw darren henson (choreographer for britney and nsync) on his cell phone on a street corner. bumped into godfrey(dreaded guy from sprite commercials) in the bathroom.  and somehow got to talk to the ceo of a major ad agency about how to be put on.  chris - you're the shit. just don't forget to pull your sister up with you on your way to the top. 
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      What the hell are you looking at? Clearly, you should carry yourself to the store - yeah, they have stuff in your size. Why can’t I be fly in a fierce figure-flattering ensemble? Why can’t I rock my business suits on my way to the top? Why don’t I give a single f*ck ‘bout what you think? Because this is me. Deal with it.  Why you gotta have something to say? You need to look at your own life and analyze. Why can’t I work hard? Why can’t I be a successful business woman? Why don’t I knock some knowledge into your dome? Because you don’t deserve my effort. Deal with it.  Why you gotta criticize how I speak? You need to open your ears, and not just listen, but hear the educated woman that I am. Why can’t I live a decent drug-free, kid-free, man-free life? Why can’t I be the writer, the dreamer, the motivated person that I am? Why don’t I waste my time with folk of your kind? Because I don’t need to stoop to your level. Deal with it.  You have a lot of nerve, To be staring me up and down, examining my style, my voice, my aura. Girlfriend, you need to look in your personal mirror called a soul and reflect Ponder why you can’t keep your eyes off me. What is it that you see that provokes your jealousy?  I don’t think I’m better than you, I’m just doing me.  Don’t hate me cause I carry myself with confidence, It is a trait that is gained not just given. Don’t judge me cause I choose to be optimistic, No one desires a pessimist in their life. Don’t misunderstand me cause I associate with people of all races and backgrounds. I am still a proud black Guyanese-American.  Don’t hate me, don’t judge me, and don’t misunderstand me. Why do you need to read this again, carefully and slowly? Because I gave you many reasons to respect me. Deal with it.              
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Looking back…  Looking back through the window of time, Looking back on all we’ve done. Looking back on when we were just friends, Looking back on when we became one. Looking back on all the arguments, Looking back on all the times we made up, Looking back on our lighthearted jokes, Looking back on when we were serious.  But I don’t wanna look back on all our fights, Don’t wanna look back on things done right. Don’t wanna look back on how you begged me to date you, Don’t wanna look back on the shit you did to make me hate you. Don’t wanna look back on all night conversations on the phone, Don’t wanna look back on nights when you didn’t come home. Don’t wanna look back on the past seven and a half years, Don’t wanna remember the laughter nor the tears.  Don’t wanna look back, cause if I do, I think I’ll actually miss you. I’ll miss you more, More than ever before.  I can’t take this anymore,I’m going to close that damn window. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
           Just to be with you,   I'd walk across the Sahara, barefoot for miles and days   just for the chance to drink from a cup you've graced with your lips...       Just to be with you,   I'd swim through the bluest and deepest oceans and seas   just for a chance to wipe your eyes when you cry...       Just to be with you,   I'd climb the highest mountains    just for a chance to dance with you under moonlit and star-studded sky...       I'd do these things because you are the song that makes my soul sing,    you are the touch that my body aches for,    you are the one that makes my life complete...       And for your love, I'd do anything.       Anything...  
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Inadequate...that's how he made her feel.   She grew tired of being compared to other women   teased about her body   and scolded about what she couldn't do right.   Night after night...she cried.   She knew she had to go,    but something deep inside   kept telling her no.   Something...kept her there.   But she wanted to leave so badly -    to leave this hell   to be in place where she could be herself.   Still she stayed.   Pretty soon...she started to believe what he said   And she began to hate herself.   her hatred built up inside   and she couldn't overcome the immense pain,   feeling he'd never want her anyway.       Adequate...that's all she ever wanted to feel.   She knew her body wasn't perfect   and that she made mistakes   and that she didn't look like a model.   But still he he treated her like shit,   like his personal slave   abusing her heart and doing whatever he pleased.        Eventually...he found himself on both his knees   weeping uncontrollably   praying at her grave.   She took her own life just a week before.   Love...was all she wanted.   to be loved for who she was   not loved for what she was.   So with a single bullet she ended it all.   If only he stopped   to listen to accept   to love, she'd still be here.       Lucky...for him we can rewind   reverse back into time   retrieve the hurtful things   and change his awful ways.       Instead of standing at her grave   reading her last words   on this page.  
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      they say you forgive, but you never forget... learn from experiences, and never regret. no matter how difficult things may seem, i can get through it because God walks with me.   i was a young child, only 2 or 3, when my babysitter molested me. she'd lock me in a room during the day, in the dark doing what she pleased without using her heart. i would scream, i'd even cry as she fingered me with vaporub, burning my insides. i couldn't tell anyone, i was too scared. i thought as i got older, my fear would disappear.   but through my life, i've kept these feelings inside. feeling dirty and ashamed like i had something to hide. i will always hate what happened to me, though i love the woman i have grown to be. now i'm strong enough to let my hatred go, and with God's help, i've done just so.   so i forgive her for what she did, did to me when i was a kid. this is a tough but necessary step, in order to forgive...though i'll  never  forget.     
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      when i think of you, all i want to do is close my eyes and imagine that my daydreams and night fantasies would all become my reality. that's all i want to do...   when i hear your name, all i want to do is yell it from the highest of mountains to the deepest of valley lows, and rejoice in its infinity of echoes. that's all i want to do...   when i see your face, all i want to do is run my fingers over every feature and curve, look into your eyes to see your soul, kiss your lips to taste your words,  and translate the unknown and unspoken into body language. that's all i want to do...   when you speak to me, all i want to do is melt, my insides becoming a mixed concoction of nervousness, excitement, attraction and anticipation. that's all i want to do...   the inner mystery of your heart has resulted in the outer beauty which is our friendship.   i've never know such a wonderful feeling, and all i want to do...   is thank you.   
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      finally! i have a place to put my thoughts. thank you to chion for turning me onto blogger.com. geez, do i have a lot to post!   
      
</post>


</Blog>