<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      [just a  caveat emptor  here: there may be more questions than answers presented in this post.&nbsp; consider yourself fairly warned.]   what exactly does it mean, and what exactly should one do, when on some particular day you don't feel much like a Christian at all?&nbsp; that is, you  know  you're a Christian: you prayed a prayer, you believe in Jesus, that His life and death and resurrection were for you, in your place, because you couldn't; you go to church; you pray, read the bible and even watch TBN once in a while (sorry, it was just too easy!).&nbsp; but all that being said you wake up one rainy (or sunny) day and it just feels like it's gone, like when the after affects of a drug have worn off and you're back to "normal".&nbsp; what's a Christian to do when he just doesn't feel it?   and i think this is going to happen to all of us at some point in our walks,&nbsp; if it hasn't already.&nbsp; (one thing i do know is that God would not have us placing our assurance of salvation in the way we feel.)&nbsp; and to be clear, my question is not are we still saved when we don't feel it?&nbsp; rather, i wonder what you out there do when these days come your way.&nbsp; is it harder for you to pray?&nbsp; do you "ride it out" until some feeling comes back?&nbsp; do you get dejected and think God has left you on your own?&nbsp; I'm curious to hear.   as you may have properly inferred from my present interest in this topic, today is one of those days for me.&nbsp; my initial inclination was to think of something i could do to get my "saved feelings" to increase, but in the next thought that seemed to be folly (see above re: assurance and feeling).&nbsp; so i took&nbsp;a walk.&nbsp; and now I'm writing about it.&nbsp; and, to be honest, i don't feel any more saved now than i did when i woke up.&nbsp; what, you ask, am i going to do?&nbsp; well, I'm going to get up and work on Sunday's sermon (i welcome any and all tips, pointers, etc.), have lunch in a bit and probably take a nap in the afternoon.&nbsp; for me, the important thing is to live my life based solely on the promise of God, made known through Christ Jesus.&nbsp; i know that sounds "preacheresque", but it really is all we have to hold to.&nbsp;   for me, feeling this way serves to remind me that the only absolute guarantees, the only things upon which you can truly, fully,  eternally  depend, are the promises Christ made to us and sealed with His life, death, and resurrection.&nbsp; going about the rest of my day as if i felt saved prompts me to contemplate the truth that i  am saved , not by works or intuitions or feelings or weather patterns, or the opinions of others, but by the grace of God, and that grace alone.   what about you?   
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      if i have said this before, then bear with me:&nbsp; letting go is tough business.&nbsp; over the past few weeks and especially in the last few days i have been forced to confront the need in my life to let go of things that i have been holding onto very, very tightly.&nbsp; and it's not so much that these things (or persons) are going away, per se, it's just that i have to release the idea that things will always be the way they've been, or the way i want them to be, or the way i think i deserve them to be.&nbsp; i know, i know, vaguery 101, but the principle is the same regardless the what or the who or the when, etc.&nbsp; we own nothing- nothing is ours.&nbsp; if we live, we live unto the Lord.&nbsp; if we die, again, we die unto Him.&nbsp; everything in between life and death?&nbsp; yep- His too.&nbsp;   the kicker is that everything is actually better in the long run when we realize that the things we hold in our hands are not ours to hold, but rather His to give.&nbsp; when we view the people, places and things in our lives as gifts to treasure rather than posessions to own we are careful to avoid the bondage of ownership and instead enjoy the blessings of graceful stewardship.&nbsp; to wit, my wife is not mine in the sense that she does what i want when i want and all that.&nbsp; rather, she is mine in the sense that in His eternal wisdom God has allowed her life to be joined to mine, and each day He allows us together is a gift for which i should exercise particular care.&nbsp; the best way for me to thank God for her is to enjoy her for who she is, not to expect her to be what i think she should be, or worse to ask her to live the way i think she ought to.&nbsp;   why is it we hold so tightly to so many things?&nbsp; why do we so strive to be owners, dissatisfied with the call to be stewards?&nbsp; i don't know for sure, but i have a strong sense that it has something to do with pride.&nbsp; We esteem ourselves to be beyond the need for God and in turn fail to realize that it is because of Him we have all the things we are quick to call our own.&nbsp; maybe this is why sometimes it takes pain (a loss, a confrontation, a bitter realization, or worst of all,  an unexpected change)  to bring us back to the place where we ultimately confess that we can't&nbsp;own or control anything, so please God, you be you and i'll rest in your hand.&nbsp; for that is where (along with the whole world) we really are, where we were meant to be.   so i'm letting go.&nbsp; and it absolutely, positively, stinks.&nbsp; but only for a moment.&nbsp; or two.&nbsp; but i know that all He has far surpasses all that i think i want or need.&nbsp; and i know that the people, places and things in my life will be more to me when i view them not as things to have but as gifts to treasure.   peace,  s.   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      sunday has come and gone and i am still standing, more or less.&nbsp; it is late now and the bed calls, so i will keep my review of this past Lord's day brief.  on saturday i read a devotion by charles spurgeon based on a verse from exodus.&nbsp; the israelites have come to the shore of the red sea and are grumbling about how good it would be if they had stayed in egypt.&nbsp; moses tells the people to "stand still and see the salvation of God".&nbsp; Spurgeon commented that there may be times in the life of a christian when it is unwise and unsafe to go forward and ungodly to lie down and give up- no turning back.&nbsp; the only option availabe in times like these is to stand still.&nbsp; stay put.&nbsp; and i thought to myself, "yeah- stand still.&nbsp; i think that's what i need to do".&nbsp;&nbsp; and then i thought, "so should i just get in the pulpit and stand still?"&nbsp; and as it turns out, that is very nearly what i did.&nbsp; i ended up reading that certain passage of scripture (&nbsp;i think exodus 13) and then kneeling in prayer, inviting the members of the congregation who felt so inclined to do the same.&nbsp; after a few moments i shared a couple thoughts on God's grace in the face of our inherent unrighteousness, declared the days of grace to have begun in our local fellowship, and dismissed with a benediction.  was it a "good" service?&nbsp; i couldn't tell you.&nbsp; and to be honest, i couldn't care less.&nbsp; we weren't necessarily called to have "good services"; we were called to be faithful.&nbsp; paul reminds us that the growing-&nbsp;bearing the fruit of the Spirit, growing in His mercy, growing&nbsp;in our fellowship, our community, etc.-&nbsp;is God's part.&nbsp; yes we should plant and water, but it is not our power, our words, or our services that actually change people from grace to grace.&nbsp; that is the work of the Spirit of God, and a good thing, too, 'cause i'm sure we'd make an absolute wreck of it if given the chance.  good night, goot tidings, and sleep well-  peace, s. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As I continue to look ahead to Sunday morning's service I realize that I keep falling into the trap of trying to come up with something to say that may actually  change  those who hear it.&nbsp; not that people's lives don't sometimes get changed in services, but it's the idea that  I  might be clever or well-spoken enough to bring about change that is an absolute fallacy.&nbsp; can God change people through words that leave my mouth?&nbsp; sure.&nbsp; can I change anyone?&nbsp; not a snowball's chance in a hot, hot place.   it's a slight difference, that I'll concede, but as far as the condition of my heart and the weight of my soul it's a huge difference, one that I have to address and set right.&nbsp; if I enter tomorrow bearing the weight of actually changing the congregation then I will most assuredly leave the building a defeated, broken man.&nbsp; I hat not been given the power to change, I have been given the commission to declare a life-changing message.&nbsp; now that, I can handle.&nbsp; just as long as I keep it all in its proper perspective I'm okay, but given the fact that I'm  still  an imperfect human, keeping perspective is not always my strong suit.   all of which brings me back to my question from the previous post:&nbsp; what am I to do?&nbsp; would you say that I should just pray for God to speak through me and then, to put it one way, let 'er rip?&nbsp; or should I focus all of my energies on just the right words, just the right phrasing, just the right vocal cadence, in hopes that God will use not just the content but the presentation to effect change in the life of john q churchgoer?&nbsp; or maybe I should just leave it all in the hand of the Holy Spirit and stand back?&nbsp; (I think no- if we didn't have a part we wouldn't have been sent)   maybe it's a combination of all three: first, I think I should pray that God would speak through me, and furthermore I need to be willing to say whatever it is God has for me to say, be it popular or unpopular, refined or simple, long or short.&nbsp; second, I do need to prepare, availing myself first of Scripture and then of any aid I might come across which will help me as I prepare.&nbsp; there's nothing wrong with using the gifts God gives in His service, in fact maybe that's the idea!&nbsp; and finally, while not abdicating my responsibility to be a vessel for His use, I should be mindful to let the wind of the Spirit blow as it will.&nbsp; God is in charge and He knows what He's doing, even if I don't.   well that should be easy enough, right?&nbsp; I wish.&nbsp; if it were churches wouldn't split over the color of a carpet or a man or woman wearing&nbsp;a wedding ring.&nbsp; if there were one formula pastors wouldn't leave the ministry faster than others can enter it; churches wouldn't be full of backbiters, gossips and manipulators.&nbsp; if it were easy we wouldn't need God and the transforming power of His Spirit.&nbsp; if it were easy I wouldn't find myself at His feet, confessing my inability to do, well, anything, only to find that where I can't He can, where I won't He will.&nbsp; Again, with the clarity of a ray of sunlight it dawns on me that the entire point of the gospel is that we can't- so God did.   God, forgive us that we've imprisoned your grace in a jail of rules; forgive us that we've traded our freedom for slavery, your mercy for our merit.&nbsp; take us back to the place of our inability, back to the place where you took God's judgment for us, that we might live and not die.&nbsp;    "for the wages of sin is death,  but  the free gift of God is eternal life in Christ Jesus our Lord." -Romans 6:23     
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i've been agonizing over the sunday service.&nbsp; our church (i mean to say the local church i pastor) has so badly lost sight of Jesus.&nbsp; i wonder how in the world i could lead them to find Him again, and the answer i keep coming to is that i can't.&nbsp; great.&nbsp; but i think i'm right, at least this one time.&nbsp; i can't really make them do anything.&nbsp; i can't make them pray more or read their bible more, and to be honest i don't think i would even want to.&nbsp; most christians nowadays don't need help being pharaseical (i guessed on the spelling there).&nbsp; but even those things that i would love to see them do i can't make them: surrender to grace, grow in God's mercy, allow the peace of God to flow through their lives like a river through a dry and thirsty land.&nbsp; these, these things i would absolutely love to see and feel happen in our local church, but the reality is i just can't make it happen.&nbsp; again, great.  so where does that leave me for sunday?&nbsp; no, really, i'm asking you, gentle reader.&nbsp; play preacher for a moment and tell me how i can get them to turn their eyes upon Jesus without making them.&nbsp; is it a matter of selling the joy of it?&nbsp; if i can convince them how wonderful it would be to find Him and hold on to Him and find Him to be holding onto them- is that the trick?&nbsp; i leave you tonight with this assignment:&nbsp; give me my sermon for sunday, and if not that exactly at least give me your insight on how best to lead, point, direct, cajole, people towards Christ.&nbsp; and not just any people, the hardest people to lead, christians.&nbsp;   peace, s. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      as I sit down to type peals of thunder roll across the night sky, so I may have to cut this short and resume my&nbsp;thought(s) later.&nbsp; I'll type until I see lightning, and I'll pray that the flash I see isn't the one that fries my computer.   psalm 46:10 says, "be still and know that I am God".&nbsp; this is all at once one of my favorite verses in the whole bible and also the scourge of my impatient soul.&nbsp; mind you I don't generally have a problem knowing that He is God, although there are times I forget that I'm totally dependent on Him, et al, but generally speaking I do pretty well to remember that He is God, and, well, I ain't.&nbsp; but "be still"?&nbsp; are you kidding me?&nbsp; that one's not so easy.&nbsp; what's worse, I feel like the call to be still is now ringing throughout every part of my life.&nbsp; at every turn I find that there may be things I would like to do but there's actually nothing for me to do but be still.&nbsp; and to be perfectly frank, that stinks.&nbsp;   this may not be true for everyone, and it may not be true for you as you read this, but I think I feel safer when I'm doing something.&nbsp; I feel like I'm proving my worth to God and to this world if I can just stay busy.&nbsp; being forced to stop and just stand still absolutely kills me because it forces me to take an honest appraisal of 1)what really matters to me and 2)why I think I matter to God.&nbsp; it's easy to say that God needs me on His side because of all the things I do; it is not so easy to face the reality that His eternal and indefatigable love for me doesn't spike when I do things nor does it ebb when I don't do things.&nbsp; being still and considering Him to be God makes me remember that He is not a god, He is the God, my God, and He loves me.&nbsp; not when I pray, nor when I preach a really good sermon.&nbsp; He loves me when I breathe and when I whine and when I lose my temper with my kids or my wife or myself.&nbsp; To think that God loves me if or when is to serve a god that doesn't exist, and sometimes I have to be "stilled" by life to remember that.&nbsp; sitting around the house, feeling as if there's nothing to do, no one to call, no work to be done, it has forced me to reexamine the grounds on which I approach God and also the basis of His love for me.   (there's the lightning.&nbsp; good night and sleep well-s.)   
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We had our bible study at church last night, and as we were discussing Christ's letter to the church at sardis in the book of revelation (chapter 3), the conversation came to the topic of honesty.&nbsp; I was reminded how scary a word honesty is for so many Christians.&nbsp; I suppose Billy Joel is right, and maybe because it can be a  lonely  word it is also a  frightening  one, but it seems to me that honesty should be the bedrock for any Christian, indeed for anyone who desires genuine relationships with either God or others or both.&nbsp; but&nbsp;such is not the case&nbsp;for many.&nbsp; and if I were being&nbsp; honest,&nbsp; &nbsp;it's not always the case with me.&nbsp; but why not?&nbsp; what is it about the truth that so frightens us?   drawing from my own experience, I know that sometimes hiding behind a mask of pretense can seem safer, easier, than confronting the reality of who I am or what I feel or what I know to be true.&nbsp; but it only  seems  that way: in the end the pretense always falls, fails, leaving me weaker and more afraid than before.&nbsp; if I put my hope in the image I can project, where does that leave me when the image cracks and crumbles at my feet?&nbsp; the curtain is pulled back and I am the one pulling the ropes and levers, attempting to control the wizard.&nbsp; the one difference is that I know the secret, I just pretend that I don't for the sake of the story.&nbsp; even writing about it is wearisome!, how much more trying to live that way.   one point that occurred to me last night, which I shared with the group, is that it is heart-breaking to realize that many Christians play this game because they are afraid of each other.&nbsp; they are afraid of critical words, condemning looks, soul crushing gossip.&nbsp; I ask my self, what in the world&nbsp;is wrong with us?&nbsp; the words James wrote in his letter are true today, that we devour each other; our passions control us instead of the Spirit of God and His love.&nbsp; I am not so naive or wide-eyed to think that this problem is new or unique to us, and furthermore I know that we must have the help of God to love 1)as He has loved us and 2)as we should love each other.&nbsp; I know all that.&nbsp; but what kills me is that we deny even the need for more love, true love.   the pretense extends to our very assessment of ourselves.&nbsp; we fear each other, we talk about each other, yet when pressed on the issue we are quick to declare that our churches are loving and kind and lights on hills.&nbsp; the truth is, we're called to be lights but more often than not we bear more resemblance to the world of shadow than to the Kingdom of Light.&nbsp; can we change this on our own?&nbsp; of course not.&nbsp; can we at least start the process by admitting our faults and falling at the feet of the grace of God?&nbsp; yes.&nbsp; so what's the problem?&nbsp; well, as g.k. chesterton said when asked what was wrong with the world in his day, I am.&nbsp; I am the problem insomuch as I am the only person I can control.&nbsp; I can rant and rave, and as a pastor I have a responsibility to teach and preach, and on occasion rant and rave, but at the end of the day the most I can do is take my own advice, admit with honesty where and who I am and give control to God to change me into His image.    honesty .&nbsp; a lonely, scary word.&nbsp; but one fraught with the promise that if we will admit our illness we will find ourselves under the care of the Great Physician.&nbsp; to borrow from Luther, we are at once sick and being made well.&nbsp; the most dangerous thing is to stop realizing we need His care.    O God, give me the strength of Your Spirit to be myself before you, not to pretend to be what I think I should be or what I wish I were.&nbsp; you want me, as I am, that you might make me what I was meant to be.      
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      People.&nbsp; it's all about people.&nbsp; in&nbsp; a wonderful paradox, God first reminds&nbsp;me that it's entirely about me and Him, and then He says, but&nbsp;go and journey with other people:&nbsp; live in the same house as a few others (for me that would be my wife and children), meet together on a regular basis with a group of folks who are spiritually like-minded (again, for me this is my church), and on a broader scale don't be afraid to surround yourself with people in your everyday life, all kinds of them.&nbsp; when I think about what it is God is doing in my life, I realize&nbsp;that while His work  in  me is sacredly personal and unique, the  result(s)  of this same work is meant to have an impact on the lives of at least a few of the people around me&nbsp;(my family for sure) and possibly many more (my church, neighborhood and beyond; see Acts 1:8).   it's funny that I would be alone in this room as I write this, but perhaps it is the juxtaposition of solitude and community that God uses to work in us to His perfect will.&nbsp; bonhoeffer said to beware of any man that could not be alone- he would be no good to the community.&nbsp; sitting here in front of the computer screen, the hum of industry (that would be a tolkkien-esque reference to my computer tower and the buzz it produces) my only company, I am forced to consider my worth to my community.&nbsp; who I am when alone says much about who I am and will be when I am again with others.   which brings me back to my original thought: it's all about people.&nbsp; or perhaps it would be better said that it is all about relationships.&nbsp; my relationship with God, stripped to its core, is seen best when I am alone, or at least being alone offers me a context in which I might best examine myself and my walk with Him.&nbsp; and yet the fruits of my relationship with Him are best seen when I am in community, first in my home, then in church and then in the broader setting of the world and its inhabitants around me.&nbsp; I say I love God but I can't stand the sight of a homeless man asking for money?&nbsp; there's something wrong with that equation.&nbsp; perhaps I should retreat into a moment of solitude with my God and address this communal error.&nbsp; and then back to the world I go, praying that by His grace I might share some of Him with the beggar,the checkout lady, my wife, and on and on.   does this make any sense?&nbsp; I fear not.&nbsp; in short, I was made, created to be in relationship with my Creator.&nbsp; from this point of origin I am called to engage with my fellow man, loving him or her as God has first loved me.&nbsp; yet it is only as I re-visit the font of His love and grace and mercy that I can hope to share these with others.&nbsp;   it's all about relationships.&nbsp; it's all about people.&nbsp; it's all about love:   "greater love hath no man than he lay down his life for his friends." -Jesus, the Bible, the Gospel according to St John, chapter 15, verse 13.   peace, s.    
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Kathleen Norris, a poet and author, once wrote that her reply to the question "are you a Christian?", was most often, "I try".&nbsp; I know that many evangelicals would disagree with this statement on more than a few theological grounds, but I have to say that I know where she's coming from.&nbsp; as this day draws to an end, I go to bed secure in the knowledge that I am God's and that God is mine, but even still if someone asked me if I were a Christian, I'm not sure I could do much better than a feeble, "I try".   which I suppose brings us to a question: is Christianity more about doing or being?&nbsp; well, what do you think?&nbsp;   I think that in some ways it has to be both- perhaps the more important issue is one of "relational chronology", i.e., does the doing bring about the being or vice versa?&nbsp; I would have to argue (and would hope to God that I'm right) that my doing happens because of my being.&nbsp; that is, I'm not a Christian because of the things I do (however pitifully and haphazardly), but rather I do certain things (don't forget pitifully and haphazardly) because of the fact that I'm a Christian.&nbsp; so then, if semantics matter, and I suppose they might, I don't have to try to be a Christian, but I may in fact try, indeed struggle, to do Christian things.&nbsp;   in church speak, this is an issue of grace vs. works.&nbsp; in the language of the rest of the world, the crux of the issue is earning God's love or receiving it.&nbsp; orthodox Christianity teaches us that God's love is offered to us on the basis of Christ's sacrificial and atoning death.&nbsp; as the words to the classic hymn say, "I owed a debt I could not pay and He paid a debt He did not owe" (or is the song written the other way around?&nbsp; either way you get the point).   it is late and it would appear that I have begun to ramble- forgive me.&nbsp; let me see if I can't rein in my thoughts and draw this to a close.   I fell short today.&nbsp; I'm not proud of it but it's true.&nbsp; I didn't do enough of the things that a Christian should this 20th of July, 2004.&nbsp; I should aspire to do more, to do better, tomorrow.&nbsp; and with God's help (that, my friends, is crucial) , I will.&nbsp; but I don't sign off this evening secure in God because of how many points I've earned with Him today, rather I rest easy because, well, Jesus paid a debt he didn't owe and I couldn't pay.   peace,  s.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      it's 11:53am on tuesday morning, and the thought runs through my mind, "what can i do?".&nbsp; as you may or may not have seen from my profile i pastor a church in illinois, and as the introduction on the home page states, it is a small church, but one that has already taught me much about myself and my faith.&nbsp; owing to its size there are frequent interludes of time wherein i am free to study, pray, play freecell, or just think.&nbsp; this last option is without a doubt the most dangerous, for it is in my runaway thoughts that i often times come closest to who i am and what it is with which i most often wrestle.&nbsp; (yowsers, that's all a bit much, isn't it?&nbsp; and slightly self important as well, no?)&nbsp; to return to some coherent train of thought, as i sat in front of my computer it dawned on me that i could at least use this tool of technology to help someone, even if that someone was me.&nbsp;  &nbsp;  this begged another question: what good could i possible do anyone whilst sitting in front of my computer?&nbsp; "well", says i, "it would be great if i could establish a website of some sort that allowed people, pastors especially, but really anyone in general, a place to let off some steam , a  safe place , if you will, wherein folks could feel free to be honest and genuine and real, with regard to their own personal spiritual journeys, and perhaps also gain insight from other beggars who've found bread."&nbsp; okay, i didn't say all that at first, but that's a fairly concise (loquacious?) background of this blog, et al.  &nbsp;  so there you have it.&nbsp; if your surfing has brought you here, then welcome.&nbsp; if you're a pastor and i've invited you here, it's simply because i know sometimes you feel like an island, even though you're not.&nbsp; if you have simply happened upon this grain of sand on the coast of the information superhighway, then welcome to you and please feel at home.  &nbsp;  peace,  s.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    this is me, in all my, er, glory.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      there hasn't been much to say of late.  check that- there's been plenty to say but i haven't felt like saying it.  i suppose we all go through times when silence seems to be the only appropriate response to life.  for me, this is one of those times.  but, really, i'd love to hear from you.  unless, of course, you're going through a time of silence as well, in which case, well, be quiet.  peace, s. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i was in the mall this afternoon when i heard a voice behind me. for some reason i made the foolish assumption that i might turn around and find two individuals engaged in conversation. silly me. instead what i saw was one person talking on the phone to another. and as i continued on i spotted another cell phone conversation to be in progress. why are we always on the phone? it seems that we've become unable to go more than 30 yards or 5 minutes without making a call or sending a text message. we spend the majority of our "down" time talking to people via electronic connections.  and yet as a society we seem to be more disengaged than ever before. the more we are promised the power of communication, the possibility of contact no matter our location, the more we have to supposedly draw us together, the farther apart we feel. whence the paradox? i wonder if it's because we 've forgotten how to be by ourselves.  dietrich bonhoeffer said that a man who couldn't be alone would be dangerous to a community (in his context he had in mind a community of saints, i.e. a church). his idea was that if we don't know how to handle the moments when it's just us and God, how do we think we'll be able to handle moments when it's us and other people? i think he was onto something.  those who can't be alone can in some way never be with other people because the time they spend together is not actually spent sharing their lives or telling their stories. that is, there's no real life enrichment because the company is just a guard against being alone. if the people with whom we surround ourselves are there simply to assuage a fear then we are not actually engaged in true  relationship . keeping people (or things for that matter) around for the sole purpose of avoiding solitude diminishes the value we assign to those same people: "i don't really care who you are or what's going on in your life, i just wanted you to be here so i wouldn't have to be alone".  only after conquering our fear of solitude, and in turn recognizing the joy of "aloneness", are we able to fully experience the people with whom we are joined together in community, be it in a church or at work or even in your home.  so go spend some time by yourself. and then go contribute to your community. repeat as needed.  peace, steven. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       i was just re-reading my last post, from wednesday, and it was really good. hey, if you can't love yourself, who can?     i apologize for the break- we've been making some adjustments around the house: my wife just began a job outside of the home, and i've taken the last part of this week to acclimate myself to the resulting changes. In addition we have a house guest for part of the weekend.  apology number two: this post will again be more questions than answers. although, thinking about it, i'm not sure we should expect to get too many answers from other people. but then, is that too cavalier? as they say, there are no lone rangers in the body of Christ.  here is the $64,000 question: how do we get more faith? as i type that a scripture comes to mind. i'll see if it occurs to any of you as well. even if it does though, how would you then apply it to everyday life? ultimately that's what i'm after: in the real world, amid the dust and dirt and grit that is our lives, how do we "grow our faith"? (sending money to a TV evangelist won't suffice here, by the way)  i've heard some say that moments of crisis cause our faith to grow. but is that only when the crises have a "good ending", or does faith grow even in the midst of grief and disappointment? are failures considered to be crises, and if they are then would we go so far as to say that faith can grow even in the soil of our own failure? (i have to say here that one could make a strong argument- at least i think one could - that the very hope of our faith is built upon a failure of divine proportions)  can we ask for more faith and then, well, receive it,  by faith?  but then faith can't be measured like sugar or oil. the proof of our faith is in the works, or so james might have us believe. so then does faith grow when we endeavor to do things beyond ourselves and our natural ability? as the title of a book says,  you can't walk on water until you get out of the boat .  faith is not a peripheral issue. ultimately, it is central to our walk, to our communion with Christ, to our being light in this world. we are described as being "people of faith". we make "professions of faith". the reformation was built upon  sola  fide.  it is at least something to which we should give some thought. hopefully we will.  peace, s. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      does it ever seem like some sins bother you more than others? I don't mean to go so far as to imply condoning any sin, but I've noticed in my own life that there are  some sins I commit about which I'm very embarrassed, sorrowful, et al; there are other sins I commit that don't cause me as much turmoil. I don't think that's the way it should be.  for instance, my sins of  omission , things I ought to do but leave undone, as a group don't tend to cause me as much sorrow and shame as some of my sins of  commission,  things I do that I shouldn't. First off, am I the only one in this particular boat, or is it possible that other Christians, if they were being honest, would admit this is true for them? I may never know. But secondly, why is this so and what can I do about it?  firstly, I think pride plays an important role in all of this (go figure). That is, we (by "we" I mean "I", since I can't at present tell if this phenomenon is unique to me) are more embarrassed by some sins because we feel ourselves to be above them in some way. If for the most part I am not a gossip, and all of a sudden find myself drawn into a deliciously gossip-laden conversation about someone in the community, I may afterward feel absolutely terribly about what I've done, because, after all, "I'm really not a gossip." of course we know from the Bible that the fastest way to find oneself caught in some transgression is to boast about one's ability to resist it (that whole pride goeth before the fall thing comes to mind). to extend this idea, it may also really bother us to commit some act (or abstain from one) that we thought we had put aside entirely, or defeated, so to speak.  I suppose it would be akin to thinking you had finally kicked a bad habit only to find yourself giving into the impulse, almost entirely out of the blue.  granted, my first observation may be a bit tenuous, but I am fairly confident that I am onto something with this second one: we (by "we", I now actually mean "we") have for some reason felt the need to classify sins, either according to our own societal appraisal of their heinousness or perhaps based with a slanted view to protecting our own proclivities (like when fat preachers tell smokers they're going to hell: "nevermind my lack of self-control around fried chicken, smoker man, you need to throw those cigarettes away and make things right!).  in the church today there may be an agreement that all sins are bad, but all too often there is an unspoken rule which makes some sins  badder  than others, whereby allowing those Christians who avoid these second level sins to feel as if they've accomplished something by "sinning small". To put it real erudite-like, that's just silly. God's view on sin is simple and straight to the point: sin-  all sin - equals death. There are no big sins and small sins. Jesus drove this point home by taking adultery out of the bedroom only and into the minds of men. He did the same thing with murder: I don't need a knife or a gun or any physical act to be guilty. Sin is sin is sin. We should sorrow over all of them, public or private, individual or aggregate.  ultimately, confronting the horror of all of our sins brings us to the place where we more fully understand the magnitude of God's grace, made known through Jesus Christ. If some sins aren't so bad, then by extension you may arrive at the place where you don't  really  need all of God's grace, just enough to cover the  badder  sins. This is, of course, a lie. I stand in need of all of God's grace all of the time. On my own, I am unrighteous in every way: word, thought, deed, and then some. Yet in Christ I find myself clothed in perfection, forgiven of all iniquity, made to stand and not fall, to live and not die.  we will rejoice in our redemption all the more when we summon the courage to experience sorrow over all of our sins. It is only those who are most fully aware of their illness who can appreciate the work of the physician on their behalf.  peace, steven. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just a quick note before the end of the day-  we've started a "biblical knowledge" class at our church, and tonight was the second night (every Monday). I originally had the idea of a discussion group designed to help people learn why they (we) believe what they do. Often times in my church when you ask someone why they believe this particular way or some specific doctrine, their reply will be "because that's what I was always taught". Now don't get me wrong, I believe that God has given teachers in the church (Ephesians 4?), and certainly we need Christian ed, etc., but if the only things we know are the things other people tell us then we know too little, and what we know may even be wrong.  and so it has to be that we return (or perhaps go for the first time) to scripture. And more than anything else, I think it's important for us to go to the Bible to, as rich mullins put it, find God. More than attempting to mine nuggets of truth for sermons, or scriptures to use as artillery against other Christians (guilty), we should go to the Word to learn about the One who is the Word. In the pages of Holy Scripture, from Genesis to revelation, we see Jesus. And, though this may sound fundamentally simplistic, Jesus is the one we should be looking at.  scripture isn't always easy, and I don't expect that I will ever "master" the Bible. To be honest, I don't want to. I would much rather the bible master me. What I do want is to take paul's advice and work out my own salvation; I want to have more of a defense for what I believe than the words of someone else. I want to know what I believe and why. I'll always remember the way josh mcdowell put it once: "the Bible isn't true because I believe it, I believe it because it's true".  why do you believe what you do? Just wondering-  peace, s. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      monday- and so begins another week.  by and large we had a good weekend, and in particular a pretty good sunday (at least from our vantage point).  herein a summary:  sunday morning i finished up my discussion on letting go.  i don't think this means that for me the process is over- i wish!- but i do think that as far as the church folks go i have made my point as best i can and now it's time to move on.  even as i talk about releasing our grip on all of the things we clutch so tightly, i can see in some of their faces a renewed decision to not let go at all.  i know that i can't change people, that even God can't change people who won't let Him, but it still befuddles me that we would rather hold on to our things, our stuff, when He offers us perfect and unadulterated grace.  i likened all of this to a man dangling from a trapeeze, unaware that there was a safety net just below him.  as far as he's concerned, the bar and the wires and his grip are all that he has to keep him safe.  you see, he thinks it's  him, his strength,  that he needs, when in reality what he needs to do most is to  let go.   and i shared with the church, that's me.  i so often think that i'm am the one keeping me afloat when really it's God, and i will only understand that fact in all of its wonderful fullness when i let go of the bar.  maybe it's a bad analogy.  maybe i'm the only one who has to go through this (i seriously doubt it).  maybe christians are some of the most prideful, stuck-in-their-ways, people on earth (i really think i'm onto something here!).  whatever the reason, i believe it is incumbent upon us to really and truly let go, to find that God's grip on us is stronger and surer than our grip on anything else could ever be.  if we start from grace, and if we establish the true nature of our salvation in Christ, i think some of this would be easier to deal with.  but i'll save that for another day, except to say this, that if we didn't do anything to earn our salvation, why are we sometimes so quick to think that there's anything we can do to  keep  our salvation?   if it was all about Jesus and what He did on our behalf at the beginning, when and why do we shift to the idea that maintaining our salvation is dependent upon what we do?  food for thought.  peace, s. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>