<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Who were the bride & the bridegroom? Romeo & Juliet  When did he propose? Twelfth Night.  What was her reply? As U Like it.  Who were the chief guests? Anthony & Cleopatra.  From whom was the ring obtained? The Merchnt of Menice.  Who were the grooms friends? Two gentleman of Verona.  Who prepared the wedding feast? The merry wives of Windsor.  Where did they live after marriage? Hamlet.  What was their honeymoon like? A Midsummers Night's Dream.  What was their married life like? The Tempest.  What was the groonms occupation? Taming of the Shrew.              
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The BEST batch tht one cud ever see Was our batch of 2003.  V r really intelligent, naughty & smart Once U meet us we'll steal ur hearts.  Lets begin wid the bookworms of the lot Some brains Tejas & Bakshi have got(actually many brains)  Ashwith & Anuj follow near U'll see them in IIT in the coming years  Sharad can U into laughing spells Arjun is as high as church bells  Pooja & Madhulika----the inseparable For doing the craziest things they r quite capable  Ali & Abhinav r soul mates When it comes to gals, they have different tastes  Pawan is the happiest of all Has lots of potential, untrapped & uncalled  Ishita Jain is all about smiles Whose glow can feed ur miles She'll brighten ur day If she ever comes ur way(well thelines r certainly by me, but the name has been suggested by......)  RT , a gem of a grl A frnd like hers is hard to find, just like a prefect pearl(again i m the writer......n the name is given by me &........)  Anurag is a man of few words He is out of the bunch of nerds(IS HE???????)  Neil & Andy r like two feathers of the same bird Proud of being "PSYCHOS", they quarrel wid ppl on simple matters(hey guys don mind!!)  Reshul is closest to a grouch Shrikant behaves like a slouch  Barath is a basketball freak(god knos weather he can play or not)  When Preeti speaks her voice creaks  Rohan is always on the lookout for birds Saket, Rohit & Sreenath have a world of their own  Rahul Panse always wears a smile Ravinder thinks hez full of style Pratik is the bhai of mumbai while Yash is very reserve & shy  Ameya & Adhiraj have loads of fun "Dost ho tho aisi" which can be shaken by none  Amanpreet clearly resembles a teddy bear Whlie Aashray bunks without any fear(gutsy guy)  Savyasachi is a rare sight in class Crushes for him is a usuall time pass  Saloni is certainly charming personified While Siddharth is jocial,crazy but bright(hopefully i m not wrong)  Hey now one is lefy & tht is me What do i say about me??????? U ppl temme something about me!!!   THTS ALL I HAVE TO SAY, MY MOTTO IN LIFE TO BE HAPPY EVERYDAY!                                                                                
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hey frdnz!!...... well this not a poem, article,........... well i have jus started my blog.so if any of you wanna comment at at it, u r most welcome. moreover come up wid suggestions to make this blog a nice one. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>