<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it't coming to the end of another long day.&nbsp; I guess I decided to come on here because I found a few minutes in my day to put down my thoughts.&nbsp; I have a lot of things going on in my head.&nbsp; I haven't really taken the time to come here since I signed up.&nbsp; So there is a lot of catching up to do.&nbsp;   This weekend was an interesting one.&nbsp; Ever since my boyfriend and I broke up, I guess my life has gotten a little bit busier.&nbsp;&nbsp; I guess God has away of filling up your time so you don't become idle, which will usually get you into trouble.&nbsp; I went out with one of my good friends this weekend,&nbsp;we had a good time.&nbsp; Wow some of the people and things you can see downtown.&nbsp; I like going out just for the laughs.&nbsp;   So my boyfriend and I have broken up now for about 3 weeks.&nbsp; It's hard for me because I love him so much but I really think we need this.&nbsp; We both have hopes of being back together but I know God has a lot of work to do on me before I can truly commit myself to anyone.&nbsp; We just going into this vicious cycle of breaking up and getting back together.&nbsp; I decided I really need to stay focused this time and not get comfortable with him when I see him or talk to him because that is what I know.&nbsp; Whenever we go through these break up phases and I stick to my guns he starts talking marriage or living together.&nbsp; It drives me insane.&nbsp; When we are together he isn't happy with certain things about me.&nbsp; But when we are not together he starts talking about stuff that would mean we would be together for the long haul.&nbsp; I wish he would get it togher.&nbsp; Well this is to be continued because the title of this message was concerning a completely different subject so I will have to finish that topic at a later date. 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow this is exciting .&nbsp; This is my first time ever doing this.&nbsp; One of my girlfriends  urlLink  Legally Purple   told me about it.&nbsp; She is really creative and always knows about the stuff no one has ever heard of.&nbsp; I am at work now, doing exactly what I am not supposed to be doing.&nbsp; Not working.&nbsp;   &nbsp; I guess as you can tell by my title that I am a Wedding Planner (I prefer the name Professional Bridal Consultant but ever since that movie with J Lo, Wedding Planner just sounds catchier).&nbsp; I spend most of my days doing that but I have a job that pays my salary which I rarely do.&nbsp; That is so sad.&nbsp; I always get my work done but I love doing my passion and until I can get that company on it's feet I will be working for THE MAN.&nbsp;  &nbsp; The name of my company is  urlLink  WEDDING FOR 2  .&nbsp; It was started by a fellow church member of mine and soon after I came on board.&nbsp; We have been trying to raise this baby ever since.&nbsp; It is a lot of hard work starting your own company.&nbsp; I love it though.&nbsp; I don't think I would want to do anything else.&nbsp;  &nbsp; Well, I really should be getting back to work.&nbsp; Thanks for telling me about this Netta. 
    
</post>


</Blog>