<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What do Uday and Qusay have in common with  urlLink this woman  of Miami Beach, FL?  Well, they both have the same dying wish.  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Some bright bulb (Reuven Pedatzur) at Haaretz is  urlLink complaining  that Israel's successful test of the Arrow Anti-Missile Missile will cause an arms race in the middle east, and paradoxically make things less stable.  I think the only thing being made less stable by the Arrow is Mr. Pedatzur's brain.  It was the  threat  of an ABM system that caused the Soviet Union to spend itself into annihilation.  And that was a  threat  against the  Soviet Empire .  This is not a threat.  This is a  reality  against a bunch of borderline Third World thugs.  The real thing causing instability in the Middle East is a network of anti-Israeli countries who seek the end of Israel as a sovereign nation, a people, and a religion.  Get that and learn it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Whenever the Democrat Dufus looks like a dufus, the Dem's  urlLink complain  that its a Republican conspiracy to make the dufus look like a dufus.  You don't need a conspiracy to make this dufus look like a dufus.  The reason is very simple.  HE'S A DUFUS!  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I just got done reading the  urlLink interchange  between Bill O'Reilly and Michael Moore at the DNC convention.  Moore just keeps ranting about sending the "children" in to fight for a "lie."  First, there were/are WMD's in Iraq!  We got hit with them!  Doesn't anyone remember the Sarin in the IED they found on the roadside?  What's wrong with these people?  Selective memory, or selective understanding?  Second, we don't send children into war!  These are grown men and women.  And, we don't have a draft.  They were all volunteers.  If he wants to keep saying silly things like this, I'm going to have to tell his mother.  She'll slap him good!  Silly little boy.  Third, O'Reilly and Moore both said that Bush said this was for an "imminent threat."  Except that he never said that.  In fact, he said that we needed to do this BEFORE the threat became imminent.    Fourth, Moore said that Bush kept saying there was a supposed connection between Iraq and 9/11.  Bush did NOT say that.  He said there was a connection between Iraq and Al Qeada.  He never said they colluded specifically on 9/11.  So, on every point Moore is the one who's lying.  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I was checking into this "separation" thing regarding the help with the flood.  The lady who is coordinating the whole effort at the township is in my church.  I went up to her and asked "Why hasn't the church been sending anyone to help?"  The look on her face told me she'd obviously heard the "rumors" and was sick of them.  So, that got me to thinking.  The only thing worse than if this is true, is that this is false.  I mean, this is just a distraction from doing the work that really needs to be done.  So, I gave her my number and said I'd like to help.  Unfortunately, I have to coach 3 more weeks of Flag Football.  This is annoying (but that's another story).  I'll try to help a little bit here and there in the meantime. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So some of you may have heard of our recent floods in Burlington County, NJ.  I have friend who lost almost everything he owns.  Well, the church I attend (Fellowship Alliance Chapel, Medford, NJ) has been helping out with people and material, and coordination.  It's been amazing.  But, my town (Lumberton) got hit as bad, if not worse, than Medford.  Our church hasn't sent any crews to my town.  I've been wondering why.  On a work crew assignment today someone told me that the genius mayor (or someone?) in Lumberton turned down the offer of help from the church.  Yes, that's right!  THEY TURNED IT DOWN!!!  Why?  Well, get this!  They were told its because they're concerned about "Separation of Church and State."  I don't know who said this, or even if its accurate.  But I promise you this: I will get to the bottom of this and if its true, I will have a new mission in my life.  My mission will be to completely lay waste to the political career of whoever has done this!  Mayor?  No.  Councilman?  No.  Dog catcher?  No.  The guy at the fire department who polishes the chrome on the pumper truck?  No.  (You can MAYBE hold his towels for him though ... MAYBE.)   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Eddie George  is headed to Dallas.  He came so close to being loved by a whole city.  Heck, he's FROM Philly!  How could he do this?  Its just tragic.  Oh, well.  Break his legs!  
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yes, I'm an Eagles fan.  And yes, I'm also a Dittohead (that means I'm a Rush Limbaugh fan for those of you from Rio Linda).  How, you may ask, do I reconcile these two seemingly contradictory things?  Well, its not that hard really.  Lets look at the McNabb-Limbaugh controversy.  Rush said: 1- the media are a bunch of dopes, and  2- that McNabb is overrated.  Number 1?  No problem.  Anyone care to argue? ... thought not.  Number 2?  I can understand someone coming to that conclusion.  Because, quite frankly, he has not lived up to the hype.  But why?  There are two reasonable conclusions.  Either he was over-hyped, or he is under-achieving.  Rush believes the former, while I believe the latter.  Anyway, its all for nought at the moment.  Training camp starts next week.  Terrell Owens is in town.  Jevon Kearse is here. (There are rumors that Eddie George wants to come to Philly... don't know.)  Perhaps we will see who is right this season.  Because with all of these acquisitions, there are no more excuses for McNabb.  Either he performs or I'm going to start agreeing with Rush.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       DRUDGE is currently (as of this writing) flashing a quote from John Edwards, saying NATO leaders told him they (essentially) want Bush to lose.  Which NATO leaders?  Cut-and-run-Spain?  Oil-For-Palaces-Germany and Russia?  Oh, wait!  I know!  It's the Dutch!  Evil Dutch bastards!   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, now the detailed press reports are starting to come out. ( urlLink Washington Post , and  urlLink News Leader )  I've been in classified meetings, and have taken notes, and have had those checked before I left.  Believe me, folks, you don't do what he says he did just by accident.  It HAD to be intentional.  That's why there's a procedure.  You follow the procedure to minimize and/or eliminate any potential for accidents like that.    And this was not just a single document or two.  This is (from press reports) over 50 pages of notes that left without approval.  Its amazing how many people have to fall on the sword for the Clinton's.  Web Hubble, Susan McDougle, and now Sandy Burglar.  I like the way FrankJ put it, "Why can't this guy just steal furniture like the rest of the Clinton people?"  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've been thinking about blogging for a while.  Everytime I think of something I'd like to say, I think "Wow, if I had a blog...."  Well, here's one of those things.    Media Bias  Yeah, I know.  It's been dealt with.  But I just want to tell the story of how I understood media bias from a very early and highly impressionable age.  I was born in South Africa (Mom was American, Dad is an Afrikaaner).  I grew up in NJ.  We used to get these newspapers from South Africa occassionally so my Dad could keep up on the goings on back "home."  When I was about 8 or 10 we got one where the front page had Nelson & Winnie Mandela marching down the street of some city in SA (probably Cape Town... don't really remember where) with banners and a crowd behind him.  Then within a couple of days I saw the exact same picture on the front page of our local rag the Courier Post.  There was one major difference.  You see the banners and flags in the crowd behind him were Communist flags, complete with hammer and sickle.  Only in the Courier Post is was cropped so you couldn't see them.  You only saw Nelson and Winnie, smiling to their adoring fans.  I knew from that moment that the mainstream press was not to be trusted with giving us the truth.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So Doonesbury is  urlLink getting dropped .  I don't care.  I never liked it to begin with.  Even in satire he's not funny (Trudeau that is).  Cartoons are supposed to be funny.  Enough with the left-wing propaganda, MAKE ME LAUGH!  What I love is the response to a company that decides not to do business with a big Lib like Trudeau gets from other big Lib's.  They shout censorship, like a company ending a contract is keeping Trudeau from saying his opinion.  HEY ALL YOU LIBS!  He's NOT going to JAIL, he's getting FIRED!  There's a distinct difference!  I like the way Rush put it, "You don't have a Constitutional Right to be heard."   
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Okay, lets get the obvious out of the way first.  Why Undercover Hippie?  Well, I wanted a convertible.  I wanted a CHEAP convertible.  I wanted a NEW convertible.  I went to the 2003 Philadelphia International Auto Show and I sat in a new 2003 VW Beetle Convertible.  I liked it.  It was cheap.  I bought it.  Check  urlLink  here  to see how it went at first.  Anyway, after my initial problems, I started getting grief from some friends about the "masculinity" of my choice.  Well, I kind of expected that.  But, I'm married with 4 kids.  What do I care?  I just keep the flower vase thingy in the dashboard filled with a cigar.  Its not much, but it helps.  Then the cherry topping was a friend who said, "Oh, it's not gay... but it IS liberal!"  Well, I also failed to mention that I work in Princeton, NJ.  That's East Coast Hippie Central!  Oh they just all LOVE my new Beetle.  So then I got an idea!  I'm really an undercover hippie!  They think I'm one of them!  ...  and then I had to go and ruin it all by putting on a  urlLink Viva Bush  bumper sticker.  But you should see the looks of complete confusion I get while driving through East Coast Hippie Central! 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Thanks to FrankJ of  urlLink IMAO  for inspiring me to start this blog.  Heck, I didn't even know what a blog was until I stumbled upon IMAO.  Anyway, I'm not  urlLink funny  like FrankJ, not as  urlLink smart  as FrankJ, not as  urlLink boyishly handsome  as FrankJ, not as skilled a  urlLink Ronin  as FrankJ, and I don't have  urlLink SarahK  for a  urlLink T-Shirt Babe .  But I do have lots of opinions.  So, if this site generates any traffic, then there you are.  If not, then I'll just be talking to myself.  At least I'll be more disciplined in my soliloquy's.    
    
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Step right up, folks!  Inside you will see the most amazing things.    "What is it?" you ask.      It's a White African-American, Conservative, Christian, Republican, Bigot, Homophobe, Sexist, Dittohead, DrudgeReport-reading, IMAO-posting, CNN-ignoring, non-Keyboard-playing, Democrat-mocking, non-Mountainbiking, non-emasculated-Beetle-driving, husband of one, father of four, totally right-wing voter (who's also been known to have the most amazing finger-toes!).       
    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I remember during one of the Clinton scandals (I don't remember which one... doesn't matter ... take your pick) that Dick Morris was on some talking heads show saying, "If there are two things out there that can hurt you, then admit to the lesser one and that will give you cover for the more serious one."  That's what this is about.  Nobody resigns from office in 2004 because they're "outed."  Has anybody ever heard of Barney Frank?  No sir.  This is McGreevey admitting to the lesser scandal.  Mark my words.  This is not over, and its not about how he spends his recreational hours. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink This play  is just a typical liberal stunt.    How interesting that these people who claim the Republicans are hate-filled and murderous, are putting on such a display. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It looks like Missouri has  urlLink joined the list  of states to outlaw Gay Marriage.  The most compelling argument the proponents of gay marriage have is to play the "bigot" card.  Its discriminatory to exclude same-sex couples from matrimony.  Well, I'd like to ask a simple question to those people.  Is there ANY kind of marriage you would not allow?  Which ones?  For example, in your all-inclusion, non-bigoted world of same-sex marriage, would I be allowed to divorce my wife and marry ... say ... my 3-yr-old daughter?  How about my neighbor's dog?  What about if I do both of those and STAY married to my wife?  If the answer is, "Of course we wouldn't approve of that?"  then you can't say I'm being discriminatory.  You are too.  We just disagree on where we draw the line.  If the answer is, "All of those things should be up to the individual."  then you've essentially defined marriage to be whatever the anybody wants it to be.  If it can mean anything, then in effect, it means nothing.  There's nothing special about my commitment to my wife if it can be defined any way you want, at any time, under any circumstance.  Is defining marriage as being between a man and a woman discriminatory?  You bet!  When you add definition to anything (not just marriage) you are effectively excluding everything that does not fall under that definition.  But, that's not a bad thing.    
    
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       If Bush has intelligence that attacks on businesses are being planned and doesn't do anything about it, then they'll complain because he's not doing enough.  Could you imagine if an attack occurred and THEN we found out that they had all this intel and it was 3 or 4 years old?  Kerry would explode on the spot. (Hey, maybe that's not such a bad idea.)  If Bush acts on the intelligence, then he's doing too much.  Or, its political.  Or, he stole the election.  Or, Kerry served in Vietnam.   
    
    
</post>


</Blog>