<Blog>


<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Isso dizia numa carta escrita em 1991 a uma amiga. Eu tinha 14 anos, da para acreditar! Entao, mudei de vida ou nao? Sim, e muito! 1991 - 14 anos, estudante, residindo em Natal/RN/Brasil. 2004 - 27 anos, secretaria numa firma de advocacia, residindo em New York a 3 anos, longe da familia, longe dos antigos amigos, mas muitos amigos novos, um novo lar. Nesses 13 anos muita coisa mudou alem do meu endereco. Na cartinha de amigas q moravam em cidades diferentes eu dizia que queria 'mudar, mudar, mudar'. Ainda tenho esse mesmo desejo de mudar, essa sede de explorar lugares ainda desconhecidos por mim, ver as coisas de minha propria otica. 'Paris e linda!!!', 'London e fria e cinzenta.' Eu quero dizer o que eu acho, nao repetir o ponto de vista de outros. Provavelmente vou constatar o mesmo. Mas quero contar sobre um dia chuvoso em Paris e sobre um ensolarado dia de verao em London quando estava la. E bom saber q nem tudo muda - e que uma pessoa que me correspondo a mais de 13 anos me fez perceber isso numa conversa hoje.
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jehovah told a certain man He had work for him to do. This certain man had a large rock in front of his house and Jehovah explained that the man was to push against the rock with all his might. This the man did, day after day.  For many years he toiled from sun rise to sun set, his shoulders set squarely against the cold, massive surface of the unmoving rock, pushing with all his might. Each night the man returned home sore, worn out and feeling that his whole day had been spent in vain. Seeing that the man was showing signs of discouragement, Satan decided to enter the picture by placing thoughts into the man's weary mind: "You have been pushing against  that rock for a long time, and it hasn't budged. Why kill yourself over this? You are never going to move it." This gave the man the impression that the task was impossible and that he was a failure, these thoughts discouraged and disheartened the man. "Why kill myself over this?" he thought. "I'll just put in my time, give the minimum effort and that will be good enough." And that is what he planned to do until he decided to make it a matter of prayer and take his troubled thoughts to Jehovah. "Jehovah, I have labored long and hard in your service, putting all my strength to do what you have asked of me. Yet, after all this time I have not even budged that rock by half a millimeter. What is wrong? Why am I failing?" Then Jehovah responded compassionately, "When I asked you to serve and you accepted, I told you that your task was to push against the rock with all your strength, which you have done. Never once did I mention to you that I expected you to move it. Your task was to push. And now you come to me, with your strength spent, thinking that you have failed. But is that really so? ...Look at yourself. Your arms are strong and muscled, your back is sinew and brown, your hands are callused from constant pressure, and your legs have become massive and hard. Through opposition you have grown much and your abilities now surpass that which you used to have... Yes, you haven't moved the rock but then all I ever asked was that you be obedient and push. It was through your works that you exercised faith in me. This you have done, and now I will move the rock for you."  At times, when we may tend to think little of ourselves and our service to Jehovah and we become disheartened and discouraged, we need to remember what Jehovah asks of us and that is just simply obedience and faith in Him.....  By all means, exercise faith that moves mountains but know that it is still Jehovah who does the moving. When everything seems to go wrong, just Push.  When your job gets you down, just Push. When people don't treat you kindly, just push. When people don't react the way you think they should, just Push.  When people reject you in the ministry just Push.   PUSH = Pray Until Something Happens.
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This illustration was given at a circuit assembly:  There was a farmer who raised sheep and had trouble with wolves stealing his sheep. He loved his sheep and didn't want to lose even one of them. One day the wolves came and the farmer quickly raised his rifle and POW! - killed every wolf he shot at. As he turned his rifle toward a shadow he saw a puppy wolf huddling beside a fence post shivering. The farmer felt sorry for him, picked him up, tucked him inside his coat and took him home.  As time passed, the farmer grew to love the puppy wolf and took him everyday to help him tend his sheep. The sheep loved the puppy wolf too and thought of him as one of one of them.  The puppy wolf learned to call the sheep by their names, just like the farmer did. It wasn't long before he grew to full size and the farmer trusted him t o care for his sheep while he rode to town to buy supplies.  Then one day the puppy wolf was running in the farmer's field and heard howling in the woods. He ran to the edge of the fence and watched as a pack of wolves approached. They seemed happy to see him although he didn't recognize them. One by one they told him of all the fun they were having, running anywhere they wanted, doing whatever they pleased...no one telling them what to do!  They invited him to come on the other side of the fence with them. The puppy wolf thought about the fence, and how he'd never been on the other side of it. The more he listened he began to wonder if he was missing out on something. It only took another minute and he dug under the fence and left with the pack. For three seasons he lived with the wolves. They had plenty to eat and did whatever they wanted. It was such fun and he was glad for the choice he made.  But winter came and everyone became hungry and restless. It was cold, so cold, where they had to sleep. The puppy wolf began to think about the farmer and how he'd never slept cold and never felt hunger. Soon he heard the leader of the pack announce it was time to steal some of the farmer's sheep, so they could survive the winter. The puppy wolf loudly exclaimed, "NO, they are my friends, don't hurt them". But the leader said, "You're one of us now, do as you're told!" They all began to run fast toward the farmer's property.  The puppy wolf reluctantly followed. Soon they arrived and began to dig under the farmer's fence. The farmer heard his sheep cry out so he grabbed his rifle and ran to shoot at the wolves. BANG! He killed one after another and soon was face to face with a wolf backed up against the fence post who cried out, "Wait, don't shoot me. I'm the puppy you raised. I'm your friend. Don't you remember me?"  But the farmer looked at the wolf and saw how matted his coat was and how he smelled like the rest of the pack. He said to the wolf, "I don't know you." He raised his rifle and shot....BANG!!! The wolf was dead!  There was silence in the auditorium, and then the brother giving the talk aid, "Brothers, when Armageddon comes and Jesus is doing his destruction work, will he recognize you"?
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Terremotos  Dizem que passado o terremoto de Lisboa (1755), o Rei perguntou ao General, o que se havia de fazer.  Ele respondeu ao Rei: "Sepultar os mortos, cuidar dos vivos e fechar os portos".  Essa resposta simples, franca e direta tem muito a nos ensinar.  Muitas vezes temos em nossa vida, "terramotos" avassaladores como o de Lisboa no século XVIII. A catástrofe é tão grande que muitas vezes perdemos a capacidade de raciocinar de forma simples, objetiva. Todos nós estamos sujeitos a "terremotos" na vida. O que fazer?  Exactamente o que disse o General: "Sepultar os mortos, cuidar dos vivos e fechar os portos".  E o que isso quer dizer para a nossa vida? Sepultar os mortos significa que não adianta ficar reclamando e chorando o passado.  É preciso "sepultar" o passado. Colocá-lo debaixo da terra.  Isso significa "esquecer" o passado. Enterrar os mortos.  Cuidar dos vivos significa que depois de enterrar o passado, em seguida temos que cuidar do presente. Cuidar do que ficou vivo. Cuidar do que sobrou. Cuidar do que realmente existe.  Fazer o que tiver que ser feito para salvar o que restou do terremoto.  Fechar os portos significa não deixar as "portas" abertas para que novos problemas possam  surgir ou "vir de fora" enquanto estamos cuidando dos vivos e salvando o que restou do terremoto de nossa vida. Significa manter o foco no "cuidar dos vivos". Significa concentrar-se na reconstrução, no novo.  É assim que a história nos ensina. Por isso a história é "a mestra da vida".   Portanto, quando vocês enfrentarem um terremoto, não se esqueça:  enterre os mortos, cuide dos vivos e feche os portos.
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You can't love too much one part of it...  O mundo nao para de girar - ha sempre a possibilidade de tentar se agarrar a algo e fingir que isto nao esta acontecendo. Mas sera que vale a pena no final? Quero dizer, nunca podemos realmente para-lo, ou retroceder. Pense que se voce acompanhar essas voltar e mover junto, que surpresa agradavel e voltar ao lugar que ha muito nao vamos ou reencontrar pessoas queridas que fazem parte da nossa vida, mesmo que nem se deem conta! Sabe aquela de sensacao de 'dejavour'? Eu amo. Viver e bom demais para virar rotina.   "Wheel"  People have the right to fly And will when it gets compromised Their hearts say "Move along"  Their minds say "Gotcha heart" Let's move it along   And airports  See it all the time With someone's last goodbye Blends in with someone's sigh Cause someone's coming home In hand a single rose   And that's the way this wheel keeps working now That's the way this wheel keeps working now And I won't be the last No I won't be the last, To love her  And you can't build a house of leaves And live like it's an evergreen It's just a season thing It's just this thing that seasons do  And that's the way this wheel keeps working now That's the way this wheel keeps working now And you won't be the first No you won't be the first  To love me  You can find me, if you ever want again I'll be around the bend  I'll be around And if you never stop when you wave goodbye You just might find if you give it time You will wave hello again  You just might wave hello again   And that's the way this wheel keeps working now That's the way this wheel keeps working now  You can't love too much, one part of it  I believe that my life's gonna see The love I give return to me 
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quando decidi comecar esse blog veio o primeiro dilema:  O NOME. Questao simples na verdade - mas como pode ver questao esta sem acento, meu teclado nao tem acento. Estou em morando em NY, daqui vou ao Brasil e entao a Londres - e de Londres? Nem eu sei ainda. Meus email addresses agora sao sempre fabiana_ny@... Mas como estou indo embora do que tornou-se 'home sweet home' achei que um nome apropriado seria Wherever e basicamente onde vou morar. 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quando estava preparando a reuniao da escola* achei algo interessante: No capitulo 11 de Numeros fala dos Israelitas se queixarem do alimento que Jeova provia e Jeova decide entao mardar cordonizes (aves) para eles de uma forma milagrosa, mas por causa de sua atitude queixosa contra Jeova alguns foram punidos com a morte. Mas no capitulo 16 de Exodus, apos ouvir os resmungos do povo, Jeova tambem os deu codornizes, mas desta vez nao os puniu. Por que? Por que nesta primeira passaggem eles ainda nao eram um povo dedicado, nao tinham dito "Tudo o que Jeová falou estamos dispostos a fazer." (Exodus 19:8) Dedicou voce sua vida a Jeova? Esta vivendo a altura desta dedicacao?  * Reunioes que as Testemunhas Jeova realizam para treinar seus membros como evangelizadores. Nesta reuniao em particular ha uma parte em que sao destacados alguns versiculos de dados capitulos. Atraves deste estudo lemos a Biblia toda como grupo.
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Na leitura da Biblia para esta semana eu destaquei o versiculo 23 do capitulo 11 do livro de Exodus, onde depois de Moises indagar de Jeova como ele alimentaria aquele numeroso povo, Jeova responde: "Será que a mão de Jeová é encurtada?" As vezes quando passamos por muitas dificuldades nos questinamos se mesmo Jeova podera nos ajudar. Mesmo Moises, 'o homem que andou com o verdadeiro Deus', demonstrou esta atitude quando pressionado. E facil sucumbir a pressao deste sistema e ceder. Mas parte b deste mesmo verso Jeova continua dizendo: 'Agora verás se vem ou não [vem] sobre ti o que eu digo.' As vezes tudo que precisamos e parar e ver Jeova agir. O que Ele diz ele faz. Ele promete nos proteger e cuidar de nos. Ele o fara. Ele nao mudou. 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hoje estava respondendo a um virtual card e decidi mandar um cartao musical a esta amiga. O cartao citava partes da cancao de Milton Nascimento, aquela 'amigo e coisa para se guardar do lado esquerdo do peito, dentro do coracao, assim se falava a cancao...' Eu nao pude acha-la, entao comecei a procurar outra. Encontrei 'Pais e filhos'. Voce deve conhecer, senao 'get out my blog, you're not cool enough' - just kidding! Esta e outras musicas do Legiao Urbana foram o lema de nossa geracao (geracao coca-cola). Hoje ao ouvir um pedacinho dela que saudade desse tempo. De ouvir a voz desse poeta tao apreciado por nos jovens. Espero que haja um lugar na memoria de Jeova para essa pessoa tao confusa e sensivel. Como muitos de nos tao insignificante um grao de areia ou uma gota d'agua mas que deixou sua marca em nos.  Pais e Filhos (Renato Russo)  Estátuas e cofres E paredes pintadas Ninguém sabe o que aconteceu Ela se jogou da janela do quinto andar Nada é fácil de entender  Dorme agora É só o vento lá fora Quero colo Vou fugir de casa Posso dormir aqui Com vocês? Estou com medo tive um pesadelo Só vou voltar depois das três  Meu filho vai ter Nome de santo Quero o nome mais bonito  (chorus) É preciso amar as pessoas Como se não houvesse amanhã Por que se você parar,pra pensar Na verdade não há  Me diz por que o céu é azul Explica a grande fúria do mundo São meus filhos que tomam conta de mim  Eu moro com a minha mãe Mas meu pai vem me visitar Eu moro na rua não tenho ninguém Eu moro em qualquer lugar Já morei em tantas casas que nem me lembro mais Eu moro com os meus pais  (chorus)  Sou uma gota d'água Sou um grão de areia Você me diz que seus pais não lhe entendem Mas você não entende seus pais Você culpa seus pais por tudo Isso é absurdo São crianças como você O que você vai ser Quando você crescer?  
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a cliché!!! But it's so true. Today I had a american breakfast (pancakes, which i love) and went out on service (preaching the good news) with the Portuguese congregation. In our group we had Brazilians, Portugueses, Cape Verdians, Americans and South Americans. Later we went to a French restaurant for lunch. And in the afternoon me, a Jamaican friend and a Colobian friend were browsing around a flee market. It was such a gray, gloomy day. A day that you don't want to do anything. But in NY you can't stay indoors on summer - you gotta be out there, even if the only thing to do is going to a flee market and chit-chat with old friends.
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everything I need to know about life, I learned from Noah's Ark...   1 - Don't miss the boat. 2 - Remember that we are all in the same boat. 3 - Plan ahead. It wasn't raining when Noah built the Ark. 4 - Stay fit. When you're 600 years old, someone may ask you to do something really big. 5 - Don't listen to critics; just get on with the job that needs to be done.  6 - Build your future on high ground. 7 - For safety's sake, travel in pairs.  8 - Speed isn't always an advantage. The snails were on board with the cheetahs.  9 - When you're stressed, float a while.  10 - Remember, the Ark was built by amateurs; the Titanic by professionals. 11 - No matter the storm, when you are with God, there's always a rainbow waiting.  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Do not go where the path may lead, Go instead where there is no path and leave a trail" - Ralph Waldo Emerson  I saw this statement somewhere, wrote down in a piece of paper and saved it. Yesterday going through some stuff I found it.  I had put aside the plans to go to London for a while - actually for two years. I kinda decided to walk through others' path. Thought about getting settled. Moved on my own, bought furniture, kept the same job for over a year, made stable friends. Sounded like a plan! Consider this: For many in the US, moving from their parents' house and making on their own is a dream. The American dream. As a matter of fact, I am Brazilian. We live in our parents house for ever, unless we get married and move to somebodyelse's house. But I did it differently. I moved to the US without knowing anyone nor speaking any English. It was hard, scary sometimes. I made it though, with Jehovah's help, and I am proud of it after all. But I want more, I wanna leave a trail. Natal(Brazil)->New York->London->Wherever. But it's just a trail, my trail. No need to be followed. Leave your own!!!
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Estava conversando esta manha com uma amiga e essa frase veio em nossa conversacao. Lembravamos de um tempo que passavamos ferias juntas. Ela viria com sua 'galera' a minha cidade ou minha irma e eu iriamos para la. Festinhas na minha casa, um bar chamado muralha (que na epoca era o 'point' e so quem era 'cool' ia la), e praia, muita praia. Na cidade dela tinha um pessoal bem legal e sempre saiamos a noite. Na verdade o que fazia coisas simples tao especiais era o pessoal reunido. Era ver quem conseguia cantar 'Faroeste Cabloco' sem tropecar. E cantar muita brega bem alto. Era ver fotos e contas historias engracadas de um verao passado. Desse pessoal poucos restaram, e os que restaram tomaram rumos diferentes. Tao diferentes que seria dificil reagrupar. Alguns nao queremos falar mais, outros nao podemos, outros e melhor nao falar sobre eles. Os lugares, alguns deles, so existem em nossa saudosa memoria. 'Tempos que nao voltam...' - eu disse. E minha amiga disse: 'Haverao outras pessoas, outras historias' E verdade. Haverao outros tempos. E a estes dirigiremos a mesma frase, 'que estes nao voltam'. Embora com saudade dos que passaram, vejo com antecipacao os por vir.
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A man found a cocoon of a butterfly.   One day a small opening appeared, he sat and watched the butterfly for several hours as it struggled to force its body through that little hole.   Then it seemed to stop making any progress. It appeared as if it had gotten as far as it could and it could go no farther.  Then the man decided to help the butterfly, so he took a pair of scissors and snipped off the remaining bit of the cocoon.   The butterfly then emerged easily. But it had a swollen body and small, shriveled wings.  The man continued to watch the butterfly because he expected that, at any moment, the wings would enlarge and expand to be able to support the body, which would contract in time.  Neither happened! In fact, the butterfly spent the rest of its life crawling around with a swollen body and shriveled wings. It was never was able to fly.  What the man in his kindness and haste did not understand was that the restricting cocoon and the struggle required for the butterfly to get through the tiny opening were Jehovah's way of forcing fluid from the body of the butterfly into its wings so that it would be ready for flight once it achieved its freedom from the cocoon.  Sometimes struggles are exactly what we need in our life. If Jehovah allowed us to go through our life without any obstacles, it would cripple us. We would not be as strong as what we could have been...and WE COULD NEVER FLY.
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When things in your life seem almost too much to handle, when 24 hours in a day are not  enough, remember the mayonnaise jar and the coffee... A professor stood before his philosophy class and had some items in front of him. When the class began, wordlessly, he picked up a very large and empty mayonnaise jar and proceeded to fill it with golf balls. He then asked the students if the jar was full. They agreed that it was. So the professor then picked up a box of pebbles and poured them into the jar.  He shook the jar lightly. The pebbles rolled into the open areas between the golf balls. He then asked the students again if the jar was full.  They agreed it was. The professor next picked up a box of sand and poured it into the jar. Of course, the sand filled up everything else.  He asked once more if the jar was full. The students responded with a unanimous "yes."  The professor then produced two cups of coffee from under the table and poured the entire contents into the jar, effectively filling the empty space between the sand. The students laughed.  "Now," said the professor, as the laughter subsided, "I want you to recognize that this jar represents your life. The golf balls are the important things --- your God, your family, your children, your health, your friends, and  your favorite passions --- things that if everything else was lost and only they remained, your life would  still be full. The pebbles are the other things that matter like your job, your house, and your car.  The sand is everything else-the small stuff. "If you put the sand into the jar first," he continued,  "there is no room for the pebbles or the golf balls. The same goes for life. If you spend all your time and energy on the small stuff, you  will never have room for the things that are important to you. Pay attention to the things that are critical to your happiness. Play with your children. Take time to get medical checkups. Take your partner out to dinner. Play another 18. There  will always be time to clean the house  and fix the disposal." Take care of the golf  balls first, the things that really matter. Set your priorities. The rest is just sand." One of the students raised her hand and inquired what the coffee represented. The professor smiled. "I'm glad you asked. It just goes to show you that no matter how full your life may seem, there's always room for a couple of cups of coffee with a friend."
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "How can you expect your life to change if you don't change?" I heard this sentence on a sitcom. It's so obvious, yet interesting. If you don't stop whining about your life and take actions things will never change, not even your complaints. So get up and move your butt. Stand up for the things you value and let go the past. You don't live the same things twice. This could be the last chance....
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quanta alegria o gritar desta palavra traz a nos brasileiros amantes do futebol. Mas gol, assim como futebol (football), vem de uma palavra inglesa mas esta primeira com muito mais significado.  Goal Definition (AIM or PURPOSE), (GAME - in many sports, a point scored when a player sends a ball or other object into a particular area of play or into a netted structure that is defended by the opposing team)  Ontem estava lendo uma revista a caminho de uma reuniao em russo, lingua da qual sei pouquissimas palavras. Entre outras materias nessa revista a que mais me chamou atencao foi uma sobre alvos. Esta fez-me pensar que preciso estabelecer alvos, alvos tangiveis, de curto e longo prazo. Todos precisamos de alvos - eles dao-nos motivacao na vida, nos impulsionam. Assim como jogadores de futebol vem trazendo a bola la de tras passando por varios obstaculos e entao encontram o atacante que atira a bola com toda sua capacidade para acertar o 'gol'. E que alegria e senso de satisfacao nao so o atacante, mas os outros jogadores, e toda uma nacao ou mesmo nacoes sentem quando a bola entra na rede!!! Nesta reuniao em russo eu vi isso. A alegria daqueles que aprendem esta dificil lingua com um alfabeto diferente e daqueles que sao motivados por seus esforcos, e quanto esforco, em aprender e agora serem ajudados por se comunicar com mais facilidade. Mas o real motivo destas pessoas em aprender tal lingua eh compartilhar com pessoas que tem o russo como primneira lingua as boas novas do reino, a mesma mensagem pregada por Cristo cerca de 2000 anos. Agora estas sao pregadas em 235 terras e ha publicacoes em 400 idiomas. Nao, nao acho que vou me dedicar a aprender russo. Mas quero aprender outra lingua. Falo ingles fluente atualmente e posso me virar bem no espanhol (sei que sorvete de morango se diz helado de fresas e nao sorviete de moriango, como diz minha mae). Mas quero aprender outra lingua e assim compartilhar com outros as Boas Novas do Reino e gastar mais tempo em fazer isso. Algumas das sugestoes nessa revista era que os alvos estabelecidos fossem plausiveis (check). Outra sugestao era escrever estes alvos para assim ficarem registrado (check). Agora e tomar acao em alcanca-los (_____).
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A friend wrote and sent me - it's very interesting and true. Hope i will keep awake.  "A time comes into your life when you finally get it when, in the midst of all your fears and insanity, you stop dead in your tracks and some where the voice inside your head cries out ENOUGH! Enough fighting and crying and blaming and struggling to hold on.   Then, like a child quieting down after a tantrum, you blink back your tears and begin to look at the world through new eyes.   This is your awakening.   You realize it is time to stop hoping and waiting for something to change, or for happiness, safety and security to magically appear over the next horizon.   You realize that in the real world there aren't always fairy tale endings, and that any guarantee of happily ever after must begin with you and in the process a sense of serenity is born of acceptance.   You awaken to the fact that you are not perfect and that not everyone will always love, appreciate or approve of who or what you are and that is OK. They are entitled to their own views and opinions.   You learn the importance of loving and championing yourself and in the process a sense of newfound confidence is born of self-approval.   You stop complaining and blaming other people for the things they did to you or didn't do for you and you learn that the only thing you can really count on is the unexpected.   You learn that people don't always say what they mean or mean what they say and that not everyone will always be there for you and that everything isn't always about you.   So, you learn to stand on your own and to take care of yourself and in the process a sense of safety and security is born of self-reliance.   You stop judging and pointing fingers and you begin to accept people as they are and to overlook their shortcomings and human frailties and in the process a sense of peace and contentment is born in the forgiveness.   You learn to open up to new worlds and different points of view.   You begin reassessing and redefining who you are and what you really stand for.   You learn the difference between wanting and needing and you begin to discard the doctrines and values you've outgrown or should never have bought into to begin with.   You learn that principles such as honesty and integrity are not the outdated ideals of a bygone era, but the mortar that holds together the foundation upon which you must build a life.   Then you learn about love. You learn to look at relationships as they really are and not as you would have them to be.   You learn that alone does not mean lonely.  You stop trying to control people, situations and outcomes.   You learn to distinguish between guilt and responsibility and the importance of setting boundaries and learning to say NO.   You learn that your body really is your temple. You begin to care for it and treat it with respect.  You learn that being tired fuels doubt, fear, and uncertainty and so you take more time to rest.  And, just as food fuels the body, laughter fuels our soul. So you take more time to laugh and play.   You learn that, a lot of times, you get in life what you believe you deserve. You learn that anything worth achieving is worth working for and that wishing for something to happen is different that working toward making it happen.   You also learn that no one can do it all alone, and that it is OK to risk asking for help.  You learn the only thing you must truly fear is fear itself.   You learn to step right into and through your fears because you know that whatever happens you can handle it and to give in to fear is to give away the right to love life on your own terms and more importantly-Jehovah's.  You learn that life isn't always fair, you don't always get what you think you deserve and that sometimes bad things happen to unsuspecting, good people and you learn not to always take it personally.   You learn that nobody's punishing you and everything isn't always somebody's fault. It's just life happening.   You learn to admit when you are wrong and to build bridges instead of walls.  You learn that negative feelings such as anger, envy and resentment must be understood and redirected or they will suffocate the life out of you and poison the universe that surrounds you.   You learn to be thankful and to take comfort in many of the simple things we take for granted, things that millions of people upon the earth can only dream about; a full refrigerator, clean running water, a soft warm bed, a long hot shower.   You make it a point to keep smiling, to keep trusting, and to stay open to every wonderful possibility.   This is c. mckenzie  C.S. (Clean and Soft) saying that finally, with courage in your heart, you take a stand, you take a deep breath, and you begin to design the life you want to live as best you can."
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So a turkish singer said at an Arabic/Israeli/Turkish concert.  The concert itself was awesome - I do like Arabic music and dance. But seeing all those people together on the stage was even better. They are mortal enemies back in their countries. But at the concert they were just co-players. And they do it so well.  I don't speak arabic but I do have some Arabic friends, so I learned how to write my name and phone number and how to say 'I love you' and some other words. It's a beautiful and hard-to-learn language. It's full of sentiments, specially when sung. I had no clue what were they say but they put so much feelings on that that you know they surely singing love songs. Interestingly most of them are love songs from are a country in war. Not so surprising though, they battled for love of Allah and their land. Anyways - It was a nice and worthy-remembering experience. I look forward the time when we will all love the same God and the Earth will be united in only one worship and language.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Acho esta ilustracao interessante e quero registrar aqui para usa-la quando precisar.  Na Grécia Antiga, Sócrates detinha uma alta reputação e era muito estimado pelo seu elevado conhecimento. Um dia, um conhecido do grande filósofo aproximou-se dele e disse: - Sócrates, sabes o que eu acabei de ouvir acerca daquele teu amigo?" - "Espera um minuto", respondeu Sócrates, "Antes que me digas alguma coisa, gostaria de te fazer um teste. Chama-se o "Teste do Filtro Triplo." - Filtro Triplo ?! - Sim, continuou Sócrates, antes que me fales do meu amigo talvez fosse uma boa ideia parar um momento e filtrar aquilo que vais dizer. Por isso é que eu lhe chamei o Filtro Triplo. E continuou: - "O primeiro filtro é VERDADE. Tens a certeza absoluta de que aquilo que me vais dizer é perfeitamente verdadeiro?" - "Não,", disse o homem "o que acontece é que eu ouvi dizer que..." - "Então,", diz Sócrates," não sabes se é verdade. Passemos ao segundo filtro, que é BONDADE. O que me vais dizer sobre o meu amigo é bom?" - "Não, muito pelo contrário..." - "Então," continuou Sócrates "Queres dizer-me algo mau sobre ele e ainda por cima nem sabes se é ou não verdadeiro. Mas, bem, pode ser que ainda passes o terceiro filtro. O último filtro é UTILIDADE. O que me vais dizer sobre o meu amigo será útil para mim?" - Não, acho que não..." - Bem, concluiu Sócrates, se o que me dirás não é nem bom, nem útil e muito menos verdadeiro, para quê dizer-me?   Usa o Triplo Filtro na tua vida diária, de cada vez que fores falar sobre alguém.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Despedidas fazem parte de mudancas. E o preco delas. Na verdade da parte mais dificil. Eu odeio despedidas. Ao mesmo tempo que se esta excitado pelas coisas novas a frente, e tao dificil deixar as coisas presentes, que ficarao para tras. Mas ainda sao tao presentes.  Presentes mesmo: amigos, muitos amigos. Foram um presente, e presentes tambem. Estavam la quando eu precisei deles. Talvez por conversar comigo, me ouvir, tentar desviar minha mente de algum problema, ou por se oferecer a bater naqueles que causaram-me alguma dor. Foram uma constante numa vida em constante mudancas.  Lugares, a segunda coisa que mais me apego. Um lugar no parque. Um bar que fui com alguem especial e que gosto de voltar e reviver um momento de minha vida. Minha casa, acredite ou nao eu sou um housecat. O cheiro das ruas. As pessoas da vizinhanca, pessoas que nao digo nem oi. Mas que estao la todos os dias.  Quanta nostalgia!!!  Vale a pena entao?  Vale, e muito. Pelos mesmos motivos que faz a partida tao dificil.  Os amigos que se faz num novo lugar, conhecer pessoas novas e tao gostoso, conhecer novas culturas, saber a historia da vida delas e ver como estranhos passam a fazer parte de sua vida e como serao para sempre lembrados e muitas vezes com saudades.  E os lugares que se conhece. Ficarao sempre em nossa memoria e serao associados a experiencias antigas e as pessoas que conhecemos nele. Vemos atraves de nossos proprios olhos, sentimos o seu cheio, o clima, a mistura de cores. O julgamos pelo que vemos e experimentamos. Isso e maravilhoso e nao tem preco.  Sendo assim vale o preco da despedida, e torna cada despedida num recomeco. Recomecar e bom, muito bom.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pérolas são produtos da dor, resultados da entrada de uma substância estranha ou indesejável no interior da ostra, como um parasita ou um grão de areia.  Na parte interna da concha é encontrada uma substância lustrosa chamada nácar.  Quando o grão de areia penetra as células do nácar, começam a trabalhar e cobrir o grão com camadas para proteger o corpo indefeso da ostra.  Como resultado, uma linda pérola vai se formando ali no seu interior.  Um ostra que não foi ferida, nunca vai produzir pérolas, pois a pérola é uma ferida cicatrizada.  Você já se sentiu ferido pela palavras rudes de alguém? Já foi acusado de ter dito coisas que não disse?  Suas idéias já foram rejeitadas ou mal interpretadas?  Já sentiu duros golpes de preconceito?  Já recebeu o troco da indiferença?  Então, produziu uma pérola.  Cubra suas mágoas com várias camadas de amor.  Infelizmente, são poucas as pessoas que se interessam por esse tipo de sentimento.  A maioria aprende apenas a cultivar ressentimentos, deixando as feridas abertas alimentando-as com sentimentos pequenos, não permitindo que cicatrizem.  Assim, na prática, o que vemos são muitas "ostras vazias" não por que não tenham sido feridas, mas porque não souberam perdoar, compreender e transformar a dor em amor.  Fabrique pérolas você também! 
    
</post>


</Blog>