<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well guess what I HAVE BEEN WORKING LIKE SOME KINDA CRAZY ON A FORUM TO GO ON HERE YAY YAY YAY. Oh wait no one comes to this so no one cares, well I care and thats all that matter. Well I have some really good news (for myself again since no one comes here) One of my bestest friends in the world is coming over today and is going to spend the night then spend all day saturday with me and then spend the night again yeah. He is really cool he is on of those people who just come up with the craziest ideas&nbsp;at the craziest times and seems to get them from no where. Any how my forum provider is down so I am going to work on my html writing course some more see ya. 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those of you who have been here already, and are now looking for songs or poems. I put them in the side bar, so they would not take up so much of the space on the main page. So now there is a handy link right over there -------------------------> 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a story I want to tell you   There once was a kid who was all alone all the time and he was lonely. He did not have any friends He sat by himself at church. He had great things to&nbsp;share with other people, because he really was a smart guy, but he had no one to tell. One day he decided he was going to get alot of friends. He went up to a bunch of different people and hit it off really well. He soon become very popular and had tons of friends. One day he realized that he was a lot less happy since he become popular. He wondered about this and thought to himself. I have a great family. I know Jesus and he loves me. I have lots of friends why am I sad? He thought about this for a long time. Then he realized the reason he was sad&nbsp;was because of his many friends. He constantly was trying to help them anyway&nbsp;possible and live up&nbsp;to his standards of what a friend should be. So one day he decided he was going to stop having friends. It was hard&nbsp;everone kept trying to talk to&nbsp;him but one by&nbsp;one he slowly become alone again....................................How does the story end you ask? I don't know we will have to watch as my life unplays. 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In a matter of a week I have been able to make most of my friends mad, sad or convinced I hate them. I dont know how I did this because normally its the opposite. I usually make them happy no matter how they are feeling in a couple seconds but whatever. It doesn't really matter soon I will be gone. 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well that is all for now I have some more later I might put on here Tell me what you think   
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am going to post some poems that I have wrote and maybe some songs I will see how I feel 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right now my life is hectic. With school coming, maybe moving and friends being dumb its a little tough. I am thinking I am going to go back to the way I was anti-social. No Friends No Pain.   
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I have made almost my whole youth group mad at me in a little over 24 hours. Pretty impressive sense I was trying to do something I thought (and still think) God wanted me to do. All I did was tell them about my blog and my forum and they go psycho. Anyhow I can't really do much about it. They are going to believe themselves anyhow. No matter how I present the truth they see it as a attack aimed at them. It really is ok I will keep praying for them and for me that I will be open to what they say too. I was reading my bible and I saw this verse that kinda seem to fit   Mark 6:11  "Any place that does not receive you or listen to you, as you go out from there, shake the dust off the soles of your feet for a testimony against them."    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok I have been working on my blog. I now have a chatterbox and a guestbook. So use them. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "Why is it as humans we cling onto only what we know never expanding going outside our comfort zones. We walk alone and then roam in ignorance. They turn back around and use it as a defense for shallowness. This seems to be a concern cuz not known' is not an excuse for those who willin' to learn". John Reuben  Now normally I would not quote John Reuben because he is not my favorite rapper, but this line always strikes something in me. It seems to me that Reuben really hit the thing right on the head with this. Anytime someone tries to stand out and make a difference, they are persecuted for being "Non-conformist" "Rebels" and told to stop trying to change the way things are. You usually hear "we've never done things that way before," but again Reuben has a reply.  to each his own correctin don't select my flavor while see them in the back critiquin' my behavior now tryin' to take creation and me to fit his mold he yelled out sellout but maybe he wasn't told so let me tell this shallow mind why we do what we do I create for the creator but not to impress you ok I'll challenge your thinkin' but not to test you you might not like me, I'll still say "God bless you" and this trust issue, it's all love n' respect and honestly bro I don't think that 's too much to expect but too many times your shallow mind will keep you caught you can't escape your thinkin' all you've ever been taught is that you walk this way you talk this way you front this way you pose this way you react this way na, na that ain't me I got to be who God created me to be  God made me and he made me right. I may not like some of the ways I look, but if I am honest with myself God knows what is best. God made me with a fire inside to not accept the "ordinary" or the "average". He never intended us to all fit in "cookie cutter boxes" and I refuse to submit into what you want me to be. As long as I am pleasing God you can have as much "righteous anger" as you want. Tell me I am "judgmental" "preachy" or that I am going to hell, I know where I'm going. Sometimes people's toes need to be stepped on its whats best for them, in fact some people's toes need to be jumped on. Too many people's eyes and ears don't see or hear the light, because too many "Christian" are worried about offending people. I don't think we need to run around with signs screaming that the world is going to hell, but being afraid to offend someone is the least thing we need to worry about. Myself I've got to be who God created me to be. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I have been trying to find way to make more people want to come to this site. I have put it in directories and search engines. So if you came here because of one of those then Welcome. Please read my poems and songs on the sidebar please also comment or post so I know that I am being effective. Also please visit my  urlLink forum  register, read, post, be heard. God Bless you and thanks for coming.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK all the forum is complete and up and running there is a link for it on the sidebar and one right  urlLink here  Anyhow I put alot of work into it so register post enjoy. 
    
</post>


</Blog>