<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now it may just be the cappuccino that I just very much enjoyed but for some reason my body is exhausted while my mind is ready for a night out on the town.&nbsp; Its quite an interesting mix when you feel all of your muscles screaming for a time out but your mind and heart just won't have it.&nbsp; Sigh... oh well, life goes on.   I would like to apologize for the last post.&nbsp; Normally I am not that pathetically metaphorical but when nothing happens in my life, I start to think about life and what it means.&nbsp; And because life is such a huge topic for a nieve mind such as mine to comprehend, I must talk in metaphors.&nbsp; I promise I will steer clear of metaphors tonight though, today was somewhat interesting.   I finally got my long awaited school housing information and my roomie is just who I wanted it to be! YAY!!!!! S.U.- WATCH OUT... I'M ON MY WAY!!! I don't know what else to say than "I'm Mega Pumped!" and I thought I'd never say that in my life, how embarrassing.&nbsp; So I got put in a Split Double which, as most of you college bound students out there know, means that there will be a wall between me and my favorite person ever.&nbsp; BUT as&nbsp;I was thinking about it, and as my father pointed out so bluntly, when we decide to bring boyfriends back to the room... things won't get as weird.&nbsp; Upon hearing this my mother decided that it might have been a better idea to request an Open Double.&nbsp; HAHA! Yeah, OK Mom.   This split double business will come especially in handy when someone comes up to visit during the upcoming seasons for some skiing/snowboarding.&nbsp; AHEM and to see his favorite "pazza femmina".&nbsp; Damn bastard had to go to Fire Island tonight to get drunk with his buddies.&nbsp; "I wish you could come too"... "Yeah ok,&nbsp;right up until it means I have to cover for you, right?" LoL! How can someone drive you so crazy and then make you smile so much? :)&nbsp; "Have a great time tomorrow night!"... "I'll try.&nbsp; It would be better if you were there though."&nbsp; A smiley face needs to be created that gives off the impression of someone feeling all special inside, tehehe.   Well I think pretty soon my body is just going to shut down and refuse to work, so I am off to collapse on my bed.&nbsp; Which, now that I've read about my day, shouldn't be that necessary but oh well.&nbsp; To each his own, right?   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  Buona notte.   
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder how many people really accomplish everything they want in life.&nbsp; But even more, I wonder how many of our 8 year old selves would like to kick our asses for not being the cool grown-ups that we dream of becoming.   Everyone has that goal, whether they keep it to themselves or share it with the world, everyone has that one star in galaxies far, far away that they would give anything to make it to.&nbsp; And while some people may just ask for this star if they were given the opportunity to have anything they wanted, I think a lot of people would only take something that would put them in line with this star.&nbsp; Obtaining that star isn't the goal of life, its just the end mark, the finish line at the end of a triathalon, the moment of satisfaction when you can look back and say "I did it."&nbsp; I think most people would actually rather enjoy that long hard road to that far away twinkle of light.&nbsp; that's the idea that our 8 year olds wish to belive life is.   Much of society today lose that 8 year old mentality as soon as they hit double digits, realizing that life just isn't that simple.&nbsp;&nbsp;Those many meteors which tend to hit you in a new direction guide you to a new star.&nbsp; It may be just as far away as that twinkle that reflected in your eye only 2 years before, but it doesn't quite compare to the creme of the crop that you wanted so much not so long ago.   However, there is some good news.&nbsp; Once in a blue moon, someone will realize that meteors may be avoided, and that twinkle of a star can still reflect in your 8 year old eyes despite how close you are to triple digits.&nbsp; One in a blue moon, someone gets to that star they always wanted and it means so much to them to be able to look back on the wonderful meteors that they've encountered, overcome, and even dodged; and that twinkle in their eye is now a reflection on the star they started off from so far away.   I am not ashamed to admit I have a very big twinkle in my eye.&nbsp;&nbsp;This twinkle&nbsp;is not a reflection however it is the spark of the unknown.&nbsp; My destination is&nbsp;nothing more than an empty space&nbsp;and you may choose whether it is fortunate or unfortunate that it is probably the furthest of all.&nbsp; For&nbsp;I wish to not only make it to the stars, but to become one.&nbsp; I say that one day I will make it big, everyone will know me, and I will be me, not the next Julia Robberts, Susan Sarandon, or Meryll Streep.&nbsp; I say this half because I am in denial, half because the world is in denial.&nbsp; There is no other choice than for me to achieve that dream and I hope that I will not let my meteors push me away from the twinkle my 5 year old eye had not so long ago.&nbsp; Seriously, who really wants to be pushed around by big dumb rocks?   That having been said, if I were given the opportunity to have anything I wanted, whether possible or impossible, I think I would be&nbsp;3 years older than I am today while still keeping my heart locked up in the 5 year old mentality that gives my eyes the twinkle of the future.&nbsp; As corny as all of this sounds, I believe it.&nbsp; As much as this resembles a valedictorian speech gone awry, its true.&nbsp; Its a shame that today most people&nbsp;don't push their limit.   And when I fall asleep at night, I am proud of my deepest impossible desire.&nbsp; I don't think I'm settling for less, and I don't think I'm taking away any of the long journey I have to obtain my star.   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  Bon soir.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, how pathetic? Me, jumping on the bandwagon once again.&nbsp;&nbsp;Somehow this seems familiar however, you know, one of those deja vu moments.&nbsp; That could be due to the fact that this is now the third website that I have registered myself in so that I can "share my with the world via this beautiful cable modem".&nbsp; I have unsuccessfully attempted these darn things at deadjournal.com and livejournal.com, kind of&nbsp;ironic that those were the two that I chose but I guess you could say I was going through those teenage years where one never really knows how they feel.&nbsp; One day you hate yourself, the next you think you're the bomb.&nbsp; Anyway both of those wonderful glimpses of my past were put to rest due to some stupidity that I published and got caught for, the 'rents don't really approve of sharing your life with complete strangers.   I get it though, I don't even know if I'm really all that comfortable with some complete stranger guy reading this and trying to&nbsp;imagine me sitting here and describing my life.&nbsp; With my luck it would be some old fat man who's been outside in the sun too many hours of his life, smoked too many cigarettes, and probably hasn't showered in days.&nbsp; Hey, everyone attracts a type right? Ha.&nbsp; Anyway, I think I'm going to keep this wonderful glimpse of my life on the dl for a little while, not really register as anyone so that my friends who have all created their own (and about 10 of them have in the past month or so) won't be able to find me and accuse me of being somewhat hypocritical.&nbsp; I think I have a tendency to do that at times.   So in order to protect my own identity and the identities of those I love and care oh so much about, and so that I don't bore you, the reader, to death, I will follow 2 rules when writing these hopefully enjoyable blogs:  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 1. I will not refer to anyone in their real name.&nbsp; I don't even know if I'll use the same name for the same person in multiple blogs, its more fun that way.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; 2. I will not provide you with the boring details of every moment I get supper giddy from being in love with some stupid boy.&nbsp;&nbsp;Basically, no one wants to hear about my love for someone when nothings going to happen and, if it is possible, even fewer people want to know about some beautiful relationship where all I say is "oh I love  insert name of love here ".&nbsp; Gag me, please.   So there are my rules: simple, easy, and logical.&nbsp; And now that I have established this blog with&nbsp;all of the necessities, I will make my way into slumberland having left this one question for all to ponder:   If you could have one thing in the world, anything you want (physically possible or impossible) what would you ask for?&nbsp; If you were to attain it, would you be happy or want something more?   &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp;  Goodnight.    
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Life as been pretty straight foward.  Wake up; do the chores; sitck to the routine; go to work; come home and go to sleep.  I've been liking everything I've been doing so the normal isn't a bother to me but a little change is more than welcome.  Tonight was definately a little different.  Getting to know someone is like getting into a pool that could be ice cold.  Tonight I stuck my big toe into the water and found out its pretty luke warm, I think.  A very smart person (who just so happens to be very talented with an ice cream pricing machine) told me that instead of sticking my foot in next I should just go in to the knee.  I wonder what that means. HA, I'm sure I'll figure it out.  I just hope its all figured out by the time I leave (12 days and counting).  If not, then I guess it will have to be figured out during "weekend trips".  Whats really interesting is how people go about getting to know one another.  Its no longer "Do you want to come play at my house? I have the new lego set!", or "Do you want to sleep over?".  These days strong emotions get intertwined into these words, they mean so much more than the actual meaning.  It was nice for "Do you want to join me for ice cream?" actually mean that.  I hope it stays that way and I hope life continues in this basic routine, with a surprise thrown in there every once in a while.   Maybe I'll step into the water a little further with each surprise down the way.  The sparks of new and exciting stuff are so much brighter if you seize them for everything they are.  Meanwhile this routine is done.  Its time for bed so that I can wake up, drive, do the chores, go to work.    Buona Notte.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In three weeks time I will be sleeping in my dorm room bed after a LONG day of driving and unpacking. The next big chapter of my life will be starting and it will finally be setting in that I am no longer a child. Tonight's entry is going to be filled with a couple of allusions to my shift at Pazzo Cucina tonight. For instance, "Tiempo y Silencio" is the name that a waiter, Matt, at the restaurant will give his next horse. For those, like myself, who need to seek out their Spanish speaking friends to decipher this not-so-foreign language, it means "Time and Silence". Its actually quite a beautiful name for a horse and arouses some interesting thoughts about life.  Another memory of this evening that I keep returning to is one of Angelo, the owner. We were discussing how I was having a hard time believing how short three weeks really are. (I don't know about you, but my past three weeks have gone by faster than it takes to count the days, maybe because its been so quiet.) In response to my amazement about how quickly sand falls through the hourglass, Angelo tells me that before I realize it I will be his age (a ripe old 33) and I will probably be pregnant ("out to here" he says, making the appropriate gesture about a foot away from his stomach) with a wonderful family to boast. I know he speaks the truth. I know that when that day comes, I will remember his prediction, and I know that those 16 years will feel like a day. My only hope is that when I sit back and really think about all that time, I don't remember silence.  Silence, while experiencing it, lasts forever. One minute of silence can feel like an eternity. But when remembering that minute at some later day, it holds as much value as a nanosecond. When I am 33 with a belly "out to here", I hope that I can look back on 16 years of adventure, happiness, accomplishment, maybe even a little failure (who learns anything without a little bit of mishaps?). I want to remember everyone who has touched my life, all the places I will have touched, and be ready for many more 16 years. Because really, who wants to remember life when they are old and about to die? Then you just get depressed about all the things you planned to do, and don't get the opportunity to actually accomplish them. Its funny how time works. Just when you have it figured out (which obviously, I don't), you've miraculously ran out of it.  Maybe its my nostalgia for everyone I've missed out on this summer. Maybe its my nostalgia for everyone I've missed out on all my life. Its not like I've purposefully missed out, it's actually exactly as Tyler put so perfectly: "It's not that my desire is false, but rather that my intention is optimistic at best and ultimately vapid", and that's rather sad. Things may pick up in the next few weeks as everyone realizes how close we are to saying goodbye. I sure as hell am going to miss all of them (even my very close family at Pazzo) but I don't want that loneliness to remind me of silence. Even more, I don't want my life to resemble my memories of this summer.       Per adesso, Buonanotte. Para ahora, Buenas noches. For now, Goodnight. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will be 18 years of age. I will be able to die for my country in battle, buy a piece of property, even decide who will lead our country for the next four years. That last privilege is one that will impact many, many lives, more so then usual, and if all us "young people" do not participate in this very important act, things could go horribly wrong. Tonight I was schooled on this, and I was forced to grow up a little bit.  In order to vote properly, you have to have a set of ideals, know whether any of the candidates share in these ideals, and be willing to compromise on their ideals you do not share. I was never one to follow politics, its so messy. Candidates are too concerned with getting votes than just showing who they are and what they will do. Its about getting elected, not leading the country. I knew that this was something I'd eventually have to get into because I hate the thought of being a stupid "young person" who doesn't care less about where the country is headed. I just didn't expect it to come so soon.  So I joined my new roomie and her friends at Fridays tonight for some late night munchies. We began discussing Kerry and Bush (there were 2 VERY SUPPORTIVE Kerry-ins) and everyone else didn't have much to say. I decided to play Devils Advocate just to see where it would go. From the Presidential Election we moved to Gay marriages and progressed to Religion. We were a bunch of late teens discussing the major debates of society. It felt good.  But as good as it felt at the time, I look back on it now and realize that I like to discuss topics, not get in heated debates about them. We almost got to that point tonight. And with my firm beliefs about my religion and the good man upstairs, sometimes people get defensive when discussing these fragile concepts. Case and point: Do not get into a discussion about the differences between the Roman Catholic Church and the Episcopal (Anglican) Church with a Catholic and an Anglican... It may get ugly. But the point I'm trying to make is that if everyone could put their thoughts aside for a moment and realize that sometimes there's another way of looking at things, maybe things would be a little bit easier. Maybe this scramble for presidency wouldn't be a competition for votes, but a a competition for values. Things get interesting between two people when they can listen to each others differences without taking it as a personal offense.  Maybe I'm just too naive to realize the harsh realities of life. Maybe I just need to take off these glasses... Maybe I have a point.       Sleep tight.  I now travel to my dreams, where forever I will be young 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>