<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i just HAD to do it! haha         AN IDEAL GUY   aka "HIM!"    [if you know of anyone, let me know ;) haha]     ethnicity-  White, please. =P haha    hair color-  Brownish. (red heds~ haha =P)  eye color-  Light eyes...haha...(like BRIGHT EYES! haha ok nm i don't think anyone'll get that)  height-  Taller than me.    six pack-  It's not a must.  really, it's not. haha    dress-  oooh. hmm. His pants have to fit nicely! i don't mean they can't be baggy, i mean like... you know...ok maybe not.  but i like the CUTE and CASUAL style...i like HATS. haha no abercrombie or hollister, please. =P    long/short hair-  I think i've developed a fettish for shaggy-ish long hair. but it can be short haha    glasses-  sure, why not...haha    piercings-  oooh. MAYBE! i like piercings...but not too many.    bug eyes-  ...maybe not.    mustache-  ...i think only AJ Mclean can pull that one off haha =]    eye brows-  not too bushy.    buff or skinny-  in between. i don't like BUFF...being cut is nice. :) someone you can hug. =]    funny or serious-  i like someone who can make me laugh! but can be serious enough to come to me with his problemos.    should he cook or bake-  yummy!!! i like to eat...and i like sweets but i can't cook...so BOTH, please!    should he have alot of friends that are girls-  hmm...toughy. i don't see why not, because i would be able to trust "him" =P    should he have a bestfriend-  ME!!! haha jk jk. or am i? but sure! why not?? i just hope i'm one of them : )     outgoing or shy-  being shy can sometimes be endearing...but i can get shy too. so maybe a sprinkle of both :)    should he love his mother-  CLARO!!!    smart-  yes. hopefully we can learn from each other and he can teach me a lot!    personality-   this one is flexible...    would he smoke-  no...    would he drink-  haha...like AJ?? maybe not to that extent =P haha    would he swear-  no...well, i would prefer no...but boys will be boys. haha    would he pay for dates-  he would OFFER to pay. i'm looking for the offer. =P    does he kiss on the first date-  not sure...    where would you go for dinner-  somewhere fun! but nice, but not too fancy. like..IN-n-OUT! hahaha    would he bring you flowers-  aww, flowers...:)    Would you hang out with him and his friends-  yes. hopefully we'd be friends beforehand...and have the same amigos :)    would he walk you to the door at the end-  yes, please. i'm old fashioned. that, plus i'd probably be scared to walk alone. haha    holding hands-  YESS, PLEASE!!!  "i wanna hold your hand..." =D    take care of you- yes...that would be GREAT!    wear suits-  when necessary. JOHN STEVENS does =P    basketball-  pro bball! LAKERS! he has to like/love   the lakers! and sure, playing the sport isn't a negative.    snowboard-  sure. but he'd have to teach me how.    football -  maybe not.    tennis-  yeah~ he can play with me :)    play piano-  ok~    play drums-   oooh, drums would be cool.    plays guitar-   oooh guitar, yes puhleaasse!    clean his room-  as long as the floor is visible i think i'll be ok.     use the word "hot" -  ok~ haha    would he watch the sunrise with you-  ... and we would have a blanket...and drink hot cocoa...and...ok the answer is yes. haha    what kind of car does he drive-  one that drives me around, since i can't drive myself :( haha    how old-  my age. (which is old now...17 :[ )    WILL HE TAKE YOU TO CONCERTS AND SHOWS-  YES!    WILL HE TAKE YOU TO DISNEYLAND-  YES!    WILL HE TOLERATE YOUR WEIRD OBSESSIONS - YES!    WILL HE LAUGH AT YOUR LAME JOKES - YES!    WILL HE PUT UP WITH YOUR RANDOMNESS - YES!    WILL HE PUT UP WITH YOUR MOODINESS-  YES!     WILL HE LIKE YOU BACK  - YES!!!    ok, so i added those last few, but hey! i'm allowed to. "HE" would understand that. hahaha     
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Today i learned what WTR meant...how exciting!     &nbsp;   taiwaneseguy: wtr? 
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I'm Sick of Smiling ...And so is my jaw       Can't you see my front is crumbling down?      I'm sick of being someone im not      Please get me out of this slump      I'm sick of clapping      When I know I can do it better for myself      I'm sick of waiting      Sick of all these words that will never matter      - nfg  (...yes...nfg =P)     
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       WOW! today was... FRIDAY ~...yup. that's right! haha.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   I played with my sister and cousins and shopped at  ULTA ...well,  THEY  did.     &nbsp;   I dropped in on   POKER NIGHT   with the boys @   JACOB'S   house.&nbsp;   JOHN  ,   RISHI  ,   DARYL  ,   JOSH , &nbsp;and  Andrew , I believe, were there playing.&nbsp;   SUSAN   came later with  LOVE ACTUALLY .&nbsp; But she got bored of it so we watched the  KELLY CLARKSON  music video instead. "the trouble with love is....." *sings heart out.* ok i'm done with that. haha     &nbsp;   Then went to  MCDONALD'S.    JOSH   drove me. THANK YOU, you great driver. haha.&nbsp;&nbsp;I saw the c/o 2005 t-shirts =P...oh and his&nbsp;cool flashlight and AWESOME CELL PHONE! he gets to be&nbsp;a texting beast! haha     &nbsp;     RISHI   didn't sit with me =( he was too COOL so i am 'mad' at him. haha but i gave some of my CHICKEN NUGGETS to&nbsp;   SUSAN  !!! Yummy. haha&nbsp;   CHRISTOPHER   was supposed to come play...but there was a communication error so i didn't get to see him =( NEXT TIME!!!     &nbsp;   Then i left because my other sister and other cousins came to pick me up early.&nbsp; Didn't get&nbsp;to play TOO much, but it was nice seeing some of my  FAVORITE PEOPLE  after a long time! =D     &nbsp;   I MISS PEOPLE.&nbsp; I didn't realize how out of it I had been until i realized i didn't get to play some more.&nbsp;   I MISS IT.  &nbsp;     &nbsp;    THE END!!!     
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What a funny word. haha   BLOG  ...  BLOGGER  ...  BLOGGING  ...ok...no, i do NOT have a life. haha.&nbsp; Wow...I started a Blog. Don't know why, don't know for what, but I did =D. Ok. That is it..for now i think. haha YAY!!! ok bye. &nbsp;     &nbsp;  ps. I WANT TO   PLAY  !!! sorry...i'm quite random&nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;  pps. I WANT TO GO TO  DISNEYLAND !!! ...i'm still random. &nbsp;     &nbsp;  ppps. I WANT  CHOCOLATE !!! ...yup, still random.     &nbsp;  pppps. I WANT  THIS !!!   urlLink  http://www.hottopic.com/store/product.asp?LS=0&ITEM=208120&amp;RN=1.#QNAN   &nbsp;=D haha    &nbsp;  PICTURES DON'T WORK! BLAH! :( help me!    &nbsp;   THE END!!!   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>