<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [It's true the way I feel, what is promised by your face. The sound of your voice, painted on my memories, even if you're not with me, I'm with Dan] With Dan - Danbrid Theory - Dankin Park  How many normal days are there in ma life?! Ok today was quite simple with a good start during MT and again we all went to play an exciting game of guessing. Quite funny actually. Cikgu didn't give us any homework (yet again) but tomorrow got TEST. Haiz I kinda miss my old MT teacher, Cikgu Nor.  After that M.E. Nothin important to say except that we had to write letters to "Aunty Agony" ( Or sumthin ) and "She" will reply. A lil borin.  Hmmmmm let me see..... oh yeah after that was IPW! The groups had to present and while they were doing all this, I was in the corner there in my own world (again). Then this Sheryl kept saying "I Miss My Brother". I think she crazy or depressed : ). Kendrick watch out. Noticed sumthin about Miss Lum - No porno, no games and no music.  Wah after the whole hoot was MLM's lesson. Haha got a few people sleep during her class. Quite sad to see that actually coz she there teaching so hard and there we are sleeping :p Then Jordan* kena caught by MLM for hibernatin lol.  The lesson after was Maths and to me, it was the lesson of the day. This time I understanded all thanks to Mrs Selvan : ) She teach teach teach then suddenly she said "Ok that's all" then we all clap for her! ( Pro sia ). Then she gave us some work to do on the Maths textbook. Tomorrow still got a lot more to do. I'm looking forward to finishing it.  The scourge of my day was ASSEMBLY. A bunch of Sec 1 classes, went on stage to perform skits about telephone call ( WHO WAS THE GENIUS WHO GAVE THIS IDEA?! ) which were hard to understand. Yeah I admit that it was all A BAD BORING MUSTY JOKE but I can't say anything becoz I couldn't do it better if I were out there. Then my "bro" went on stage take prize (BOOOOOOOOO TYCO) :)  After school, we all played football. Wah for once I become a proper keeper for a few moments before I flopped at the end ( LEHMANN FLOPS TOO ). Today I also very happy coz it's my first goal from A VERY LONG TYCO SHOT FROM HALF THE PLAYING SPACE. LEON DID YOU SEE THAT ?! I shall not say anymore coz like I said, it was tyco.    > love you. You love me. Nuff said. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [Take  everythin from Dan inside, and throw it all away, coz I swear, for the last time, I won't trust myself with you] - From Dan Inside - Danteora - Dankin Park  Hullo now in cyber-centre during IPW lesson. It's very noisy in here. I can hear Kendrick acting cute and Han making noise. I can hear Nat and Sally chattin. I can hear some girls laughing and giggling. Aiyah not much to say except that I'm in the cyber-centre and I'm very bored and I have nothin to do so here I am, typing.  Me not being blur for one day is like Jeremy having a father's day ----- It won't happen.     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [I've tried so hard, and got so far. In the Dan, it dansn't even matter] In The Dan - Dankin Park  Firstly I would like to apologize for not updating yesterday! I was too tired - I slept at 7pm.  Well, today was another day in the 2/8 bootcamp......ain't got much to say actually. The first miraculous signs of significance came during CME when we all had to present our recipes. Had to mix two foods from two races together to make one. ( Kind of reminds me of Frankenstein's monster - harmless and kind but UGLY. )  Next came English lesson, but no lecture today! ( Should have taken my video cam and record it ). Well it lasted one period only so if she were to lecture, Mdm "Lullaby" Mok no need to come and teach us oredi.  Then came Mdm "Lullaby" Mok to take us to another dimension where 1 hour = 1 month. We managed to survive the 2 months, killing time doing worksheets and scribblin graphs on graph paper. One thing I noticed about Mdm Mok is that, she doesn't care whether to make lesson interesting or not, unlike some other teachers. Thank God that's over.  After that was mee-yew-zick. Again Ms Quek ( Or should I say, Mrs Lee ) didn't come. Some people said she go honeymoon, some people said she pregnant and some people say she's sick ( Physically not mentally ) Then some weird sub teacho with a name Mr Lim replaced her. Wah we learnt a lot from him....things such as having guts and the word of the day.... IGNORANCE. Things went pretty well with him, though sitting beside Jeremy was the worst thing to do in the music room ( His mind is controlled by cartoons ). Oh yeah speaking about Jeremy, I would just like to announce that HE CAN NO LONGER BE A FATHER BECOZ HIS PEN  -  IS HACKED OFF WAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAARGHARCGHARGHACK HACK HACK KOFF KOFF *CHOKE*  Extremely important note specially for everybody, especially for Jeremy Loh Yan Hao: COCKS DON'T GROW BACK HARGHARGHARGHARGHARGHAARGHARGHARGHARH  Another highly, extremely, very "salient" note: I am lame. If you don't like lamers, you've come to the wrong place. :)  Reminder: Bring your Report Book tomorrow with all slips of paper SIGNED.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [I don't what's worth fighting for, or why I had to scream. I don't know why I instigate, and say what I don't mean] - Linkin Park - Breaking The Habit  1st Entry for this week! Well today wasn't much of a day.  I hope this doesn't disappoint you. Ok today was quite the normal. First lesson Science nothing. After that English also nothing. Then the things started in recess.  I go and itchy leg play football during recess ( I couldn't stand it ) and when I came back to class, Mr Tan go and drive all the perspirin people to get out and dry themselves ( What an embarrassment) then I go to the toilet, fanning myself walking around the toilet. Then the Qi Zhi couldn't dry himself. When he perspire it's like a sponge, squeeze out water then some of it can suck in back. In the end, Aaron had to call us back to class.  After history was Maths. Woah at last Mrs Selvan came back! Then she explained why she never come and apologized for not coming then she went through the Maths questions that we cannot do. Maths lessons were the best coz I can sit behind where nobody can disturb me where the wind blows and the birds sing where the sky is blue and the sun shines brightly in the cloudy, beautiful sky. ( Excuse my lameness ).  My god then came PC lesson. Mrs Chua gave us quite a lecture on our poor performance in work and poor effort. Oooooh quite scary lah when she call out my name say whether I got kick ball in class. Lucky she quickly skip. I like that also scared. ( Excuse my cowardice )  Woah after school was the BEST. We all played football. 2/8 vs other class. Wooooooo we're maintaining a steady record for defence and attack. Kendrick scored two, Han as usual scored a lot, I scored two, Jeremy scored one very SETAN goal and Leon scored a magnificent 15 metre curling riser to the top right corner. Leon your shooting rules the world. From his record, he is not tyco. Then today I very happy coz I actually SCORED, a very rare occasion for a defender. I don't have the shooting of Leon. I don't have the speed of Han. I don't have the stamina of Kendrick. All I have are my three dearest legs ( If you know what I mean ) which I use to dribble :)  >It's all fun and games till somebody loses an eye     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhhhhhh another day in school again. Started out all the same: I go to class, see em all cheery faces and then I sit down to do two questions in Maths homework. I got this bad habit of not finishing homework.... All too normal. But what went on was bit weird.  Firstly, during the assembly, there were no teachers. Dun know where they go meeting upstairs while we all wait at parade square. Then in came Mr Nathan to start another lecture on life. Then when we going to sing National anthem, the teachers all go down. This school is weird.  Then just now MT got test. I barely escaped from a forfeit. My lucky day.  After that Maths. Don't know what's going on with Mrs Selvan. For two lessons she hasn't even entered the class. Too busy with admin stuff I guess. Then Mrs Ram go into the class and asked us to do the Maths questions Mrs Selvan wanted us to do. Please be reminded, its Review Questions 13, Questions 1-3.  English was the most exciting lesson for today, we went to the LC to borrow books and I borrowed a book about football basics. Yeah, I know. Boring. I think this whole blog itself is boring but I don't mind writing the crap that happens in a day of ma life.  Then got D & T. Mr Irfan was off for reservice so there's a sub teacho, Mr Suwandi (Is that how you spell it?). First we sat there for a few minutes. Silent. Then suddenly he started to talk and talk and talk and talk and talk....... and only the girls got to listen. Us boys were left to rot, so while he was busy entertaining the gals, Wilfred and Endika started to play some hand games, then the others followed. Then all started laughing. HAHAHAHAHAHAHA. Lame. After that, we continued doing our project. My group, consisting of Han and Chimpo is making Sadako coming out of well....oooooo scary. Then our sub teacho taught us how to use some of the tools. Arghhhhh there's just not enough excitement in ma life.   After school was the worst. I spent 4 hours of my precious time for a Life Science workshop. Yeah it wez fascinatin but it's DAMNED TOO LONG. FOUR HOURS?! I CAN GO PA SIAO 1000 TIMES. Wooooo I didn't know the playground was so much fun when you're together wif all yer comrades :D&nbsp; Then we all sat there for like 4 months before finally released at 6pm. Went home so late boohoohoo 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Henry on TV! &nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Alright before I start, let me introduce myself. My name is Muhammad Danial Shah Bin Zahari. I came to this world to serve two purposes: To prepare for death and to play   FOOTBALL  . A lil bit of myself, I like   FOOTBALL   very much. Note that I like to call soccer "football" coz that is how Thierry says it!     &nbsp;   I'm a fan of&nbsp;  ARSENAL   football club, the   GREATEST FOOTBALL TEAM TO EVER     GRACE THE SPORT  . Most of you would know this, my all-time favourite player is   THIERRY HENRY.   &nbsp;The fast, flying Frenchman from Paris who scores goals for a living. If you got any issues bout   FOOTBALL  , come to me.      &nbsp;   Ok more bout me. I'm a bit of a shy person, especially around gals.&nbsp;I don't why. Maybe it's just me. Hopeless with girls I guess.     &nbsp;   Yeah I admit. I'm a FUCKING blur person. Sorry fer that. I'm in a world of my own when alone. Hey, but I enjoy that. When I'm angry, leave me alone. You won't do betta by talking to me.&nbsp;Hey, I talk to myself sometimes. (Doesn't mean I'm mental.)     &nbsp;   I love Linkin Park's and Eminem's works. I listen to em everyday. It helps me relax. Uh huh I don't quite like love songs. Mushy. I'd rather listen to a toilet flush.     &nbsp;   Well, that's all I have to say for today. I'll start bloggin (Grrrrrr) tomorrow..... GOOD NIGHT Y'ALL    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [Why I never walked away, why I played myself this way. Now I see, you're testing me, Pushing Me Away] Linkin Park - Hybrid Theory - Pushing Me Away  Just like to inform everybody that I won't blog on Tuesdays and Weekends. Tuesday I'm too tired and there's nothing to blog on Weekends. Case closed.  Ok today was JUST another day. Forgive me for a VERY, BORING BLOG. Thank you. Here it goes.  Started the day fine, with MT bein the first period. Got 33/40 for writing test! But I guess that was tyco.  I don't want to get started on ME coz it's still not exciting.  Didn't play football at recess even though got ball! WHAT A RECORD.  English.....oops never bring Dictionary! Think I'm gettin more forgetful. First it was the form now this. Time to eat lotsa fruits. Oh yeah, today no lecture. (Shit video cam no battery)  Science. HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA Did a few experiments that's all. (Insert mad laughter here)  Music was qwertyuiopasdfghjklzxcvbnm. I just sat there with my mouth welded shut. Han, however, had other ideas. He was behind me making so much noise. It was raining in there. Raining his saliva.  After school was quite the fascinating. Played football for a while. Got one time I bring the ball with me to the end of the field and waited for Kendrick they all to come. Instead, I heard some girls calling me. Then saw the "Shoe-Gals". Why you call yourselves "Shoe-Gals"? Everyday scrub shoes. (NO OFFENCE. JUST TELL ME THE REAL MEANING WHY)  What do you call a person who has a big hole in his groin area? Answer: A jeremy. What do you call a person who risked his penis in a big bet? Answer: A kendrick. What do you call a person who is short, fat and ugly? Answer: A L...Hitler. 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [I'm painted on the walls...... Coz I'm the one at fault......I'll never fight again......And this is how it ends] Breaking The Habit - Meteora - Linkin Park  Uh oh! It's the start of Week 8. A lot of things happened and is gonna happen. Today was eventful.  Started off by coming to class. Then Endika reported saying that he found a ball. OBVIOUSLY the ball was from the Sports Equipment Room so I didn't dare take it home. But they were whining "Bring it home, bring it home". All I could say was **** *** *** **** *** ** ****.  Oh yeah. A newcomer has arrived into our class! I forgot what her name was though. All I know that she's from China, she's good in Maths and she's going to some educational institute named "Wellington". She's quite pretty too. :D  Science was as always, boring. MLM was there trying her best to make the lesson interesting A LIL WEE BIT for the newcomer. She failed.  Later came English. We went into groups to discuss the whole OPA thing. Glad it was all finished.  Recess played soccer! No record today.  History was quite fun. We had a good laugh with Mr PanzerFourStar Tan. He kept TRYING to talk Chinese. Wah he bastard sia say what if cannot answer question, can go back to China.  Maths we learnt about the Trigo something something. It was quite hard to understand at first but I eventually got the hang of it. Lucky get it or else I'll be dead for the next test.  PC period was nothin actually. Mrs Chua brought us down to the bookfair to let us recommend books for the LC. What the shit was that?  After school, went to play soccer. Never scored today although I got two chances. One hit the post :( Lost the match 5-3. IT WAS NOT A GOOD GAME.  All I did to you was pinch you. Why you go and fuck me until like that? - Kenshik Lim      
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [I can't faint the way I did before, don't turn your back at me. I WON'T BE IGNORED] Faint - Meteora - Linkin Park  Just scared myself silly playing Doom 3. But this game rules the world. I had the best adrenaline rush yet! Today I used 6 pants, 2 barfbags and 9 computer seat covers. What a bummer.  Today, I should say, was quite gay. 1st two periods were OK, quite uneventful. After that CME they all came out and act, and it was better than last time's!  Recess didn't play football. Another record but it's just because some asshole stole the ball.  IPW was a great in the 1st period we watched PART of Looney Tunes Back In Action due to popular demand (F*** You Jeremy). Then after that we had Mrs Chua steal one period!!!! ARGH. Next time, I'm discharging firearms.  After that Science. Same routine. ( Today was very boring day, so blame dun me if this blog is boring )  Maths was lesson of the day! Got back the Maths test marks and I got 12/20!!! LIKE SHIT RIGHT? But more importantly, Kendrick is now robbed of his manhood and can no longer breed! WOOOOOOOOOO CELEBRATIONS HERE I COME.  Assembly today was outstanding. A few guys went up there and did some beautiful music and I liked it so I took out my shoe and grooved to the beat. Lame.  After that had to stay back to do some 1 hour English test. Hope I get high marks for this bugga.  MIRACLE: NO HISTORY REMEDIAL WOOOOOOOOOOOOo  Went to McDonalds with Eugene, Han, Nat, Kendrick, Leon and Jeremy. Man we had a hoot there! I never knew that this group of friends was all that I need to enjoy a good time. Just like to say, I enjoyed my time with y'all. Thanks!   Anticipation is after all, Everything. - Dr Betruger from Doom 3 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [When I look into your eyes, there's nothing there to see. Nothing but my own mistake, staring back at me] P5hng Me Aw*y - Linkin Park - Reanimation  Wow it's been a long time since I update my blog. I'm now suffering from Post-Doom3 Syndrome. I had two sleepless nights and I can't go to the toilet undisturbed in the mind. If you don't understand, go to  urlLink www.planetdoom.com  and you'll know. Now that I have composed myself, I can update my blog.  Today was not a good day. First period, I had a composition test. It wasn't that hard but I was the only one who wrote on that number. Scary.  CME was again, not quite entertaining but at least we got into groups but we talked instead of doing the work we were supposed to do :D  Recess, played football. So no record today :(  English we got back our news report and grammar test. I got 21 and 16 marks respectively. LIKE SHIT RIGHT?  After that Science we did a few experiments which I say were a lil bit interesting. MLM was going and going, sometimes stopping coz somebody was talking. I just sat there, clipped the wooden thingies on my ears coz they have little balls in em that I want to crush.  Music was uneventful. Again I zombied myself through it. I don't feel like talkin in the music room. Han was behind, making A LOT of noise. Next music lesson, I'm bringing a tranquilizer so I can stick one into his ass ( NO OFFENCE HAN ). Then we watched the Stomp Out Loud and they are so pro they can make music out of anything, literally.  After school was the worst. Some ugly, fucking, desperate, faggotbitchassclown stole the ball. Man I'm off my temp. This person, obviously doesn't have balls coz he has to steal some. If I could, I would, tear off his balls and eat em, RAW. Now I'm depending on witness Lopez to spill out the information.  Then went to McDonalds to do OPA, very confusing coz the girls keep saying they will do this, but never do. Must command with iron fist. NO MERCY. Anyway there was a bunch of girls there, so I cannot anyhow make noise.  Note for Chia Lat Mee: BRING YOUR CME WORKBOOK 2B TOMORROW IF UR READING THIS.  Braggards are stupid and outdated coz they keep dwelling into the past and tell lies. :)  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [You selfish bit** I hope you ***kin burn in hell for this sh**] Cleaning Out My Closet - Eminem Show - Eminem  Firstly I would just like to say that SHERYL IS LOVESICK, WITH SOMEONE. If anyone can help her solve her problems, please kindly come to me :D  I'm finally fit enuff to come to school. Had a fever of 37.9 and a bad flu with cough. Had my MC in ma wallet but Mrs Chua wasn't here today (Another video cam moment). It was surprising actually and everyone was going "Mrs Chua never come today?" coz she rarely take leaves. Weird.  Mother Tongue was alright.......but after that was the moment where everyone was hatin.  Went downstairs....with em index numbers 31-34.....and we sat down on chairs near the DENTIST TRAILER.  It was a terrible experience, waitin. Waitin fer your turn to get those CRUEL DENTISTS to take those TERRIBLE LONG TUBES OF DOOM into your mouth and DRILL INTO UR TEETH OMG and all your blood will SPLATTER ALL OVER THE WALL OH THE INHUMANITY.  Forget the lame crap I just said. When I went inside, the guy on the left, nearest to the door checked ma teeth, said that they were OK and did some cleanin, no pain and no blood at all.  It was all over before CME, UNFORTUNATELY so I had to go up and take it fer bout 15 minutes.  Another record for not playing football during recess today.  Then came English lesson but today that was non-existent. Instead, we had to do an introduction on a newspaper report. I kept changin places coz I couldn't find a quiet place to do. NOTHIN ELSE TO SAY.  Next came MLM's lesson. We went down to the Physics lab to do some work on the practical book. Quite a number of people weren't there so it was all not whole-heartedly done. Sad.  The lesson of the day was music. The boys and the girls sat different places and we had a challenge where the boys lost, but Mrs Lee forgot the forfeit. Some people are just blessed with forgetfullness. Then we watched a very cool video "Stomp Out Loud" and in it were some pro musicians who did their music using normal stuff. It BRIGHTENED up my day.  >Love is not in the air because air is only made up of nitrogen, oxygen, water vapour and other rare gases 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [Why I stay, when you just push away? No matter what you see, you're still so blind to me] - P5hng Me Aw*y - Linkin Park - Reanimation  Argh today I'm so dang tired and depressed. Must be the hormones inside of me. THIS IS ALL PUBERTY'S FAULT.  Another start to the week with a Science practical test at the first period. It wasn't as hard as I expected but I'm still worried bout the marks I would get. In fact, I worry about every test and every mark. But when I get em, I don't care anymore. TOLD YA I'M WEIRD SO DON'T COME NEAR ME.  The lesson after was English. No lecture again ( Damn where's my video cam?! ).  So she was teachin us on how to write a good argumentative essay and what what the techniques of it. It could all have been good if I wasn't sittin there locking my 160mm ( You will never understand ).  Today is a record day coz I never play football during recess.  Hmmmm after that was History....... and we had to arrange tables and sit in groups of fours. Then this Mr Tan go and write down a few words on the board. All I could remember was "Initiative" and "Self-respect". Then he started by flashing the super sick pictures of the Japanese atrocities during the war ( I still hate the one with the pussy and a stick in it ). Lucky Mr Tan covered it, or else.....  Next came, Maths and this time Mrs Selvan did come to class. She taught us how to find the median ( THANK GOODNESS ) and the Pyagthoras Theorem ( Is that how you spell it?! ). I would just like to thank wonder woman YELYN for helping me in one of my Maths question. Many thanks to you.  PC was the lesson next and we had to go to the garden ( wherever it was ) and we all sat in an oval and we did the things together and then Mrs Chua assigned Eugene and Kendrick to give out sweets to the whole class and the sweets were really sweet and I liked em and I asked for more but Kendrick wouldn't give some to me coz he's a bastard but luckily Eugene came around again and I got one and I was happy and I ate it and it tasted good and I wanted more but I told myself that sweets are not good for your teeth so I did not eat anymore sweet instead I went on to do my PC file so I wouldn't worry about it tomorrow and I managed to finish it and then the bell rang and we all went up to class. ( This is a very good example of an "Act Cute" paragraph".  Didn't play football after school today coz I was feeling a lil bit feverish and weak and I have this annoying sore throat. Everytime I swallow something it fires up.  Damn. Hmmmmm I can't wait for National Day!!!! But I must be patient becoz.....  >Patience is the key to contentment   
    
</post>


</Blog>