<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Joshua had patented two additional new technology upgrades for GD that year. When his bonus came out, it had shrunk from 1% of the profit base, to 0.75%. He ended up seeing a bonus of only F3,000 for the entire year. He finally got fed up after five years with General Dynamics and decided to start his own company. Placing his house, which he had inherited from an uncle he had never met, as collateral, he borrowed F750,000 and formed his own company. He introduced his first patent 2 months later. He had developed the idea several months before, but had kept it private, never researching it while at GD. The first two months passed quickly as he spent almost 20 hours each day testing and improving his concept until it was ready. The DefGen had been patented, manufacturers located and signed, and the customer hunt began. The DefGen was a radical departure in technology. It was a pump that compressed water as part of the pumping process. The expansion of the water as it was forced through the pump generated a kinetic force used to drive a uniquely shaped turbine. The turbine shaft spun a highly modified dynamo and generated electricity in excess of that required by the pump to move the water. In effect, Joshua had invented a water pump that generated free electricity. Other liquids could be used, but the density and molecular properties of standard drinking water worked best. A small capacitor stored an electrical charge that started the pump. Once the pump reached 2,000 rpm, the electricity generated recharged the capacitor and provided an excess power above that required running the pump itself. The pump, after the first 5 minutes to spin up, generated 96% more electricity than it used. Hating long scientific names, Joshua had taken his description, Dynamic Fluid Generator and created the name DefGen. Power companies, traditionally bound to coal or nuclear, suddenly had a clean source of power. Water companies had suddenly had the ability to provide power as well as water. This had led to a round of mergers and changes in the utilities industry. Joshua had paid off his loan 2 months later and had been profitable from that time on. In addition to the royalties, he also provided consulting services for new applications of his technology. Anole Technologies had become an overnight success. Newspaper sand magazines heralded the DefGen as the biggest breakthrough in technology since the introduction on the Digilog computer chip in 2009.&nbsp; While the Digilog chip had changed computers from binary, on-off systems; the Digilog chips had added a third state, partial-on. With this new, trinary technology, computer speeds had grown exponentially without increasing chip speeds. The ability to handle base 3 data had generated a new coding system made of 0s, 1s, and 2s instead of the old 0s and 1s. 1 megabyte of memory now held 25 times more information In the 6 years since he started Anole Technologies, Joshua had 12 patents in public use. He had expected to see his inventions improve society. If the cost of production was reduced, products became cheaper to produce and the consumer's EUs went further. That was what he had been taught in economics. But the greed and avarice he had glimpsed at General Dynamics still controlled the economy. Costs in many areas had fallen 40% or more, but prices to the consumer stayed the same. Company profits climbed. Helping the public would not happen by making production cheaper. Perhaps making the maintenance or other costs lower would allow people to enjoy a better prosperity. If a car were going to cost F85,000 regardless of how much the manufacturing costs went down, maybe the key would be to make running that car cheaper. So, he started work on his next project. Joshua wanted a car that did not cost an arm and a leg to fill up. After several false starts, he ended up returning to the source of his first personal fortune, water. There had been attempts to build a viable engine that ran by burning the gaseous hydrogen + oxygen created by electrically splitting water into its component elements. As early as 1920 and up to the 90s, people had tried. The problem was it always used more pure energy to get the hydrogen and oxygen out then burning them produced. Inserting a micro version of his DefGen allowed 90% free electricity to be used to generate the fuels for the engine. What he finally ended up with was a slightly modified gasoline engine, with a micro-DefGen; it basically ran on water, provided 165% horsepower compared to a gas engine, and got 65 miles to the gallon. The major exhaust of the engine was water vapor, with other gases mixed in. No harmful or noxious fumes or byproducts. A 16-gallon tank would go 1000+ miles between fill-ups. Joshua tested it on his personal car. Originally bought on his company's first anniversary, it was a classic 1999 Lamborghini. After modifying it with a 4-liter V8 replacing the original 6.0 V12 (to make room for the micro-DefGen), it was still able to reach 223 MPH and now got 65 mpg! He had been testing the car now for 2 months, constantly tweaking, adjusting and improving the design and computer calibrations. He felt he was ready to publicly release his invention. Joshua was currently documenting his latest tests and what changes it had created. He was also recording the ideal settings he had determined and all the related information. This was an important step, since it was how he organized his thoughts and findings in preparation for the formal application. Joshua stopped typing and reread what he had written. This journal allowed him to review the past and see if he was thinking objectively and correctly. For the past several days, he had been feeling like he was being watched. There was nothing that he could prove, or even put his finger on, just a feeling at the base of his skull. Joshua was not a paranoid individual. He was sarcastic, jaded and disillusioned with corporate America, but not paranoid. In the next few weeks, that would change.   

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     The Present    Joshua couldn't believe the world he had grown up was a fake. He had lived 37 years and never seen the clues.&nbsp; To the best of his knowledge, no one ever saw the clues. As he stopped to catch his breath, he thought back to how he had gotten pulled into this mess.     The Past, Six Months ago    Leaning back in his favorite chair, Joshua continued typing. He had started keeping a journal about a year after he finished college. It wasn't a diary. He didn't end each day by ritualistically writing down what had happened to him. It was a journal of the important things in his life. A way to look back and be able to see when something happened and, years later, remember his initial thoughts before the jaded curtain of time colored his vision of those events.  He started the journal for a very simple reason. The pace of life in the corporate world was so fast that if he did not take time to write down the important things, he felt like he was forever swimming upstream against an ever-increasing load of priorities and activities. It was a way to decompress. It wasn't a regular activity, more like a release valve when something big, memorable or inundating happened. Joshua had found that taking a few minutes every week or so to sort out his thoughts and decide what was important and what was just distraction helped him focus.   But even that had not helped him be able to stomach the constant infighting and maneuvering that the executives within General Dynamics were preoccupied with. As a Research and Development engineer, he was hired to help GD develop new technologies to, as their ad campaign preached, "better the human condition." The company's public face was a humanitarian company that was constantly trying to make life better and easier for everyone. Behind the concrete and steel walls, the company was concerned with developing new technology that entranced their current and prospective customers. The biggest question was "How much can we charge without the public realizing their being overcharged?" The main driving force behind technology was to be the first with a new product. That allowed you to charge any amount imaginable for about 9 months. That was when the competitors came out with their versions and started the price wars. Once that point was reached, any additional models sold were gravy. The profit was in the first 9 to 12 months. After that, it was on to the next big thing. If too big of an improvement was made, the standard response was to back it up a notch, release a lesser version, and then, right before the competition released their models, pop out the original design as the "New and Improved" model. That way you got 18 to 24 moths out of a single new product.   Joshua had become disillusioned within the first year. After five more years trying to climb the corporate ladder by his intellect and creativity, he realized that duplicity; plagiarism and pure, unadulterated ruthlessness were the only way to move up in the company. Joshua had generated 15 new patents during his time with General Dynamics. He had considered leaving to work for another company. When he reviewed the other companies he would be interested in, he found that their organizations were structured and ran the same way.   Joshua was a quiet person who tended to think before saying anything. He was rarely the first to say anything. Not for lack of ideas, but because he saw very quickly that saying something too soon let others take your ideas and claim them as their own. This reticence made it easier for him to document and get credit for his actions, but distanced him from the rest of the engineers and staff in General Dynamics. The only person he really got to know was Brad Whisterly. Brad worked in the accounting department and had been hired the same week as Joshua. They had attended orientation together and Brad, who had a very outgoing personality, had struck up a conversation. Where others felt Joshua's short, direct answers were attempts to prevent dialogue, Brad simply accepted it as Joshua's personality and made up the difference by talking even more. Joshua found himself becoming comfortable around Brad. They become friends and frequently saw the latest films, worked on Brad's 1969 Camaro, and generally hung out together. Brad was an outgoing person who frequented the latest clubs and always knew where the best parties were. Joshua had gone with him once, but had left early, bored with the constant noise and activity. That might have offended others, but Brad never even blinked.  It was Brad who, over a few beers on a mild Saturday afternoon, had told Joshua that General Dynamics had made F500,000,000 on his first patent in the first 8 months. Joshua had been told by his supervisor that it had been a mild accent and had stated that his annual bonus, which was 1% the profit GD made on any patents he generated for them, would possibly see as much as F2,000 for that one. That had been the year the United States and the rest of North America joined the European Economic Union, which was subsequently renamed the Economic Union. The change resulted in all member countries converting to Economic Union Dollars, or EUs. At first glance, Joshua felt like he had gotten a pay cut. After all prices had been adjusted, he realized that the entire country had lost. The newscasts announced the change as a benefit, allowing free trade without currency conversion between the member nations. But the prices for items in England, Germany, or Australia were half that in the US. Canada had joined the year before and where they had once been more expensive than the US, prices on books and other joint produced products showed Canadians could buy 20% cheaper than their American neighbors. Politicians had praised the move, saying it would end the economic sanctions and import/export tax wars that had existed. The public at large, dazed by the change in prices, payrolls and having to learn a new monetary system; grumbled, but for the most part accepted the move.   

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Disclaimer:   This is a work of fiction. The names, places, companies and all other entities named or described in this are purely the creation of the author and any resemblance to authentic entities, whether living or non, is purely coincidental.  I want to make sure everyone who reads this understands this point.&nbsp; No one mentioned in this book is real. Anyone who might be real has had their names changed, faces remodeled, and entire credit history changed so that no one will take the information as it is written as being true.  If what I have written here were true, it would never have made it to print. So this must be fiction. Somewhere, someone looked at information freely available to any who look, realized many unrelated topics could potentially be explained. Is this the right explanation? No. If it were, you would never be able to read it. This is a work of fiction. A mere mental game of the author playing "What if?"    

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This blog is not a normal one.   I am a big fan of Science Fiction and have wanted to write for years.&nbsp; This is my little hideaway to start writing and hopefully get some feedback and comments from any readers who might stumble across my humble efforts.    If anyone sees anything they like, dislike or just want to comment about my storyline or style, please feel free to do so!   Thanks!    Mike Piper     

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The next morning, Joshua logged onto the WorldEx website to check his package. Entering the tracking number, the screen displayed the various points the package had gone through. It had been checked in at San Antonio, Shipped to Austin by truck, then checked in at Austin. It had then been shipped by plane to Washington D.C. After that, there was no additional data. Pulling up the number to call, Joshua dialed and waited while it rang.  After the fourth ring, it was picked up.  "Hello, World Express. Can I help you?"  "Yes, I shipped a package yesterday. I just tried to track it online to confirm delivery, but it only shows it being loaded on a plane to Washington. There's nothing afterwards saying it was delivered."  "Sometimes the tracking list is too long for a single screen. Did you hit 'Next'?"  "There was no, 'Next.' It said 'Report complete'."  "Let me see. Can I have the tracking number?"  "Sure. G154WQ765-23."  "OK, just a moment while I pull that up. Hmm. You're right. It was loaded on the plane to Washington, but it was never checked in."  "So what happened?"  "Let me locate that plane and see if the rest of the shipment arrived. I haven't heard of anything happening."  A few seconds went by, Joshua paced back and forth, then grew absolutely still as he listened to whispered conversations on the phone. He couldn't make out much, but it seemed the WorldEx employee was asking his boss if anything unusual had happened. When the boss' voice responded with a questioning tone, the employee said something about a missing package. After a silence, Joshua heard the boss' voice state, "lost in transit."  "I'm sorry sir. But it seems your package was lost in transit. I can enter a trace on it and we can have the plane and Washington office double-check in case it stuck to another package. Is there anything else I can help you with?"  "No. I just want my package delivered. What about your guarantee?"  "That is what the trace is for. Once we complete the investigation and determine what happened, we can issue you a credit, or we can provide a reshipment at no charge."  "How long will this take?"  "I don't know sir. It should be less than a month."  "What?"  "Well, this was a simple shipment within the same country. So we only need to locate the same plane, have it double-checked and then have the Washington office do a thorough sweep to check in case it fell somewhere. I have already alerted Washington to check all current packages to make sure nothing is sticking together. I apologize for the delay, but at least we only have to check the one plane and office. If you had sent it to another country we would have at least two planes and three offices. Investigations like that can take 6 months sometimes."Shaking his head, Joshua hung up the phone. The money wasn't the important thing. He turned to his computer and printed the documents again. For the next hour, Joshua replayed the actions of yesterday and mailed a second overnight delivery, this time using UPS. Delivery was guaranteed by 10:00 Am the following morning.  At 9:30 AM the next morning, Joshua answered the doorbell to see a uniformed UPS delivery driver.  "We're returning this to you.  The address is incorrect. I have an extra label if you would like to correct the address. I can then take it and it will be delivered by tomorrow at 10:00 AM."Joshua took the envelope, left the delivery driver at the door and walked to his computer to pull up the Patent Office website and check the address. The zip code was off. It should be 20500 and his label showed 20050. He pulled the label off to put the new one on. As the label pulled up, a second label was ripped off with it. The second label was partially stuck to the envelope. The zip code showed 20500.  Joshua paused and stared at the labels. With a mental shake of his head, he quickly wrote the address down and stuck the new label on.  Then he gave the package back to the driver. The driver turned and walked back to his truck, the package tucked under his arm. As the truck drove off, Joshua felt sure this wouldn't work either.  Pacing back and forth in his living room, he decided to have a delivery service take care of it. Returning once again to his PDA, he found a delivery service named Face2Face. The subheading guaranteed face-to-face delivery, with no delivery left with anyone except the named recipient. This seemed a safer way to do this. It was a privately owned company operating out of Texas, but willing to do any deliveries within the continental US. Setting up his printer to make another run, he dialed the delivery service and scheduled a pickup. An hour later, the package was on its way under the watchful eye of a bonded and certified currier.  

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Ch 2   At 7:00 AM, after a quick breakfast, Joshua sat down at his computer and filled out the application for a patent from the U S Patent Office. He printed out the application, diagrams, specifications and supporting documents. He placed them all in a manila envelope and wrote his own address on it. He would mail this later today. His lawyer had suggested this as an additional protection. Having a sealed, stamped envelope that can be opened in court proving when something was mailed was a very good way to determine who was first if multiple inventors were ever involved in a court battle over who owned the patent.  Once that was done, he accessed the U S Patent Office website, clicked on the application tab and uploaded all the documents onto the website to be emailed to the acceptance office. Once the 'Email Sent' message displayed, he picked up the manila envelope and walked outside for the drive to the post office. The drive, at 8:30, was leisurely, since he had no appointments for the rest of the day. Other cars drove by, furiously racing to get to their destinations on time. This was one of Joshua's favorite things about owning his own company. No time clock to punch and no one to answer to if he took the day off.  Arriving back home, he picked up the newspaper and walked in the front door. He sat down and started to read the paper. Looking at the clock, which read 10:30, two hours after he sent in the application, he got up and walked over to the computer. He opened his email to check for a delivery confirmation of the application. Among the load of junk email and newsletter subscriptions, a delivery error email was the only unusual email. Frowning, since he hadn't sent any emails in a few days, he sat down and opened the email. The message stated the email to the U S Patent Office had been undeliverable due to a virus in the contents.  Joshua's eyebrows rose, since he ritualistically updated his software weekly. It was almost impossible to get a virus and not know it within a day or two. He pulled up the anti-virus website and downloaded the latest update, installed it and ran it. The scan showed his PC was clean. Doing a search, he located two other brands, purchased the download versions. After installing them, he ran first one, then the other. Both came back and showed his computer was clean. Either the virus was one that had just come up and wasn't known, or the virus was from somewhere else. Guessing that the Patent Office web server might be the culprit, he opened a new email directly in his email program and attached all the documents. He manually entered the email address for applications and sent it. It was just after 11:00.  Brows furrowed, Joshua walked back to the couch, picked up the paper and flopped down to read and wait.  At 12:30, Joshua put down the paper, checked his email, which was still empty, and left to eat lunch. Stopping at a burger joint around the corner, Joshua sat down, and ordered iced tea and a Bacon burger from the waitress who appeared before he had even settled in. She set down his iced tea and left to turn in the order.  The TV playing in the corner caught his attention while he was waiting. It was the headline news stories running through the daily list of local wars in third world countries, recent election results in several European countries and the latest murders and missing people. Joshua was on the verge of looking away when a new report came on. A reported was talking about the leader of the Republican Party in Germany who was missing. He had been scheduled to appear for a press conference and had not showed up. His staff was unavailable to comment.  His burger arrived and he began devouring it, enjoying the heat and fresh tastes. The news report ran through his mind. Every sop often, you hear about someone important going missing. But while its news, they never seem to care to report the outcome. Was he located, dead, missing, or sick? No one ever came back and filled in the blanks. News was about attracting attention, not actually giving answers.  Finishing up his lunch, Joshua paid, got in his car and drove home. When he walked in, the first thing he did was check his email. Once again an email was waiting for him stating the email could not be delivered due to a virus. Muttering sarcastic comments about technology and helping humanity, Joshua printed out the documents again. Once they were all complete, he collected the stack of documents and left the house. Walking over to his still-warm car, he sat down and started the engine. He started to pull out, but stopped, slammed the car into neutral and pulled out his PDA. Doing a search in the yellow pages, he located the closest WorldEx office. Putting the car into gear, he left his neighborhood on the way to WorldEx.  Pulling into the WorldEx Parking lot, he glanced at the company logo as he found a parking slot. It was the same purple and orange logo it had been before they became a worldwide company. He climbed out of the car and walked into the building. Grabbing a large flat cardboard envelope, he slid in the papers and folded the top closed. He stopped at the address desk and used the chained pen to write the address for the patent office, as it was listed in the yellow pages on his PDA. He walked over to the clerk and handed his package over. The clerk weighed it, told him it was F21.75 for guaranteed overnight delivery with confirmation. Joshua waved his credit key over the paypad and then placed his thumb on the indention. Once the paypad light flashed green, the clerk looked up from his monitor, smiled and said, "have a nice day." Joshua turned and, walking past the others in line, walked out to his car.  Irritated by the extra work and delay in the application, Joshua drove quickly back home. Instead of a leisurely drive, he pulled in and out of lanes, quickly sliding right or left, irritated with the slower traffic. Arriving home, still full of frustrated energy, he walked into the house and turned left into his workout room. Still in Dockers and a Polo shirt, he started chain-punching the heavy bag. As the bag swung back and forth from the force of his blows, he stepped forward just enough to slowly work the bag up until it was horizontal, held up by the chain on one end and his pistonning fists at the other. After 10 minutes of this, Joshua was drenched in sweat and his normal ambivalent mood had returned. He backed up a step at a time, never slowing his punches, until the bag was once again hanging vertical. Finally stopping his punches, Joshua placed his hand against the bag to still it's swinging and then walked out to take a shower and change.  

						
</post>


<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have been watching the DNC in Boston and I’ve seen good and bad.&nbsp; It doesn’t really matter; but what I did notice is all of the “politicizing”.&nbsp; Even the responses from the other side fits into a&nbsp;very calculated&nbsp;context.&nbsp; They have a strategy and it is reflected in what they say.&nbsp; That’s ok for THEM.&nbsp; As a citizen, it’s not ok for me or you.&nbsp; They are trying to sway votes and take back the white house; we are trying to verbalize what we believe.&nbsp; Being “liberal” or a democrat means you believe in a specific ideology or way&nbsp;to accomplish a better America for us and future generations.&nbsp; It means more to me and, hopefully you, than just a speech or an argument.&nbsp; It’s a belief system that impacts our choices, our votes and our future.&nbsp; Take it seriously.   It is not good enough to repeat what you hear from Bill Clinton (even though I thought his speech was masterful)  It is not good enough to read every liberal book by Al Frankin or James Carville  It is not good enough to call someone stupid (even if they are)  It is not good enough to despise the stranglehold that the conservative right has on the media and the government   You MUST know why you believe in what you do.&nbsp; Here’s what I suggest to get liberals into the arena with more ammo than you can possibly need in a conversation:    Watch and listen to the other side:    It is not good enough to think you are right; you must also know why the opposite side isn’t.&nbsp; You should be as versed in their logic as they are, with the addition of research and true facts.&nbsp; Watch Bill O’reilly, listen to Rush Limbaugh, and if you can stomach it, watch Colmes get man handled by Hannity.&nbsp; No matter which you do, you’ll start to notice a pattern.&nbsp; To varying degrees they say the same thing because they are organized and share ammo (also known as talking points).&nbsp; By watching or listening, you are prepared for the next discussion.&nbsp; You know what they are going to say and you already know how to address it.    Articulate:    Find a way to explain your beliefs in plain English.&nbsp; I’m not suggesting dumbing anything down, nor am I suggesting that we script our answers.&nbsp; However, if your logic is sound and your beliefs are right then you should be able to explain them in a fashion that anyone can understand.&nbsp;     Drop the name-calling:    Calling the other side names and getting furious only proves, in their twisted logic, that we are all crazy/America hating whackos.&nbsp; We aren’t.&nbsp; Approach a discussion as if all parties are generally good people and want what’s best for America.&nbsp; We just disagree how to accomplish it.&nbsp; You should be able to shake hands and, at minimum, agree to disagree.&nbsp; Humanize your side.&nbsp; Your example will dispel the pabulum that they are being force fed about us.&nbsp; Meet them as equals, your message will be more palatable.    Pay attention:    Half of democrats think the media has a liberal bias.&nbsp; WHHHHAAAAAT bias?&nbsp; Liberals inherently believe in the system and fight to keep it fair/without bias.&nbsp; But the other side is organized and right leaning things tend to creep into your head when you’re not looking.&nbsp; By acknowledging a liberal bias, as 50% of democrats have, we have already lost.&nbsp; This pushes people to obviously right tainted news because they don’t want to be influenced by a “bias”.&nbsp; All because the other side screamed fowl for so long, that it had to be true.&nbsp; It’s not (a side note: even if all journalists were liberal, studies have proven that most editors and producers, who have the final say on what goes out, is predominantly conservative).&nbsp; Pay attention to what your being fed.&nbsp; Don’t let things seep in.&nbsp;    Here’s a funny example.&nbsp; I was watching the coverage of Lance Armstrong’s victory.&nbsp; Everyone was hailing it and talking about its impact.&nbsp; I watched two local channels, ESPN, ESPN 2 and Fox Sports at various times.&nbsp; None mentioned anything political, EXCEPT Fox Sports.&nbsp; Fox Sports highlighted that Crow was at the finish line, as did everyone, but also had to throw this in “Lance received a call from George Bush, and he had time to wish President Bush luck on his re-election campaign…”&nbsp; No other channel saw this as news, if it was even true.&nbsp; If I were objective, I would say that he got a congratulations call from the President and a commentator threw in some speculation.&nbsp; No harm, no foul.&nbsp; If I wasn’t paying attention, I wouldn’t have even noticed it, but its impact would have seeped in as it probably did with one or two people.     Don’t engage with a spoon fed conservative/republican:    You can’t win, it’s pointless.&nbsp; Anyone who’s only political knowledge is fed to them by a daily dose of Rush is unreachable;&nbsp;all they want is to hear why they are right.&nbsp; I know this sounds harsh and these people are the exact people that need the discourse the most, but you will waist your time and make an enemy.&nbsp; It’s like a drug addiction; you have to want to be cured to start the road to rehab.&nbsp; It would be like trying to change Ann Coulter’s mind.&nbsp; It just isn’t happening.&nbsp; Enter the arena with someone who is willing to at least entertain the waves of sound coming out of your mouth.    Don’t engage in pat session:&nbsp;   A pat session is where a bunch of like minded people sit around and talk about why they are right and pat each other on the back for being so.&nbsp; Rush is a pat session.&nbsp; People listen to reaffirm why they are right not to analyze and judge for themselves.&nbsp; You look pampas and only help yourself and hurt the cause when you do this.&nbsp;     Welcome the discourse:    You should be willing and prepared to engage a republican or conservative at any time.&nbsp; If I were a radio talk show host, I wouldn’t let a liberal call in.&nbsp; I don’t want to hear that I’m right.&nbsp; I don’t want to hear an argument for my side.&nbsp; I want to hear the other side and let them try and prove their case.&nbsp; Bottom line is that if you put the issues and compare them to the average American, most are moderate to liberal and most are democrat.&nbsp; We are losing to word association.&nbsp; Liberal is bad.&nbsp; Look at Newt’s list of words that should be used against your opponents (traitor for example).&nbsp; They’ve taken psychology and used it to convince people they are conservative.&nbsp; Dispel the myth with fact and good conversation.   &nbsp; Be open minded:    Kerry gets blasted for “changing his mind” or flip-flopping.&nbsp; Recognizing when you made a mistake or when someone presents a better solution is not a flaw, it’s a strength.&nbsp; Admitting when you’re wrong and trying to fix it is one of the hardest things to do in life but it is also one fo the most worthwhile endeavors.&nbsp; When you converse, be willing to listen to the opposite side.&nbsp; At least gain an understanding of why that person thinks the way they do.&nbsp; If you aren’t receptive, how can you expect the person you are engaging to be.&nbsp; I’m not saying adopt their point of view, but at least be willing to listen and don’t formulate a response until they are done talking.&nbsp; If you are prepared, you won’t need to.  I’m proud of being liberal and I know why I am.&nbsp;   Stay tuned for more declarations in my “manifesto”.    Hollow1ne     
    
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have decided to use the about portion of this page to highlight comments on this blog.&nbsp; So I will be transferring old "about" posts to the blog section as I update it.&nbsp; Below is the first description of this blog:   This blog is an addendum to    stream of consciousness(a friend of mine)   .&nbsp; It is where I intend to write a manifesto for liberals and progressives on how to change the level of discourse in this country.&nbsp; How to get angry the right way.&nbsp; How to level the playing field and dispel the pabulum that is being fed to us by certain ideologues.&nbsp; I encourage honest debate, whether you agree or not.&nbsp; Just don’t throw spoon fed regurgitation.&nbsp; Know why you believe what you do and be able to defend it.&nbsp; I hope a true conversation can be achieved rather than the back and forth yelling that I see and hear daily.&nbsp; Welcome.    
    
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is the first of what I hope to many posts.&nbsp; This is my test of the blog service.&nbsp; I will begin posting in a few days as I gather my thoughts and decide the order in which to address things.&nbsp; I have way too much on my mind and not enough time in the day.&nbsp; A little about me:   32 year old liberal democrat  I live in San Antonio, Texas  I'm working on my Master's degree in Education  I'm working for a major energy corporation   If you read this, drop me a line.&nbsp; I choose not to put any limitations on posts as of now, so have at it.&nbsp; Thanks for the visit.  DBL.  
    
    
</post>


<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I like Rush Limbaugh's logic.  A few days ago, in response to a caller saying that no solid ties showed Iraq was connected to Al Queda, Rush had a brilliant piece of logic.  It went something like this: "Okay, so Al Queda wasn't in Iraq.&nbsp; But we have solid evidence it was in Iran, Syrria, Afghanistan, Pakistan, Kuwait, Yemen, Germany, France, Florida, and basically every other location in the world EXCEPT Iraq." "No, Al Queda was in Iraq and for that reason we had to take out the people who supported and allowed them to be there."  HMMM. . .  By that logic, we should also attack Iran, Pakistan, France and Florida. Why did we single out Iraq if the reason we attacked was they had Al Queda in their borders? I thought it was for the Weapons of Mass Distraction (uh, Destruction) that Saddam had. Did we ever find those by the way??  I think we need tighter security to prevent a reoccurance of 9/11. But I think we should focus on home and not divert attention away from our borders.  A quote from the Bible says to remove the log from your own eye before you try to remove the speck from your neighbors eye.&nbsp; Maybe we should listen to that advice and clean up our act before worrying about others.  Laters!  Mike 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      G.W.Bush has been reported as stonewalling the report.  Why would the President who said we needed to attack Afganistan and Iraq to overthrough the axis of evil not want a report to come out that should tell us what went wrong and then how to correct it?   Also, On a side note,   why does the Iraq war look like a sequal to " Wag the Dog ." Bush was low in the polls. 9/11 and Bush's response against Afganistan causes polls to rise.&nbsp; BinLaden gets away and the polls fall.&nbsp; So we attack another country and Bush's polls rise.&nbsp; Now Bush is low in the polls again.  What is my prediction? Bin Laden is already captured and he will be "announced" as captured about 3 weeks before the election.&nbsp; That way his ratings will rise just in time for the election.  I think Bush is using "Wag the Dog" as his playbook.  Thoughts anyone????  Mike 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I listen to Rush.  Not because I like what he says, but because he is so audacious in his delivery of half truths and inaccurate facts.  Rush claims to be right 98.2% of the time.&nbsp; Well, considering he is a right-winger, I think it is more like 100%.&nbsp; But as far as being right on his statements, he once stated he was right 98.2 % based on a listener opinion poll by an independant poll.&nbsp; Hmm, if his audience thinks he is right 98% of the time, what does that have to do with actually being correct with his facts? A huge number of people thought the earth was flat at one time. Did the number of those who believed it make it true?  I do like some of his information though.&nbsp; A few weeks back, he was talking about a group of research scientists who used a computer model of the current economic and environmental, blah, blah, blah, statistics to predict the winner of each presidential race. Rush stated they had been doing this since the early 80's and had been correct every time except the 2000 election, when they had predicted Gore would win by 58 to 62% of the vote.&nbsp; HMM!&nbsp; The only election in their history is the only one that was decided by the supreme court?&nbsp; Seems to me they were right then too, but no one knew it.  By the way, Rush says that the Florida election was and still is a stupid arguement for the Democrats because the counties in question had the voting run by Democrats. So the ones who disenfranchised the black and other voters were the same ones who are complaining.  I wish Rush would check into a little more about their claims.&nbsp; The claim is based on the fact that many Florida does not allow convicted felons to vote, and a list was compiled of all felons, and all those whose names were similar (just in case of spelling errors I guess) and sent them letters stating their voting rights had been suspended.&nbsp; So, even though the Dems controlled the voting, the right eliminated a large number of potential voters.&nbsp; I have also heard (*don't know the facts on this) that Florida law specifies the felons had to be florida or federal convictions, and other states did not matter.&nbsp; Seems Texas (Bush was in charge at the time) and several other states provided Florida with lists of ex-residents that could be added to the list of those not qualified to vote.&nbsp; If an ex-Texas resident moved to Florida to get a new start, planned on voting, got a letter saying they could not due to previous convictions, what would be the chance they would know Florida law well enough to know they could still vote?  I suspect this is part 1 in an ongoing series of rants about Rush.  By the way, is "issue" pronounced "is- sue" in any state of the union? Or "schedule" as "shedule?"&nbsp; My opinion? I think Rush is putting on airs and doesn't know he sounds like he doesn't know proper english or enunciation.  Laters, Mike 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In the recent years, I have become more and more convinced that we are being decieved.   I don't think that most of what we are told in the news is accurate.&nbsp; Not that we are being lied to by the journalists or reporters.&nbsp; I think they, for the most part are innocent victoms just like us.   I think that there are those who have specific goals and agendas and they are editing and altering the facts that they present to us.&nbsp; Conspiracy?&nbsp; No just egocentric individuals. I think.  Here are a few examples:      Weapons in Iraq.  Are there any?&nbsp; Were there any? Or was this exagerrated and altered to help foster support for the war?   G. W. Bush won the 2000 Election.  Did G. W. Bush win in the actual vote? If the electoral college is the actual electoral device, why have the public vote at all?&nbsp; Technically, the college can vote any way they want.&nbsp; It is only tradition that says the votes go according to popular votes. Can the Supreme court rule on a Presidential election?   Televangelists.  Almost every televangelist promotes God, but seems more interested in talking hellfire and brimstone than helping people become more like Jesus Christ. Jesus only spoke in a negative or angry tone once, which was with the moneychangers.&nbsp; All the rest was about love, caring and being truthful and forgiving. Why don't the televangelists' sermons match Jesus' ratio of love versus anger?   Nixon was the first to make illegal recordings.  When was the first tape recorder invented? Nixon was the first to ever use it?&nbsp; Really? Was Nixon right? No, but should he have been treated the way he was? I don't know. Just a question.   Testing will improve our schools.  I believe testing can validate someone's learning, but having required tests without improving the actual materials and school methods seems ludicrous.&nbsp; If I fail a test on Monday, will taking it again Tuesday make me score higher? If I fail, shouldn't I get something different in the way of education before I test again?   More to come.  I just wanted to start a few thoughts. I don't have any clear plans, yet, just a need to start.   They say a journey of a thousand miles start with the first step. This is my first step. Let's see where it leads. . .  Mike 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Now they are after their most outspoken opponent, Michael Moore.  There is a new book out I saw at Barnes & Nobles the other day. I picked it up and started leafing through it. Titled " Michael Moore Is A Big Fat Stupid White Man " and illustrated on the cover in his style, it is a gross attack on his character, his facts, and anything else they can think of.  First, they attack his character and work history. What's funny is they act like it is a big secret and it should determine that the facts he presents are not true just because he didn't follow a traditional work pattern.  While he does not trumpet it, M.M. has freely admitted he was fired by Ralph Nader because he was working on another project at the same time. He has also detailed his employment history, so it's really no surprise, except they ignore the successes and highlight his failures.  Actually failures puts M.M. in fairly good company.  Look up the history of some of our most famous president's (like Abe Lincoln) and you'll quickly learn that failure only matters if it takes ypou down with it.  Failing and washing out are commonplace and lead to successes if the person is persistent.  I think it is a testament to M.M.'s tenacity and desire for reaching his desires and goals that he did not sit down and conform to the desires of others.  Back to the book. Another topic they attack are his facts in his books.  One that stood out because I had just read the chapter they were attacking was about the budget of 250+ Billion dollars building a single plane.  M.M. states clearly this is a multi-year budget and if the funding were stopped in 2003/2004, the remaining budget would pay for a college education for every student in America (a possible exageration, but the point is valid). The authors of the anti-M.M. book act like he presented this as a single year's budget for a single physical airplane.  This is not what he says.  He explains it is multi-year and for a fleet of a single MODEL of aircraft.  This book is the easiest example I have found yet that shows the lengths and extremes the Right will go to to put a spin and raise the noise level in their quest to destroy all who oppose them.  The interesting thing is M.M. has an entire section in the back of each of his books that states where and when he got his information.  They found one examplke where he used only a single report from a liberal source as an example of how he does not researcjh his facts properly.  Too bad they only had to look one item above or below their example to see others that were supplied with multiple sources.  Anyway, enough ranting and raving for tonight.  Kerry/Edwards 2004! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Will Ferrell - A message from White House West   Here is a new item I found today.  I plan to ask each and every person I know to see it. What is scary is that Will Ferell isn't half as good at acting lost as the "real" person he is impersonating.  See it today!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>