<Blog>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I finally received my copy of The Used on cd, purchased through ebay.&nbsp; Copied it onto my xbox, onto my computer, burned a copy.&nbsp; Then back on ebay it went.&nbsp; Seriously, why does anyone keep cd's anymore? By the way, the band is very good, if you're into their sound.&nbsp; Kind of a mix between punk and metal.&nbsp; Nifty. After the burning and the auctioning, it was time for the Thursday Night Routine.&nbsp; The TNR consists of playing an assload of hockey on my NHL2004 dynasty and drinking beer, smokin' smokes.&nbsp; To those that don't know, I don't smoke from Sunday to Thursday, as it affects my hockey playin' on Monday and Wednesday.&nbsp; Some people don't believe it, or don't know how I can do it.&nbsp; Meh, I just don't have a very high addictivity quotient I guess. Also composed a rebuttle to a dumbass who likes to write in my local paper. Here's the link:&nbsp;  urlLink http://www.kpcnews.com/main.asp?SectionID=11&SubSectionID=57&amp;ArticleID=72614  Its your usual "liberal Media" blather written by an old fellow who not only composes this sort of thing, but hands it in to the newspaper.&nbsp; Got that?&nbsp; Hands it in.&nbsp; Doesn't mail it, doesn't email it.&nbsp; Nope, drives into town to hand it in. Coot. 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Didn't see this one coming...   First thing this morning, one of the machine operators on the floor comes into my office and hands me a printout of an email they received.&nbsp; It would seem that this particular email struck a nerve for her, and I guess she thought I would like it.&nbsp; I wasn't rude enough to say that I look down on pretty much anybody who feels the need to print out their emails, and instead told her I'd read it later.&nbsp;  Now, if she'd sent (sent!&nbsp; not printed out and handed!) the email to me a couple of years ago, perhaps I would've responded a little better.&nbsp; Perhaps.&nbsp; Because since the first time this email crossed my path, it has returned countless times by family members who are taken by it on first reading, or by co-workers who've been duped as well.&nbsp; So to have it handed to me (argh!) today is perhaps pushing me a bit over the edge.  I&nbsp;had discussed political issues with this lady, Dawn, at a christmas gathering at the Angola VFW Post.&nbsp; We pretty much agree on the same basic tenets, which is why I got the email.&nbsp; Well.&nbsp; I guess I should have clarified some things, because this is not indicative of the way I think or feel in the slightest.&nbsp; Pfft!&nbsp; Not at all!  Well here it is, i'm sure you've all read it before:   --------------------------------------   Bet you stand up and say HELL YEAH!After you read this.     &nbsp;   I like big cars, big boats, big motorcycles, big houses and big campfires I believe the money I make belongs to me and my family, not some governmental stooge with a bad comb-over who wants to give it away to crack addicts for squirting out babies. Guns do not make you a killer. I think killing makes you a killer. You can kill someone with a baseball bat or a car, but no one is trying to ban you from driving to the ball game. I believe they are called the Boy Scouts for a reason, that is why there are no girls allowed. Girls belong in the Girl Scouts!     &nbsp;   I think that if you feel homosexuality is wrong, it is not a phobia it is an opinion. I don't think being a minority makes you a victim of anything except numbers.     &nbsp;   The only things I can think of that are truly discriminatory are things like the United Negro College Fund, Jet Magazine, Black Entertainment Television, and Miss Black America. Try to have things like the United Caucasian College Fund, Cloud Magazine, White Entertainment Television, or Miss White America and see what happens. Jesse Jackson will be knocking down your door.     &nbsp;   I have the right "NOT" to be tolerant of others because they are different, weird, or tick me off. When 70% of the people who get arrested are black, in cities where 70% of the population is black, that is not racial profiling, it is the law of statistics.     &nbsp;   I know what sex is, and there are not varying degrees of it. If I received sex from one of my subordinates in my office, it wouldn't be a private matter or my personal business. It would be "FIRED" immediately!     &nbsp;   I believe that if you are selling me a milk shake, a pack of cigarettes, a newspaper or a hotel room, you must do it in English! As a matter of fact, if you want to be an American citizen you should have to speak English! My father and grandfather should not have died in vain so you can leave the countries you were born in to come over and disrespect ours.     &nbsp;   I think the police should have every right to shoot your sorry ass if you threaten them after they tell you to stop. If you can't understand the word "freeze" or "stop" in English, see the above lines.     &nbsp;   I feel much safer letting a machine with no political affiliation recount votes when needed. I know what the definition of lying is.     &nbsp;   I don't think just because you were not born in this country, you are qualified for any special loan programs, government sponsored bank loans or tax breaks, etc., so you can open a hotel, coffee shop, trinket store, or any other business. We did not go to the aid of certain foreign countries and risk our lives in wars to defend their freedoms so that decades later they could come over here and tell us our constitution is a living document and open to their interpretations.     &nbsp;   I don't hate the rich I don't pity the poor. I know wrestling is fake, but so are movies and television, and that doesn't stop you from watching them.     &nbsp;   I believe a self-righteous liberal or conservative with a cause is more dangerous than a Hell's Angel with an attitude.     &nbsp;   I think Bill Gates has every right to keep every penny he made and continue to make more. If it ticks you off, go and invent the next operating system that's better and put your name on the building.     &nbsp;   Ask your buddy that invented the Internet to help you.     &nbsp;   It doesn't take a whole village to raise a child right, but it does take a parent to stand up to the kid and smack his/her little ass when necessary and say,"NO"!     &nbsp;   I think tattoos and piercing are fine if you want them, but please don't pretend they are a political statement. And please stay home until that new lip ring heals, I don't want to look at your ugly infected mouth as you serve me French fries!     &nbsp;   I am sick of "Political Correctness" and of all the suck ups that go along with it. I know a lot of black people, and not a single one of them was born in Africa, so how can they be "African Americans"?     &nbsp;   Besides, Africa is a continent. I don't go around saying I am a European American because my great, great, great, great, great, great Grandfather was from Europe. I am proud to be from America and nowhere else.     &nbsp;   And if you don't like my point of view, tough! GET OVER IT!!! WAKE-UP WHILE YOU STILL HAVE A COUNTRY TO WAKE UP TO!!If you are not ashamed of America, forward this to everyone in your address book while you can still do it for free!"In God We Trust" If you don't like it in the schools, DON'T SPEND MONEY!!THAT'S A BIG HELL YEAH!!!!--end E-mail--     &nbsp;  -----------------------------------------------------   Okay, American pride is one thing, but this is just stupid.&nbsp; Let me count the ways:   1.&nbsp; Welfare only goes to crack addicts who pump out babies.  2.&nbsp; Catering to the black culture is actually discriminatory.  3.&nbsp; There are cities where 70% of the population is black.  4.&nbsp; Bill Clinton should have been removed from office for receiving oral sex,  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;because being president of the United States is just like any other job.  5.&nbsp; No one should be allowed into America until they learn to speak English.  6.&nbsp; Not knowing English in America is disrespectful.  7.&nbsp; The police are always right.  8.&nbsp; Only natural born Americans should have access to federal aid.  9.&nbsp; Politically Correct speech is unnecessary.   *sigh*&nbsp;   &nbsp;   
    
</post>


</Blog>