<Blog>


<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I still cannot decide which schools to apply to and which to drop from my list. This might be a little wacky, but I am going to list all the schools that I was thinking about applying to and my percentage of getting in based on numbers alone... Hopefully when I see them all listed, I will be able to see how pathetic it is that I am holding on to schools that I have like no chance of ever getting into.   I guess I am just too stubborn to accept the fact that there are some schools I am just not going to get into, no matter what I do. But, I cannot help but believe in miracles. I keep telling myself that I am unique enough and have a good enough package to get accepted at some of the places where it looks slim, but in actuality I am not so sure I have something so special that would make up for a low LSAT score.   Eh, you have to have faith in something, might as well be yourself right?  I know this is probably rambling, but I was in Atlantic City at a craps table the day I had to take my LSAT in June (I could not sleep, it must have been around 7:30 am.) The dealer starts up conversation with me as I waste away my money. He finds out I am taking the LSAT and that I am a little nervous because of my odds at most schools. He gave me the most wonderful lecture about having faith and confidence in myself, it related to gambling. It made perfect sense to me….   “If you are standing at the line and you have to place a bet, aren’t you going to bet on yourself to throw the dice the way you know you can!”   Then again...having faith in my dice throw in craps is quite different than having faith in the dismal looking percentages below :p  University of DC: 65%  Western New England School of Law: 64%  Widener: 64%  University of Dayton: 57%  New England School of Law: 54%  Roger Williams: 54%  Touro Law School: 54%  Albany Law School: 49%  Vermont Law School: 48%  North Carolina Central: 41%  Loyola New Orleans: 31%  Suffolk: 31%  Quinnipiac University: 30%  University of Baltimore: 30%  Syracuse: 28%  New York Law School: 28%  City University of NY (CUNY): 25%  Stetson: 23%  Duquesne University: 19%  Pace University: 17%  Southwestern School of Law: 12%  University of Buffalo: 11%  Penn State Dickinson School of Law: 10%  Catholic University 6%  Hofstra: 6%  Villa Nova: 8%  University of Pittsburgh:&nbsp; 5%  Rutgers: 3%  University of Maryland: 3%  Seton Hall: 3%  Temple University: 1%  Cardozo Law School: 1%  North Eastern: 1%St. John’s: 1%    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I found a really interesting (and disheartening) website that tells you the chance that you have of getting into a school based solely on numbers. It is  urlLink http://www.chiashu.com/lsat.html &nbsp;... lawschoolnumbers.com is also a good&nbsp;site that can kind of help put things into perspective, but you need to remember that the population on law school numbers is not representative of the entire applicant pool..so putting too much faith in what you find there could let you miss out on an opportunity   I do not know how much stock to put into the chiashu site because it is based on numerical factors alone....But it is an indication that I&nbsp;should probably think about dropping the schools that I have a .01% chance of getting into. I guess I am just holding on to the dream that some top of the line school will love me even though I do not have the&nbsp;LSAT score&nbsp;to make it in. I guess I need to burst my bubble and face reality. ~sigh~   Time to start narrowing this down. Application time is a month or so away and I want to have everything in order. I am going to pick my transcripts on Friday and get them out to LSAC. It is kind of exciting in a way, but I know once the applications are out, the suspense is going to kill me!   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, thankfully I got through all of the reading and papers that I needed to get through for Monday. Today, I should be able to get through the rest of my list of law schools and then&nbsp;start narrowing it down a bit. I would really rather not spend the $2,000 to apply to all the schools on the list, but if I have to I will.&nbsp;&nbsp;   I know that I will most likely wind up in a T3 or T4 school, but I am still going to apply to a few T2 (huge reaches) and see what happens. It only takes one school to look my application over and give me a chance. I am lucky when I am at the roulette tables, maybe I will have some luck here also! Hey... I can hope.   I recently found out that my boyfriends cousin graduated from one of my first choice schools, Seton Hall. He is good friends with the dean and said that he would see if he could pull some strings because of my low LSAT score.&nbsp; I think he might be able to put forth a compelling argument because he had a low LSAT score and had to go to a T4 first. He was at the top of his class and then he transferred into Seton Hall. He remained at the top of his class there and graduated in the top 10%. Since he had a low LSAT score and was able to do it, he might be able to parallel his experience to mine. I am really hoping that he can help me out. I know that I have what it takes to make it in school, I just need the chance. I also know someone else who might be willing to put in a good word at Seton Hall for me.   I know that I should not put much stock in knowing people and using them to put in a good word, but the world works on networking, so why not give it a try. I will still apply to a ton of other schools just in case it does not work.   It still kills me that I was unable to beat the LSAT. I just keep telling myself that&nbsp;if this is the only wall I have hit thus far, I am lucky. I have a lot to offer, it is just too bad that most schools will not even take the time to look at my package since my LSAT score is not in their range.&nbsp; Eh, this is just one of life's little challenges... I am sure I will wind up somewhere. :)     
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have such a busy weekend. I do not even know where to start. I want to try to finish finding out information about all of the schools that I want to apply to,&nbsp;but I just have so many other things to do. Hopefully I have time to do this, I really want to get a better feel for where I stand. I have a list of about 30 schools, and I would like to narrow it down so that it does not cost me $2,000. I guess if I can not narrow it down, I can always apply to them all, I do not expect to get accepted to most of them, in fact...I am pretty sure I would get waitlisted or declined from most. I just really want to ensure that I have options open, I would rather make a decision on where I go as opposed to being a slave to the only law school that accepts me. I wish I had a higher LSAT score, it would make this so much easier.   I read a ridiculous post from a T1 graduate about how she was having a hard time finding a job and she was at the top of her class so anyone in the bottom part of a T1 school or anyone in T2, T3, or T4 schools were not going to even get interviewed for a job. I found this absolutely asinine. Just because she has a problem getting a job, does not mean that all those other people will. There are a million reasons that she could be getting overlooked for a job (my speculation):  ~She did not pass the bar yet and firms do not want to invest in her.  ~There is a problem with her resume  ~She does not interview well  ~She is only applying for jobs in a select field, maybe she should broaden her horizons until she establishes herself  ~Maybe she is only applying in a certain area, and she needs to start applying farther away  ~Maybe her standards were to high.  ~Maybe she lacked work experience or maturity  ~Maybe she does not have good networking skills and that is hurting here  ...The list could go on an on....   I just can not believe that someone who just went through law school could make a post like that. I agree that the job market is rough and finding a job is hard, but to say anyone not in the top portion of a T1 is not going to get a job is ridiculous. There are a ton of lawyers from all different kinds of schools who get jobs. I think that the poster needed to feel better about herself by making a blanket statement like that. Too bad it only makes her look stupid...   On another note, I have two family birthday parties to go to this weekend, one for my cousin and one for my sisters godfather. On top of that I have to write a paper on freedom of speech for my media law independent study, and I have to write an analysis for my intercultural and diversity management class. Added to that is reading about 5 chapters in a very theory laden book for my class on Monday. I work full time and go to school full time at night, so I do not have a ton of time for me this weekend, but I will try to manage.   I am done ranting for the moment :)   &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Welcome to&nbsp;the law school hopeful blog. This is my first attempt at blogging and I&nbsp;think it is going to become somewhat therapeutic for me, and hopefully helpful to anyone wondering what it is like to go through the law school admission process. I know that at times I will probably ramble on and on, but at least&nbsp;I will be able to get my pent up aggression out.   I have been told that&nbsp;I am a traditional applicant, I suppose in some ways I am, but I am hoping that I am untraditional enough to get myself into a good school. I have already lowered my standards when I came to the realization that I was not going to get into a T1 school because my LSAT scores were &nbsp;just not going to&nbsp;cut it. Hell, I probably will not get into a T2 school either. I contemplated not going to law school at all, but that made me even more miserable. So here I am leading a life of uncertainty. I have no idea where I will wind up or even if I will wind up getting into law school at all.   I read somewhere that less than half of the people that apply to law school get in. That thought really freaked me out. I really hope that I am not going to be thrown into the percentage of people who do not make it into law school. Do not get me wrong, I think I have a great package, aside from my LSAT score, and I am sure that I will pull through and do fine, but so much rides on that stupid test that it makes me unsure of myself.     I have to admit deciding that I wanted to go to law school has been the most humbling experience of my life. I have never felt so unsure about myself and about my life as I feel now. I am sure that as I obsess over the application process this will get even worse.     &nbsp;   I just wish that I had something stable to depend on or fall back on. Well, I would be lieing if I said I had nothing to fall back on. I was a double major in college, I graduated with a really good GPA. I have a good job and I am almost done with my masters degree. If I do not get into law school I will be really upset and feel like a failure, but when push comes to shove, I am not really in that bad of shape. If I do not get into law school, I could always reevaluate and get my doctorate in communications or psychology. Let's just hope it does not come to that!         
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been pretty busy this week at work and at school. I just wanted to make a quick post about what I have going on.  School is winding down for the semester, it will be over on the 18th (which is also my birthday). I am going to make an effort to get out of class early, but I will have to see what we have going on. I know that I am going to go to Atlantic City with some of my friends the weekend after my birthday...I am not sure which day, we were talking about staying overnight, we will see though.... I love spending time playing craps and roulette. I have not been there in about a month and a half, I am going through withdrawl :p  I am also looking forward to having a few days off work, I am going to go to the poconos. That should be really fun, I can not wait to get some time to sleep in and sit at a pool. I know I am not going to want to go home!  I have to go to get another sonogram done tomorrow. Apparently, something was not done right and they need to get new pictures. I was somewhat annoyed when I got that phone call, but atleast they are erring on the side of caution.  My addendum for law school apps is done for the most part. I am not sure of it, but it is done. I just keep rereading it and second guessing myself. I am really afraid of sounding like I am discrediting the LSAT or making excuses. I have been looking for books or information on the proper way to write an addendum, and advice on writing them, but I have not been able to find anything. Maybe I will ask one of my professors to look at it.    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I had an extremely busy weekend.       I had the sonogram on Saturday. It did not go well. The technician was unable to get a picture of the lump. I guess I will have to go back to the doctor and tell her that I want a mamogram. I am so tired of taking the time to get sonograms that hardly ever work. I think that when they do not work,the technicians should automatically, just move a patient over and give them a mamogram. So what, I would pay $40 for the visit as opposed to $20. It would make life so much easier. But, what do insurance companies care that it would be easier on the patient, they just have all of their little quirky rules... and we just become slaves to the rules that the insurance companies give to our doctors.      Enough venting on that...      I also had the wedding to go to on Saturday. The ceremony was at 2:30 and the reception was at 6. The wedding was nice, they had great weather which was a plus. If it were my wedding, I would have had a few problems since the vows and the prayers they chose were very traditional and valued women as much as dirt. They really needed to get with the times a little and make the ceremony revolve around equality. At one point the groom said, "Give me the strength to support my family and to try to be there as much as possible for my wife and children..." Then her part went something like, "Give me the strength to be encouraging to my husband while he supports the family through hard times, and to always be there for my husband and children." I think that prayer imagines the wife barefoot in front of the kitchen sink. And then at the end they said, "You are now man and wife" no...you are husband and wife or man and woman. Not man's possession.      I know I can get hung up on semantics sometimes. I pity the priest who agrees to do my wedding, we will have to sit down and go over what is acceptable and inappropriate wording of the ceremony.       The reception was very nice. The bride and groom were so adorable together, they really fit one another and compliment one another. They really do make a wonderful couple. I felt so old after all of this was said and done. I kept imagining myself getting married and it gave me the chills because my first college friend got married. The first person my age that I know is now married and moving into a nice house and thinking about having kids. It blows my mind!      Sunday, my best friend came home from Greece for the summer. We spend Sunday running around and catching up. It was nice to see him again, I am surprised he did not come back with a Greek wife. Apparently while he was in Greece, he had three people serving his every need. He had massages every night before he went to bed, he had people cleaning up after him, and getting him anything he needed. He definitely came home a little lazy, but I quickly brought him back to reality when he asked me for a glass of water and I told him that he had hands that looked like they were in working order to me and that he knew where the glasses were. I guess all good things come to an end.      I have to go start a powerpoint presentation I need done for class tonight.      I am counting down the days till I take vacation. ~sigh~  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I receive a daily mailing in my email from law.com. They have really great articles for lawyers, people interested in law, current law cases and events, important happenings, and information about law school and law school life. If you are interested in law, I definitely suggest getting on the mailing list (it is free):   urlLink  http://store.law.com/registration/register.asp?subscribeto=nw     Anyway, there is a really interesting and funny article about two types of law students the gunners and the backbenchers, the link is below:   urlLink  http://www.law.com/jsp/article.jsp?id=1090180199000     I hate to admit that I am somewhat of a gunner. I think it comes with the territory of being an overachiever. I do not sit in the front row with hands waving, but i do interject my thoughts into the conversation from time to time. I am not extremely overzealous, but I never mind defending my opinion or bringing up an interesting thought...in fact, I kind of like to debate hot topics with my classmates...I do not know that I love hearing myself speak, but I can admit that I do not mind listening to myself :p   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       After work today, I went shopping and picked up a really nice dress for the wedding on Saturday. I bought it, but I liked 2 other ones a little more, so I am going to try to go to another Macy's on Thursday to see if they have the other 2 dresses in my size and return the one that I already bought.... Oh the wonders of being a woman. Sometimes there really is a method to our madness :)  Anyway, I am almost done writing a paper on Libel and Slander in media law. I am happy with it so far. I was going to finish it tonight, but I forgot to email myself the draft before I left work, so it will have to wait until tomorrow.  I can not wait to finish the paper because then I will have some time to whittle down my school list. I am tired of dicking around with this since September is around the corner and I have to have my shit together by then.  Oh, today I found out that there is a school in California called Cooley law school that you can get accepted into without finishing an undergrad degree. I thought that was insane. I do not think I would want to hire a lawyer who was unable to finish their undergrad before getting a JD. It seems a little shady to me. I can not imagine that a person who graduates from a school like that would get a very good job after school since the standards to get in were so low. You can check this out at:   urlLink  http://www.cooley.edu/admissions/admw_outba.htm     Enough for now...  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am having the most miserable weekend. I just hate everything about everything. I can not concentrate on anything. I have a paper due, and a test on Monday night, and I am so depressed that I can not even fathom picking up a book and trying to read through it.  I went to see a surgeon on Friday for a breast lump. It turned out that the original lump is just a cyst (apparently I am cystic because there were quite a few cysts) but as she did an exam, she found another lump that is not a cyst. She is not sure what it is and is concerned about it, so I have to go for a sonogram this week. I am too young to get a mammogram (you have to be 35), apparently they give off too much radiation and can cause breast cancer at young ages. It just seems ironic to me that a mammogram that detects cancer can cause cancer in young women, but almost everything causes cancer these days.    I just hope that this is nothing serious and it is not cancerous. I am really nervous about all of this.    Like that was not bad enough, the surgeon told me that I should have my physician take blood and run some tests because she thinks I could have a thyroid problem or some kind of hormonal imbalance that is causing the cysts. I really just do not need this right now. I do not like giving blood, I hate doctors, and quite frankly, I do not have time to run around to a million doctors to figure this entire ordeal out.     On top of all of this, I need to go to a wedding next weekend. I HATE shopping, but I had to go because I wanted to try to find something nice to wear. It is so hard being an overweight woman. I am not obese, I am just curvy, but it seems like in today’s world only skinny women get to wear clothing. I must have tried on 100 dresses. Either they only make things for tiny women so I looked like a stuffed pig or they make things that look like fucking tarps. Good god, I am not ready for the moo moo dress….I am not that overweight for god’s sake. Yes… I can stand to loose a few pounds, but who can’t. All I want is to feel good about myself and look nice. I have curves, I want to show them off, but no…I can not do that because pop culture just makes it so hard for people who do not fit the mold. I am sorry to rant about this, but I just get so frustrated. I know I am not as overweight as a lot of people, I wonder how they cope with things like this. It is bad enough I have a low self esteem, this just makes it unbearable at times.  So I try to hide in EQ, a MMORPG (massively multiplayer online role play game). I hit level 53 last night, then I went linkdead and my computer bugged out. I had to reinstall everything this morning. I logged on. I was walking up some stairs, I feel off of them somehow for 20k damage…died.. and lost my level. My luck is just so great sometimes… so I am back at 52.  Another thing that is pissing me off is that I just heard that one of the 4 buildings that the terrorists are looking to blow up during the republican convention is one my mom works for. I am so worried for her. I do not know what I would do if something happened to her. I would just be a mess.  I hope that all of this pans out smoothly.  On a positive note, Friday I paid for my transcripts to be sent to the LSAC, atleast I did one productive thing before hitting bottom.  This rant is over.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>