<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know you guys know that there are  2 actual bands at J.W.B.  There are the  Trans  and  One Man Cult . Well I've seen em both perform and  I have to say  that  the Trans were better . Lol.  Sorry Colin, Bucky, Chris, and Jon .  Jon   I really like your guitar strap . Lol. I made myself a  duct tape  one and  it rox your sox!  lol.  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why do most people think that  Christian Music  sucks?&nbsp;   They think that its all   Gospel&nbsp;    Music  which&nbsp;I can assure you  ITS NOT !&nbsp;  There are some  really&nbsp;    good Christian Bands  out&nbsp;  there and you all are probably like&nbsp;   "Yeah     sure..." &nbsp;B  ut  I'm not kidding . For all you  head&nbsp;    banging people, check out Skillet . Wow!&nbsp;  I have their CD and  they ROCK ! For all you&nbsp;   "punk" people who like bands but not head banging bands , check out&nbsp;   Relient K &nbsp;  (guys) or&nbsp;   Superchic(k) &nbsp;  (guys and girls).  For all you&nbsp;SKA&nbsp; &nbsp;  people,&nbsp;  &nbsp;  try&nbsp;Five Iron Frenzy&nbsp;    or O.C. Supertones .&nbsp;&nbsp;  ive Iron is done now but I saw their&nbsp;       CHEESE  cd somewhere the other day (Mike M. I think youd like that... lol)      Theres no need for   SAUCEPANS   in the    SKILLET    world!         SO    Go out and Buy yourself a great CD! lol. Hey Hannah, Erin, Jessica, Mike if you all have any other suggestions, feel free to but in! lol. Good bye now.     urlLink  http://www.skillet.org    or   urlLink  http://www.panheads.org        urlLink  http://www.relientk.com        urlLink  http://www.supertones.com        urlLink  http://www.fiveironfrenzy.com        urlLink  http://www.superchickonline.com         
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I like bacon . Do  you  like  bacon ?  Bacon is good . I  really REALLY  like  bacon ! Almost as much as  I hate bananas . Thats the  weird thing  about  me ... I  really REALLY   dont like  bananas. But my name is  practially   Anna Banana . It makes  absolutely  no sense . .. but thats ok.    I dont make sense   . :-D If  you  know  me   you  know that  I  know that  you  know that  I  know that  you  know that  I  dont make sense.  Make sense ? And if  you  dont know  me  and  I  dont know  you  and  you  want  me  to know that  you  want to get to know  me  tell  me  so  I  can let  you  know that  I  will let  you  get to know  me .  Make sense ? Good  bye  now.  
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I like jelly beans . I dont know  how many of you  all like jelly  beans , but i do. Do you like  jelly beans?   I feel special.   Do you feel special?&nbsp;  I feel special be  cause I am someones   Beautiful   Blue   Jelly Bean.   Whos jelly bean are you? Are  you   anyones   beautiful jelly bean? If you arent   im sorry for you. I dont mean to   Brag.   But i am a beautiful   blue   Jelly   bean.&nbsp;  Good  bye    jelly  beans .   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             Once upon a time, there was a boy. The boy had a flower. The boy loved the flower dearly. He watered it, kept it in sunlight, and even talked to it (plants use carbon dioxide – from our breath – to create food for themselves.). Once day, a group of mean kids picked off the flower petals. The flower began to wilt.        The boy saw this and was upset, but what could he do? He took care of the flower, and within a few days, it had beautiful petals. The boy was happy again.  The mean kids saw how happy the boy was, and they didn’t like it. So, they took the flower out of the pot and deprived it of water.        The boy saw this and was upset, but what could he do? He replanted the flower. It lived, but it would no longer have the beauty that it once had. The boy was still upset. The flower was beginning to die. The mean kids saw this and were happy. The boy’s grief made them feel good. When the flower died, the boy was so upset, he never bought another flower. He avoided the bullies and hoped to be left alone. The End.                     Now… the moral.  Was this a happy ending? No. I didn’t intend for it to be. In this story, the mean kids are the bullies. You may know one, or you may be one. The boy is the person being picked on. You may be that person, you may know one, or you may be the one picking on that person.  The flower is something that the boy thinks is very special. For you, it may be your self-esteem, your confidence or something else. The mean kids pull that apart until it no longer appears in the way you act or who you are. In this story, who are you? The mean kids? The boy? Or both? 
    
</post>


</Blog>