<Blog>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       this morning i had to get up at 7:00, i repeat 7:00 in the morning to go to this new babysitting job.&nbsp; the girl was two and a half and just getting potty trained.&nbsp; so around 11:00 i realize shes wet her pull ups so i change her and then about thirty seconds after shes got her pants back on she runs into the bathroom to her own little plastic potty and rips off the new pull ups i just put on and sits down claiming shes got a "pooper"&nbsp;and a "tinkle" coming.&nbsp; oh god ... but then she sits on the toilet for about a half an hour waiting for the piece of shit to come out, and it never does.&nbsp; i end up reading her a book while shes sitting there and nothing ever happens.&nbsp; so then she gets up and says she doesnt have to go anymore!&nbsp; wtf?&nbsp; so i have to put on another pair of pullups, and im really bad at that.&nbsp; i suck with little kids.&nbsp; you know how i got this job?&nbsp; i was recommended to them by the parents of two eleven year old boys that i babysit for ... what were they thinking?&nbsp; "oh hey, this girl down the street is great with our boys who are really big and dont really need a babysitter cuz theyre bigger than she is, and she would probably be great with your two year old who requires constant attention and at least three diaper changes in six hours!!"&nbsp; um ... no.&nbsp; im surprised shes still alive after an entire morning under my watch.&nbsp; and i have to do it again tomorrow.&nbsp; argh.&nbsp;    im starting a new thing this summer, im going to&nbsp; summer camp!&nbsp; ive never been to summer camp before, its just like a regular 4h camp that almost every kid does at least once and some kids do every summer.&nbsp; but now sheas working at this place in moodus, ct and im going!&nbsp; ill be the oldest kid there cuz 15 is the cut off age and most 15 year olds are going to be sophomores anyway, but what the hell.&nbsp; itll be fun.&nbsp; many hot male counselors and cits.&nbsp;&nbsp; yum.&nbsp;    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       so i just got back from the cape, it was very nice.&nbsp; pot head son was extremely hot, no mention of pot either, yet he wanst home much, no fun stories there.&nbsp; BUT hearing my mom's high school friends reminisce about being my age was ... interesting.&nbsp; lots of drinking stories and lots of smoking stories!&nbsp; but my mom insists that while she did participate in the drinking and was, in fact, the star of several of those stories, she never smoked, only her friends.&nbsp; and i think that that is the funniest bull shit ive ever heard! my mom was a stoner!!&nbsp; she just wont admit to it, but i know the truth.&nbsp; how long did my parents expect me to believe that out of the entire generation of the 70s they were the only two teenagers that never smoked pot?&nbsp; now i know the truth!&nbsp; haha, it was a good weekend.&nbsp;    we also went to provincetown and i saw many drag queens in some very cool dresses and they also had some great shops there!&nbsp; i bought this awesome bag in a store called shop therapy, haha, i love it.&nbsp;    tonight my sisters coming home from camp long enough to go to her college orientation, but yesterday she spent the day in new york with her friends, im sooo jealous!&nbsp; she bought the cooooolest stuff (she bought me happy socks, yay!).&nbsp; so we both have lots of good, private stories from this weekend if you wanna talk, haha.&nbsp; see yall later.&nbsp;    
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       so im going to cape cod tomorrow, just for an overnight.&nbsp; ive never been there before, and i know its weird to be going for such a short time, most people go for at least a week at a time, but im just accompanying my mother while she visits her high school friend who lives there.&nbsp; and today my mother tells me, "now you better make sure to stay away from les' son, molly."&nbsp; les being the high school friend.&nbsp; now having never heard anything about les' son, im struck with a sudden confusion and curiosity.&nbsp; i ask why? of course, only to find out that her son is a blonde haired blue eyed sophomore in college, and i believe my mother may have used the word "hunk."&nbsp; then she goes on to tell me that this boy is using the entire bed of his truck to grow marajuana plants.&nbsp; this kid is not only a serious pot head, he is a drug dealer.&nbsp;&nbsp;erm, what do i make of this?&nbsp;  curious information.&nbsp;  itll be an interesting weekend, thats all i know.&nbsp; ill catch you all on monday.&nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       hey everyone, i decided to start up this blog thing again because im having the  best summer of my life  and i want to SPREAD THE LOVE AND HAPPINESS!&nbsp; of course.&nbsp; i want to discuss the summer reading books a lot and also other books and music and movies.&nbsp; also i have some  great  pictures to share with&nbsp;you if someone can tell me how to get the onto the internet.&nbsp; i am absolutley computer-retarded in everyway.&nbsp; not just retarded, though, cuz that just means slow, but i mean if i had eighty million years and twenty four or five days, i could not figure out this god damn machine.&nbsp; so ... help, please!&nbsp;     &nbsp;   so about the summer reading, im going to be interpreting and analyzing what i read as i go, and because all you loomisers are reading the same thing and&nbsp;some of&nbsp;you gburyers (haha, allie!) might have read some of the same things, i expect you to comment occasionally and tell me what an incompetent, stupid ass i am.&nbsp; and also, if you dont comment, ill think no ones reading my blog and ill have to discontinue it again, and i know how sad that would be for everyone.&nbsp; so please, do us all a favor and contribute to my journal, here.&nbsp;     &nbsp;   and of course, my first comment will be from some computer  savvy  person (and i know i just caught someones attention there for using johnny depps word!), telling me how to get my wawesome pictures on here, right?     &nbsp;   6.2.04    TIN FOIL!!!    hahaha, good times girls ~ summer is amazing!!!     
     
    
</post>


</Blog>