<Blog>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I thought I fixed the car.&nbsp; Isn't that how it usually works?&nbsp; Just when I'm feeling I accomplished something, the damn thing starts acting up again.&nbsp; Overheating and now dying when it's low idling in drive.&nbsp; I dunno.&nbsp; I'm done with it.&nbsp; It's going to the shop tomorrow.&nbsp; I still got oil under my fingernails no matter how hard I scrubbed.&nbsp; I don't know why I wanted to do it to begin with.&nbsp; It's no fun working on a car because you  have  to.&nbsp; That sense of urgency, that I-have-to-do-this-or-we're-screwed takes the fun out of it and makes it one big stress.&nbsp; Fuck it and let the mechanic fix it.&nbsp; I'm trying not to think about it in case that wasn't apparent.&nbsp; On to better things though.  I'm making a lot of headway on this site!!&nbsp; Working on this site has got me hyped about gaming stuff again.&nbsp; I was a bit burned out on gaming for awhile (I confess), but I'm getting back in the groove again I think.&nbsp; I'll have to call Matt tomorrow and let him know I can't take him skating tomorrow since the truck still isn't running right (there it is again).&nbsp; I'll make it up to him.&nbsp; I hadn't skated in so long I'm a bit afraid to.&nbsp; Remember when the skating rink was the place to pick up chics??&nbsp; Nerveous flirting, sweaty hands and slow skating to Every Rose Has It's Thorn.&nbsp; I actually found a few friends I went to school with back then on Classmates.com but what do you talk about with someone you haven't seen in over 10 years?&nbsp; Sure, the "old days" are fun to recap but then it's just awkward.&nbsp; Maybe I'll drop em an email anyway.  
 urlLink 05:05 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today wasn't the usual day around here.&nbsp; I've been out sweating my balls off working on the damn truck.&nbsp; The other day (I think it was Friday) I realized the truck was dumping oil all over the driveway.&nbsp; What is it with our luck with cars???&nbsp; Luckily I think it's just a busted gasket to the oil pan but lucky for me Jeeps require you disconnect the exhaust and remove the starter just to get at the damn oil pan.&nbsp; I was going to take it to a shop and have them do it but when they told me 200...&nbsp; fuck it right?&nbsp; There's always one freakin bolt that doesn't wanna give.&nbsp; I gave up for tonight.&nbsp; It did give me some time to plot and scheme my next game session and Marcel had fun "helping me".&nbsp; I used to enjoy working on cars and I think, for the most part, I still do.&nbsp; If it wasn't for the mosquitoes and that one damn bolt I think it would have been pleasent despite being covered in oil and dirt.&nbsp; After a cool shower I felt much better and decided to relax here.&nbsp; Lana's in a domestic mood and wants to "cook or clean something" and is talking about taking a cab to Walmart.&nbsp; Let me repeat that in case you didn't catch that.&nbsp; Our car is out of commission right now and Lana  needs to go to Walmart right now .&nbsp; To get a floor matt for the bathroom and "something to bake like cookies or something".&nbsp; Addictions are a nasty monkey on your back, but I guess it's better than smelling like the monkey.&nbsp; Off to Walmart I guess.&nbsp; Arg. 
 urlLink 02:10 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Lana's out of town for the weekend and it feels so weird here without her. To make matters worse, Marcel wanted to sleep over grandpa's house yesterday and how can I say no?&nbsp; So there I was, in the house by myself.&nbsp; I ended up turning the radio on, watched some tv and read until I fell asleep.&nbsp; That is, after a trip to Jack in the Box for a big coke.&nbsp; Today I wasted away with an all day bookstore rampage.&nbsp; I went to Barns and Noble, Waldens, Half price and Re-Run.&nbsp; Funny thing is I managed to buy not a single book.&nbsp; I was hunting and if I don't find what I'm looking for I just end up frustrated and get nothing out of the trip.&nbsp; Oh well.&nbsp; I ended up ordering the damn thing at Waldens.&nbsp; So here I am tired, but not sleepy working on my site a bit.&nbsp; I  hate  a quiet house.&nbsp; Marcel is out cold and I can't help but want to wake him up to play some nintendo or bionicles.&nbsp; Man, bionicles are so cool...&nbsp; I wonder if you can buy them by the bulk like you can magic cards?&nbsp; I bet I could make some really cool stuff if I had more parts...&nbsp; Whenever Lana's not in the house I always feel a little guilty for watching my horribly bad movies becuase I watch them really loud.&nbsp; Reminds me of when I was little and knew my parents wouldn't be home for a while.&nbsp; I'd get on my dads stereo, turn it up all the way and put on a Bruce Springsteen record or my Beastie Boys (it was the first and only record I ever bought).&nbsp; I still hadn't confessed to him that I blew out his speakers.&nbsp; Bad Horror just feels right when at really high volumes.&nbsp; It's that guilty satisfaction I think that gets sated.&nbsp; Tonight?&nbsp; Basketcase and popcorn.&nbsp; Then I'll move to Dog Soldiers if I'm not asleep by then.&nbsp; Past few days I just wanna relax.&nbsp; I don't know what I've been doing but I just don't feel much like "going out" other than a little bit of "me" time.&nbsp; Bookstores, movies, writing, working on a project, etc.&nbsp; Well, gotta get the popcorn in the microwave sometime...&nbsp;  
 urlLink 01:13 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Wow, what a trip.&nbsp; It's been a hectic past few weeks.&nbsp; It all seems like a blur.&nbsp; I've feel like I haven't really stopped moving every since the car trouble.&nbsp; I keep telling myself, "In the morning I'm going to start my morning gym routine back up" but something always comes up.&nbsp; Staying up late to all hours of the morning visiting, roleplaying, or just watching movies with lana doesn't help me drag my ass out of bed.&nbsp; As soon as find a quiet time with nothing to do, I do all the things I shouldn't be doing rather than doing those I should (like laundry or dishes).&nbsp; Hey, the bathroom has a new light though!&nbsp; Yup, I decided I was going to be Mister Fixit when the toilet wobble got really bad.  After getting all my tools out, cleaning the toilet, draining it, and lifting it off the hole, I found that the concrete mounting brackets weren't ancored right and had rusted badly and the concrete crumbled around them.&nbsp; So I redrilled, reseated it, and bolted it back down.&nbsp; Man, I was feelin good.&nbsp; I fixed the toilet, I rock.&nbsp; Guys can be silly at times, I know.&nbsp; SO I'm thinking, I could go ahead and put that extra light fixture up since I already have my tools out...&nbsp; To make a long story short, two days later of crawling around in the attic running new wire, punching holes in the bathroom wall, and almost cooking myself a few times I finally finished.&nbsp; Both lights turn on now when you hit the light, there's now a spot for a future fan, but the damn outlet flips everytime I plug something in it.&nbsp; Fuck it.&nbsp; Another problem for another day.&nbsp; I guess I should patch those massive holes in the wall too.  A note to myself, "I  will  get up early tomorrow and take Matt out somewhere.&nbsp; I feel bad but I've been so damn busy with everyday stuff that finding time for just him and me has been next to impossible nevermind finding one on one time with my own son.&nbsp; But he calls, and often.&nbsp; Man, where do kids learn how to inflict such guilt trips?&nbsp; Anyway, I'm taking him to the movies tomorrow morning.&nbsp; Gotta get up early, gotta get up early, gotta get up early...  
 urlLink 18:17 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Fucking viruses.&nbsp; Sometimes the convenience of a computer just doesn't seem worth the hassle.&nbsp; It's been a while since I've messed with this thing I was so frustrated with it.&nbsp; Not having the computer up gave made me realize I could be doing other stuff when I'm bored.&nbsp; But it knew I'd want a fix sooner or later.&nbsp; They know you'll come back so they just wait, big black screen just waiting to swallow down hours of your time in a few gulps.&nbsp; Yup, and where am I at this moment?&nbsp; But I've got so many tools at my disposal with a computer.&nbsp; Movie times, maps, porn clips, movie trailers, news, pictures of naked redheads dressed in high heels and leather skirts that go all the way - nevermind.&nbsp; I missed the computer but sometimes I just wanna smash it for killing my time. Marcel's birthday is coming up!!&nbsp; It's only a little more than a week away and Lana and I  still  don't have anything planned.&nbsp; My dad went out and got him a HUGE Encredible Hulk pinata, candy, table cloth, napkins, plates, etc.&nbsp; Think he's hinting at something?&nbsp; Yeah, we've been putting off making plans but I cringe at cleaning up after another birthday party.&nbsp; He's turning five.&nbsp;  FIVE .&nbsp; A monumental day, besides his birthday, has snuck up on me.&nbsp; His first day of school.&nbsp; When did he get old enough for school?&nbsp; It seems like I was just potty training him and watching blues clues with him.&nbsp; Now he's asking questions that make me pause without an answer and finding a level of independence I'm not used to.&nbsp; He's always staying the night at my dad's or Lana's moms place.&nbsp; Sounds selfish (becuase it is) but I miss having a sleeping baby on my chest or burping him after he ate.&nbsp; There's a lot about the "baby" stage I miss.&nbsp; I never thought for a second I'd understand my mom telling me, "You'll always be my baby."&nbsp; I used to hate it.&nbsp; I used to get really mad at her for embarrassing me and get mean.&nbsp; Teenagers are such assholes.&nbsp; Sometimes we grow out of it.&nbsp; I think I have, I think I have, I think I have... 
 urlLink 14:16 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, it's pretty damn early in the morning for me and I've managed to stay awake.&nbsp; So I figured, what the heck.&nbsp; It's been awhile...&nbsp; With Marcel going to school now our schedule (Marcel and mine) has changed up a bit.&nbsp; Getting up at 6:30am in the freakin morning tends to do that.&nbsp; I have a hard time convincing him to get out of bed when all I wanna do is roll over and snooze some more.&nbsp; He seems to be enjoying it though.&nbsp; He did manage to floor my jaw the other day while we were eating yesterday though.&nbsp; So there we were, eating lunch and chatting with Marcel about his day at school.&nbsp; The conversation turns to his friends at school when Lana asks him about his girlfriend.&nbsp; He then proceeds to tell us about his girlfriend at school and how pretty she is.&nbsp; He's  five !!!&nbsp; Makes a daddy proud... Halloween is getting closer and closer and I'm falling further and further behind on these costume projects.&nbsp; I think Marcel might be the only one sporting a costume if I don't kick into gear.&nbsp; I've just got so many other things going on right now it's hard to focus on one thing.&nbsp; Starter one the truck on day, the damn water heater flooding the bedroom and laundry room the next, cleaning out my gaming room before friday (Lana's aunt is moving in for a short while), cleaning the tank, etc.&nbsp; I get so busy at moments I don't know what I'm doing.&nbsp; I think I've been spending too much time in the house, but I'm in one of those moods where I don't feel like "socializing".&nbsp; It's not a bad thing though, despite what those of you who can't go 10 minutes alone without feeling the need of hearing someone else's voice (freaks!!)&nbsp; I'm not saying I don't enjoy socializing, but I hit stages where I need "me" time.&nbsp; Sometimes sitting on the toilet a few minutes longer for piece and quiet just don't cut it when you have a five year old in the house.&nbsp; I think I just need to plan a bookstore trip by bus.&nbsp; I remember those rides and walks being so relaxing.&nbsp; Even though your surrounded by people, everyone is lost somewhere else thinking about something else.&nbsp; I need to just load up my backpack with water and a good book, and hit the bus stop.&nbsp; Hit all my favorite bookstores reading on the way, do a little walking now and then, and wander home by bus when it gets late.&nbsp; Sounds like a plan in the making... 
 urlLink 10:19 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Today was a very special day.&nbsp; Today, my little brother, became a dad again.&nbsp; I became an uncle for a second time.&nbsp; With just those few words, "It's a girl." from my brother I couldn't help but feel proud and envious at the same time.&nbsp; She's such a beautiful baby and when I held her I knew I held her for someone else other than myself.  We didn't always see eye to eye and there were moments I said things I'd cut my tongue out to take back.&nbsp; Those things are done and can never be undone but I do what I can to attone for them in my own ways.&nbsp; I'll never lie about the woman she was, as I knew her, becuase that's what made me love her as well contemn her.&nbsp; The one thing my mom wanted, before she passed away, was to hold a baby girl in her arms.&nbsp; So many opportunities for forgiveness stolen from us by something as stupid as a car accident.&nbsp; Wounds left open to fester.&nbsp; Wounds I can't stop picking at over and over again.&nbsp; But when I held little Marian in my arms...&nbsp; My brother is a lucky man.  Congradulations Mike.&nbsp; Mom would be happy to see "her men" still standing together as a family with a place for her in our hearts still.  Xiamara and her baby girl should be coming home tomorrow evening.&nbsp; I can't wait to see the baby again and hold her.&nbsp; It's been so long since I held a baby.&nbsp; Man, do I miss it.&nbsp; The diaper rashes, the teething, the constant crying.&nbsp; I'd have to be crazy to want another baby.&nbsp; Then I remember him falling asleep on my chest or hearing that full belly laugh only a baby can do.&nbsp; I know I have a lot more of those "little moments" ahead of me, but I want more.&nbsp; Don't even get me started on brotherhood.&nbsp; I'll get even sappier on ya.&nbsp; Single children will never know what their missing and for them I feel sad.     Name:  &nbsp;  Marian Joy Camacho     Proud Parents:  &nbsp;  Michael J. Camacho and Xiamara Gozman    Date of Birth: &nbsp;  14th October, 2003 (11:04am)     Weight:  &nbsp;  6 Pounds 15 ounces &nbsp; 
 urlLink 23:09 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I realized something a little weird today.&nbsp; Yesterday everyone came by to roleplay (micah's GURPS Star Wars conversion game, not mine) at my place.&nbsp; It was sorta last minute plans after I had planned on doing nothing more then vegging out.&nbsp; Trust me, it was no fun trying to do dishes, sweep, laundry and vacuuming a house that hasn't been really cleaned since  last week .&nbsp; Nevermind I get winded and go into coughing fits just walking fast with the remains of this flu.&nbsp; I can't even think bout anything too laborous without coughing.&nbsp; Don't get me started.&nbsp; I'm beyond "frustrated".&nbsp; I hate being sick.&nbsp; I  reeeeeeaaally  hate being sick, but I'm getting off topic. So once we're all gathered (or at least those of us who didn't beeeey yatch out watching a tv show he coulda recorded!!!!) we were doing the customary gathering of all nerd/geek clans.&nbsp; We gathered around a computer while we discussed the impact of cgi on the movie industry, the deeper meaning behind Nightmare on Elm Street, and where would be a good place to have the piss scared out of us this year for halloween.&nbsp; Somewhere in there we even brought up the holy trinity (Episode IV, V, and VI).&nbsp; Anyway, while we were discussing this away Derek sat at the helm of the computer looking for somewhere to have the shit scared out of us when he showed us this haunted hospital here in Houston.&nbsp; It looked vaguely familiar but I was too deep in conversation about the new Freddy vs. Jason movie to pay much attention.&nbsp; So we moved on to other subjects eventually making it back to the game room, now that the customary gathering/greeting had been met.&nbsp; So on with the game we went into the early morning hours like the old school gamers we are.&nbsp; Hoooo Waaaaaah!!!&nbsp; *coughing fit* Today, James calls me up after I just got back from my brothers house painting care bears on his new baby room (Their inducing Xiamara on Tuesday!!!) and asks me if I could look through my history file for the site on that hospital.&nbsp; So I look it up and I get that nagging vague familiar feeling again when I find it.&nbsp; James is talkin away to me on the phone when it hits me.&nbsp; I reach into my file cabinet and pull out my birth certificate.&nbsp; Yup, that's the place alright.&nbsp; I was born in a hospital built on the burial grounds of thousands of plague victims.&nbsp; It would later become a juvenile detention ward, a drug and alcohol rehab, and lastly as a psychiatric ward in it's final days.&nbsp; And I was born there.&nbsp; I'm almost proud.&nbsp; I was born in a place of local history, even if it is a little fucked up.&nbsp; I mentioned it to my dad and he says, last he heard, the city is having a problem with homeless people living it it.&nbsp; I made the mistake of mentioning to him I'd like to take a look inside and all he responded back with was, "I think that's called breaking and entering."&nbsp; No matter how cool your parents are, they have their instinctive killjoy parental moments.&nbsp; With proper planning, some flashlights and my digital camera though...&nbsp; I'll keep ya posted.&nbsp; Oh, here's the link by the way.&nbsp;  urlLink http://www.houstonhaunts.com/articles/jeffDavis/jeffDavis.htm  
 urlLink 19:56 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "Were going to win the lottery."&nbsp; Lana announced to me the other day.&nbsp; Here's her logic.&nbsp; The starter goes out on the truck, I get my credit card stolen, Lana has a blowout on her way to Dallas, Marcel gets sick, and the water heater spewed all over the rug.&nbsp; Somethin good  must  be coming our way.&nbsp; If I had my wallet I'd go to the store and buy one, but since "Lucky John" still has it I'm still screwed. Lucky John.&nbsp; I lost my wallet on Friday.&nbsp; I honestly thought I lost it in the pile of laundry or maybe left it in the truck.&nbsp; Well, I put off looking for it until Monday.&nbsp; That's when Lana checks our account and tells me someone (Lucky John) found my wallet and helped himself to my credit card.&nbsp; So now I have the joy of canceling my card, filing a claim, and waiting.&nbsp; Meanwhile I get a envelope in the mail today with my driver's license in it with a return address of Lucky John.&nbsp;  Hey Lucky John...&nbsp; suck my cock you freeloading ass muncher. If you're going to return anything of mine, return my fucking wallet!&nbsp; You know how hard it is to find a good wallet??? 
 urlLink 10:19 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Halloween has come and gone, thankfully. I never did get my samurai costume done. There just wasn't enough time and I waited way too long to get started. I did end up pulling a cool costume outta my butt though (I'll be posting the pictures soon in my photo album soon). I'm still a little exhausted by halloween but excited about next year. The Monday before Halloween I started and completed Marcel's costume (I learned how to sew!)  and  I did my costume! I was knee deep in fabric, bondo, plaster, silicone, and hot glue. The entire house was trashed, I hadn't done laundry in days, and something was living under the pile of dishes in the sink. But I got em done!! We were a little late to the halloween party (I had to wait for the spray paint on my armor to dry), but we were there. I must say, the party gets better every year. The past few days I've taken upon myself to do a complete overhaul of my tank. I'm completely relandscaping everything. You'll hafta check out the tank page for details. Over all, things are going good these days, if you don't count the battle lana's having with the electric company. Don't ask. I mean it, don't. Only thing putting a dampner on my high right now is my dad might be moving. Still in state, but moving. I don't see him as much as I should since he lives just 10 minutes away and I have no excuses except that whenever I think to visit it's usually kindda late and I hate to bug him late. He went for the job interview and I really do hope it went well even if I do have selfish thoughts bout him moving. He's a good guy and deserves it. Heck, he's still my rolemodel. Is there a certain age that should stop? I hope not... It's a roleplaying night so I can't stay on here too long with company getting ready to invade my home. I've been coped up too long I've realized. Been buried inside too long. While not always the social animal, it's good to be in good company now and then. Plus I need some input on how I should redesign my tank. Where the waterfall should go, should I put in a river, etc. To put it simply; All is good in the world right now. ;) 
 urlLink 18:56 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's just a few hours until the beginning of a new year.&nbsp; I look back on this year and can't think but ask where all the time went.&nbsp; Special things that happened this year?&nbsp; I became an uncle again.&nbsp; My son started School.&nbsp; My wife's business team hit over a million dollars in sales this year.&nbsp; I heard from an old friend I hadn't seen in over ten years.&nbsp; What does this add up to?&nbsp; There's no stopping time and the only thing to do is enjoy the ride.&nbsp; I've made it a point all this year to try and not be so negative and I think I've succeeded on a lot of points.&nbsp; It's been a self improvement year really.&nbsp; Maybe not physically, but spiritually.&nbsp; Hey, I'm no beer swigging gut man or nothing but I sure as hell can't run two miles in thirteen minutes (but I bet I could still do it in under sixteen!).&nbsp; I've tried to take on more of my dad's outlook on everything.&nbsp; He's the strongest man I've ever known.&nbsp; He never gives up, even when the world seems set against him from all ends.&nbsp; What does he do?&nbsp; He turns to his family and gathers strength from them and keeps going knowing all will end well in the end if you want it to.&nbsp; Thinking positive.&nbsp; It seems like such a little thing and I know now how much of a difference it can make.&nbsp; I never really thought about how negative I can be at times until it Lana pointed it out to me.&nbsp; So, when I wonder how I'll go at something I just ask myself what my dad would do.&nbsp; Sound cheesy?&nbsp; It may be but my father has always been my role model and he's even more so now.&nbsp; It doesn't matter how much money you make, what kind of car you drive or what kind of shoes you lace up in the morning.&nbsp; What matters is spending those first few moments awake in bed before going to bed laughing and tickling your son (or wife), sneaking up on your kiddo to watch him play, and lots of other private moments with your family.&nbsp; It's going to be a good year, I can feel it. New year's resolutions?&nbsp; Hummm...&nbsp; More quality time with Marcel and Lana.&nbsp; Visit my brother more often.&nbsp; Get out of the house more often even if it's just to the park.&nbsp; Call my dad when I think of him even if it is a bit of an inconvenience.&nbsp; Spend more time with my nephew and niece.&nbsp; Here's a biggie for me;&nbsp; write more often and maybe get the balls to even put a few short stories up here.&nbsp; Lana's positivity is contagious I think.&nbsp; The woman can see the good in just about anything.&nbsp; She has this weird way of picking me up out of a bad mood without even knowing it.&nbsp; So out with the negative and in with the new.   HAPPY NEW YEAR!!!!  
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, it's just right around the corner and I'm not finished shopping.&nbsp; Every year I tell myself I'm going to get started early and every year I put it off just a little bit more.&nbsp; It's okay though cause I got most of my Christmas shopping out of the way.&nbsp; While we didn't go crazy this year like we did last year, but Marcel probably won't notice.&nbsp; I still gotta get a tree up...&nbsp; I still have a few days left though.&nbsp; ;)&nbsp; My birthday just passed for those who care.&nbsp; I turned 23 again for the 4th time.&nbsp; Fourth time must be a charm because this was one of the best birthdays I've had.&nbsp; Lana, me, Marcel and Jonathan all drove out to Corpus Christi and stayed in a bay side hotel.&nbsp; We left on Thursday and came back yesterday.&nbsp; The hotel we stayed at was right on the beach overlooking the water and the Lexington.&nbsp; We didn't tour it this time around but I figure we'll save it for this summer when we rent a beach house and take those sand castle classes.&nbsp; The kids had a blast.&nbsp; There's this monstrosity of a castle playground right on the beach.&nbsp; It's a parent's nightmare.&nbsp; It twists and turns everywhere.&nbsp; Children turn into tunnel rats and quickly lose their parents only to show up on the other end of the playground.&nbsp; To make it worse, it isn't fenced in.&nbsp; So what does that mean?&nbsp; It means mom and dad get to chase the kiddos through this gauntlet of stairs, latters, and tunnels.&nbsp; More than once I caught that pleading look from another parent.&nbsp; Took me a while to realize I had that same look stretched across mine.&nbsp; Needless to say, Lana and I got our workout chasing Marcel and Johnathan through it.&nbsp; I'd like to go back when we don't have the kids so I can enjoy it.&nbsp; It's really freakin cool and I'm getting ideas about a backyard castle...&nbsp; It's been a while since we had a big family outting like this and I'm happy my baby Lana did this for me.&nbsp; There's just something about not having a place to be, no deadline to worry about, and just driving where ever looks enteresting.&nbsp; I think I almost got deported coming back from Mission, Texas though. On the way back from my dad's after dropping the kids off for the night, we got stopped by a cop on 77.&nbsp; Apperently, my license plate light is out.&nbsp; He asks me to step out of the car and stand to the rear of the vehicle.&nbsp; Lana gets the interrogation in the warm truck while I stand behind the truck suckin down exhaust fumes in the cold.&nbsp; Then it's my turn.&nbsp; He snaps the questions at me and never lets me finish a sentence before he's snapping another one at me.&nbsp; Hell, by the end of it I felt guilty.&nbsp; He let us go with a warning to get our registration taken care of as well as the light.&nbsp; I'm sure I'll get around to it eventually. On a completly weird and good news note, I heard from a family friend I hadn't heard from in years!&nbsp; Family friends we met back when we were living in Colorado.&nbsp; I was checking my email today and there it was.&nbsp; A name I hadn't heard in years sitting in my junk mail folder.&nbsp; I figured it was just a coincidence, but just in case...&nbsp; I shot her an email askin if it was who I thought it was and I got a response back!!&nbsp; So if they follow my link they might end up reading this...&nbsp; sooo...&nbsp;  Hi Jas!&nbsp; Hey Jacob!!&nbsp; Hey, Debbie!!!&nbsp; Miss you guys and can't wait to come up and see ya'll sometime.&nbsp; Marcel has never seen real snow and I miss it!!&nbsp; See ya'll soon hopefully!&nbsp; Merry Christmas!!!!&nbsp; --Alex and Family  
 urlLink 13:09 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's been a few days since we got back and I still feel worn out.&nbsp; We left on Thursday for Vegas, arrived at the Stardust hotel in our limo around 2:00pm, and settled into our suite.&nbsp; That's about as much relaxing we did the entire weekend.&nbsp; The rest was a blur of faces, camera flashes, hand shaking, and "she went that way."&nbsp; I did manage to get out of the hotel a few times though.&nbsp; Lana stayed pretty busy the whole time with a packed schedule.&nbsp; I was left to wander sometimes on my own (scary huh?) and ended up on the strip, had 40 dollars sucked from my hands into a slot machine or two, hit the suchi bar, and the hot tub a few times.&nbsp; I was a little disappointed.&nbsp; The strip wasn't as big as I always thought it was.&nbsp; I never did get to pick up some more sets of casino dice, but we've decided Vegas is a definite come-back-to trip.  It's always weird going to Lana's conventions.&nbsp; I get to meet some of the ladies I talk to on the phone, I get to put a face to the voice on the phone, the name in the Spotlight-er Partners in Passion.&nbsp; It's always great to see familiar faces too, people I've grown to really like not just as "Lana's Business Partners" but as friends.&nbsp; The first year I was dumbfounded, floored, humbled, and humiliated all at once all weekend.&nbsp; I never took her business very serious that first year or two.&nbsp; Her first convention came and went and I just "that's nice dear" the whole thing for the most part.&nbsp; Convention 2002 slapped me in the face.&nbsp; Lana and her team swept the awards.&nbsp; I couldn't have been prouder but at the same time I couldn't have felt more like shit.&nbsp; The saying, "If your not helping your in the way" comes to mind.&nbsp; While I never said she couldn't do something or berated her for her business decisions, I never told her how good she was doing.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; Because I didn't know.&nbsp; Yeah, you don't need to tell me.&nbsp; So I made a decision and have been trying to stick to it.&nbsp; I don't stand in her way, I don't tell her how to run her business (she does that fine), I throw in my two cents when she asks for it, but for the most part I try to take out the distractions of running a business at home.&nbsp; I'm tryin to be more like Mike.&nbsp; Not the basketball player.&nbsp; The cooler guy, Mike Horwath.&nbsp; This dude rocks.&nbsp; I couldn't begin to tell you all the stuff this dude does to help his woman but he should do a seminar for the guys next convention (HINT, HINT).  This year they had Sue Johanson as a speaker as well as Brian Biro.&nbsp; While I dig Sue Johanson and her style of sexual education, Brian Biro's seminar was what I really enjoyed.&nbsp; If you ever have the opportunity to listen to this man speak, seize the Woo!&nbsp; Woo?&nbsp; Go buy his books or listen to his siminar and find out ( urlLink www.brianbiro.com ).&nbsp; After listening to him speak I felt so focused I was ready to go home and start applying what I learned from him.&nbsp; The best part of his seminar is the board breaking though.&nbsp; Sounds cheesy doesn't it?&nbsp; I thought so too the first year they had him as a speaker until I saw how powerful of an action it can be.&nbsp; All these women (a few husbands too) break off into groups.&nbsp; Everybody has a board.&nbsp; Written on one side, with an "X" in the middle, is their obstacle (procrastination, laziness, fear of failure, etc).&nbsp; On the other side is the reward waiting for them on the other side when they break through their obstacles (more family time, recognition, more money, etc.) and those people they'll share it with.&nbsp; Everyone looks nervous.&nbsp; Ever see over 200 hundred women all trying to hide in a big open room?&nbsp; The first few step forward reluctantly.&nbsp; IT's written on their faces.&nbsp; F-E-A-R.&nbsp; They don't think they can do this.&nbsp; This is silly.&nbsp; I really don't want to be here but I'll give it a try.&nbsp; The crowd begins shouting their name and clapping.&nbsp; After a minute or two of this the name loses meaning.&nbsp; It's a speaking in tongue effect.&nbsp; It's the power of the voice and energy, not the sound itself.&nbsp; Between the clapping, stomping and shouting, the room is charged, hot with focused energy.&nbsp; You can  feel  it.&nbsp; Then they thrust forward at the climax of it all.&nbsp; All that fear and self doubt?&nbsp; Gone.&nbsp; Blown away like tissue.&nbsp; An incredible experience.&nbsp; So incredible in fact, this year I wanted to hold the boards.&nbsp; I jumped when I was asked if I could because it's one of the things I had been looking forward to.&nbsp; I got front row seats this year.&nbsp; I watched it in their eyes.&nbsp; You could read it in their eyes.&nbsp; Then you caught their eyes and didn't let go.&nbsp; For a moment that seemed to last forever all the chanting, clapping and stomping became white noise and only the energy was there.&nbsp; Often times the only way I knew the board had been broken was by the reaction of the crowd.&nbsp; Then our eyes unlock and they look at the broken board.&nbsp; I can't explain to you the kind of energy that comes off a person after they've accomplished something they thought they couldn't do.&nbsp; You want to do it again and again.&nbsp; When all were done I found myself looking around the room wanting more.&nbsp; An amazing experience I won't forget.&nbsp; I found my Woo that day and grabbed it.&nbsp; I can't wait to listen to him again next year.  So this year's convention is finally done, Lana's back in the saddle, hyped up and supercharged.&nbsp; Sounds scary doesn't it?&nbsp; Not quite four years in the business and she's already a big dawg, collects a fat check monthly, has close to 300 people on her team who sell over a million in product a year, and she's yet to really apply herself.&nbsp; Am I braggin?&nbsp; Damn right I am!!&nbsp; 
 urlLink 21:21 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I spent most of this week just being lazy and relaxing after a busy and stressful weekend.&nbsp; It was Owlcon convention weekend and I pretty much screwed the pooch on it this time.&nbsp; I promised I would make trophies for all the winners.&nbsp; I knew what I wanted in my head and didn't anticipate any problems.&nbsp; So, like usual, I put off starting it.&nbsp; So when I did start it with a little over a week to go and found that it wasn't as easy as I thought it would be, I slowly slipped into panic mode.&nbsp; To make a long story short, I worked on them all the way up to the last minute trying to pull it off.&nbsp; I still feel bad about it but I'm thinking positive again.&nbsp; Without the stress on me now, I can focus on making them come out really good and I've got a new game plan. The convention itself turned out really well.&nbsp; Both my GURPS' games made, I saw a lot of familiar faces and met a few new ones.&nbsp; There didn't seem to be the huge flux of people there was last year but there did seem to be a wider variety of games.&nbsp; Hey, and Micah and me picked up a near mint copy of Hero Quest!!!&nbsp; We played it on Sunday and had a few guys walk up and jump in.&nbsp; One of the guys had me laughing so hard I bout died.&nbsp; It was a good weekend, I just wish I woulda been able to enjoy it more.&nbsp; Hey, it was my own fault and I'm going to make it point to not procrastinate from here on out.&nbsp; Yup.&nbsp; It's a whole different matter when others are relying on you for something...&nbsp; No more procrastination.&nbsp; No more, no more, no more.&nbsp; Now if I could just remember all things I've been putting off... 
 urlLink 21:21 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've been a little down in the weather I guess and I'm sure not being able to get restful sleep doesn't help any.&nbsp; Dosha and Kathy got me all revamped bout my main fish tank again.&nbsp; It feels good to be making progress on that project.&nbsp; I even emailed the guy who inspired the whole thing and he's a really cool guy.&nbsp; I've just felt so restless lately.&nbsp; I guess I could put that energy to good use by doing laundry, dishes, mowing the yard, etc.&nbsp; but instead I stay up til four or five in the morning playing canasty with Lana, Kelly and Dosha.&nbsp; Restless.  Speaking of restless, I've decided I need a J-O-B.&nbsp; Not like a real job with responsibilities but something I'll enjoy doing for a few hours a day after I drop Marcel off at school.&nbsp; I've decided to try and get a job at Petsmart.&nbsp; I'll enjoy the job, take what I've learned to the job and the discount would be great.&nbsp; I've owned ferrets, hamsters, gerbils, sugar gliders, turtles, cats and dogs.&nbsp; I enjoy having pets.&nbsp; That's why I've become an aquarium guy now.&nbsp; I'm not allowed pets in our current rent house so I found a way around the lease that's acceptable to our landlord.&nbsp; I think my wife is secretly grateful bout the no pets thing.&nbsp; Anyway, I'm looking to get a job at Petsmart.&nbsp; Something fun, educational, and will pay to support my habit-er hobbies.  Speaking of fish, did you know it's illegal to own piranha in the state of Texas?&nbsp; It's a B Class B Misdemeanor.&nbsp; What does that mean?&nbsp; A maximum fine of 2,000 dollars and/or confinement in jail up to 180 days.&nbsp; I understand the state not wanting to introduce this type of animal into the wildlife but a Class B Misdemeanor for something that is so readily available if you know where to look?&nbsp; Sound familiar?&nbsp; Marijuana possession of&nbsp; two ounces or less carries the same penalty.&nbsp; So why not make it a Permit Only fish?&nbsp; Say a five hundred dollar permit cost paid annually to the Wildlife Commission with a minimum (but not maximum) number of inspections per year.&nbsp; Should the inspector not be satisfied with the environment, the animals could legally seized for neglectful care (just like the laws for sugar gliders) if a set list of conditions aren't meet (proper housing, feeding, care, etc.).&nbsp; For the really cautious, upon death the owner has to provide the carcass to the Wildlife Commission and to insure no misunderstandings or confusion, each fish has to be measured, weighed and tagged upon each inspection.&nbsp; Sound a little out there?&nbsp; Not really when you consider these laws already exist for other animals such as sugar gliders which are considered hazardous to local Texas wildlife as well.  So lets examine this.&nbsp; The current law bans and punishes dedicated aquarists from owning an understudied animal and treats them as criminals and the state makes a maximum profit of 2,000 per offense.&nbsp; Or the law could be changed as follows to allow these dedicated individuals to care for this understudied unique animal in a controlled environment and the state makes a profit of five hundred dollars a person.&nbsp; It may seem like a hefty cost but when you consider that the tank required house such fish is going to cost a minimum of two thousand dollars, to the serious aquarist it isn't a lot (they require 20 gallons of water per fish on average and are schooling fish with the recommended number being around six).&nbsp; The State wildlife makes more money, learns more about the fish for educational purposes from independent responsible sources, and has the right to revoke and seize the animals if requirements aren't met and aquarists get to house a fascinating fish in their home.&nbsp; Everybody wins.  Back to folding laundry.  For those of you in Texas, here's the link to the Texas Park and Wildlife's list of  urlLink Prohibited Exotic Fish, Shellfish, and Aquatic Plants .   &nbsp;    On a side note there's a certain phrase which I will never  EVER  utter again.&nbsp; I never meant it and it'll prolly bother me for a while so here's another heartfelt apology.&nbsp; :(     
 urlLink 19:27 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I keep meaning to add a blog to here, but it's always that hesitation that keeps me from writing here.&nbsp; It's not that I haven't had anything to blab about or bitch about but everytime I sit down and pound away for 10-20 minutes, I finish, read it, then delete.&nbsp; Why?&nbsp; Well, there's some things that just ain't noneyabusiness.&nbsp; So there.&nbsp; Maybe I should start a secret blog somewhere... Our wedding anniversary just passed last Sunday.&nbsp; Seven years married.&nbsp; Doesn't seem like it's been that long.&nbsp; This year was a little frustrating for me only because we were some broke fuckers.&nbsp; I had a little something planned out but now it'll just have to wait.&nbsp; No big deal I guess since we decided to celebrate our anniversary this weekend instead.&nbsp; I really just wanna get out for the weekend.&nbsp; Maybe go to Galveston for the weekend like we did for our "honeymoon" although getting her to stay in a place with no room service or bellhop might take some convincing.&nbsp; We're trying to tighten our budget belt so we can move into a bigger house.&nbsp; I've been wanting to move out of this house for a while but I've been getting seriously buggy lately.&nbsp; I need Change.&nbsp;  CHANGE .&nbsp; I dunno, a move, a new hobby, something outdoors.&nbsp; Been just really restless lately.&nbsp; I need somethin but I'm not sure what, but I'll know it when it happens.&nbsp; I think. 
 urlLink 22:59 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I woke up late today, about fifteen minutes ago to be exact. I hate getting up this late. I don't sleep well (bad dreams), I feel tired all day, and half my day is down the toliet. With the level of boredom I've been experiencing lately, that might not be a bad thing. Lana actually got up at ten this morning. She has a party at two and wanted to visit her mom a bit today so I kicked her outta bed when the alarm went off. I was up late last night just waiting for Lana to come home from her party. I've watched about all the He-Man I my mind can absorb at this point and have decided to attack a book. It's pretty good so far and I'm really digging the plot. It's title is  urlLink Heroes Die . Imagine a world not too far into the future of automated homes, personal A.I., automotive slavelanes to control traffic, and entertainment rules all. Sound familiar? Lurking behind all this is a 1984 government that controls it all. Then comes our Heroe, Caine. He's an actor, but not as we might recognize them. He transports to another parallel world and lives out a life of a street brawling assassin in a world where magic works, all for the entertainment of the higher castes. While he's on an Adventure, millions of viewers are watching, feeling, tasting, smelling everything he is via a transmitter inside his brain. They  are  Caine via induction seats. Hari, his real name, has the celibraty life along with the celibraty wife. He's still in love with her despite their differences. When he finds out she's lost in the Otherworld and in danger, he contracts for one last Adventure to bring her back before she's lost forever.  Knowing he might not come back this time, he goes to see his father who was imprisoned for what Orsen Wells called Thoughtcrime. Anyway, I'm digging the book a lot so far. I like the 1984 setting with a sci-fi twist and would like to see it in a GURPS game. I'd get to use all the sci-fi I want plus the option of going to Otherworld for Fantasy... Hmmmm. This has the potential to be better than the He-Man world... Off to read more!  
 urlLink 13:29 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I didn't blog yesterday. I sat down to though, if that counts. I was told by Lana that I had to play cards with her, Kelly, and Brit. She twisted my arm, as always. ;) Yesterday I cleaned Marcel's pool in the backyard and filled it. He's had a pretty rough time having his stuff packed up while we wait to move (the 5th!!!) so we decided to have a Marcel Day. He had two of his best buds over and they swam in the pool then painted after we all went out to dinner. Then Micah and I went to the movies. I would have stayed home but I had already bought my ticket online before Marcel Day was declared. I originally was gonna take Kelly with me since she's been having the opposite of my troubles lately. Here I am, bored out of my skull at home with nothing to do. I've torn through five books in the course of two and a half weeks, watched dozens of movies on DVD, slept, been to the movies a couple times, and slept some more. I can think of no crueler torture than boredom. I take that back. Kelly has been at home as well but with a whirlwind of drama going on. Escaping to her bedroom is only a temporary retreat. She wishes for ten minutes of peace where I'm ready to tear my hair out after five. When she came over and was de-stressing, I invited her to go along with me to see The Village at the midnight showing. She declined but her man Micah decided to go along (no vodka involved). We had to sneak Micah in since they were sold out. The theatre was pretty full but definitely not to capacity. Yeah, I'm trying to justify sneaking Micah in, so what? We had every intention of paying. Micah did buy one of those overpriced buckets of caffeine though. Hey, the movie was pretty good though. The beginning had me crawling in my seat though. It's a pretty bad start until you learn what the plot twist is, then it all makes sense. Definitely worth seeing again. Plus there's some pretty intense scenes too. I'll probably go see it again since I have almost a week to kill until move day. Well, I'm off to watch Donnie Darko now. 
 urlLink 14:46 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Got up around 9:30 today.&nbsp; Not much happened today.&nbsp; I did laundry, cleaned the kitchen, took out the trash, and did the dishes.&nbsp; I've been putting it off since my garbage disposal is broken and my landlord won't do anything about it.&nbsp; It's been broken now for about three months now and a raunchy smell comes from it when I run the water in that sink.&nbsp; I'll be so glad to get out of this house.  I made a couple Walmart trips with Marcel for some food and other necessities (four booster packs of Mirrodin and a G.I. Joe vehicle for Marcel).&nbsp; Like I said, an uneventful day.&nbsp; I watched a few more episodes of He-Man.&nbsp; I'm on Season two, episode 79.&nbsp; A pretty bland day.  I'll keep this one short since Kelly, Dosha, and&nbsp;Barb are coming by to play cards and watch a movie.&nbsp; I picked up "Lock, Stock, and Two Smoking Barrels" while on one of my Walmart trips today.&nbsp; I've seen it, but I thought Lana might like it too.&nbsp; At least, that's my excuse.&nbsp; ;)  Oh, I did see the new batman trailer!&nbsp; I had to watch it with no sound but I'm hyped.&nbsp; Plus over at  urlLink Cinescape.com &nbsp;they had what could be a possible photo leak of the new costume.&nbsp; I must say, I'm disappointed if it is.&nbsp; I was hoping since the movis is supposed to be a return to Batman's darker roots, I was hoping for the dark knight costume like the one in the  urlLink Batman - Dead End  movie.&nbsp; I'll still go see it though, rubber armor suit and all. 
 urlLink 23:30 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Up at 11am and out the door by 10pm.&nbsp; Amazing.&nbsp; I think I might actually be on the road to a regular schedule.&nbsp; I finally got the Owlcon trophies delivered.&nbsp; Yup, I just now got them delivered.&nbsp; Let's just say I won't be taking on any timely projects for other people.&nbsp; I'm too much of a procrastinator.&nbsp; I feel so bad about delivering the trophies so late I couldn't even think about accepting their money despite Angelo's insistence.&nbsp; I won't be volunteering to do trophies next year, to say the least.  The trip did me good though.&nbsp; I hooked up with him around 4pm, which gave me some time to kill, so I hit Half Price Books and Nan's Cards and Comics.&nbsp; I picked up a few more paperbacks to burn through since I won't be moving until next weekend&nbsp;(closing date is the&nbsp;5th).&nbsp; For the most part I just wandered around the stores, soaking up the relaxing vibes.  I love used bookstores.&nbsp; The smell of old books all around you, the quiet shuffling of people patiently looking for the right one, sitting quietly in a corner reading the first few pages of a book.&nbsp; Very therapeutic.  Nan's&nbsp;has the feel of a old used bookstore, but for me it's something a little more.&nbsp; As an&nbsp;Army brat who bounced around a lot, there aren't too many places I have a very long history with.&nbsp; Nan's is one of the exceptions.&nbsp;&nbsp;The first time my dad took me I was around 11 or 12 years old and I've been going there&nbsp;regularly since then.&nbsp; Every time we visited Houston while my dad was on leave, or later when I was, I made it a point to always make a Nan's Trip.&nbsp; I'm a recognized face (as is my son's now), I know the guys (and one gal) who work there, and the store has a lot of great memories attached to it.&nbsp; Comics I used to read, toys I used to own (or wanted), dusty games I played&nbsp;as a kid (Fireball Island rocks!),&nbsp; a small wall of paperback fantasy and sci-fi, and they even have a adult section for "mature audiences."&nbsp; For the most part, it's just a bunch of big breasted super chics who happen to lose there top every issue, nude figurines, and collectible playboy and hustler cards, and&nbsp;tasteful art books.&nbsp; Yeah, I've been in there since then since I'm now an "adult".&nbsp; I swear, I don't think I'm ever going to get used to being referred to as an adult.  Overall, a damn good day out of the house even if it was only for a few hours.&nbsp; Oh, I picked up some much needed (everything I get at Nan's is much needed) tiny dice and a new game.&nbsp; The game?&nbsp; Grass.&nbsp; You're a pot dealer competing to make the most money the fastest.&nbsp; First dealer to peddle 250K worth of weed, wins.&nbsp; It came in a hemp bag.&nbsp; I can't wait to play.&nbsp; :)  
 urlLink 23:46 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I actually got up before noon today!!&nbsp; I couldn't sleep so I finally decided to get up.&nbsp; I was shocked to see that it was 1100am considering I had been out till 3am playing cards and hanging out with Micah and Kelly.&nbsp; Then add onto that I had been out the previous night hanging out with Micah, Derek, Johnny, and Chris until 630am on Saturday playing arcade games.  Thanks to Micah, I've added another project to my list of Cool Things To Do.&nbsp; Micah is building an arcade cabinet.&nbsp; He downloaded a shitload (not just a buttload, but a shitload) of emulators for games like Contra, Streetfighter, Mortal Combat, Marvel Vs. Capcom, etc.&nbsp; Quiet literally hundreds of games.&nbsp; Like I said, a shitload.&nbsp; So now I've got this idea in my head for my own arcade system for my big screen (61in rear projector television).&nbsp; A table height cabinet on lock down wheels with a long A/V cable and power cord.&nbsp; I'm hyped just thinking about it.  On other good news?&nbsp; We heard back from our bank financing guy about our house.&nbsp; The house was appraised five thousand less than what the sellers were trying to sell it to us for.&nbsp; When the sellers found out, they dropped the price rather than going through the hastle of negotiating the cost, a new contract, etc.&nbsp; So hopefully by this weekend!!!!!!   Oh, here's a few links for DIY arcades from Micah to me to you.&nbsp; Enjoy!    urlLink http://www.mame.net/ &nbsp;&nbsp; - the emulator (also look for mame32 windows version)   urlLink http://www.rom-world.com/  - roms   urlLink http://www.romnation.net/  - roms   urlLink fceultra.sourceforge.net &nbsp; - NES Emulator   urlLink http://www.zsnes.com/  - SNES Emultaor   urlLink http://gens.consolemul.com/  - Sega Genesis emulator   urlLink http://www.shinytechnologies.com/nostalgia.php  - Intellivision emulator   urlLink http://webpages.charter.net/rbecker5/index.html  - cool Cabinet site with lots of links.   urlLink http://www.ultimarc.com/  - ipac and optipac boards   urlLink http://www.happcontrols.com/  - sticks, buttons, lightguns, spinners, etc.   urlLink http://www.byoac.com/  - build your own arcade controls   urlLink http://www.oscarcontrols.com/  - spinners and more 
 urlLink 12:43 
       |
          1 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I think I finally got this blogger thing tweaked out the way I want it.&nbsp; One of these days I'll actually learn CSS but until then it's just a bunch of trial and error (with lots of errors).&nbsp;  I think today I'm going to try and get out a bit before Lana goes to her party tonight.&nbsp; Maybe pick up a new movie or something.&nbsp; He-Man is starting to grow a little old (I have over 20 more disks to watch) and the more I watch it the more I want to GURPify it.&nbsp; With all my gaming stuff packed away, I really want to wait until we're in the new house.&nbsp; Arg.&nbsp; That was supposed to happen this weekend.&nbsp; I have patience for all the wrong things I think.&nbsp; Anyway.&nbsp; Off to the movie store.&nbsp; I feel like sci-fi tonight...&nbsp; Gawd, I gotta get outta this house.  
 urlLink 14:51 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, I finally did it.&nbsp; I switched to a real blog thingie.&nbsp; What finally prompted me to do so?&nbsp; Pure chance, actually.&nbsp; I just submitted my first Steve Jackson GURPS demo (which was accepted) and was contacted by the guy editing it.&nbsp; After reading his email I noticed he had a website posted at the bottom.&nbsp; So I followed it out of curiousity.&nbsp; He's the guy who wrote the GURPS SWAT book!&nbsp; How cool huh?&nbsp; He also has a blog (check it out at  urlLink brian underhill ).&nbsp; I didn't get around to reading any of it yet (though I plan on it) but I really liked his blog format and look.&nbsp; So I followed yet another link at the bottom...&nbsp; Yeah, I'm bad about that.&nbsp; I get lost in porn pop-ups, but who doesn't?&nbsp; Gotta be particularly careful now that I'm using Lana's computer since mine is down.&nbsp; ;)  Well, back to my He-Man episodes. 
 urlLink 22:51 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Been a lazy past few days.&nbsp; All my gaming stuff is packed up other than my GURPS stuff, all my costuming projects are shelved until the move and the radiator on the truck went out over the weekend.&nbsp; I have the worst luck with cars I think.&nbsp; It started out as a small leak at the airport picking Lana up.&nbsp; We canceled a weekend trip to San Antonio with my mother in law camping since I was scared it might not make it.&nbsp; So five hundred dollars lighter the truck has a new radiator.&nbsp; Not a major setback (never thought I'd hear myself say that about five hundred) but it did keep up cooped up in the house.&nbsp; Move day is now just pending on a house inspection (scheduled next week sometime) and a closing date set.&nbsp; Whooo hooo!!!&nbsp; It looks like I won't have to burn this house down after all.&nbsp; I'll be free soon!!&nbsp; So what have I been occupying my time with?&nbsp; Just about NOTHING other than watching movies and cleaning.&nbsp; I'm going to go crazy if we don't move soon just from sheer boredom.  Hey, saw a cool movie last night.&nbsp; I had never heard of it but I took a chance since I've really been trying to see movies with other people besides "A" list actors.&nbsp; Anyway, the movie is called  urlLink Love Object .&nbsp; It's got all the great elements of a good horror flick.&nbsp; Okay, this anal retentive guy orders a Love Doll.&nbsp; Not a blow up doll but a full-sized, made-to-order, silicone doll (with a built in jerk off hand).&nbsp; Yup, just like the ones found at  RealDoll.com .&nbsp; In fact, the ones used in the movie were direct from the factory from Real Doll.&nbsp; Anyway, he falls in love with this thing and begins to believe it's alive somehow when it begins to express jealousy towards a growing relationship he has with a woman at work, the woman he built his Love Doll to look like.&nbsp; I laughed, I cringed, I laughed some more, and in the end it creeped me out a bit.&nbsp; A true classic to be I think.&nbsp; Well, back to watching some He-Man with my little man.&nbsp; :)  
 urlLink 00:10 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Okay, so a out-of-the-house J-O-B isn't what a needed.&nbsp; I'm still a little on the restless side these days but I don't think getting a J-O-B is the solution.&nbsp; I work damnit.&nbsp; I keep a clean house (maybe not spotless), I do laundry (always behind but who isn't), I feed my clan (gotta love fast food), and then theirs the things I enjoy that I make time for.&nbsp; A little defensive?&nbsp; Sure, maybe but this staying at home thing can make you cagey.&nbsp; On one hand, I'm unemployeed ex-military, been out of the work force for three years, and my educational background stops at high school and a couple community college class credits.&nbsp; On the other, I spend more quality time with my son than most.&nbsp; I include him in most of what I do around the house, we rough play and bicker like brothers.&nbsp; Lana and I spend as much time as we want just "hanging out", watching movies, plaing games, and being around friends.&nbsp; I think my restlessness stems from me letting others defination of success cloud over my own.&nbsp; I don't need a J-O-B to structure my time around or define my success.&nbsp; I just need to remember what's important to me and keep my eyes on the prize. What got me thinking about the whole thing more was Lana.&nbsp; She just got back from a five day Banff Springs Hotel trip where she was pampered, compliments of Passion Parties, Inc. and C.J. Haynes interrogated her about me somewhere between the mud baths and massages.&nbsp; As Lana put it, the old woman told her she was limiting my potential.&nbsp; Told her she needed to let me know I was free to do the things I wanted to do and that I was supported.&nbsp; Here's the thing about C.J. Haynes.&nbsp; Here's a successfully shrewd business women in her sixties who Lana and I actually have a lot of admiration for in more ways than one.&nbsp; She's one of the founding women for the very successful company my Lana works for.&nbsp; She barely knows me but knew what I needed to hear.&nbsp; Hell, I didn't know I needed to hear it but I guess I did.&nbsp; Despite all the money this woman has earned with blood, sweat, and tears, she knew that the real prize isn't money, but family.&nbsp; I've always known that Lana supported me in whatever oddball ideas popped in my head, but sometimes you just gotta hear it I guess.&nbsp; So I'm going to make an effort to do the things I enjoy, make time for me, and stop putting them off.&nbsp; After all, I still have a full G.I. Bill waiting for me.&nbsp; Some sculpting classes, an art class or two, photography class, a welding course, start reading more like I used to, and writing. My point to all this rambling?&nbsp; I dunno, it's five in the morning and I need sleep.&nbsp; Why I woke up, I'm not sure.&nbsp; A little restless still I guess, but not an uneasy kind.&nbsp; Excited I guess.&nbsp; Lots of changes going on around this house lately.&nbsp; Marcel's turning six next month, he's lost two teeth, a family move is in the works into a house we've been drooling over for more than a year, and I'm back on focus I think.&nbsp; It's funny what a dark and quiet house will get you thinking about.&nbsp; Well, off to bed again.&nbsp; 'Night all. 
 urlLink 07:12 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm thoroughly exhausted. My feet ach, my legs throb and my back in humming away quietly. Remarkably though, I feel good. It's only a few hours til Zero Hour. The house is supposed to close at 10:00am tomorrow. I loaded the Uhaul up today. It'll take two trips but I've already loaded a majority of it up. We're on a bit of a time crunch though. We're paid up until Saturday with our landlord and Lana's going out of town on Friday morning. So that leaves me to do the unpacking, cleaning and sheet rocking in the bathroom. I'm prolly gonna hit up a few friends for a favor to help out with the time crunch(that's a hint mofo's!!!). I feel almost like a kid on Christmas eve. Tomorrow I'll be sleeping in my new house... Next time I blog, it'll be from the new house!! I've threatened Reggie, our bank guy, that I'll park the Uhaul in his front yard if I gotta wait any longer to get outta this house. I'm not sure if I was joking or not the more I think about it. ;) Well, I better get some sleep if I'm going to be worth a damn. 'Night.  
 urlLink 04:32 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today is Next Monday. I knew it was coming but I still can't help but get frustrated and mad. We're now looking at this Wednesday but it'll probably be Next Monday. Sometimes I just want to scream. It's all paperwork. I realize this but I can't help but hate it. Nothing to do but wait. Serious De ja vu here... Marcel was supposed to start school last Thursday. We figured him missing the first two days wasn't a big deal as we would be in the house by Next Monday. So here we are and Marcel still isn't' in school. Then Lana hit me with something we talked about years ago. Home schooling. I always wanted to do home schooling for Marcel but we never had the time and/or money to devote ourselves to it. With us both staying home and Lana pulling home a fat check every month, there's no more excuses and it's looking really great. I've been hitting all afternoon. If what I've read so far is true, Texas has no laws or regulations regarding home schooling. I've joined a few groups in Texas and plan on picking some brains in the next 24 hours. I think we're going to put Marcel in school until we know the ins and outs of all of it. For a week or two starting tomorrow. I'm really excited about it and I think Lana is too. Marcel's not sure what to think of it just yet. We told him the pros and cons of it and asked him to think about it. Meanwhile, I'm wondering how we're going to move, get the power turned over, the telephone transferred, water turned on, cable up and running all before our landlord Elmor gives us the boot here since we're only paid up for this month. Lana's gonna try and sweet talk the home owners into letting us get all that transferred/turned on so we can start moving in before the final closing date. I'm hungry. Maybe I should eat to stave off the bitchiness. I still wanna scream though. Arg. Gonna go clean the house a bit and get some food. Later. 
 urlLink 16:26 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Last night I dragged some of the guys out to see the new AVP movie. It was a midnight premiere on an Imax screen. They had two screens open and it was pretty full. I have to say, the movie was much better than I thought it would be. Lots of action and pretty fast-paced. There were a few things I didn't like about it but nothing major other than the ending. Total cheese. I won't give it away but any fan of the Alien and/or predator movies will enjoy it for what it is. As a bonus there was some major hotties at the theatre. Micah and I had a good conversation about the movie on the ride home and got into much heavier conversation when we got to his house. The girls were watching X Men 2 and we ended up getting into a little debate as to the possibility of peaceful coexistence of mutants and humans. Personally, I don't see it possible. I'm a firm believer that man has deluded himself into thinking he's no longer an animal and is above the survival instinct. Hate and fear (as well as all other emotions) are all just instictive survival tools that allow him to assure the survival of the species, not the individual. To make a long story short, I believe that hate, fear, and all the other emotions man has deemed socially unacceptable are all a necessary part of the human psyche and are just as crucial to species survival. Like all survival traits though, the pack must cull out the extremes that could hurt the survival of the group. Anyway, a deeper argument for another time. ;) I found something really cool online today looking for more examples of the predator costumes. Marcel has, yet again, changed his mind on his Halloween costume. I'm really sort of relieved because a Buzz Lightyear costume would be possible but difficult with time running short. Anyway, I found the official website of the guys who did the  urlLink Batman - Dead End  film. They are now making a Batman and Superman Teamup Movie!! I downloaded the trailer and can't wait for the movie to come out. Other news? The house survey didn't get faxed over in time to our bank guy for it to close today so it's been postponed to... Next Monday, of course.  I did pricing for my NES emulator system and the computer cost is going to be 525. That's not including the cost for four joysticks, buttons, and the ipac board. It's cheaper than most arcade cabinets though since I won't be buying wood or a monitor so I'm saving at least a couple hundred. I'm still pretty hyped. Here's a mockup of what the controllers will look like. The controller shell is longer than the original Advantage and will be custom built out of fiberglass with a plywood bottom. I'll make a mockup out of wood (beveled edges, routed lines, and button holes), make a negative out of silicone from that, a mothermold out of plaster, and cast them in fiberglass. I think it'll work. My ebay purchase (three NES systems, two paddles, and an Advantage) ship on Monday. I plan on rebuilding the old NES cabinet Mike and me had as kids to house the whole thing since I can't find one online. They used to sell em at Toys R Us. It was a small cabinet on wheels, a shelf for your NES, a door below for your controllers and a shelf below for your games. The whole planning phase of this project is distracting me from the perpetual Next Monday I keep hearing will eventually come. Off to the Movie store. I'm gonna go pick up Predator and Alien on DVD if I can find em. Costume Research. ;) 
 urlLink 15:43 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Despite having slept in some today and finding out that our move has been delayed until next Monday (insert scream here), I have to say it's been a very productive and enjoyable day. I've been really stuck on the idea of creating a emulator arcade for my big screen tv. The other day I was roaming through Kroger for a lack of anything better to do, when I picked up a computer magazine. I proceeded to camp in the magazine department despite how much I hate how people do that and began reading an interesting article on a cool case mod. This guy had turned two cases and various car parts into a cool computer case mod. When I got home all I could think about was how cool that was and how I could do it better.  So I hit the net looking for different ideas on case mods when I came across  urlLink mini-itx.com . One the site the sell mini motherboards, power supplies, and hard drives to construct - well, mini computers. Then they proceed to show you examples of how you can creatively utilize these mini computers. Suddenly guys are turning everything from toasters to Commodore 64's into mini computers. The one that caught my attention was the one that turned a  urlLink NES  into a emulator. Then it hit me. I could make my emulator system an old NES case and use the casings for the old NES Advantage for the controllers!!! Micah and I started brainstorming, and before too long, we had a plan on to do just that. That led to a pawn shop trip (looking for a NES case), Nan's and Gatti's with the kids (to look at some actual arcades). Most of the time we spent bouncing ideas off each other. We decided to pull Derek, another good idea kindda guy, into it.  Trust me, we had to twist his arm really hard. Initially, we planned on roleplaying but we were just too distracted by the whole process of brainstorming. Before too long we somehow came to the idea that we should make our own short films. Hours later, a coke run (Mountain Dew but everything in Texas is coke) , and a food run, we had an awesome plot lined out that we weren't just happy with, but hyped about. I'm pretty excited and can't wait to actually start writing it out with the guys. It'll be the first writing project I've taken on collaboratively. I'm excited. The story has a lot of heart I think. Hell, I'd pay to see it if it was a movie. Hey, we could be the next Kevin Smith, Matt Damon, and Ben Aflick trio. I think I'd be the Kevin Smith. He's the super cool guy. I'm sure some might argue, but it's my fantasy so screw you. ;) Been a busy day and my head is still buzzing with ideas. How to build the NES emulator and controllers, our Halloween costume projects, the initial writing for the short films. Do I need sleep??? It seems like such a burden sometimes. Arg. I guess I'll go harass Lana. 'Night. 
 urlLink 04:53 
       |
          2 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's been a busy day. We woke up around our usual time today, around 1pm, but decided to actually get moving before the day was shot. I wasn't really feeling up for the drive to the beach like Marcel was, so we compromised. We grabbed a few towel and hit the pool at the Y. Marcel loves the water and has always firmly believed he can swim despite contrary evidence. Today he actually did a little on his own. Okay, so he had a little help from a life jacket. He's been telling everyone that will listen that he swam without help from his daddy. He's told me at least a dozen times today and I was there. What really got me today though was watching him play tag with a few kids he met there. It may not seem like that big of deal to most, but I was never (and still aren't) much of a socializer. To watch my own son strike up a conversation with two older boys who he didn't know and start a game of tag was simply amazing to me. I was mesmerized. I found myself numerous times trying to keep from laughing out loud when I saw how much fun they were having. I now know what my dad meant when he once told me he sometimes wished he could jump in like one of the kids when he'd hear my own few friends and me playing. I wasn't the only one though. This somehow tangible  excitement  the three of them were unknowingly pouring out soon had all the kids out of the pool and playing tag. If you have kids, you know how great a feat it is to convince them out of the water without pulling them out bodily. Hell, I wish I could have jumped in the game. You ever envy a child for no other reason then the want of a good game of tag in the sprinklers? Anyways. Afterwards, we went for snowcones. While not as great as the ones my brother and I enjoyed after a busy day at the beach in Hawaii, the place off Normandy and Market serve a mean rainbow. After that? We hit the Movie Trading Company and picked up the first season of a new Spiderman show. I had Johnathan and Marian for the night too so we spent the evening on the couch eating ice cream and watching cartoons. I had to grudgingly send them to bed when they started passing out on the couch. It's three in the morning and I need to figure out where I'm sleeping. Marcel, Johnathan, and Marian are hogging up a king size bed in the manner only a child can; all limbs flailed out in every direction so that ever quarter inch of bed is claimed. Marian fell asleep on my chest while I watched a movie. I forgot how good a feeling that is. I think I'll just squeeze in with em. 'Night.  
 urlLink 03:36 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Lana's off on another business trip. It's a car party for one of her girls. We stayed up until her flight had to leave doing laundry, and watched a movie, among other things that are nonyabusiness. I'm bloggin on my computer! Yup, it's up and running now. I'm now running 2GHz and 512 RAM!! My computer sounds like a damn helicopter taking off thanks to the megafan I bought, but I have a computer again and don't have to submit myself to the smoke room to check my email. Speaking of email... The mystery email was from an old friend of my mom's. To make a long story short, a lot bad memories came back. I had posted previously on the whole thing, but I felt it was a bit too personal. (Never blog when your in a bad mood.) The year the two of them became best friends was the same year my dad left for Korea for a year. My mom clung to her newly found faith in the church and I became a introvert (I guess I never grew out of it). We fought constantly, sometimes physically. It was one of the worst times of my life. I was at that horrible year of thirteen, my dad was gone, and my mom was struggling by herself with two boys. I felt so alone. One of the most horrible memories I have was celebrating my dad's birthday that year. His duffel bags were packed, the candles on the cake were lit, and he was in his uniform. The only time I've seen my dad look more miserable was at my mom's funeral. I don't think we even bothered to cut the cake. We dropped him off at the airport that night. When my dad returned he found an angry teenager, a reborn Christian wife, and a confused eight year old who was stuck in the middle. The church's pull almost tore our family apart. To say I harbor some bad feelings towards the church and some of the members is an understatement. They made what was an already hard situation unbearable. I've been sitting at her email for a day wondering how to reply. I know now looking back she was doing what she thought best, and trying to help us but I just feel that some things a family must get though together to bring them together. I don't know. I'll email her tonight after I've thought about it some more. For now though, Marcel and I are going to go eat and catch a movie. I hate when Lana's not here. The house gets so quiet. 
 urlLink 18:41 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well, I finished  urlLink Heroes Die  today. I haven't read a book that good in a while. I had to sit awhile and just digest the ending. I can't say enough positive things about the story and can't wait to wrap my hands around the sequel to it. I see now it's going on my Favorite Books list. I'll probably go out to the bookstores tomorrow and see if I can't find it. What else have I got time to do right? Arg. Now concerning this weird email I got. I sat down to check my email before curling up on the coach with some grub when I see an email titled "Colorado Springs, CO??? " I get a LOT of junk mail in my hotmail account. It's been an active account now for over ten years now and I use it for all those things online that require an email addy. The title caught my attention though since my family used to live there. My dad was stationed there for four years and I spent some of my most turmoiled youth there. It's a place that has a lot of very fond memories as well as painful. I've always wanted to go back. I know that most of the people I knew back then have probably moved away but I'd like to see the places I remember again. I still keep touch with a friend of the family who lives there and it would be nice to see her again. The email pretty much just asked if I was the same Camacho family she/he knew. This person knew my birthdate so I was a little thrown back. The name does sound vaguely familiar but that's all. He/she said they had been looking for us and there seemed to be a bit of urgency to the email. I did respond though. I'm nervous as all hell about it. Like I said, a lot of fond memories as well as painful. I guess I'll find out soon enough who it is that not only remembers me and my family but has been looking for us.  
 urlLink 01:15 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was out pretty late last night so, again, no blog. Lana came home from her party and mentioned the Dosha was  really  wanting to karaoke. I shudder at the word now. It's not that they sing bad, but last time we got together for games and the K word Micah, Dosha, and Chris ended up karaoke'in all night long. I eventually ended passing out on the coach listening to karaoke follow me in my sleep. So I when the girls came to pick us up for some karaoke action, I hung back, bought me a movie ticket to see The Bourne Supremacy online, and told Lana to call me on the cell phone when they were done with karaoke. I just didn't wanna ruin everyone else's fun and be bored. I can be bored at my house. The movie was pretty good. The car chase was a dizzying experience that almost made me nauseous but in a fun roller coaster sort of way. Lana might argue with me on that one and just call it nauseating but she'll torture her way through it just to see Matt Damon. Sorry ladies, no new "Shampoo Scene" in this one. We ended up playing a few rounds of Hiding Go Peek A Boo until everyone was too tired or too hot to continue, then talked about movies that scarred us as children. Poltergeist; my cousin Siris had a clown that looked just like the one that pulled that kid under the bed and tried to kill him. Cats Eye; Who hasn't heard the noises in their room and thought something was coming after them? Jaws; I was living in Hawaii when this damn thing came out.  Twilight Zone The Movie;  That goblin scared the piss outta me as a kid when it licked the glass. I could go on and on, but I should get my day started now.  Later! 
 urlLink 14:52 
       |
          0 comments 
       
 

						
</post>


</Blog>