<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My new site is up, the pictures on my weblog are fixed, and I created a chatroom... yay? 
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's official, my new website, PepinHazan.com, will be up within the next 2 days!  The blog will soon be hosted there as well, so say goodbye to that ad the top of the screen.  I also created the  urlLink H.P. Shrine , a site dedicated to HiggedyPiggedy.com (no longer in exsistence).  The pictures in this blog don't work right now.  That will be fixed soon.  Bye!
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry for not posting lately.  I'll go back to daily entries when I'm done changing domains.  When will that be?... Soon
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not much to say right now, but I've been thinking about changing my domain name to something else, so check back here if you can't access my site in the coming months.
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's a game you probably haven't heard of...:  In the upcomming Gamecube Game, Amazing Island, you will be able to draw monsters on-screen, and the game will actually smooth and render them in 3d.  You can also apply different textures to them.  urlLink Amazing Island E3 Trailer  On another note, I added a poll to the side of this page, and I deleted the guestbook back at HiggedyPiggedy.com.  Lastly, if you're a mac user, here's a trick:  Open a bunch of windows, and, while holding option+shift, minimize the one in the front.  It's like magic!
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I found this odd animated gif while browsing a messageboard, so I posted it here for all to see.  Enjoy!  
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is one of the   C  R  A  Z  I  E  S  T   sites I've ever seen:  urlLink www.com: the web starts here...  
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For any mac users reading, I hightly reccomend downloading the FREE utility, Wiretap.  It allows you to record any sound your mac is making using a simple tape recorder interface.  When you're done recording, it saves the sound as an aiff file.  It's probably the easiest method I've found for recording streaming audio.  Just remember that it records ALL sounds your machine is making, not just the sound from the application in the foreground.  urlLink Wiretap (requires OS 10.2+) 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm completely overhauling my website, so I won't be posting for a week or two.
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I made  lots of changes to the interface today, so go to my website and check them out.
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I added some buttons to the toolbar on my website today.  This was pretty short... oh well.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've finished the new site, and it's being uploaded right now.  Here's a list of some changes/additions:    1.  A site history page    2.  Frames and No Frames views    3.  Typos on the chat page have been fixed    4.  Obsolete contact information in the imac guide is fixed    5.  The frames version has a toolbar    6.  The Links page is updated    7.  I have added to the FAQ page    8.  The site now is viewable is resolutions of 800x600+ On a sadder note, the following pages have been removed:    1.  The screen resolution page has been deleted    2.  The E3 info in the basement has been deleted    3.  The old interface is nowhere to be seen (maybe a good thing) On yet another note, about that list of my favorite games... I just bought Golden Sun:  The Lost Age, and I think a may have a new number 5.  Also, I realize that Rayman 2 is not a Nintedno-exclusive game, so please don't email me about that.  Also, I just downloaded GameTracker.  It's a program for Mac OS X that lets you keep track of your videogame collection.  I don't have much use for it, but I like the rating feature.  If you lend videogames to friends a lot, it might be useful.  Also, if you use  urlLink Gamefly , it might help you keep track of what make you already rented.  If you would like to download this program, visit its website  urlLink here .  Lastly, if you remember, a while back I posted an entry about Wiretap for Mac OS X.  I forgot to mention that you can also use it to record music from save-disabled music composition demos.  You should still buy the product, because doing this is a pretty tedious process, but if you just want one song, and you don't mind using AIFF format, you might want to try it.  Check out the new interface of my website, and have a great day.  Bye!  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I recieved the Novell Suse Linux Technical Resource Kit.  Unfortunately, I don't have any computers capable of running Suse 9.1 (I use  a mac).  If I ever download a ppc linux distribution, I might be able to salvage the applications on the disks, so all is not lost.  In other news, today I started working on the new interface for my new domain.  I'm not going to make any promises about when it will be uploaded.  You can't rush these things, but when it's up, It'll be GREAT!!!
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have nothing to right about.  I promise this won't happen again; at least not tomorrow(:
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was bored, and I didn't know what to post here today, so here I go.  Pepin Hazan's Top 5 Favorite Videogames (on Nintendo Systems)  5- Golden Sun 4- Rayman 2:  The Great Escape 3- Sword of Mana 2- The Legend of Zelda:  Link's Awakening 1- Donkey Kong 64  What are yours?  Please post any comments. Bye!   
    
</post>


</Blog>