<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Whoa, PRAISE THE LORD!!! Things just keep getting better! Today, it was raining at my place in the morning, other people may think it is gloomy start to the day, but I just loved the cool breeze and listening to the rhythem of the falling rain... haha.... went to do my QT and then took a lovely chicken pie for breakfast(mum's cooking is the best, man!" After that, I bid Wenhan farewell and all the best as he went for his prelim oral... Then I went into my technology centre, put on my dustcoat and started preparing for the operation on No. 5, it was quite a daunting task and if I ever had a disappointing time today, this would be it... a bit of CA(superglue thingy) and eproxy(strong glue thingy) and some sawing and grinding. Before I knew it, the preparation work was done, and the only thing that was left was .... well... nothing... haha, I needed the plywood and balsa wood to do the neccessary patch work... By now, it was time for lunch and I was called in for a sumpteous meal by my mum...(told you mum is the best cook), my dad was tired out by not enough sleep last night, so he told me there was a slight possiblility that I would not be able to go and get materials... It didn't really matter to me, so I went back to "vomit in the toilet"(a phrase I use to mean outputing of info(thinking) in my technology centre(toilet))... My dad managed to get his work done eventually(thank God) and we had enough time to go down to Fook Hai... This was where the fun started... ahh, I can't control myself... I shall just say what cool stuff I bought today... =P  Of course I got the "skin" for No. 5...    I upgraded this...   (Sanwa RD6000, 6 channel)  to THIS!!!   (Futaba 9C, 9 channel)  Whoa, I tell you, this really made my day, cos one of these babies cost about $775!!!  I did get some fuel tubing also...   And a spare glow plug...    As it was, I think my dad had already spent a bomb on my and I was smiling like an idiot, but check this out... one step out of the shop and guess what my dad says..." I think you are good enough, do you want a Scanner?" i was like so shocked lor....... I said, then I would need another engine... He said, yah go ahead.... WHOAOAOAOOA!!!!!  So I got a SCANNER!!!    and an O.S. 46 AX   (with a fibre glass prop...)  How could the day get any better huh?... =P  Feeling in seven heaven and cloud nine at the same time....=P  Can't believe it...=P  Coming back to earth here... you guyz know that there is a very rich guy in my estate? He has a house that has 7 cool cars? SEVEN!!! including BMW 7 series, Lamborghini Diablo, Porshe 996, Jaguar XJR(4.2 litres,supercharged....), Mercedes SL 500, Ferrari 360 Mondana and check this out....    A LOTUS V8!!! sorry lah... will try to get pics of the other cars soon... only managed to sneak past his house and take this pic.... his house is like showroom lor.... heehee.... (fyi, me next door neighbour's son drives a Honda Integra... !)          READ: Genesis 40    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A few things I would like to address:  1. Thank GOD for His guidience through today's piano exam  2. Thank you to all who have kept me in their prayer  3. Thank you Teacher Dorothy...your exam preparation was so good...you really are the best!   Now, informally, I think I had a very good day... My piano exam is not bad, thank you, but not excellent... People on MSN Messenger keep telling me not to think in terms of being best, but I am a perfectionist lah, don't make me feel what I don't like to feel, leh... heee... anyway, the latest in sport: I played&nbsp;with Nicholas today, so unexpected, so unprepared, but whats a hustler if he is not given a challenge once in a while? hee... Anyway, I finished my piano exam and happened to bump into Nicholas on the bus(with his cue lah!), so he chio me go and play... so I played without my glove, my jump cue, Excalibur, and worst of all, without Scorpion! We both had an 8ball warmup rack and them prceeded to have two races to five. Nicholas won the first rack convincingly 5-1 with a couple of good memorable shots. I managed to win the next race 5-2, with only one nice shot on the last rack, a thin lengthwise double last shot on the 8 ball and rolling the cue ball nicely back for the&nbsp;9 ball. Haha... may go down to Fook Hai tomorrow and buy a transmitter and wood to heal No. 5...       READ:&nbsp;Genesis 39      Are&nbsp;you a&nbsp;Follower?&nbsp; 
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       STRESS!!! Tomorrow, my piano&nbsp;exam lah.... Please pray for me... Really need help here.... Thank you all.... Doing this during C Programming class in school... haha... won't have time to blog at home cos will be preparing for exam... Tomorrow, may the glory be to God and God alone...     &nbsp;    READ:&nbsp;Gensis 37      Are&nbsp;you a&nbsp;Believer? &nbsp;  
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Gotta a new old phone today&nbsp; :&nbsp; Motorola E365! Finally got a camera phone! WHOA !!! best part is, i traded in and only had to pay $60! What a feeling man! Those who know me well will know that I love clamshell phones, but too bad, too expensive, so I went for this... Played pool today with Sylvester, got trashed inside out... he says i'm out of form, but i guess there is an element of luck.... Besides, i'm not that good am i??? Anyway,in the midst of all the materialistic stuff guess what my QT was about...     &nbsp;       READ:&nbsp;Gensis 34        Are&nbsp;you a&nbsp;Good Soldier?&nbsp;      Key verse: "But three days later, when their wounds were still sore, two of Dinah's brothers, Simeon and Levi, took their swords, entered the town without opposition, and slaughtered every man there,..."-v25&nbsp; 
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Tuesdays... the longest day of the week....8 to 5.... haha... but im not complaining... it was quite dull today at Critical Reasoning Skills(CRS) class... normally, its quite bubbly and stuff like that, but today was way off... became like an english lesson.... haha... probably not used to it cos haven't been in an education system for three months... anyway, today was pretty nice when i managed not to fall asleep during Electrical Technology Class ( though it was still very boring . . .=(&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; )... wanna play pool, 4 days never shot already.... tomorrow have to kill time between 11am to 3pm... wanna play? call me lah....          READ:&nbsp;Gensis 28:36, &nbsp;Genesis 33 &nbsp;&nbsp;       Are&nbsp;you a&nbsp;Apologizer?&nbsp;      Key verse: "Then Jacob went on ahead. As he approached his brother, he bowed low seven times before him."-v3 
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Whoa sianz lahz.... 11 aug got free joyride at Youth flying club, wanna go but got some stupid self-mangement workshop....*sigh*... wat to do.... real tired also lah... today 8 to 4.... not complaining, but got piano practice today.... check out my QT today... what a great reminder the Lord gave at the beginning of this day...     &nbsp;    &nbsp;     READ: Genesis 32 : 22-32      &nbsp;     Are&nbsp;you a&nbsp;Wrestler?      &nbsp;    Key verse: "Then the man said," Let me go for it is dawn." But Jacob panted," I will not let you&nbsp;&nbsp; go unless you bless me."-v26     &nbsp;
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hiz all... erm... dunno really wat to say lah.... not very good at this kinda stuff... i start writing normally and you guyz&nbsp;start saying it sounds too formal.... DARE 1A01 will noe lah...&nbsp;anyway... i thought i might get a blog cos its somewhere i can put all my stuff... release any kind of who noes wat in me.... will try to make this an interesting place to be....     &nbsp;   Today i kinda had a minor crash... No. 5 took a turn for the worse when it stalled during take-off.. well here is the broken fuselage...          &nbsp;   the engine is still intack, thank God... (its abt $150 if it gets incinerated)... will be doing repairs ASAP... check out the photo...         i'll need to go down to NTC Engineering Hobbies at Fook Hai to get some plywood and balsa to  heal  my plane...      For the benefit of those who don't fly, here are some pictures of what aeromodelling is (or was)  all about...     ____________________________________________________     A Picture of&nbsp;No. 1       No. 3... I think i may want to do her up some day... fix her and maybe fly her again??? who knows?         This is X-1( a B2 Bomber) electric glider i flew at Bedok Reservoir...      &nbsp;      Some of the electronics you have to do if you wanna start this hobby....       The reciever unit onboard all the planes to control the servo mechanisms...    &nbsp;   Over and out guyz!    ____________________________________________________     &nbsp;   [[Faded out at 2 205db]]    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       OOoo... common tests coming up soon... will be busy studying from around now till the Sept. holidays...need prayer from all, health detoriorating proportionally with stress...  today got some silly CIP thingy which lasts till 10pm tonight.... got to go... C Prog Class now...    ____________________________________________________   [[Faded out at 0829db]]  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       C Prog class now... steal some time to blog... feeling a little sick, caught a cold yesterday.... well something to pray fro me about i guess... gonna buy Need For Speed : Underground today....cool man... NFSU!!! finally!!! can play already! last time, gavin lend me, cannot play.... haha... gtg... write cya soon!      ____________________________________________________   [[Faded out at 1557db]]  
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey guyz... internet bill very high this month, parents got mad... so this will be the last of my regular blog entries... if i update my entries, that's either because i'm in school or i'm using someone elses internet access... erm... quite sad abt this rite now... dun really noe how to blog... pls pray tt i may have time to study and play at the same time, like timemanagement... also, please pray that i may not stray away from Him(the only Lord my God)... thx all, hope to see you guyz soon... will miss you....            Till the next entry,   Nat Xie      ____________________________________________________   [[Faded out at 2308db]]  
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       whoa, stayed awake at the most boring of classes... (its a miracle!!!)... i normally am not very good at chemistry stuff so engineering materials is always a challenge for me... today i made it, with less sleep then usual... anyway, today was pretty cool doing a tensile test on brass and copper... Nested if function is so cool(erm... this is abt C Programming)...          READ: Genesis 45   
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        all through the night, when everyone's in bed, I sawed and screwed my airplanes parts to hasten the process, of building my plane... of building my plane, the plane which i had just bought, last saturday...(to the tune of the Gardenia song) 
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       haha... no CRS today...(Critical Reasoning Skills)... , could go home at 3 today...haha, no class cos our teacher has some national day celebration performance thingy... haha... oh yah... psssst... fyi, my teacher is Actor Edmund Chen's sister, how cool is that man?! Anyhow, today, I managed to continue building No.9( the new SCANNER)... mounted three servos(throttle, elevator and rudder) and the new OS 46 AX engine... eh, go to go, cos got some work to do and my mum is walking right behind me...        READ: Genesis 42  
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tired... exhausted... dead... in SP Avaiation Planning Committee now, the 5th committee or 5th Squadron as they like to call it... anyhow, it doesn't make a difference... Squadron meeting yesterday from 5+ till 7:30... got gastric when I got home for dinner at 8:30...=X... so i'm sorry for the lack of this blog yesterday... struggling to finish my homework, tutorials for Dipolma Plus... Yeah, the University maths 1 thingy... Do pray for me yeah?        READ: Genesis 41   
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       haha... typed this during C Programming class again... hee... teacher pacing up and down... must try to avoid being detected.... hee... anyway, sorry for the lack of blog last night, too busy trying to finish my SCANNER and heal No.5... haha didn't managed to achieve any of the above though =P. Will blog in another entry tonight for today... for now, stay cool and come back often k?      ____________________________________________________       [[Faded out at 0825db]]  
    
</post>


</Blog>