<Blog>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey all im so0o bored ......today i was a perfect day for a party! lol too bad i couldn't throw one but n e wayz i feel really alone right now i wish i could see my ex-boyfriend he is like my best guy friend ever! He's really understanding and cute and funny and i think i like him again but i would never have another chance with him :-( too bad but I'm excited to see what the future will hold for me in the catagory of guys!!!       &nbsp;   your till the heart breaks,     Sammi aka Samantha   
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    this is when i went to mahoney a couple hours ago!!! This was a pretty shot i thought and i cant wait to go back there again!&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    gotta love me&nbsp; urlLink   
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Elmo rocks!!!      PiEcEs Of Me      on a monday i am waiting on a tuesday i am fading into your arms......      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; ashley simpson      Hey all today i woke up around 9:30 a.m. and im just enojoying the marvelous day it is outside .....It's beautiful and i love every minuite of it! Today i really want to throw a party with all my old elementary school buddies!!! Cuz one of them is my crush.....But im not getting into that and the other one is my best friend and the other ones are just awesome people i could never give up on!!!        &nbsp;    Brian,Derek,Daniel,Brii      ^^^Ponca peeps!!!!!      lol enouf about that i think im going to go roc climbing today!!!! Sounds adventurous and fun and i want to climb cuz i miss climbing!!! At camp I climbed every morning for a week!!! I love climbing because you can allways go back or go on with new and exciting challenges!!!! I think it shows everybody something and how to live you have to move on to make it to the stop but just because your stuck doesn't mean you have to fall!!!      SoRrY foR BoRiNg EvErYbOdY wItH mY sTuPiD thEoRy On LiFe!!!   
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey everybody im so0o bored so if anybody wants to chat about music t.v. celebrity's gossip clothes shoes or anything becides suicide or killings then im me at softballgirl9219 on aim or email me at  urlLink www.blondy92191@2die4.com &nbsp;and i hope everybody has a safe night.......     p.s. all i really need to meet some peeps on this hello thing so please if you see this add me to your hello buddylist if you have hello!!!       &nbsp;   yours till the dog barks,     Sammi aka Samantha     p.p.s. i need a boy!   
      
</post>


</Blog>