<Blog>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hello, Mr. Police Offficer, knocking at my door. I am just a black woman&nbsp;but you accuse me of being a whore. Just because you are prejuduice, I am getting all of this torture. You come around the block everyday to see if I'm on the corner.  Hello again, Mr. Police Officer. No, I'm not a crackhead.  I am just a lawyer, but you hate for it to be said. A black woman, a lawyer? This truly cannot be. A black woman out there making more money than me?  Hello, Mr. Police Officer, pulling out your gun. This time you come around saying that I abuse my son. Hold up, Mr. Officer, out of all these things you accuse of me You find out I"m just a black woman trying to live free. 
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't never dream about becomin' a milionaire. And becomin a famous actress is almost completely rare. But when I dream, I dream big. I dream I'll make it far. I dream I'll make it out the ghetto, and that's shootin for the stars.  Some people dream of bein' rich, some don't wanna be poor, But I just dream of goin to school and livin a little more. You see- livin' a ghetto life is not an easy thing to do. And when I wake up and someone's gone- it really ain't nothin' new.  So when you dream of yo' fancy cars and yo' fancy cup of tea, I'm dreamin' to make it out the ghetto, I'm dreamin' to live free. So, all ya'll dreamers, keep on dreamin'. But yo' dream ain't as big as mine. Cause I'm gone make it out the ghetto, and I'm gone make it just fine.  
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We all sleep with a piece of sound mind that the birds will sing in tomorrow's beam of light. So rest assured are we that the moon will glow and the angels will twinkle at night.  Why not do we have this same devotion to the heavenly substance we possess in our hearts? Creating this morbid seed of doubt, we manifest little monsters that nest in the crevices of our souls, preying on that murky filth.  We were perfectly created, created we were with impeccable flaws.  To each mound of wrinkled flesh was something given that was sacred.  We are all blessed with this gift that is richer than the gold on heaven's floors, mor pure than the pearls on its gates, even more precious than the diamonds that sparkles its doors.  It is not governed by laws, but is free as the angels that soar throughout the universe.  The essence of it precedes everything else that festers in this carnal entity.  I have faith in this completely!  It is what makes the grains of every planet, the star dust of every galaxy, the drops of all oceans, and the particles of every man.  It represents what is above as to what is below.  It is undying love......So I must trust it.....I freely let it grow.
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One night as I got on my knees and said my prayers, I told God that sometimes, I wondered if he cared. I stated simply that I felt like the modern day Job. Plainly, I wished my life's purpose would just unfold. As I was on my knees, I notified him of my doubt. "If you are God, please hear my cry and help me out! I was told that you are fantasy, you're really not true, For what God with so much pride would choose to be invisible?" Now, I didn't believe that because I remember when you were in my life. You took good care of me and you carried me when my mind was filled with strife. But, lately it seems you've disappeared. You don't think I need help? I sincerely do, all of this stress in interferring with my health. You have all of the souls that were most dear to me. You have Grandma, Grandaddy, my brother, and my babies. You took them from me and left me here all alone. Even you left with them to their newfound home. What am I supposed to do? Are you there? Can you hear? Until I get an answer, I'm not gettin up from here! You said you wouldn't leave, but I no longer feel you around. You're supposed to be God, but it sems when I pray you don't even hear a sound. Look, I believe in you, I need you in my life. I been on my knees all night long, please show me a sign.  My Child, please get up and look at the clock. I am your shepherd, you will always be apart of my flock. I haven't left your side- You just needed time to grow, And I didn't take your family, they were ready to come home. So, get up, stop cryin, and just look at the time. Please, my child, you said that you wanted a sign. So, after it seemed as if I had been prayin' for hours, I got up and looked at the clock to see the extent of his power. When I noticed the time, I really couldn't believe my eyes, For what I thought were hours, were only minutes, just five.
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      If tomorrow never comes for me, To all my Thug Misssus, Keep on keepin' on and kick it as if I never existed. The first day I take my last breath should be the only day you mourn, And don't cry about my pain and suffering, just cry because I'm gone. And take every day after my last day and commence to celebrate. Celebrate all the joy and smiles I bought to people's face. Celebrate cause I ain't got no bills, no trials, and no sorrw. Celebrate cause I ain't gone feel the pain that comes with tomorrow.  If tomorrow never comes for me, To all my Thug Brothas Rest assured I'm in a better place cause everyday here is a struggle. Get you another pack and flip it - Keep on makin' loot, And don't forget, I'm a soldier- give me a 21 gun salute. Take that fifth of hen that ya'll know I just couldn't pass up, And take it to the head for me, but don't end up assed up. My flesh is dead- but my soul lives on, I'm gone be everywhere. So roll a few blunts, and don't be stingy, put some of it in the air.  And if you don't feel what I'm sayin' as I'm writin' down these words, That's because you ain't never felt the pain of tomorrow's burn.
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I never wanted you to be perfect. I fell in love with a man who had flaws. I never expected you to say everything right and agree with me just because. I never believed that you would love me right from the start, And I never thought I wouldn't have control of giving you my heart.  I love you because you're imperfect, that's what gives us that shine. I love you because we ague, and whent he fight is over, you're still mine. I love you because we're compatible, your rights make up for my wrongs. I love you because even when I'm mad, Your arms is wher I belong.
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Regardless of my faults, regardless of my fears, Regardless of my problems, regardless of my tears, Regardless of my color, regardless of my class, Regardless of the love affairs I've had in my past.  Forget about my shoes, forget about my clothes, Forget about my pain & strife, forget about my foes, Forget about my money, forget about my car, Forget about my education taking me very far.  Just look past my beauty, & look deep into my eyes, Just look past all the pain and all the tears I cry, Just look past my fumbles, and look past my pride, Just look past my skin, and look really deep inside,  And tell me now.....Will you still love me?
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      On days when all is beautiful and everything is going my way, And trials don't pass my door path; they refuse to blemish my day. When all my bills are paid and I have extra money to spend, And just for an instant I wish the day would never end. I know it's you in heaven smiling down upon my life, And making sure your sister's day has not even a hint of strife.  On days when there's no sunshine and the world outside is cold, And nothing seems to go right, and I don't want to live old. When misfortune draws near and never goes away, And worry tries to tear me up and consume my whole day. I know one thing I can count on that will brighten up my while Is to think of you up there lookind down upon me with a smile.  Your beautiful ghetto smile, filled with pure rays of gold Left us entirely too soon, for it was too great for earth's hold. But all of us who knew you will never forget your shine. We'll never forget our brother, whose soul conquered time. God took you because he couldn't find a heart that was better, But I'm glad I knew you Andrew, your smile will last forever!
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The kiss of a thousand years just came my way.  It was like a waterfall of a cool refreshing day. Just like a sun that never sets in the east, the kiss was never-ending. It never did cease.  The kiss of a thousand years was the kiss of my dreams. It made me shine throughout like a sun's shining beam. I'll never forget that everlasting kiss that ook me away from fear. And there'll never be a kiss like the kiss of a thousand years!  (c)chance4me
      
</post>


</Blog>