<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I know   this shouldn't bother me as much as it does, but does. I figured kevin would call me after he got off work yesterday, but he ended up not calling til like 1 am and then he was in a pissy mood and wanted to get off the phone right away. He said he'd call me early today becuase we both have to work, and I don't get off til 11:30. Well, he didn't call. I guess that shouldn't have suprised me as much as it did, but it kinda hurt. A lot. We're drifiting apart, and hes letting it happen. I still think its fixable, but we both have to put in a lot of effort. I think he doesn't want to. If he decided for sure that its over, I think hes not telling me so he wont hurt my feelings. Thats just dragging it out so it'll hurt a lot more later on. The biggest thing we have to work on is openness and telling eachother everything. I don't think he is at all, and I wish he would, even if its not what I want to hear. At least be honest with me. Tell me if you don't want to be around me or even talk to me. Just tell me what you want.      On a completely different topic, our power is out. Right now I'm at the library. This sucks becuase I can't dry my hair or straighten it. Oh well, it has to be up in a ponytale for work, and I dont really care how I look because no one important (kevin) will see me. **sigh** I wish he'd just talk to me about it, about anything really.  
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I just got home from work. It was good cuz I wasnt scheduled so I got paid, and if I had stayed home I wouldnt have done anything, so I turned a potentially wasted day into profit. Thats good. I have a huge burn on my elbow from wrestling with kevin on my trampoline last night, it hurts. I'm tired, but I need to go to kroger soon b/c I'm fixing dinner tonite for me and mary cuz both my parents are at work. My friend wants me to go drinking with him tonite, but I dont think I'm up for it. At least not while everything is up in the air like this with Kevin and me. I'm not in the partying mood at all. I'm kinda bummed, but I dont wanna talk about how much I miss him and stuff, cuzI don't want to pressure him too much. I want him to make his decision based on how HE feels, not on me or his friends or whoever. I know its only been two weeks, but it feels like a lifetime. I don't want him to get used to how it is now, becuase it SUCKS!   
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       "When life blows, sometimes you just have to swollow"    &nbsp;  goddammit kevin, what do you want from me? I know I hurt you and I know&nbsp;I fucked up but you cant lie to everyone about where you are (I think ur embaressed for people to know ur with me) make out with me, be all over me and expect me to do&nbsp;nothing and wait. You still tell me you love me... And I will wait for you, but I'm just saying, it blows. You gotta make a choice sooner or later. Just remember I love you. Everyone else thinks it'll work out, everyone but you.  
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      &nbsp;  Rick- dont worry about it, you didn't do anything, I don't think you understood the whole situation, and I'm sorry for being a bitch. The thing is, I love kevin and being with him is the only thing that is important to me, and I'm sorry if I hurt your feelings in the process. you really are a great guy, but I love kevin. Of course we can still be friends.     &nbsp;  I went shopping  today, and that made me very happy. I didn't get much, but I had a good sister bonding experience. I got a really cute blue and white shirt for $2.99 at fashion shop. Did you hear that? $2.99!! holy shit!! Its really soft, like a cross between velour and a beach towel. Its low cut too yay. I also got vanilla lip shimmer, mostly becuase kevin likes vanilla. Is that bad? I also got the worlds cutest sunglasses, they have little white flowers on the side with rinestones. Wahoo! I'll write more later, I'm going to eat dinner.  
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As of today, I have lost about 10 lbs since kevin and I broke up!!! 11 more to go! wahoo! This is exciting. I still would rather be fat and be with kevin. grrr 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I miss him and I wish he wanted to be with me  
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Today was the most confusing day of my life. I love kevin, and I wish he'd decide what he wants. I'll wait, and pretend to be patient. **sigh** I thought he would never want to talk to me again, but then as I was making plans for tonite, he asked if he could come over. Of course i said yes, and so he did. We spent the whole time making out and rolling around on my trampoline. What does he want from me? More and more I'm leaning toward the friends with benifits thing. He is a boy... But I could never do that. I love him too much to just mess around while he dates other people and has no feelings for me. He even went on a fucking date with this chick my other ex, Marc, cheated on me with then broke up with me for. AWSOME! he even called it a date. When I went over to Mikes the other night, there was nooo romantic feelings at all, and I feel kind of bad about that becuase mikes a nice guy. On the other hand, I was too busy thinking about kevin for anything else to cross my mind. Ok, I've got to stop thinking about that. I'm getting teary dammit. On the up side, at least hes talking to me, the horny bastard. (I don't mean anything negative by the word bastard, if you know me, you know I call everyone that, especially cops). The longer he doesn't want to be with me, the worse and worse it looks for us. My dad said something today that made me feel a lot better tho. He and my mom dated for 4 or 5 years before they got married, and there was a point they didn't talk for 8 months becuase my dad didn't think it was going anywhere. But 23 years later, they're happily married. Still, I don't think I could handle not talking to kevin for 8 days, much less months.     &nbsp;  On a totally different topic, I'm going to coach 5/6 grade volleyball for my grade school, MGC. Thats pretty exicting. Actually, I'm not for sure I'll be coaching them becuase I'd much much rather coach cheerleading. The only problem with that is cheerleading is a two season, 5 day a week sport, and I'll have so much else to do my senior year, with college apps and AP classes and parties and whatnot. We'll see what happens.    &nbsp;  I think I'm going to try to get some sleep, even though I know I won't. I take that back. I'm going to watch TV or something, maybe he'll call.     &nbsp;  grrrr (thats my tiger growl cuz I'm fusterated)  
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "goodbye" by Jagged Edge is in my CD player, and it perfectly describes how I feel right now  Sometimes... What may be the best thing for you to do Sometimes it the hardest thing for you to do And thats real Cause I know that I love youI know how I feel about you But I also know that don't make everything alright And for that reason I gotta say goodbye Tell me have you ever been in a  Situation where the best thing you could do  Is the hardest thing you've ever done  But you try to do whats right And I know that deep down inside That I really wanna be there by your side But I can't stand to see you cry Not when its because of me  And its over,  I'll never love another I'm always thinking of him,  I'm doing this because of him Don't wanna say goodbye I don't wanna let him see me cry Looking out the window and wondering why Did we have to say all those things that we said last night  Baby I don't wanna say goodbye So I'm just standing here wondering why Just don't like to see when you cry So I'ma say goodbye If you think I cause I packed your stuff That inside I ain't really really cracking up Cause you're wrong I just hide it good Cause I know thats what you need And there's more to life than loving yourself You gotta learn to love somebody else And thats why I do the things that I do  And its over,  I'll never love another I'm always thinking of him, I'm doing this because of him Don't wanna say goodbye I don't wanna let him see me cry Looking out the window and wondering why Did we have to say all those things that we said last night Baby I don't wanna say goodbye So I'm standing here wondering why Just don't wanna see when you cry So I'ma say goodbye  There's no one in this world that can ever take your place All the love that we share, it can never be erased And I know that, that it hurts so bad And its so that, that you're the best I've had There's no one in this world that can ever take your place All the love that we share, it can never be erased And I know that, that it hurts so bad And its so that, that you're the best I've had There's no one in this world that can ever take your place All the love that we share, it can never be erased And I know that, that it hurts so bad And it's so that, that you're the best I've had There's no one in this world that can ever take your place All the love that we share, it can never be erased  And I know that, that it hurts so bad And it's so that, that you're the best I've had 
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        &nbsp;  LIFE SUCKS       and the time it says im posting is wrong, its 1:45 am       Not only did i fuck over the person I love, but&nbsp;I also lost the best thing I ever had       **sobbing, in need of a hug**     &nbsp;   
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We all know I talk about  Kevin   ALL  the time, but i never realized how much until i read over everything I've posted so far. Just for fun, I'm going to bold everytime I've mentioned  him&nbsp; on here. This should be pathetic.   
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Today at work, my mannager made an off-hand comment to a coworker and I about how theres only two weeks til school starts. TWO WEEKS!!!! I'm a SENIOR! I get a senior sweatshirt, I already have my ring,&nbsp;I'll have to start filling out college apps,&nbsp;and prom is in like 10 months (note to self: start looking for a dress!) While this is the most exciting thing EVER, if I think about it too long it makes me sad. Over the last three years at AHS, I've made some awsome friends and great memories. One of those is  Kevin . I was talking to my friend about prom and I started to say something about me and  Kevin , but then I remembered  he  hates me and never wants to talk to me again. Whenever I think about anything in the future, it always includes  him . I mean, we had kid names and everything. I've made mistakes before, but nothing like this. I hear people say you&nbsp;never know what you have until you&nbsp;lose it. That&nbsp;is so disgustingly cliche, but its so true.&nbsp;Well shit, im getting teary-eyed. &nbsp;I say that I've done things I regret but I wouldnt go back and change anything, but thats not true anymore. It was just so stupid. I fucked up and theres no excuse for it. I just hope  kevin  will eventually one day decide  he  does want to talk to me again becuase I love  him  so much.  He  is the most amazing, wonderful person I have ever met, and I don't deserve someone that great. Dude,,, this blows.     
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Arite, i did something dumb last night. I went over to the guys house I cheated on  kevin  with and got a lil tipsy. I really wasn't drunk tho. It was a mistake, but I'm SINGLE, as much as I hate that, but I'm making my own decisions now.  Kevin  got really pissed off, and I don't blame  him , i'd never talk to me again if I was in his position, but still, he told me to make other plans so I did. and now  he  expects me to tell  him  something and i'm so confused b/c I know  he  thinks I'm going to tell  him  and i dont know what  hes  talking about. Oh wait, I'm talking to  him  on AIM, and  he  thinks I did something with another guy at IU. OMG  thats  what  he  was worried about??  That boy  is crazy. At IU&nbsp;i met tons of awsome people but... OMG i cant believe thats what  he  was really worried about!! I love  him , but  hes  crazy     
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       When I was at HSJI, I met this guy named Rick from Downers Grove, IL. We've been talking a little bit since we got home and it turns out he has to get some tests done b/c he had a heat stroke and it might have affected his brain. I'm pretty sure I got the story right, and so I'm worried about him. Hes a really great guy, and he doesn't mind when I talk about  kevin  nonstop. He asked me to pray for him, and even though I'm not religous at all, I'm going to, so if ya'll could to, that would mean a lot to me.    Rick, your not broken, I promise! I'll fix it all. I dunno how, but i'll come up with something, and you know I'm always here for you. Feel better!    
      
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Over the last week or so, I've been a mess because of everything with  kevin . While of course this sucks, and the bad definatly out weighs the good,&nbsp;a few good things have come out of it. I seriously think&nbsp;I could write a book about the benifits of being emotionally devistated. First of all, I have no apetite. Heres what I've eaten in the last&nbsp;4 days:      two bites of frosty at wendys    one chicken nugget with honey mustard sauce    a glass of milk     Since leaving for IU, I've lost&nbsp;5 lbs, so thats good i guess. On the other hand, I'd rater weigh 400 lbs and have  kevin . **sigh**      
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Work really sucks and I don't want to go. Not last night, but the night before,  kevin  came up to work and i was soo happy, you have no idea. So I rushed off to be with  him , and I forgot to clock out, among other things. Going off to see  kevin  turned out to be pretty pointless because  he  broke up with me yesterday any way. I still love  him  and I deserved it. Any way,&nbsp; so I go into work last night and Musa, my mannager, starts yelling at me about how dining room was a mess the night before (I was suposed to close it) and how I'm irrisponsibe and stuff like that. I almost cried b/c I've never had an adult besides my parents yell at me like that. I really didnt mean to do shitty work. Ely, a coworker, is awsome tho. Hes from africa, but he speaks pretty good english. I was really sad at work last night cuz of everything with  kevin , and so Ely was like, i'll jump  him  babygirl, you need to be happy. Which I thought was really sweet, even though&nbsp; I completely screwed  kevin  over to say the least, but still, it made me feel better at the time.  I have to work again today, and I don't want to go becuase I think my mannager named mark is going to be there, and hes kind of a prick, and he takes all my cigs. Hes a nice guy tho, he tries so I guess it wont really be that bad after all.      
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       My friends are the most amazing people ever, and I don't know what I'd do without them. Shout-outs:  Susie- the richest jew this side of the mississippi  Maggie- Yay! You can finally drive, thats so exciting!  Jessie- you went out with a guy named WOODY haha that makes me laugh  Rick- your an amazing guy, I'm your biggest fan  Kate- you are just dumb, thats all I ahve to say blondie  Sarah- Which boy is it this week? I can't keep them straight!  Leo- My california boy, where did your shirt go? Rick knows!      
      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I FUCKED UP! There I said it. I've never made a mistake this big in my whole life. Everything was perfect. I had the best  boyfriend  anyone could ever ask for, and I ruined it. I deserve for  him  to hate me and never talk to me, but of course thats not what I want. In the perfect world,  he'd  forgive me eventually and  we'll  live happily ever after. But I think  hes  just confused now, so I'll give  him  time. I don't think  he'll  ever read this, but  kevin  I love you so much, please just be happy, even if  your  happiness doesn't include me, just knowing  your  happy is all I want. I love  you  so much  baby .     
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Seniors! '05 big dawgs woof woof!!!!    im moving on, im gonna be ok...  
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've done a lot of thinking today. He doesnt wanna have anything to do with me, and i totally understand that, even though of course thats not what i want. I've known that for a while, but i just didnt want to accept it. So he decided, and I'll have to move on. I'm broken now, but in time I know I'll be ok. I just wish he cared at least a little. Just knowing that I'll be ok eventually makes me feel better. I'll still be here if he ever changes his mind tho. I went to st joes last night and he didnt even talk to me. I went to a party afterwards which was SOOOO fun! I haven't been that drunk since last summer. Thats the most good looking guys ive seen in one place at the same time ever. there was brice (not mitch), brandon, brad, ryan in the red shirt, and tu tu not spelled like the ballerina. Good times. I dont think ill drink for a while cuz of the hangover i had to go to work with. 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The last few days have been pretty good. I had booksales and after that susie maggie and me went walking on bardstown road trying to sell newspaper ads. I think i sold some to the kizito cookie lady, but i forgot to call her back today. I'll have to do that tomrow. Kevin showed up when we were at senica park, that was really sweet. I went ova to his house after that and did something stupid, cuz i though it might make him happy, but i feel so used cuz i know he doesnt want to date me and we prolly won't get back together, but he still wants to sleep with me. I gave him a really long foot rub, and that didnt make him want to be with me either. we saw the day after tomrow at village 8. after that he expected me to give him head. I didnt even get a back rub, which is all ive been wanting for the last week. we were suposed to chill today, but of course we didn't. I worked 10 hours and my feet really hurt. I want a foot rub with lotion now! $20 says he wont call tomorow. I really wanna go out to lunch with him or something. Hes getting drunk at a party right now. Awsome. Who knows when I'll see him again. I want everything to be good between us again, but I know thats not what he wants. Fuck, ive been crying way too much lately. OMG tomorows the 13th. I wonder if he cares. I miss him so much. I'm gonna go now before i say any more stupid things. 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       OMG! I had so much fun at work. I sang lee songs and I think ashley has a crush on me. And guess whos NOT going back to texas goddammit! I had so much energy, and I don't know why. I sang my version of the alphabet song, and here are the lyrics in case you care: (sorry, its all spelled wrong)     A you are an antelope B you are a buffalo C you are a cantolopue with ears D you are a dinosour E you are an elephant F you are a fruitloop in my bowl G you are a goodie-goodie H you are so homely I you are and inky binky boo J you are a jellybean K you are a kindney bean L you are a lima bean too M N O P I could go on all day Q R S T, alphabetly speaking, you disgust me U you wear no underwear V you are a vegstable W X Y Z I'd like to go through the alpahabet with you and tell you how you nauseate me I really mean it and tell you how you neauseate me one more time and tell you how you nauseate meeeeeeeeeeeeeee  Another good thing that happened today, which made today the most exciting day of my life, was when i poke Sean in the stomach, he giggles like the pillsbury dough boy!!!! YAY!! that made me so happy  the only bad thing is everything with you-know-who. I want to see him tonite, but I'm sure he doesnt wanna see me. I want to go see the white castle movie and go to the zoo. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I know I said I wasn't gonna write about you-know-who, so I won't. All I'm gonna say is I fucked up again. and again and again. I didn't know it was possible for me to have these kinds of feelings about someone. Dammit.   
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yay! I have happy things to write about finally. The last two days have been fun, mostly because I've been around the girls a lot. Yesterday, Susie came over at freaking 9 am before a meeting for a club. We went to the summit for shopping, and I got one of those yummy frappichino things from starbucks jessie always gets before school. Then we had the meeting for Shakers, which is like SALT, but I don't know what we do besides promote SALT. For those of you who don't know, SALT stands for service action leadership team, which is a seniors-only club. I went and saw the Village last night too. It was really weird. I didn't know anything about it going in, so I'm not sure if it was suposed to be scary or not, but the beginning feaked me out, but halfway through I guessed the ending. Today I went with my parents to pick my sister up from girl scout camp, so that was a fun 4 hours in the car with my family and the dog. After that, Susie came over and "helped me make cookies" and we had pizza at our newspaper advisor's house and talked about plans for next year. It was a lot of fun. "our" cookies were really good and I hope I get my own collum next year, but I doubt I will. We'll see. The meeting didn't acomplish a lot, but I laughed for the first time in a while and it was fun. I still really really want to go to the zoo. Oh yea, I have some pictures if you want to see:   urlLink http://pg.photos.yahoo.com/ph/babygirl05911/my_photos  I hope that link works.  
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I feel like I should write a good post becuause I haven't written anything in a while, but theres nothing to write about. I decided that from now on, I'm not going to mention kevin becuase he doesn't want anything to do with me, so I'll give him what he wants, if that makes him happy. I worked yesterday then went to a party, but it wasnt any fun. Today I went over to Charlie's house, which was fun I guess. I hadn't seen him in a while, so it was good. Hes so tall! I felt very small, which is a good feeling. I couldn't sleep again last night, but I really don't wanna take anything, I take enough pills as it is. I'm working 4-9 today. I got a paycheck yesterday, and theres almost nothing left of it. 95 went to my dad for car repairs and my huge cell phone bill. 25 went to gas, leaving me with like 30, which sucks balls. I talked to my friend jessie today, which was awsome cuz I havent talked to her all summer. Hopefully we'll hang out soon. I've got a lot of stuff comming up with week with club meetings, so I'll wait til after they happened to talk about them. I'm gonna go take a shower so I'll post more tomorow.    
      
</post>


</Blog>