<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          There's always an upside to everything...Here's mine...I got a job! Yay for me! I applied 3 weeks ago, and one of their waitresses quit, so they called me in last night, and I started working there. I was happy!  
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Glad you asked. Today was HORRIBLE. First off, I would like it known that Robert John&nbsp;Hilton has been removed from all ties to me, therefore making him no longer my brother. I can't believe that he thinks that his "girlfriend", although technically, they're not "seeing each other", is more important that me keeping in touch with my family. He doesn't understand that my family outside of this house is the ONLY thing that has kept my alive as long as I have been. I'm tired of life in itself. I really don't see how people live to be 80 years old, if I can't stand 15 years. The only people that I truly care about are the people that actually SHOW there love for me. In case you didn't know this, NOBODY in this house shows their love for me, and if they do, they have an extremely odd way of showing it. The only reason I stay here is because I have to. Oh yea, they feed me, too. There's another reason I stay. But then, they feed me all I can eat, and then tell me I need to lose weight? What type of bullshit is that? When my mother found out I lost my virginity, she called me a whore. So technically, by what this family has called me, I'm a fat whore. Oh fucking well, they'll have to deal with it, because I'm happy just as I am.&nbsp;I don't see any reason in trying to improve my body. "God" created me just as I am, and if they don't like what "God" created, then they, therefore, aren't as devout of Christians as they appear to be. Oh, and they thing that I'm the "problem child." The one thing that&nbsp;I hated most when they found out that I had lost my virginity was that they knew that Robbie had fucked an ex-girlfriend, AND THEY DIDN'T CARE! Yea, they even used the excuse that I could get pregnant and he couldn't. Sure, he can't get pregnant, but the child would still be his responsibility, but they wouldn't care. If I were to get pregnant, I'd get kicked out of the house. God forbid that Robbie not have a place to live. He's a queer fuckwad, and not worth my time. He thinks that he can play God to me. Well, I have news for him, we don't serve the same god anymore, buddy. I don't look up to you as a role model, because you're not the type of role model that I need. I need somebody that can teach my what I want to learn. I need somebody that knows a little something about what I'm getting into. I know some, but not a lot. Nobody in this house fits that description. Sure, my mother may be able to find out a lot, but big whoop-di-do! All she would do is find stuff that Christians have written against the religion. It would all be biased, and I need something that looks equaliy upon both religions. Well, I've got to get going.  
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Well, this morning, my mother and I were out to run some errands. We had to go to the bank, and grocery shopping. We got to the bank, went inside so they do whatever it is that they need to do, and went back outside. Well, we got in the truck, and the truck wouldn't start. We figured this was okay, because it wasn't the first time that it wouldn't start. Usually, you just wait a little bit, then try again, and it'll start right up. Well, we waited about 10 minutes, and tried again, and it still wouldn't start. We figured it just needed more time, so we went to this thrift store across the street from the bank. No biggie. We were in there about an hour, looking for stuff for Homecoming Week, and whatnot. I got this huge hoop slip. You know, the ones that they used to wear to make their dress stand out from their legs and look like a bell. After I paid for that, went went back to the truck, and tried to start it again. It still wouldn't start. We waited, and waited, and tried again. Still nothing. We then had the smart idea to go inside the bank, use the phone to call my grandma to come get us and take us home. Well, I went inside, and called, and she never answered the phone. I tried again, and still no answer. I went back outside, relayed the news to my mother, and we sat for a bit more, and tried to start it again.&nbsp; It still wouldn't start. Well, we then decided that it wasn't that much of a walk to the church, so we would go there, and have Kandace, the secretary, a.k.a: Rob's girl, run us home. What we didn't realize, was the fact that the church was actually like a mile and a half from the bank. So we locked up the truck, and started walking. Once we got to the church, we had to wait, and wait, and wait, because Kandace was on the phone with some woman asking about Lanie. She finally ran us home, and now we're trapped at home with no way to go, because we can't get back up to the bank to fix the truck. We know what the problem is. Its the starter. Occasionally, it hits a bad spot, and won't start, but eventually, it fixes itself. Well, it didn't fix itself earlier, so we have no vehicle.    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Well, the day went from boring, to absolutely horrible. My friend's mom went in for surgery on what could have been a malignant tumor on her ovaries. She had a total hysterectomy, which isn't what bothers me. What bothers me is that they found cancer attached to her rectum, and her ribs. They supposedly removed "every cell." That's a load of bullshit. They said the same thing for my Granny, and my great-Grandpa, but they didn't get every cell. She's supposed to be going through chemotherapy, which, as we all know, is supposed to help, but rarely does. Its just a matter of time before I loose one of the most valued people in my life. I don't want to see my friend go through that hurt. It'll take a miracle for her to live. Why does something bad happen just when my life starts to look up?  
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
          My entire blog got erased somehow. Go figure that it would happen to me. In case you didn't catch the original, here's a recap of it: I fell down some stairs, and I have a head cold.  
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        &nbsp; var mid = 3510783;&nbsp; var pic_url = 'pics/783/3510783-shelly.jpg';&nbsp; var pic_width = 71;&nbsp; var pic_height = 150;    
    
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Nothing new today...at all. I just found out where I was hurt from yesterday's fall. I just don't understand why I'm as clumsy as I am. I think its my dad's fault. I got it from his side of the family. Oh well, I'll deal.        &nbsp;    And remember kids...  
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
              Well, as if I wasn't a dork enough [put that one on my tab, Farris (and yes, for calling myself one)], I had to go and fall down the stairs at church today. It was not, I repeat, WAS NOT, my fault. I was about halfway down the stairs, and the heel of my shoe came of. Luckily nothing was broken, but it hurt. Now I have major carpet burn, a scratch on my arm, and I was humiliated in front of my closest friend! (Not that I haven't been before, but c'mon, this was pretty bad.) I was glad that I didn't end up like I did the last time I fell down those same steps. I ended up with a bloody nose, and school the next day. Talk about something that sucked.  &nbsp;  I also have a head cold. A head cold in the summer. Do you know how much that sucks? I'm bored, with nothing to do, besides try to figure out ways to breath through my nose when I sleep, so I don't wake up ever ten minutes because my mouth is dry.     &nbsp;      Life sucks royal dick.                      
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           Today was just another ordinary day. Nothing new, at all. I did create this blog, though, so I guess that's somthing new. For those of you that don't know, my name is Shelly. I'm a 15 year old girl that has nothing better to do at the moment besides this. I heard about blogs on a TV show, and that's what sparked my interest. I guess I need a ways to get my feelings out, and this is how I plan to do it.             Life Sucks Royal Dick    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Why is it that when you want something to go your way, it never does. I'm just not quite sure of that. I want certain things to happen, and they don't, or there's a slim chance that they will. I can't live like that. Its just so redundant and boring. I feel like most of the world is against me no matter what I do. I just don't understand that in the least bit. I wish I could figure out what force of Nature does this to me. If anyone has any ideas, comment on this post, and let me know!  
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Well, it seems as if I'm losing a lot this week. I'm losing long time friend and 'sister', Ashley Medders. I'm also letting a very special person go to Iraq. I'll miss Wade and Ashley very much. I know that they won't read this, but you are. I wanted to make it known that part of my heart is leaving with one of the two, no names mentioned. And as a special note, I declare the following statement officially and on the record: Jean Ellen Schultz Harrison Hilton is no longer related to me in any way.  
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
            I swear. If I had the option of moving out right now, I would do it in a heartbeat. My brother as completely ruined my life. Becuase of what him and Kandace are doing (you know, they're together, and the divorce isn't final) its like I'm in some cult that if I tell anybody that I'm in it, I'll be beheaded. Him and Kandace were brought up to me by a friend today, and then SHE goes and tells him that I'm the one that told her about them. She needs to get her shit straight, big time. He needs to realize that I am trust worthy. The only reason that I even put this on here is because of the fact that I need some place to release my anger without killing myself or some one else. Momma finally stood up for me today. It didn't help though, because Robbie's dumb ass fought back. I wish she would just kick him out, and let him get a taste of the real world. He thinks I'M not trust worthy! Me! I tell people that I don't know, and that live in another state simply because I know that they could really care less. I wish somebody would get me out of this hell hole.     
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Well, when it comes to this semester, I'm gonna have fun! (In class, anyways.) I've got Accounting 1, Physical Science (Honors), Tenth Grade Lit/Comp (Honors), and Mythology. I like all my teachers with the exception of one. Angie Bishop. She teaches accounting. I had her last year, for business communications, and needless to say, we didn't get along. But its ok, because that's my first period, and I get that out of the way right at the beginning of the day. Well, I had better go get situated for tomorrow. Bye!  
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          I haven't had anything new to talk about, and that's why I haven't written. I did go school shopping yesterday. That was fun. I did get a lot more clothes that I usually would have, since my mother doesn't have to buy for Robbie anymore.   
</post>


</Blog>