<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man, the Hoo Sisters are back!!!!!!! I missed them both. Now, it's back to me being called a wuss and a faggot. ::smriks:: I'm not a faggot! >.>  I really don't have anything to share with anyone, other than the fact that I hate being woken up before I have to, when I want/have to, because then, I get really pissy...  No, I don't feel like using the bathroom. My short temper takes it's toll. Now, go away. 
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is pretty wierd, that lately, faces that are new to me, I feel like I've seen them before. Today adds more thought to one I met only yesterday; I know I've seen them from somewhere, yet it is my first time meeting them. Pretty wierd.  School is actually a bit more...welcoming, than it used to be. I guess that, regardless of my experience at being the "new kid" it still remains the same: I hate the fact that I'm in the presence of people I do not know, or understand, and so, I remain to my normal self (if you know how I am) and until I learn more about the "others" I am not free with things, such as talking, or acting (I usually doze off to a sleep because of boredom).  Anywho, it just seems as if I'm here to help people understand me more, heh. Honestly, the only one who really understood alot about me doesn't know  everything,  so good luck.  By the way, I almost got into a fight with a redneck driving this oversized 6 wheeler (or something; I didn't count the wheels) who almost hit me and an acquaintence while trying to cross the street (on his red light, as well as a walk light for pedestriand) which should have known that you can't stop in the middle of the crosswalk. Yea, I challenged him out, so he got out, put his car in park, but since my friend didn't want to start trouble, we didn't have any fun...  Honestly, I would have gotten a nice hurting from that idiot. He's pretty big, but I'm sure my bud and I could have taken him. Too bad though, I forgot to get a license plate... 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Upon sleeping his 8 hours of rest, he awoken in the middle of the day. His body, well rested and already bathed, then prepared to leave the house for school.  The day began well. No anger or disturbances clouded his judgement thus far.  I didn't seem to have trouble undersatanding what was going on, as usual, but then again, I was half an hour late, and already had missed much of the teaching. ::shrugs:: I don't really care. There happened to be less seats today, as a face or two showed up that normally do not; one by the name of Deanna. I had no where to sit, therefore, I grabbed a posted chair/desk and unfolded it, planting myself in the middle of the room.  In the middle of the class (break for 15 minutes) I happened to be traveling to the same convenient store as Deanna, so I decided to go with her, and have a little chat.  The day ended pretty calm.  I also found out that I have an interview for a job tomorrow at 3. I do not feel like jynxing it, but then again, I do not really believe in jynxes, but mere coincidental acts of fate. Wish me luck.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wish I had a job. It takes effort to getting one, and yet one hates having to go to one. I, have worked before, and knwo regardless, I want one. Maybe, maybe the Subway down the street, or the Burger King next to it will hire me. It's my best bet.   Gosh, I hate driving school. Well, no, I hate having to do things when I never asked to do them, or have to do them before I wish to (when I have a choice).   Maybe I'll find some solitude and sanctum in a new online rpg...PSO.   The world around him was so distasteful. Everything that he sees is so bothersome to him, and he is having some insecure troubles with himself about things that could be changed, but considering his dispositon, there is nothing he can do. He is left with holding in his problems, wishing and hoping they can be resolved sometime in the future, but until then, he dives himself into fantasy and pleasure to mask this phase of reality with another. 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Driving school starts at 5 pm. I am awake at 12. It is 4:30 and I have still not had my before-going-out shower. It is 4:50. I still have not gotten ready to leave the house.   It is 5:00, and I'm in the shower. 5:30 I get there, late as usual (I promise, being late is like a trait that will run in my future family...::shakes head).   It's now 4:49. How did time go backwards? It did not. It is 4:49 the next morning, however, I am still not tired.   I think I'm becoming bipolar...either that, or I end up changing attitudes differently than I thought. For some reason, being out alone makes me mad at people, and well...>.>      urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Flash videos, Final Fantasy, anime, and the likes. I love them all, and I found something incorporating each.   urlLink http://uploads.ungrounded.net/164000/164193_FFA_.swf &nbsp;A must-click for anime/FF fans.  Solitude: a feeling of lonliness and tranquility, where nothing distrups the halcyon air, for it remains melanchelous...? Hah. Maybe not.  His day was pretty much normal. He met up with one that he lustfully desired, yet a gap was set between him and her. He learned of the many things one can do to others, and themselves, that were forms of sexual pleasure, tease, and just rightful when decided upon. His time spent with one of his friends was left with countless battles in KOF2k3, which in the end he won proudfully, and still faced many sorrifull defeats. His mind kept steady with his tasks, as he starved due to his focus on deeds other than his own health.  It was a normal day. 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, he stares at the female before him, or to be more technical, the literal figures of speech casted from the mind she holds, targeted to him though the use of advanced technology, to be interpreted in specific ways for his understanding, for him to know that he is, "wierd." Messaging online can be fun, yet is not a valid source for conversations for one can only interpret what they read as they see text, which is limited to how one usually reads.   Jev v? Why Jev v? Why not Jeff, as it was meant to be?  I asked for a change...my pronunciation of "Jeff" is undesirable, which gave me reason enough to speak my identity as I would prefer, with a slight change noticable by those who choose to notice.   There's nothing left here tonight; just a memory. Everyone should know to not let negative words of people bother you; all that matters most is you doing what you like to do, for at the end of the day, no one cares really...   Nostalgia...it is like, a poison that drinks life from the mind, and heart, and leaves one crying for a remedy that they can almost feel present, or a cure that they wish for endlessly, until they fall helplessly away from thought inevitably, and lose any thought of ever feeling that desire, of ever yearning for anything to begin with. Until that desire is fullfilled, until they find reach what they were searching for, do they ever feel at peace...  or so, as I feel it.    
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It rains...I like the rain;  urlLink     *Revision* Like tears of sorrow falling, deeply from high, the drops of rain penetrate, the medium through which it flies; like an anvil from heights, left rippling to the winds force, from the edges of its liquid cacoon, And with each collapse a melancholy norm, a rolling drum beat playing, from the bottom of the rising storm inside each tear, an unheard soul cries for its death, a voice trapped within, awaiting its falling last breath...   I care no more or less for the rain, for now, I am going to sleep. The End...(psyche)  Hyperbole: an extreme exaggeration.  For  example... I am up-to-date on my episodes of Naruto (ep 95-96 special) and I happened to lay my fingers on the trailer for the movie...Now, *hint-hint: hyperbole here* if I don't get to see the movie as soon as it gets here, I'm going to get a katana, shove it up someone's arse, pull out so their rectum explodes and drops their fillings, jab at the spine to dis-lock every bone piece (and if I miss, I will keep trying) fillet their private organ, and carve my signature all over their solar plexis...::blinks::  Ok, do you understand yet?  "Ah..." he sighs while closing his eyes, enveloping his arms around the beauty he claims as his; his item, his being of happiness. Deep in thought, he rests his chin over her shoulders, barely letting wind from within escape his lips, signing in the air one outrageous feeling...  "Ease.."  My two N's.  I'm sure those who know me, and a bit about my life would.... could  guess what the heck that would mean, but then again, don't bother, for there's only one person I'd tell, heh. (don't ask either, for if I don't tell you...  it's not you.)  To know ones future...it gives the feeling of being a pawn in a replay of fate's game of life, where you can only sit back and move as already scripted.   
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ::sits down quietly, listening to his music::  Hm...relationship troubles? Heh, who cares? Are ya gettin married? Thought so, so quit complaining and just have fun.  Ties have been broken, new ones made; has he finally severed his past? Or, has his past threads been needling on a path to a new quilt? My story of time, I'm going to make it one I can look back on and say..."I don't regret that, because I wanted to do it." With each their own way of living, I'm gonna have a fun way for mine. ::smirks::  Fun people; I sure will have a rough time, but when you think about it, at the end of the day, who cares about what you do but yourself and the ones you are with? Fun time...I'll have a fun time with a few people I know as well. Fun? It doesn't bother me anymore. I just go through it without much of a care, amused with it all.  Fun...it doesn't bother me anymore; I am just writing my own story of time, and finding my own cares along with it.  As for what all this has with my title? Not a damn thing. 
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ::hums this song, slowly drifting off into his lands of thoughs, sitting in a wakeful sleep, absorbing the world as it flows around::  I close my eyes and I keep seeing things; Rainbow waterfalls, sunny liquid dream Confusion creeps inside me raining doubt; Gotta get to you, But I don't know how  Call me, Call me Let me know it's alright Call me, call me Don't you think it's 'bout time Please won't you call and  * Ease my mind  Reasons for me to find you Peace of mind What can I do, to get me to you *  I had your number quite some time ago Back when we were one But I had to grow Ten thousand years I've searched it seems and now Gotta get to you Won't you tell me how  Call me, Call me Let me know you are there Call me, call me I wanna know you still care Come on now won't you  * Repeat *  Ease my mind Reasons for me to find you Peace of mind Reasons for living my life Ease my mind Reasons for me to know you Peace of mind what can I do, to get me to you   ^That song...it makes me feel alot at ease...it also makes me feel closer to certain people. ::raises two fingers:: For a fine day of not many troubles, and a happy time with many people, even Ebil Ebil, (heh) I bid you all, good night/day.  Sell xin. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Feelings of rejection; he sits there with urges he trys to deny, with a woman he tries to deny, with his feelings he tries to deny...His soul, is shared with so little, yet nostalgic for so much more. All he can really dream of is the feeling of warmth he hopes to feel someday, from that person he wishes to be with...  From that person he wishes to be with...with whom, he wonders..  My day, was pretty wierd. First of all, my whole mind went downhill and I was acting a bit out of character. I'm just alone in thought right now, chatting with Brettany. Too bad.. she  can't be on right now.. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh boy. I really don't know crap when it comes to music...especially rock. I know...songs? No, not even the titles, really. I just hear it, and that's pretty much all that I have of reference. Groups? If it's not something I listen to constantly, I know nothing, haha.  Ok ok, don't shun me just yet. It's not like I really- what?! I'm no poser!!!!  ...v.v Alright. I'm jut gonna end this entry where the dot leaves off... 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ::yawns:: I don't plan on going to school today. I just feel like skipping, because well, it's not like I'm getting too far at the time, anyways. ::yawns again::  Revelations came through with full force yesterday. I happened to come to terms very well with myself, as well as acknowledge a few other important things that'll affect my life in a big way. Still, I struggle a bit with thoughts..ugh. Man, really; I need to think less.  I never got to go for the job opportunity. I have to call again, and since I'm taking a day off, I'll just make plans for today. ::yawns:: Man, where are friends around, when you want to talk...::shrugs:: Too bad I can't just walk down the street and pull a friend out through their window, and just chill, heh. I'm gonna go to bed in a few. Ciao.
    
</post>


</Blog>