<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It doesn't seem like Windows XP needs hotburn to burn files and music to disk, I burnt some Rasmus songs onto a disk (only clips though) and I didn't use any burning software! Now I'll be able to listen to&nbsp;some of&nbsp;The&nbsp;Rasmus until I get the&nbsp;proper&nbsp;CD (one more week&nbsp;to go!). On my burnt Cd I have In The Shadows (full version),&nbsp;Guilty (clip),&nbsp;First day of my life (clip) and In My Life (clip) which is quite a decent collection but I should of put on Still standing and Whatever to fill up more space but it's too late now!!&nbsp;&nbsp; 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today is sunday, dad has gone to the Moterbike racing at Donnington, it's just me and mum. I'm listening to The Rasmus again! My mum even turnt of the raio for me to listen to them and anyway it stops me anoyying her by flicking the music channels until The Rasmus come on.&nbsp;We watched the Matrix Revalutions last night on DVD,I haven't even seen the secound film yet (reloaded)! It's alright but confusing as I don't know what happened before, I haven't seen alot of the charecters before too. &nbsp;Dad might be getting a DVD burner to go in the downstairs computer, we can allready watch DVDs on that computer and now we'll be able to make copies when we rent DVDs! It will save alot of time, but we still have to pay the renting fee though! &nbsp;Darn you printer! If only you were working! Then I could prnt pictures of Lauri and plaster tham all over my bedroom wall. The pain! Oh the pain!!! I really want pictures of him! I need pictures!!!!!&nbsp;We might get out the exerise bike from the spare room so I can get in better shape, I don't get out much so it should help. I can't keep on having naughties without exercising, is beats the pint of eating heathy. Eating healthy is really boring but it helps me not to spend my money on sweets all the time! &nbsp;I keep getiing the video for "the funeral song" AND "first day of my life" mixed up, it's so anoying! I think "the funeral song" is doneat a race track, but I can't be sure! I just don't know, I'll have to post somewhere like gaiaonline.com and ask the people there!&nbsp;Okay here's my saying; sugar just rots your teeth if you use the energy it gives you then it won't make you fat!&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've found more Rasmus merchendise and it's in pounds! I've put on wish list The Rasmus-race track which is a poster, I believe it's from the video the first day of my life and I put down The Rasmus-leaf which is a T-shirt with The Rasmus logo on. I wouldn't wear the t-shirt much, not that I'm not proud of what i like but it's just a T-shirt, I'd probally wear it around the house and then when it's a bit old I'll wear it as a night top! &nbsp;I might join the fanclub but the webpage always seems to be down, dad says I might aswell just follow the band and listen to the music. I also metioned that i wanted to buy an autograph book and it send it to them butdad says I might aswell just write and get them to sign a piece of paper (I'd make sure it was good quality!)&nbsp;There seems te be two bands doind a song to go with Spiderman 2 which is really wierd. There's one song called "We are" which is going out on singel soon and there's another one called something to with living. Both videos contain clips from the movie so it's really confusing, I think the "we are" one is probally the theme as it's going out on single and the cover had spiderman on it so the other one must just be some song. &nbsp;I've only just found out that the same person who wrote "The Crow" also wrote "The Matrix" and loads of other movies and that was around the 1940-1950's, it's wierd how alot of the best stuff comes from times were any movie containing too much sex was banned (Like Maddona's song when she kissed a lesbian who was only wearing suspenders. &nbsp;It's cool of my Dad not to moan at me for liking The Rasmus, usually when I like something he doesn't like it at all or makes fun of me but at the moment he's right behind me though i don't think he would pay for me to go watch The Rasmus when they go to Leeds during their tour. He would probally pay if it were a proper concert say in Bristol etc. but I'll&nbsp; have to wait until they finnish their tour (hahaha). I guess he use to like that kind of stuff when he was young (if he ever was) he still likes some of them, when The Best Of Guns and Roses came out he got that, I guess he's alot more than I took him for granted for!!&nbsp;I may just buy Dead Letters so I can listen to The Rasmus, it will only take me 2 weeks to have anough and I get my money today! So that's one more week to go!!! Then I'll probally get the poster and T-shirt.&nbsp;I've had a look at some personal CD players, mum said to choose one that's around £40 cause it will be my main christmas present, I've choosen a really nice one. I've also looked at Cd cases, there's a nice one that also holds your player aswell which would be really handy so I could keep all my stuff together instead of digging through my bag. &nbsp;I have to tidy the downstairs cupboard next wednesday, I'm going to through out LOADS of old stuff, hopefully I'll find loads of lost and treasured stuff which will make it worth it!&nbsp;I may ask for another GBA game though I may ask for it for my Birthday (jan 7th) cause I haven't got a list for that yet. i'm not sure what to get though, I've already got Harvest Moon 4 on ROM, I'm defently not getting Hamtaro! I may get Boktai, that game that reacts to sunlight-it would certainly get me out more!&nbsp;I may not ask for the Harry Potter things, instead I may ask for Phillip Pullman's Dark Materials, they seem better! The plot seems nice too though I'm not going to go through it cause well, I can't be bothered.&nbsp;I may print off some pictures of the Rasmus from the internet when the printer works! Dad suggested this, he asked if I could or not, I said no becausethe printer's not working. Hopefully he'll get a new one soon so I can, I did think about going down to the local library but I don't think they would aprreciate me printing off pictures of hot guys!!&nbsp;Dad's going to moterbike racing tomorrow (yay), it's near Nottingham (The Rasmus might be playing in Nottingham during their tour) so it's going to take him about 3 hours to get there meaning of course he's going to be home late! &nbsp;Here's my saying for today; If your soul lives forever then does that mean you can kill it over and over again??&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's friday, I get my pocket money tomorrow. I wish I got more that £6 a week, maybe I should get job. I brought up this with my mum but she said I wasn't old enough. I've added the Cd case to my list.&nbsp;I found myself searching tokyopop.com for manga, after I've got the Chobits collection I want to get a new series. I've thought about gettng Princess Ai but I don't know much about it.&nbsp;I made a rough copy of my layout for my site on the downsairs computer, it has a picture drawn by Auroreblackcat from france; too bad I can't save it. Dad keeps on going "you have better not downloaded anything", well I haven't except The Rasmus songs clips but it doesn't take up any room in the computer so it's not like proper Downloading.&nbsp;The Layout is called Shadow Dreams, it has writing around it saying things like "Dreams are dangerous things, some are unreachable and become obsessions. Be careful with dreams". I'll have to email Aurore to make sure it's alright to use her art, I did once ask her before but that was months ago and I've got a nw email anyway, last time I emailed her using the home email address. &nbsp;I can't wait till I go to trowbridge with my mum, I'm going to get stylish new trousers, flary ones too. Whatever I get I'll hope I'll be happy.&nbsp;I've had another think abot what I want to be when I'm older (as I have to choose my options at th end of year 9) and i've decieded between Tatoo artist and book illustrator. Tatoo artist would be hard as if I make a mistake then people can mega sue me. With a Book Ilustrator I get to meet loads of famous people and get my name mentioned in books which would be really, the only problem is that I may have to draw things that I'm not interested in or what i'm not good at drawing. &nbsp;Lately it seems that all I do is search on the internet for pictures of The Rasmus. I want to do a layout featuring them but I can't seem to find the right picture, it's so anoyying. I'll just have to wait until I get their Album, I might just get the £10 and buy it straight away instead of saving up for all that stuff, atleast I'll be able to listen to them without going on the internet...&nbsp;It seems&nbsp; get spottier by the day, I've promised myself that when I go back to school after the holidays I'm going to be clean of them. I've decided to wash my face EVERYDAY to rid myself of them lets hope that works either that or I'm going to have to buy some special spot stuff which will make it harder to get the Cds!!!&nbsp;I hope my passport is sent in time for holiday, eventhough we haven't booked it yet we're still hoping to go during the fist half term of year 9. My picutre looks wierd, I was wearing pink, shiny eye shadow and it looks like my eyelids are mirrows, I should of worn more black!&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;Okay here's my saying for the day; Do feel uninteligent? look up to the clouds. If your brain is moving slower than them, then at least it has a silver lining.&nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's the first day of the summer holidays-god year 8 went fast. I can't belive I'm in year 9 now, I'm getting some new trousers in trowbridge, they are going to be nice ones. Hopefully I can get my hair dyed, I want it a red colour or a purple (I'm not copying shelly) I might even get it black underneath (and no I'm not copying Kayleigh). This is going to mean I'm going to have to buy some better quality eyeliner I'm afraid mine is too soft and doesn't last very long.&nbsp;I've decided to save up for "Dead letters" by The Rasmus and one of their earlier albums "Playboys", also I'm going to get the last two chobits volumes to complete the set. This will cost aproxmetly £30 and about five weeks to save up if I don't spend any of it which will be probally impossible so lets say about 6-all of the summer holidays.&nbsp;Earlier I was downloading Rasmus music clips, I found the whole of In The Shadows too. I think "The First Day Of My Life" and "In My Life" sound like something Busted or McFly would come up with. I think I'm getting obsessed with The Rasmus, who can blame me? I think Lauri (the lead singer) is really fit and I love his green eyes. &nbsp;I tried to see if I could get tickets to The Leeds Festival where The Rasmus will be playing during their tour, but none of the websites seemed to say that The Rasmus were actully playing. I've decided to wait until they actully do a concert In England;then I might go.&nbsp;I also cleaned up my room incase Poppy would come over during the holidays, I threw away my old spice girls CD and put away alt of ornaments that I use to collect when I was little. I think I mainly cleaned it up because i was bored. I can't believe I'm bored already, this just seems like a weekend not like the summer holidays and it's only a thursday. &nbsp;The internet seems a little wierd at the moment, blueyonder.co.uk seems to be down and it's making the computer go even slower. Some pages aren't even showing, I have to write in http:// I can't just write www. awell.&nbsp;I hope amazon.co.uk will get "into" by The Rasmus, they list it but there is no option to buy it wierd huh? I might get "hell of a tester" but I'm just not sure. &nbsp;I want to talk about the latest Rasmus video, Guilty. I think Lauri's nose looks mucked up in the close ups, you can see up his nostrils but don't worry I still love you! I think Storm is right, The Rasmus are ripping of The Crow but atleast Lauri didn't have the feathers in his hair (but then he did have wings behind him made out of lightbulbs)! I can nether find a decent picture of the whole band, it's so anoying. It's either too small or a bad quality, I was going to do a Rasmus layout on my site but nether mind.&nbsp;I really want a Person Cd player for Christmas, so I can listen to The Rasmus everywhere I go! That also means I'll have to buy ones of those Cd cases so I carry around loads of different ones-anotherthing for christmas!!!&nbsp;I thinking the other day if I would get married, I mean it's only really religons have marridge and I'm not religious, so would I get married? I could get married at a regestiry Office but it's still like being a christian isn't it? you still doing one of their rituals, kind of like christmas, nowadays thats just about getting together and gving each other gifts not about Christ being born.&nbsp;I want to get some more black and white striped socks, i saw Milly had some trainer socks like them but I want some more long ones and some with toes, I've only got one pair and they're getting a bit mucky and old. &nbsp;I hope we don't go to the Snooty Fox during the holidays, it's so boring walking down there and having dinner. It's nice to see the familly and have nice food but it takes up too much of my sundays and they're appose to be for restng. &nbsp;I wish I had those Rasmus Cds now, I'm stuck haiving to listen to beyounce Knowles not that she can't sing but it gets pretty boring. Maybe that's why I'm bored...probally...&nbsp;I want to save up for some pink Buffaloes (trainers) when I've got the Cds and books (or just might ask for them for my birthday). I need some decent trainers anyway, mine are too long. On non-school uniform day I tripped up going up the Humanaties block stairs twice which was very umbarrassing! I must of looked like a right clutz, I am quite clumsy though anyway...&nbsp;I got a new email address, it's  urlLink death_haunts_us_all@hotmail.com , my other account ( urlLink cowseed@hotmail.com ) was cluttered and was full of spam. I'm trying to be more neat with my inbox so I can read new mail easily. &nbsp;Okay here's my own quote for today; Life is like Shit, you have to dig through it to find the good bits then you have to swallow the bad bits cause some memories are not worth sharing.&nbsp;Bye bye!!!&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cause all the leeds Festival tickets have sold out, I was planning to convice my dad to take me so I could see The Rasmus. Ohwell, I've ordered the album from Woolworths so I'll just have wait... 
    
</post>


</Blog>