<Blog>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gertha likes blogs.&nbsp; Stay tuned for details!  But first, a charming tale full of wit and excitement:   The Adventures of the James Madison Fan   Club   This episode: Blueberry Justice!     "What's that?" cried  James Madison  as he pranced around a mulberry bush on his imaginary horse. "A frog," replied  Abe Lincoln  from behind a cherry tree (the one that  George Washington  didn't unleash his fury upon). "But it has a beak," interjected  Thomas Paine , who was full of common sense and desired to share it. "Okay, so it's an orang-u-tan,"  Abe  admitted.&nbsp; "But frogs aren't hyphenated like orang-u-tans.&nbsp; How unsightly!"&nbsp; He fanned (and fancied) himself. "MOO, MOO!" exclaimed  J  o  h  n   A  d  a  m  s  in agreement, and he earnestly flapped his arms like a rather large mutant ostrich caught in the violently fatal clutches of a jell-o pudding pool. "I hate that  Jo  hn   Ad  am  s !&nbsp; I daresay he's too tall for my liking!" snorted  Abe , who then saved us all by ending the story. ---  Melodramatic Musings :  People have this uncanny knack for making me want to annihilate things with my fists and my dull vegetarian stegosaurus teeth.&nbsp; People make it their business to bother me.&nbsp; I love Frank Perdue.&nbsp; Jim Perdue is pretty cool, too.&nbsp; They would never bother me.&nbsp; I guess that says a lot about chickens, doesn't it?&nbsp; Anyhoof, I have a lovely rubber chicken collection, and I'm always adopting.&nbsp; Do you know of any rubber chickens who desire a good home?&nbsp; Send them to me!&nbsp; I promise to cherish your chicken!   Corollary :  If&nbsp;a moose sneezes in the forest, and no one is around to hear it, will the moose bless himself?   Tangent :  Opposite over adjacent.   In Conclusion :  Ditto.  P.S.: Marmaduke is not funny.  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      DISCLAIMER:  urlLink     This blog is endorsed by crazed dachshunds!! For those of you who have never met him, this is Schnitzel. He enjoys chewing on squeaky toys and taking long walks on the beach. He loves  urlLink yummy chummies . Don't mess with him.  (Schnitzie!  urlLink   ) 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is the first post!&nbsp; Excitement abounds!!&nbsp; The fonts are scary, however.&nbsp;&nbsp;   Turkey dogs?&nbsp; Oh, no.&nbsp; That must've been Sheriff Slobbitt.   Never trust a panda.&nbsp; It might&nbsp;eat your hand-a.   Snooze cruise!   &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Adventures of the James Madison Fan Club!   This episode: What Happened After Breakfast!   "I'm gooooooooin' to a Go-Go!" sang a fist-pumping  J o h n  A d a m s  with the excitement of a newly-birthed baboon. "Why do you insist on squawking like a duck-billed platymoose," yelled  Abe Lincoln  from atop his Monopoly top hat after receiving his Get-Out-Of-Jail-Free card. "Mayhaps it's because we seem to have been lost in this cornfield for three entire minutes," offered  Thomas Paine , who desperately wanted to be wanted.  "I'm beginning to worry about myself and whether I'm okay out here on my own!"  "YOU'RE NOT!" shouted Cassandra, but nobody really cared about what she had to say. "'Tis true," agreed the Greek chorus.  "If I take one more step,"   Thomas Jefferson  mumbled, "It'll be the farthest away from Montecello I've ever been!" "Oh, who gives a hoof?"  Abe  snarled with gnashed teeth (a difficult thing to accomplish when one has extremely bushy eyebrows). "Ack!" squealed  J o h n  A d a m s .  "I just swallowed a ladybug!  OH GOD, A LAAAAADYBUUUUG!!!!"  He fell to the ground as a recently-shot deer might have, had the recently-shot deer been named " J o h n  A d a m s ."  He laid motionless with his tongue extended in a rather unattractive fashion.  Then he clutched at his throat with his hairy Federalist mitts.  "Bleech, bleech," he added as an afterthought.  Abe  promptly kicked him with his boot.  Hard. " Abe !"   James Madison  exclaimed, leaning down and clinging to his Spatula of Justice for support.  "Why, I do believe you have something stuck to your boot!" "  Bat's muh toofs  !" yelled a withered old hag-man from the town they had recently pillaged, looted, and plundered in the name of  George Washington  (may he live on!). "Well," interjected  Ben Franklin , who had just come from the loo and felt it was his inalienable right to share the punchline, "I guess you could say that  Abe  finally stuck his foot in his mouth...though, well, not HIS mouth, but A mouth, anyway!"  Pause.  "MWAH!" "Yeah, that wasn't funny,  Ben ,"  Thomas Jefferson  snarked.  Then he quickly hit  Mr. Franklin  over the noggin with a rolled up newspaper.  Oddly, in that exact same newspaper, the front page read, "Thank Gourd this painful bit is over!"  Life was good! ---  Some of That P-2 Bling-Bling, Suckas!   "YO, lemme get dat noo  Madden  jawn, naw!"  It was the first customer of the morning.  Two customers, actually.  Two hoodies.  No, I don't mean "hoodlums," I mean "hoodies."  They were wearing them.  Ha!  Okay, back to the story.  While the first guy (the one who had requested the Madden football game) gravitated toward the used section, his friend walked up behind him and asked, "Yo, you guys got any new P-2 games?" P-2.  I loved it.  Not "Playstation 2," not "PS2," but "P-2."  Pretty soon, it'll just be "P."  I smiled.  "Yeah!  This wall over here is all new stuff for the Playstation 2."  Then I pointed to the area right in front of him.  He looked confused. "Naw, I mean, you got the GAME?" "Which one?" "The GAME!" Oooookay.  The game.  What game?  Did a game just come out that he desires?  Is he talking about wanting to play our demo units?  What is this mysterious...."game" of which he speaks?  Then I had a thought.  "Do you mean, the  system ?" "Yeah!"  he exclaimed.  Success!   "The  game !"  Unbelievable.  "Yes, we have those."  I affirmed politely. "How much?" "One-eighty." "Yo, lemme get a discount." "I can't give you a discount." He clicked his tongue.  Apparently he didn't like that answer. "Maaaaaaaan..."  he trailed off.  By this time, the first guy was thoroughly engrossed in his task of finding new violent stuff to play.  "Yo, you play these?" he inquires. "Some of them." "Yo, I wan' a shootin' game.  I wan' like a Gran' Thef' jawn, 'naw, like, where  I can  shoot  people!" "Well, there's SOCOM, which is a millitary-type shooter game." "AWWWWW!!  You get to  shoot  people?" "Yep." "You get to blow their heads off?" I always find it amazing how bloodthirsty ordinary people are. "Yeah, lemme get dat," he said, without waiting for my response.  " And lemme trade this--"  He threw a insanely scratched copy of Madden '98 onto the counter with no case. "Okay, you'll get fifty cents for it." "MAAAAN!!  Fitty cents?!  Ah paid like  ten bucks  for it! Yeah, and it was probably in 1998.   "Sorry, that's what's in the computer." "Can you gimme like a dollar for it?" "No, I can't change the price of a trade-in." More tongue-clicking.  Oh boy. "Okay, lemme trade this, too."  He threw a dirty dreamcast VMU (memory card) onto the counter.  I had to break the bad news again: "Um, you'll get ten cents for it." "DAMN!  You guys tryin' to ROB people!"  I tried to explain everything.  I went into the basic theory of supply and demand.  I told him how nobody wanted his old memory card from a now-defunct system.  I told him how sports titles lose their value as soon as the next year's version comes out.  I commiserated!  I agreed that it was unfair how this corporation was milking the profits from millions of unsuspecting and indifferent consumers! "Yo, lemme get dat strategy guide, too."  Freedom, however, would have to come another day.  -la reina del pollo --- 50% of Americans secretly wish they could own a camel. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "The Shingles Jingles"  Anyone who mingles With a person who has shingles Feels some painful tingles From their head down to their fingles.  It may seem outrageous, But that person is contageous! So if you're elderly Or contracted HIV, Please, just don't go near Because it's chicken pox you'll fear!  ---  The Company-Mandated Phone Greeting Example:     "Thaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaanks for calling Game Zone, where for only five dollars you can reserve  Britney's Strip Tease  for the Game Boy Advance, rated 'E' for 'everyone,' coming out October 8th or the mature-rated first-person shooter  Mickey and Goofy's Prison Break  for the Playstation 2 coming out in time for Thanksgiving on November 15th, and where you can trade in all of your disgustingly dirty, broken, roach-infested and disease-spreading used games and consoles that we honestly don't want and we will pay virtually nothing for, and where you can get a discount on all the used games and consoles you actually buy with our exclusive game zone card that we'll be sure to force upon you repeatedly at the checkout counter until you acquiesce and your soul is finally ours...my name is Marge, how may I help you?"  *click*  Now THAT is good marketing.  --- Helga says: "Don't be rudel, eat streudal."   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Camel Controversy With Robert T. Bruce!    Part Oomph: The Scary Puppet  "Mmnnnn....nothing like the feeling of warm cloth settling against the loins!" yawned Robert T. Bruce as he dismounted from the pole vault that was his mule. "I don't even care about Mount Olympus! Do you know why? I hate those ghastly pomegranates, and I understand that they are quite abundant in the afterlife!" he explained to his diseased companion, Pablo Peculiar. "I shan't miss a thing if I go to Hell instead," he reflected into his travel mirror. "That's nice," replied Pablo (who wasn't). "And furthermore," Robert T. Bruce interrupted, "I daren't wonder what I should look like in a toga!"  Silence.  "A HUH HUH HUH HUH!" He added, shoulders twitching with mirth. Pablo Peculiar said nothing. It was almost as if he had been stricken with a nasty case of the measles, which of course, he had. Robert continued, much to the dismay of the audience: "From this point forward, Pablo, we shall not wont for amusement, for I am quite the jester! I fancy myself immensely!" At this, he dismounted again and headed toward the castle conveniently placed a few yards away.  NEXT SCENE: AT THE CASTLE DOOR  "It's loched."  (drumroll)  "Oh, bother!" squealed Robert T. Bruce. "I forgot the password! Now what was it... antelope ?  Marshmallow ?  Crippled Monkey With Hoof and Mouth Disease ?" "Why," interjected Pablo, "don't you just use the key?" At this point, a very large rock fell from the sky and struck the ground a quarter mile away from Robert T. Bruce. He reacted as a child would have, given the circumstances. "Oh!" he faltered (and fell). "Oh, my head is swimming! My heart is racing! That rock was nowhere near me!"  Pablo graciously changed the subject (and his bandage).  ---  The Truth About Holiday Hiring     I found myself in the middle of a corporate skirmish. Our regional manager insisted that I hire 12 people for the holidays, when we clearly could get by with 8, and in fact, would only be generating enough income to comfortably support 7. "People get tired!" she explained. "We need to switch people from the register to the floor so that they don't get burned out!"   Don't get burned out? What was this, the military?  "..and you can cut your hours by 15." Ah. "..and make a prominent display for all of those unwanted strategy guides for delisted dreamcast games that nobody owns!" Er...? "...and make sure you ask everyone to reserve something, even if they're three years old, don't speak English, and have no arms! Sell, sell, SELL!!!!!" Oh. "...and stay within payroll!" Uh.. "God, I'm beautiful," she exclaimed as she took a break from barking orders to examine her reflection in our newly-polished glass cabinets. "Well," I ventured,"I don't really need anyone else on my staff. I can't train them if I don't have training hours, and to avoid going over payroll I need hours--" "SILENCE!" she shouted, even though we were two regrettable feet apart. "We must make money for our wonderful company! Our company treats us so well! They give us evenings and weekends off, and vehicles to drive, and free laptop computers.." "I don't get any of that," I interrupted. "WHO CARES??!!" she responded. "I GET THESE THINGS AND THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS!!" "I don't understand how I'm supposed to take on five new people, train them while cutting payroll hours, and still get everything done during the busiest part of the year. You won't even allow overtime!" Her face contorted into various expressions, almost as if she were trying to squeeze out some kind of intelligent response. This proved to be too much of an effort, however. "THE COMPANY IS RIGHT! THE COMPANY IS WONDERFULLLL!" she sang, and did what I gathered was supposed to be a "Corporate Happiness Jig." Then she turned around to face my staff: "I DON'T HEAR ANY SELLING GOING ON!"  The madness continues... --- A recent poll showed that 54% of llamas prefer the taste of root beer to Mountain Dew. My question is, "What about Mello Yellow?"  Fin. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>