<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        STOP ALREADY, I SAID STOP "A" HOLE       &nbsp;    &nbsp;    urlLink http://gimsnasium.blogspot.com      
    
</post>


<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Things I wish would go away       The N.B.A      Fox News      Nick & Jessica      Homophobia       urlLink http://www.godhatesfags.com/main/       People who Hate      People who use God for their own warped sense of righteousness      Self promoting politicions who will&nbsp;bomb womyn and&nbsp;children just to prove they were wright about WMD's         &nbsp;      &nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    So I Smoke at least I dont bomb children&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Peel it back and im whats there&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    What You looking at&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So what's the deal with with all this right wing Crap going on in the world Fundi MENTAL ist from every where making the average guy from where ever look like F#*king "A" holes. George,Saddam,Donald,Osama, They all believe they are right&nbsp; Well OK. But why the F#*k does the rest of the world have to worry about what's going to happen just because some religious kooks have to have it there way. WTF.       
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;  What to say just sitting down on a Sunday evening wishing like crap it would cool off. Not a real "heat lovin" kinda guy. Give me 23 C. Every day and I would be happy. Cant really go on forever about the heat that would bore the f@$K out of me if I was reading some one else's Bloog or what ever the F**K these things&nbsp;are called.&nbsp;What to go on aimlessly about maybe piss poor spelling, but I'm sure some "A" holes with nothing better to do than comment on some one else's short Cummings, will do that for me. So i sit here thinking mmmmm still thinking, Ive got it you little piss ant war mongering Iraqi Killing freaks tell me what i should go on about. Or Maybe You God loving Right of center Choice denying 'we believe in freedom as long as it's just us KOOK's. Can tell me why womyn cant choose or me and my boy friend cant get married.                  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I thought I would take a look for a couple of different points of views on the whole HOMO church going QUEER like me getting married thing.so here's two links feel free to read both I'm sure one will make you proud and the other will make you scream. I don't really care which one you agree with but please have the "JAM" to pick one side or the the other. "either hot or cold but luke warm i shall spit from my mouth"    urlLink http://www.infidels.org/library/modern/william_edelen/homophobics.html    urlLink http://members.shaw.ca/jondykstra/articles/00january2.html    &nbsp;  But rember what that famous philosapher Beverly Leslie said. "She's pretty untill she speaks." So please remain pretty  &nbsp;  &nbsp;   
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    WTF&nbsp; urlLink   
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I cant believe all the crap and piss that spout from the mouths of Christian conservatives in Canada. Don't get me wrong, I believe in God, the same God they do (I thinks it's the same God). I even go to a Presbyterian(Re: Scottish Reformed) Church which as far as main line denominations go, is pretty conservative. I cant understand how some people can be so adamant that BEING A " QUEER " entitles you to a one way trip to  HELL .   If I remember my Sunday school lesson's properly Mmmm lets me see.     Christianity is Named After Jesus Christ    He was born from a Virgin Birth and was the Son of God    He was also the the Second part of the FATHER,SON, and Holly GHOST trilogy thing, you there all part of God. God is "GOD", Jesus is "God" and the Holly Spirit is "GOD"     So if Jesus had important things to say (and he did) I would have thought he would have said something on the "EVILS" of being a evil,l evil ,hand bag, toting, liSssspppy speaking,man loving sodomite. So I turned to my Trust king James Edition of the Bible to see what Jesus said about me and People like me(you know HOMOS) I also looked in my revised standard version and my good News for modern man version. All tree versions all reported every thing Jesus had to say about "MY TYPE OF PEOPLE"&nbsp;you ready, this is what he said.    Absafuckinlutley NOTHING. You would think if it was such a no no to share your Love and Life with some one of the Same Sex the Guy would have said somthing.Mmmm he did say" love one and other as I have loved you" he also said "Go ye into all the world and preach my gospel to every creature.' Nothing about beating the shit out of "Fags", nothing about Hate at all . Mainly it was about Love, Respect and Compassion.(no not the type of compassion some Ass holes Showed Matthew Sheppard) The Compassion Jesus showed the dregs of his Society. Tax collectors, prostitutes, the Mentally Ill.&nbsp;    I'm proud of who I am, I am proud of what I believe, and I&nbsp;am proud to say I&nbsp;believe in&nbsp;"GOD" but not the Right Wing&nbsp;Neo conservative Fag hating God that seems to be totally different and sometimes confused with&nbsp;my&nbsp;"GOD". So to That I say "WTF"(WHAT THE F@#K)    &nbsp;    &nbsp;        
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Things&nbsp; That&nbsp;I hope &nbsp;Stick Around          The N.H.L.      &nbsp;  MSNBC news  
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Dear:  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Left wing HOMO freak  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  I just read your response to my letter you must think your really F**KING funny. I don't really appreciate you making me look like a stupid back water moron. You must think your pretty funny. From what I've heard about Canadians you must be the only one north of "the land of the free" with a sense of humor(if that's what it is). Being from the frozen&nbsp;north you should stick to what you know. Like growing maple syrup, hunting smoked salmon and playing that girlie game called hockey. You should leave being funny up to professional comedians and proud Americans like    urlLink   Jim Carrey     ,    urlLink   Mike Myers     ,Lorne Michaels,&nbsp; Tom Green and the late    urlLink   Phill Hartman      .  If Canada had citizens half as funny as these American greats maybe you wouldn't be the laughing stalk of the comedy world.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Who's Laughing Now  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Proud Young&nbsp;Yankee     &nbsp;  Dear:  Proud Young Yankee          You need no help from me to make&nbsp;you&nbsp; look like " a stupid back water moron" you seem to have that covered.      One does not grow maple syrup or hunt for smoked salmon. Maple syrup is "tapped" from the maple tree. So we might grow maple trees but we don't grow syrup, we may "fish" for salmon, but it does not come from the ocean already smoked.      If you think hockey is such a girlie game then I challenge you to strap on some skates go to Madison square gardens and challenge Mark Messier to a game of "girlie" one on one action.      You stupid F**KING idiot all those famous American comedians you mentioned are from CANADA. Are you a drug addict or just retarded. If you are the future of America I foresee a great&nbsp; opportunity for Canadians. Providing a whole nation with behavior modification programs for the mentally challenged.        &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; From the bottom of my heart       &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; God Bless (you'll need it)        &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Gim         
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Dear Gim: &nbsp;   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I not sure if you are aware of all the wonderful things America has given to the world. Like Basketball,the Telephone,the light bulb,T.V. and many, many other wonderful inventions. But the best thing America has given to the world is  urlLink DEMOCRACY.  What to you think about that you left wing HOMO        freak       &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;     &nbsp;   Best regards&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;Proud Young Yankee         &nbsp;    Dear:      &nbsp;Proud Young Yankee:       &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Thank you for you letter. I'm not sure where to start it seems to me that you may have a point or two, it also seems your full of sh*t. First of all Basketball was invented in 1891 by James Naismith a   urlLink  Canadian   . I looked into your claim that the Telephone was invented by one of your fellow Americans and sorry to say that is wrong too. It was invented by Alexander Graham Bell in 1876. Oh well lets move on shall we.So where are we oh yea the light bulb, wrong again Yankee man. Henry Woodward invented the electric light bulb in 1874 and sold the patent to Thomas Edison . I'm sure the source of all knowledge in America the television must have been invented there. It appears I was wrong, Reginald A. Fessenden patented a television system in 1927 . Well what do you know ? As for democracy "A" hole. I found a site that would back up your claim if by "AMERICAN" you meant "GREEK"      urlLink   http://www.bbc.co.uk/history/ancient/Greeks/greekdemocracy_01.shtml       But even if democracy was "invented" by Americans, your&nbsp;Idea of democracy has worked&nbsp;extremely well in places around the world such&nbsp;as Florida in the 2000 election of your President. Now that was as&nbsp;precise as&nbsp;a Swiss (maybe American invented) watch. Once again thanks for dropping me a letter even if they ( letters that is) weren't invented in the states it sure is nice to see Americans don't mind using&nbsp;foreign&nbsp;technology.      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;GOOD LUCK        &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Gim                            
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Ten Great Vacation Spots     urlLink   Abu Ghraib P    urlLink   rison&nbsp;     &nbsp; you will be absolutely floored by the five star treatment you receive from your American hosts.     urlLink   Guantánamo Bay     &nbsp; another fantastic property brought to you by the same management team that runs Abu Ghraib     urlLink   Yucca Mountain     &nbsp;If the beaches of Guantanamo Bay aren't for you maybe the crisp mountain air in the mountain of Nevada.      Middletown, Pennsylvania home of    urlLink   Three Mile Island    &nbsp; if Yucca Mountain called your name then let Three Mile Island give you a charge like you've never had   before         urlLink  Bhopal, India    if the far east seem to be calling your name remember pesticides are our friends .       &nbsp;    urlLink   3 Gorges Dam     &nbsp;if you thought only America had wonders of the world you have never   seen the beauty of China. The Yangtze River in China is the World's third longest river and now it covers thousands of homes and even the occasional farmer. Oh Good Times of course unless you used to live there.     &nbsp;    urlLink Kabul , city in east central Afghanistan&nbsp;a jewel of the world at least it was. If you can wear a  urlLink burka  and enjoy the occasional&nbsp;bomb being lobed your way by Muslim fundamentalists then this is the stop for you.       urlLink  McMurdo Base Antarctica   &nbsp;if the heat of the middle east is to much for you try one of the coolest spots on earth its the place to be seen or should I say you will only be seen 3-4 months a year since the rest of the years its dark all day. MMmmMM Cool   urlLink  Saddam's palace   &nbsp;another hot&nbsp;Uncle Sam property come look but don't touch or your trip might get extended with stops in Abu Grhaib and Guantanamo Bay.     urlLink  Canada's Senate   &nbsp;so it's not a hot spot or a cool place to be but if your lucky enough to make into the senate you have basically won the lottery. You will get all of your expenses paid, beautiful antique furniture&nbsp;, and a endless supply of&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Manure brought to&nbsp;you from the&nbsp;Prime Minister's Office.      &nbsp;                       
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink  In the beging God created the heaven and the earth   . 2 Now the earth was [  urlLink  1   ] formless and empty, darkness was over the surface of the deep, and the Spirit of God was hovering over the waters. 3 And God said, "Let there be light," and there was light. 4 God saw that the light was good, and he separated the light from the darkness. 5 God called the light "day," and the darkness he called "night." And there was evening, and there was morning-the first day. 6 And God said, "Let there be an expanse between the waters to separate water from water." 7 So God made the expanse and separated the water under the expanse from the water above it. And it was so. 8 God called the expanse "sky." And there was evening, and there was morning-the second day. 9 And God said, "Let the water under the sky be gathered to one place, and let dry ground appear." And it was so. 10 God called the dry ground "land," and the gathered waters he called "seas." And God saw that it was good. 11 Then God said, "Let the land produce vegetation: seed-bearing plants and trees on the land that bear fruit with seed in it, according to their various kinds." And it was so. 12 The land produced vegetation: plants bearing seed according to their kinds and trees bearing fruit with seed in it according to their kinds. And God saw that it was good. 13 And there was evening, and there was morning-the third day. 14 And God said, "Let there be lights in the expanse of the sky to separate the day from the night, and let them serve as signs to mark seasons and days and years, 15 and let them be lights in the expanse of the sky to give light on the earth." And it was so. 16 God made two great lights-the greater light to govern the day and the lesser light to govern the night. He also made the stars. 17 God set them in the expanse of the sky to give light on the earth, 18 to govern the day and the night, and to separate light from darkness. And God saw that it was good. 19 And there was evening, and there was morning-the fourth day. 20 And God said, "Let the water teem with living creatures, and let birds fly above the earth across the expanse of the sky." 21 So God created the great creatures of the sea and every living and moving thing with which the water teems, according to their kinds, and every winged bird according to its kind. And God saw that it was good. 22 God blessed them and said, "Be fruitful and increase in number and fill the water in the seas, and let the birds increase on the earth." 23 And there was evening, and there was morning-the fifth day. 24 And God said, "Let the land produce living creatures according to their kinds: livestock, creatures that move along the ground, and wild animals, each according to its kind." And it was so. 25 God made the wild animals according to their kinds, the livestock according to their kinds, and all the creatures that move along the ground according to their kinds. And God saw that it was good. 26 Then God said, "Let us make man in our image, in our likeness, and let them rule over the fish of the sea and the birds of the air, over the livestock, over all the earth, [  urlLink  2    ] and over all the creatures that move along the ground." 27 So God created man in his own image, in the image of God he created him; male and female he created them. 28 God blessed them and said to them, "Be fruitful and increase in number; fill the earth and subdue it. Rule over the fish of the sea and the birds of the air and over every living creature that moves on the ground." 29 Then God said, "I give you every seed-bearing plant on the face of the whole earth and every tree that has fruit with seed in it. They will be yours for food. 30 And to all the beasts of the earth and all the birds of the air and all the creatures that move on the ground-everything that has the breath of life in it-I give every green plant for food." And it was so. 31 God saw all that he had made, and it was very good. And there was evening, and there was morning-the sixth day  .     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Once again I'm drawn to the love for all of Gods people that is preached by the people at the Westboro Baptist Church, located at 3701 W. 12th Street in Topeka, KS. E-MAIL    urlLink   mailto:ghf@godhatesamerica.com      they seem like such a loving group of people. I pray every day that I could grow up to be like them. I'm working on a new name but all the good ones like Adolph,Saddam,Osama,Stalin, and even SATAN seem to have been already taken. Oh well ill just have go on living the rest of my life knowing I cant live up to the level of all worlds hate mongers. So ill resign myself to live my life with  PRIDE,LOVE and TOLERANCE . Oh I wish I could hate like them but the God I believe in fills me with  love,pride and understanding . WTF.(What The F*CK)    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink  Shrimp      urlLink Does God Hate Your Tattoos      urlLink FIGS      urlLink HOMOPHOBES      urlLink GLOBE      urlLink God hates godhatesfags.com    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink   http://www.godlovesgays.com/       
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Dear Gim Have you ever wondered what would happen if George W Bush had not won(stole) the election from Al Gore in 2000. Yours Truly Uncle Sam  Dear Uncle Sam      I really haven't given it much thought being from Canada and all. We have our own Morons, to be concerned with. I guess the biggest thing we would have is a lack of great quotes like       "Teach a child to read and he or her will be able to pass a literacy test."—Townsend, Tenn., Feb. 21, 2001      Bush before the election:"I trust the people."Bush after the election:"People can't be trusted."      "More Muslims have died at the hands of killers than—I say more Muslims—a lot of Muslims have died—I don't know the exact count—at Istanbul. Look at these different places around the world where there's been tremendous death and destruction because killers kill."—Washington, D.C., Jan. 29, 2004      "In an economic recession, I'd rather that in order to get out of this recession, that the people be spending their money, not the government trying to figure out how to spend the people's money."—Tampa, Fla., Feb. 16, 2004      I also bet Al Gore would have said equally stupid things     
    
</post>


</Blog>