<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mother :  "Eh do you know what time it is? Where are you? Who are you with? What time are you coming back?"    Me :  "Soon."    Mother :  "doooo.........."       That's my mum, in a good mood, at maybe 3.50am on a Sunday morning, calling my mobile to see if I'm still alive, while I'm out gallivanting with my mates, rotting at some 24hr coffee place. When she's in a bad mood, it's a shriller voice, lesser questions and a louder slam before the engaged tone. When I'm finally home, there'd be my mum, standing at my door, dressed in her white nightie, clutching her bolster like a weapon, hair like a squirrel danced through it, trying to stare at me through unfocused eyes. That's her showing her displeasure at me. We have very good mother-daughter communication.       Quite guiltily, I've been going home late consecutively for 5 nights. Tonight would be the sixth. Usually it's only during the weekends, but I can't help it if I'm suddenly THE 'Absolute Person To Hang Out With' for the week right? If I could I'd rather hang out in the day, go home by 10, sleep before 11 and get rid of my dark eye rings. But how could I, when work ends at 6 for my friends, class sometimes end at 10 for me, clubs open at 11 and McD's cafe is now 24hrs? And because we get home late, we sleep the entire morning away, crawl reluctantly out of bed after midday, and only start getting hyped up for the day by late afternoon. I bet you my last one-cent that if you checked our eyesights, we would have mysteriously developed excellent night-vision. That's right. We're becoming vampires, wolves, ghostly beings. We shun the light and embrace the darkness.      Digressing... So where was I? My dad keeps saying that I need to change my lifestyle. I understand why he's concerned, because I don't see my parents much anymore. While they sleep, I'm out taking drugs and drinking my life away (or so they think), and while I sleep, they're doing the housework and playing Happy Family.       Really, I don't know what it is about the night that beckons so. There's just something about it that makes us want to discard our inhibitations, leave our burdens by the door and just, hang out. I know my parents would never see my point. After all, when they were our age, I doubt they had midnight shows or 24hr cafes. And whatever fashionable music at that time, is retro to us now.      
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Alcohol. What is it about this vile liquid that makes people want to consume it in large amounts, and make bloody fools out of themselves? It's okay if you can hold your drink well, it's not so when you start shrieking like a banshee whenever your fave song comes on, then start gyrating on the dance floor like a mad chimpanzee high on E. In the alcohol-induced state, you think you look real sexy there, but let me tell you, you're just the joke of the night for the audience.     &nbsp;   I started regularly going to clubs 7 years ago. You would think I'm used to all the booze now, but I really hate it. Liquor, wine, beer... all taste the same to me. Yucky. To think I spent 3 years studying its creation process. I don't remember any text mentioning the after-effects though. I really admire anyone who can down 5 glasses of anything with more than 3 ingredients inside, and still talk coherently after. I've never been drunk - not because I'm a good drinker - but because usually after the 1st glass,&nbsp;I get the mother of all headaches. And the feeling is equivalent to severe seasickness. Many a night, I grip the edge of the seat, white-knuckled and keeping my mouth tightly shut to keep my intestines in, while the pervy cab driver reckons he's Schumacher on the traffic-light ridden streets of SG. So all I wanna do is go home with insides intact, clean up the warpaint, and get jiggy with my comfy bed. Plus I'm allergic to booze. I get these tiny,  evil -looking red protrusions on my arms and legs the morning after. Eyebags + Puffy Eyes + Stale-smelling Ciggy Hair + Red Polka Dots. Very pretty.     &nbsp;   Last night we went down to a club in MS. It was Ladies' Night, free cover, free drinks, free eye candy, free 2nd hand smoke. And to make things worse, a friend was working there, so drinks were appearing at our table on auto.  E  says she hadn't partied in a long time, so pop she goes, 2 glasses in 10 minutes.&nbsp; By 1230hrs, she's talking 10 decibels louder and getting bitchy about everyone on the dancefloor. By 0130hrs, we were stumbling out of the club and making our way home. After all, it was already Friday morning, and all of them had to work. Lucky me =). No work, no hangover, can wake up at 1 in the afternoon.     &nbsp;   We made our way ( J  ambling like an old man,  E  claiming she's flying) to the carpark at UE Square. I had to keep shushing  E  as&nbsp;her giggles were bouncing rudely off the walls of the apartment blocks, and the security guard was looking murderous cuz we woke him from his sleep.  E  says she hadn't been this drunk for a long time. I ask if she wanted to do this again next week, and she says "Of course!". 10 minutes later in the car, after stopping twice for her to regurgitate her lunch onto the pavement, I ask the same question again. This time, sprawled all over the front seat, her reply was a weak nod. What a hardy little girl.      
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       These few weeks have been frustrating for me. Well, every teeny thing would be frustrating to you if you were an analyser. I like to grab a situation by its neck, sit it down handcuffed on my couch, tear its clothes out and get to the stark nakedness of reality. Kinky huh. Actually no, the process is so Tayloristic it's boring. I like to break things down into small digestable nibblets and analyse, analyse, analyse. You see, there has to be an explanation for everything. (At this point,  C  would go "Aiyah, Virgo what")        But I've just about had it up to  here . It's bad enough that I have a screwed up life. It's even worse watching your friends screw theirs up. It's worst when it's all happening at the same time. It's a freaking chain reaction.  A  broke up with bf.  C  broke up with bf.  E  wants to divorce husband.  H  and  L  broke up.  J  broke up with bf. Aaaargh! How would you feel, sitting in front of your silver HP LCD (sexy hor!), watching, jaw to the floor, as your friends relate their disintegrating lives on yahoo and msn? At the same time? I'm no lung-rotter, but at that moment, all I wanted to do was grab a fag, sit at my balcony and develop frown lines on my forehead. Not so because I think smoking solves things, but because isn't that what people do when they're really stressed? Better than sitting like blow-up doll Annie in front of your com screen.       Well frankly, I do have a sound explanation for all the 'malfunctions' mentioned above, being the woman of the world I am (clears throat). All arguments, breakups and divorces boil down to one very corny song : People don't know what they want, what they really really want. (Shit now I can't get that song outta my head. Shit that's another song!) No seriously.        People confused. People play mind games. People get hurt. People get addicted to pain. People play more games. People get more confused. And it goes on. It's vicious, like a stomach flu virus. You puke, you shit, you pour disgusting, unidentifiable stuff down your throat, you puke it out, and you shit some more. ( shivers with the memory ) And it's freaking contagious!       Yeah I know what it's all about. Been there, done that, got the free T-shirt. We know it hurts and it's stupid, but we all love to roll around in a pit of mud and self pity. But really, we all need to fall really low before we can find the steady ground to spring back up again. For the benefit of all my friends who could be reading this, let me end on an optimistic note. All this toxin flushing is bad, but it's good too. If there's no end to a bad thing, there wouldn't be a chance for any good beginning, would there? Ah, see now. I'm confusing myself. No worries, I'll go play some sadistic, self-satisfying mind games first. (Rubs hands with glee)       Scrabble, anyone? =D      
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Talk is rife. SATC is invading SG. For months, magazines have raved about it, then journalists caught on and wrote about it. 2 weeks ago, hundreds of thousands of pink, tabloid sized advertisements were handed out to SGreans, announcing the premier of the last season on HBO. Yesterday, I was browsing through the mag rack at the newsagent and  lo and behold!  I saw those  blinking  four words on both our tv weeklies, and also on the cover of a leading  female  mag. Apparently, MediaCorp's whippin' up some local-flavoured SATC concoction, starring  both &nbsp;the Ah Jies, of course. This is my worry : Kinda late yeah, but is SG ready for SATC?     &nbsp;   For those of you (eg. my mum) who think SATC is a new diet pill, take out your credit card, log on to HBO.com and purchase all seasons of the dvd now. There are cheaper ways, but yeah, you catch my drift.     &nbsp;   Needless to say, "SATC changed my life" (camera pans on badly made up face). Am I beginning to sound like those diet pills testimonials? SATC didn't slim down "my hips and thighs" though. Too much late night tv for me. I've become more aware of my sexuality, more expressive in my dressing, and have (further) broadened my views on relationships. I'm enjoying this change in me, though my mum's kinda worried about my weekly partying. My partner feels I'm too  Carrie  for public transport, I'm as cynical as  Miranda , and aspire to be  Samantha  in bed. However, there's a little  Charlotte  in me that stabilizes my crankiness. Just like them I always hang out with the same people. Recently, I've even sat down with them for late night chats. I was beginning to think we all have no life, but I convince myself by&nbsp;saying we were just being very SATC. =P     &nbsp;   Really, it's such a funny show, I think women of all ages should be able to enjoy it. Even guys I know who had the luck to watch it, loved it. Now back to my worry. My conclusion is, walk down Orchard Road, check out the clubs, look at all the fashionable, sexy, capable, independent women out there. Of course along the way, you'd hear some 'tsk-tsking' from unapproving aunties wearing gaudy, dumpling-tight spandex spag tops with pedal pushers and platform shoes, or sense jealous eyes boring down your St Tropez-tanned back. Before you do something stupid like throw your Jimmy Choos at them, think carefully. Wouldn't you rather :     &nbsp;   a. Stride past them and flash them your boobs ( Samantha )    b. Walk right up to them and give 'em a piece of your mind ( Miranda )    c. Worry at first, but hold your head up high and waltz past them like a Princess ( Charlotte )    d. Ignore them, but fret about it, then go home and write it in your journal. ( Carrie )     &nbsp;   Is SG SATC-ready?     &nbsp;   Put on your pink tutus, girls, I think we are. &nbsp;    &nbsp;&nbsp;    &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Must forgiven = forgotten? I won't relate the times I've been adviced to forgive and forget. And each time I maintained that though I may forgive, I may not necessarily forget. Reversely, while I may have forgotten, it doesn't mean that I have forgiven. Why was the english word 'grudge' invented if not for the use of the word?     &nbsp;   If your partner two-timed you, and you decide to take him/her back, do you forget it  ever  happened? If a childhood friend betrayed you once upon a time and then disappeared&nbsp;- you may not even recall the year - do you forgive his/her actions? If you say yes to both, bless you, for you have&nbsp;the heart of an angel. Otherwise, you better have yourself checked for amnesia.     &nbsp;   I won't go as far as to say I bear deep grudges all the time. Let's just avoid discussing the grey area which include small, petty matters in which it is easy to forgive and then forget, or forget and then forgive.&nbsp;I'm talking about major, heartbreaking, name-calling, furniture-throwing, tonsil-stretching events here. Maybe I don't have an advanced emotional system that caches my feelings into b drive (brain) or h drive (heart) or Recycle Bin.     &nbsp;   Time is the mediating factor here.     &nbsp;   Incidents that I chose to forgive obviously mattered alot to me, and were central to my very existence. That, is my explanation for having engraved them on my life-giving organ. Time may have healed all the pain, but it doesn't erase the memory. Incidents that I chose not to forgive obviously tugged at my revengeful and childish nerve. Many other factors could have prevented the matters from being resolved,&nbsp;for example, having an unapologetic  bitch  of an opponent, or the sudden disappearance of a player in the 'event'. But I move on, maybe I'll harp on it for a month or two, but I move on. Time casts a blanket over unresolved matters, but nothing can deny the skeletons hiding underneath.     &nbsp;   So  J , though I like to&nbsp;bring up&nbsp;the past, it only means that you matter to me. Neither would I mind if you retaliate by telling everyone how I wronged you before.&nbsp;It goes to show that I mean alot to you. About those matters where we're both standing at the same side (re : cars, best friends,&nbsp;girlfriends), don't tell me to forget the&nbsp;grievous bodily harm&nbsp;inflicted on me, for nothing hurts me more than a punctured pride. I guess I'm alright with  M  now, for her only fault is in being weak.  A  is another matter. Not only does it stand for ArchEnemy, I've thrown down my gauntlet and shall never retrieve it. I look forward to the day of her demise. &nbsp;    &nbsp;     
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey guys, you're all invited. But please make your own way to Taipei. It's really a hush-rush affair, so please don't tell the media where it is either. Yes, yes, finally. Jay and I are getting married. A summer wedding. Lots of tulle, tulips, white and paparazzi posing as waiters. Then we'll have a beautiful&nbsp;recep in a basketball court (his idea) and we'll be married at the top floor of Taipei 101 (my idea). He'll get all the hype he needs for his new album, I'll get all the fame. He gets himself a beautiful wife, I get all his money. Then we'll have 2.75 kids and live happily ever after. Perfect. Jolin may be one of my bridesmaids but I haven't decided if I should ask her or not. I mean, thick lips just don't go well with tulips, do they?     &nbsp;   The date you say? Don't you know, it's all over the news. 3rd August. So sweet of Jay to time his proposal together with his new album's release date. *giggles. Yeah, he hasn't proposed yet, but I'm sure he will. After all I'm flying there to meet him on the 2nd. MediaCorp's paying for my ticket, ya know? Oh yes, that reminds me. I have to take part in the contest first before they'd give me the air ticket. Oh you mean I have to win first?     &nbsp;   Damn.      
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I fell in love with a song     A song I wish someone would sing to me     Its melody : common but heart-warming     Its lyrics : simple but heart-melting          I fell in love with a song     A song I wish was written for me     Its melody : soft yet heart-pounding     Its lyrics : sweet yet heart-wrenching          I fell in love with a song     A song that sounds so familiar to me     Its melody : pure and heart-cleansing     Its lyrics : clear and heart-aching          I fell in love with a song     A song that was never written for me     Its melody : my tears are falling     Its lyrics : my heart is breaking     - michelle         
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [written @ 1800hrs Thursday 5th Aug. Burger King, Plaza Singapura]    So here I am sitting alone, having left the house early to avoid conversation with my dad. Now I'm freaking 45 minutes early for my class, and the last thing I want is to be sitting in the classroom surrounded by people I don't like and dwiddle my thumbs. Got myself a Banana Split thingy (Just $2.95 for a dessert and a drink - says coupon) that's all cream and no nutrients. I'd rather be having a chicken whopper but I can't! Having dinner with  J  later.      I can't remember the last time I ate a McD's burger. In case you don't already know, Basement One in PS is fastfood heaven. Mos Burger, Long John Silver, Burger King, KFC, McD's.... every student's ideal canteen. I find it really uncanny that for 4 days in a row, I've seen school kids clutching transparent plastic bags with the yellow   M   on it, stealing furtive looks as they try to sneak a fry into their waiting mouths. Then you see them chewing really quickly, as if that oily sponge of a potato would lift its hidden legs and run off if they didn't swallow it down first. Oh, they're loving it alright. Pa da ba ba ba.      To me, Bk is called Bk for a reason. I've never tasted any fastfood burger better than theirs. My eyes light up everytime I spot a blue-capped, uniformed guy being rudely groped by ladies on their way to the MRT station. I don't grope him, for God's sake (I might just accidentally burst a few of his pimples) but I try to stride past as sexily as I can, and act nonchalant, hoping that the poor guy would be so glad to see a pretty face he'd thrust 5 coupon leaflets in my hands. Doesn't work at all. I always end up being pushed off balance by another groper. Therefore, always grope if you want the leaflets.      I know it's weird but I think KFC do serve excellent chicken nuggets. I've given up on their chicken parts - they're getting smaller and smaller, which induces you to buy bigger sets, which then results in you eating more, which in turn makes you decide to boycott KFC for 6 months to lose all that fat. Wrong strategy, Colonel, try another. But I digress... what was my point? Oh yes. There're about 15 people in the queue before me now, each clutching a coupon leaflet. Crikey, the fastfood devils' got us planning our meals their way. Oh well, who's complaining? I have like, 15 minutes left til class. Wonder if I should go next door to LJS and get me some big, fat, crispy fries...       
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Scenario:       My mum's in the shipping business and my dad is in the airline business. My family resides in an executive condominium. I have a room to myself and sleep on a king-sized bed. As far as I can remember, my dad has changed cars 4 times. In primary school, a school bus would fetch me to and from school. It was only in secondary school that I learnt how to take public transport. In the early secondary days, my dad would fetch me to school every morning. It was only after I persuaded him to give me some independence that he allowed me to take public bus with my friends. Once a year, we would travel during the school holidays. I've been travelling since I was 3, which I think is very silly because I don't even recall those experiences. So far, I've been to the US, Australia, Hong Kong and I count  Japan  as my favourite country. I've been there more than 10 times and I still can't get enough of it.       Question:   Do I sound like a rich bitch?       I don't know how open minded you are but damn! Seeing it from another's point of view it's no wonder people think I hail from some wealthy family. All I did was omit some facts. You see, my mum has been working in the same company for 27 years. She was only made Section Head a few years ago. My dad's also been with his company for a long time. He's been to almost every department in the company and he's finally settled down in Sales, where he's been bullied by his Dickhead of a boss. We're staying in an exec condo in a residential area in the east, surrounded by HDB flats. Very few people realise it's a condo because we sort of blend into the flats. But that's alright. I've got a nice, unobstructed view of Suntec.       I used to share my tiny room with my bro, but since the computer arrived, he has migrated to the other room, leaving me with 2 super single beds. The only logical thing to do was to pull the 2 beds together into a Hollywood twin. Hence the King Sized Bed. My dad switch cars out of convenience. We went from a small Honda, to a 2nd hand Honda, to a 2nd hand Lancia to the Toyota that we have now, and of which my dad is still paying his ass off. My dad used to fetch me to school because my bro's school was just next to mine, so again it was more feasible for my dad to fetch us there. We travel every year because my dad gets concession tickets with the airline he's working for, so duh, we travel more out of kiasu-ism than because we have spare cash to throw.       Moral of the story : Lying by omission is good.  It can make you sound really upperclass if you want to.      I don't own a single piece of LV, Prada or Gucci, not even a low-grade imitation. I shop at Mango and Zara, only when the big '70% End-Of-Season Sale' sign is up. 50% of the clothes I own have no brands, another 20% from auctions, and the rest I don't even remember where I picked them up from. Probably at some sale too. Some people say I look and behave rich. That's because they don't know me well. Just ask my closest friends. They know how cheena I am. I look the way I look because I carry myself well. There's no one I can attribute this to, except to my school, which thought me poise and confidence in speech. And maybe because I do have a sense of style, I choose clothes which have classic cuts and hide the flaws well (I hope?).      The first impression I give to people is that I'm really stuck up and that I'm fierce. That's because I was born with a poker face, and I find it inane to have a smile on my face when there's nothing to smile about. People usually think I'm a rebelliously wild person, who smoke and drink and club alot. I'm never rebellious, I just have my own opinions. I'm surrounded by people who can drink and do smoke alot, but only my friends know I'll never touch a ciggie with a yardstick. I won't even touch a cig pack when my friends ask me to pass theirs to them. If you've read my previous post you'll know that I don't like drinking either. I club alot mainly because I love music and dancing. I can dance 3 hrs straight without drinking a sip of water if the music's good. (That's why clubs hate me.)      See how deceiving looks can be? And woah, one sure can talk when they're talking about themselves, huh?      
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       SG is boring. Expensive, crowded and boring. My friends and I have run out of places to go and things to do. There's gonna be a  long weekend  soon, and though we started thinking about it 2 weeks ago, we still can't decide where to go. Moreover, everywhere's gonna be really crowded, and the last thing we want is to be jostling with the herded sheep and fighting for oxygen.       We had initially wanted to go to the zoo. But  R 's gf  A 's gonna be hauling ass to Bangkok on Friday, we can't leave her out of a sunny day at the zoo, can we? The thought of leaving SG did come, but even if we wanted to, KL's all booked out. The next idea was to book a hotel room, maybe watch some dvds and boogie the night away. I've even come up with the idea (actually, suggestion from my dad) of a sleepover at my place - so juvenile! Thankfully I have loud music and enough bottles of vodka to make it all adult. Ish.  C  then suggested a picnic at Sentosa, but then she has plans to go partying the night before that. Imagine having to wake up for a picnic when you have just barely slept the night away. So that's out. How pathetic.      Now if we had a bank vault bursting with gold coins, we'd be wining and dining without a care in the world. If there were problems, it would be a different story altogether : Which country to go? Which restaurant to be seen at? Which hotel suite to book? But of course, we're more likely to have oxidised silver coins jingling in a piggybank. So maybe it'll be just some cheap wine and coffeeshop dinner. How frustrating. it'll be a  long weekend , surely we have to do something different. I hope we'll not end up doing what we have been doing almost every weekend now, clubbing, or watching anti-climatic movies, or playing pool, or hanging out at 24hr McD's. Please guys, anything but these.          
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       As predicted, the previous post didn't go down very well. This one should be pretty well received though. After receiving so many emails about it recently, I just cannot ignore it anymore. It's been a hot topic between  C  and me too, well actually it's more like a complaining session.  Kimberly Locke  didn't know what she was singing about, THESE should be classified as the 8th world wonder. What else could make both men and women steal glances, gawk and stare in wonderment? A majority of us were introduced to them as babies, but the fascination only starts at the onset of puberty.      I'm talking about breasts.  J  told me about a colleague who'll stop whatever he's doing whenever a pair jiggles past. "Big ones, huh." I ask. "No, as long as got neh, he will just stop talking and look."  J  says. It's not just the males, you know. When I see a woman sitting opposite me in the MRT with her tits hangin' out, I'd stare too. I don't mean to judge, I wear cleavage-baring clothes too. That is, I  try  to bare my cleavage, if you call the 2 lumps sticking out of my chest boobs. Hence the complaining sessions. "Sigh, cannot wear that, boobs too small." "So nice, but buy for what, also cannot wear, too flat." "Woah, check out her longkang."       I love looking at boobs. Whenever I receive those voyeur-y pics in the email, the 1st thing I look out for are the girl's tits. If it's all small and saggy, I'd just delete the email. Not worth forwarding at all. Now if the girl's boobs are really pert and of the right size, I'd nod in appreciation, droop the sides of my lips in envy, then forward the email. I think the most beautiful ones are between B and C cup, round, pert, and punctuated by a small snubby nipple. To me, anything more than that is vulgarly excessive and should be restrained behind those torture contraptions known as bras.   I'm pretty troubled by my pair. It's weird because the womenfolk in my family possess huge ones. Even my dad's almost catching up. What did my mum forget to feed me? To make it all worse, I lost some weight during my recent bout of stomach flu. I'm not sure if it's a bane or a boon, cuz my mammaries decided to join in the fun and slimmed down too.       Sometimes I wonder what's with those E and F cups. It's alright if they're proportionate to the body, but it's really amazing when a 24" waist has to support anything more than D cup. There was once I saw this slim girl from afar at the MRT station. She was walking rather strangely, like she sprained her waist or something. When she came up close and stood in front of me, I realised why. Her boobs were huge!! It was quite grotesque actually. If you threw a coin down her cleavage I'm quite sure you can hear the coin's " Yahooooo !" echo down it. I decided to wait for the train a little farther back from her, in case she turned around and knock me off the platform onto the tracks.       I console myself by saying that God was making up for something. Like for example, big on talent but failing in the looks department, or big on brains but terrible personality, that kinda thing. I'm still pretty happy with that. I'm not exactly lacking in looks, have a good sized brain and a cute personality. So God's fair. I'm not a fan of surgery, so silicon's out. Meantime, I'll continue with the daily massages, continue admiring others' boobs, continue forwarding those emails.    
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [Post has been removed due to complaints from jealous boyfriends]   
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I realised yesterday that I become a different person when I'm behind the wheel. As opposed to my usual cautious and demure self, I become reckless, profanities I never knew existed fly out of my mouth like any other cab driver complaining about everything, and I smash my beautiful Lotus 340 Roadster to pieces without a care in the world. Yes, I suffer from roadrage. The victim : my tv.      I've recently become addicted to the Xbox. The game's Project Gotham, some racing thing that I can't be bothered to explain about (mainly because I'm utterly clueless about the Kudos Championship thing they have goin' on). I've always thought it was cool to be able to be the top scorers at the Daytona arcade but I've never tried it cuz I don't wanna embarass myself. I don't even know which foot accelerates and which foot brakes. I'm just the gangsta's moll, standing at the corner, cheering  J  on as the 2D cars squeal down the course.      It's another story in the comforts of my home. I rule the roads here. On the tv, that is. If you look at my scores, I only come in 1st, 2nd or 3rd. Never the 5th or the 8th. Yeah I'm that good. Well, maybe I should mention that I'm only at the novice stage (the lowest out of 5 difficulty levels) and if I'm not happy with the race I can erm, restart the game. *sheepish.  J  must have gotten a shock when she saw me in my swearing element yesterday. I was shouting at my faithful old tv, hair all cringly and voice hoarse, while the cars behind me spoil my otherwise beautiful drift while I was apexing the corners... Words I cannot even publish exploded out of my mouth (Fuck! Did that just come from me?!) while I'm wailing about like a mad woman. If the old lady from across looked into my living room and saw me like that (i'm usually acting all domestic in the kitchen) what must she have thought? Imagine a muted version of a deranged looking, IMH escape suspect, with spittle spewing like bubbles out of the mouth, jumping around in her PJs. Scary. I'm beginning to understand why men can be so uncouth and vulgar.      So you see why I'm a huge supporter of public transport. I don't think I should learn to drive. I would cause alot of accidents with my roadrage and terrible driving. I shall just continue being the  shameless, free-loading sucker  that a  certain someone  thinks I am, and sit at the backseat of the car, helping my driving friends glare at spastic drivers and point middle fingers at them. After all, 3 well-positioned fingers in any situation, are always better than 1.              
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I just received an email that was really cute.       WOMEN'S REVENGE    "Cash, cheque or credit?" I asked, after folding items the woman wished to purchase. As she fumbled for her wallet, I noticed a remote control for a television set in her purse. "So, do you always carry your TV remote?" I asked. "No," she replied, " but my husband refused to come shopping with me, so I figured this was the most legal evil thing I could do to him."       UNDERSTANDING WOMEN    I know I'm not going to understand women. I'll never understand how you can take boiling hot wax, pour it onto your upper thigh, rip the hair out by the root, and still be afraid of a spider.       CIGARETTES AND TAMPONS    A man walks into a pharmacy and wanders up and down the aisles. The sales girl notices him and asks him if she can help him.He answers that he is looking for a box of tampons for his wife. She directs him down the correct aisle. A few minutes later, he deposits a huge bag of cotton balls and a ball of string on the counter. She says, confused,"Sir, I thought you were looking for some tampons for your wife?" He answers, " You see, it's like this, yesterday, I sent my wife to the> store to get me a carton of cigarettes, and she came back with a tin of tobacco and some rolling papers; cause it's sooooooo much cheaper. So, I figure if I have to roll my own, so does she."       WIFE VS HUSBAND    A couple drove down a country road for several miles, not saying a word. An earlier discussion had led to an argument and neither of them wanted to concede their position. As they passed a barnyard of mules, goats, and pigs, the husband asked sarcastically, "Relatives of yours?" "Yep," the wife replied, "in-laws."       WORDS    A husband read an article to his wife about how many words women use a day... 30,000 to a man's 15,000. The wife replied, "The reason has to be because we have to repeat everything to men... The husband then turned to his wife and asked, "What?"       CREATION    A man said to his wife one day, "I don't know how you can be so stupid and so beautiful all at the same time." The wife responded, "Allow me to explain.God made me beautiful so you would be attracted to me; God made me stupid, so I would be attracted to you!       WHO DOES WHAT    A man and his wife were having an argument about who should brew the coffee each morning. The wife said, "You should do it, because you get up first, and then we don't have to wait as long to get our coffee." The husband said, " You are in charge of cooking around here and you should do it, because that is your job, and I can just wait for my coffee." Wife replies, "No, you should do it, and besides, it is in the Bible that the man should do the coffee." Husband replies, "I can't believe that, show me." So she fetched the Bible, and opened the New Testament and showed him at the top of several pages, that it indeed says.......... "HEBREWS"      Really. Women will always have the last word. It's not that we always wanna win. It's just the way men function. Or don't.     
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    urlLink     Nothing much to say today, so I thought a pic of a cute cat will brighten up everyone's day! Don't you think it's just idiotically cute? It's taken from a card  J  gave me. She thinks it'll remind me of her. LOL  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Those of you who have read  The Da Vinci Code  would be familiar with  Hieros Gamos . The term  Hieros Gamos  is derived from the Greek words meaning "sacred marriage". Having its roots in ancient fertility cults, the  Hieros Gamos  ritual evolved into a highly developed spiritual discipline that enables a man to attain "gnosis" or direct knowledge of the divine, through ritualised sexual union with a woman trained as a priestess. The theory is based on the philosophy that man is fundamentally incomplete and can reach divinity only by "marrying" the feminine principles in a spiritual and physical manner, which triggers an altered state of consciousness at the moment of climax.  - Simon Cox, Cracking The Da Vinci Code       Now I'm sure many of you are biting your tongues to keep yourself from saying some very mean things about this theory. Let me be really shallow and predict some extreme reactions.       The Losers (ie. men) - The Excuse    What they'll say : Without you, I'm incomplete. Let's get a flat.   What they mean : I'm sick of the missionary. I want anal and oral. Let's make it legal.       The Feminists - The Delusion    What they'll say : We don't need men to make us complete. We're self-sufficient.   What they mean : Down with bras, down with men, excuse me while I go home and get down with Girl's Best Friend (depending on context it could be diamonds/dildos/vibrators/showerheads).       The High Priestess of Sardonicism (ie. Me) - Trying to be funny      "...man is fundamentally incomplete" : Haha. Haha. Hahahahahahaha. Don't we all know that already? I mean, they either have dicks or brains, hardly both.    "...can reach divinity only by 'marrying' the female principles in a spiritual and physical manner" : Through experience (maybe I just have bad luck), I've found that spritual connection and physical attraction are almost always mutually exclusive. That's why men never reach divinity. Tough.    "...triggers an altered state of consciousness at the moment of climax" : For most men that 'altered state' would be unconsiousness.     I might sound a tad bit like a man-bashing, penis-stomping, scissors-welding, Bobbit-supporting Manhater. Though I think most men are jerks, I'm no Feminist. I believe all men should KNOW how to fix stuff and offer to carry heavy objects and pay for the dinner+movie. I have 2 perfectly formed arms to open my own door and carry my own bags, thank you, but men should at least OFFER to do them. I hate it when I find myself giving way to guys when I'm getting out of the train. Also, I don't appreciate it when men cut in front of me when I'm getting on the escalator. Really guys, you're better off standing behind (below) us on the escalator, looking up our skirts, you chauvinistic chee-kohs.     
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Goddess worship could be traced back to at least 35, 000 BC, and as such, it can be claimed that goddess worship is the oldest of the world religions, having a history and heritage that stretches back into the mists of time itself. The Goddess was associated with the moon from ancient times. This association is bound in from the bodily cycles of the female and the lunar cycles of the moon, and also with the fact that the moon has 3 phases - waxing, full, and waning - corresponding to the 3 phases of the Goddess : maiden, mother, and crone. Each of these goddess phases have a distinct purpose and value. The maiden represented youth, sexuality, and vigor; the mother represented the embodiment of female power, fertility, and the nuturing impulse; the crone represented experience, compassion, and above all, wisdom.      How to (or not to)  worship a Goddess you see at a bus-stop :     Make sure you get her attention.  But don't do anything stupid like start doing pushups at her feet and counting loudly. She'll just think you're trying to look up her skirt, you pervert.     Try to get close to her.  But don't wait creepily by the bus door and squeeze alongside with her up the bus, and then scratch her with your EZLink card. That's just not cool.     Make sure you smell like a Sex God when you sit next to her.  Not squash her breathless to the side of the window and attempt to stick to her with your post-pushup arms when you're smelling like a Sweat God.      Seduce her with your sense of style. A white T-shirt, dark blue jeans and white sneakers can be stylish if you are Usher.  Not when your white tee is almost grey, your jeans are too short, you're wearing white socks, and your kiwi-ed sneakers are the types I wore when I was in school.     Try subtle body contact to get her attention.  But don't inch closer to her when she's obviously wishing she's at the other side of the window, instead of being stuck next to you. You're not that bulky, you poser, you don't need 3/4 of the seat.     Smile and walk away suave if she rejects your advances.  Not make disgusting noises when she screams at you to stay away from her. Thank god you ran off the bus fast enough or I swear the bus-driver would have caught you in time.      Today, the veneration and understanding of goddess energy and spirituality are once more to the fore. In the millennia of modern human beings' existence, the figure of the goddess has been omnipresent. I suspect that as long as mankind will walk this planet, this will be the case. The goddess can truly claim to be the original and oldest deity.  - Simon Cox, Cracking The Da Vinci Code                    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     urlLink     A Mind Orgasm : Managing to utilise all tiles (excluding 1 missing blank tile) in a Scrabble game for 3. I was so excited I took a pic of it. Thanks  R  and  C  for the wonderful menage-a-trois. We should do this again soon. =P   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    urlLink     Pretty organised person huh?  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I feel like I could kill someone right now. What makes it worse it that no one cares to listen.      Men piss me off. Especially married ones. Well, I haven't actually had the chance to fuck one and spend his wife's money, but I've already encountered 2 such scums of the earth. My mum should really thank all the deitites she prays to for having the fortune of being the recipient of my dad's unconditional love. Regardless of all the mental, physical, verbal and gastronomical abuse she puts my dad through, he still finds space in his heart for tolerance.      My mum had 2 younger sisters. Both died young. Both had chosen  disgusting  men for partners. My first aunt was engaged when she passed away. She left her house (of which she paid entirely with her own money) to the man she loved. Less than a month after she went, that man brought another woman into their matrimonial home. Well that's another story that could go on and on. The reason for my rage today has to do with something else.      My second aunt already had 2 young children when she passed away. Apparently, her husband was  so  stricken by her death he couldn't take proper care of the kids. So my grandparents had to take over. It's a good thing that we all stay in the same postal code, so it was easy to look out for each other. Less than a year later, that man brought home a woman. She was about 10 years younger than him, dislikes children, adore branded items, lived in Malaysia. But for him, she'll make do. Why, you wonder? Because he gave her a supplementary card (my aunt left a sizeable amount of money to that man), promised not to force her to have children, promised to ferry her to and fro Malaysia every weekend. Up til now, she has refused to meet my grandparents, nor that man's parents. Both sides are utterly disgusted with her. But she seems unaffected. Maybe because once she's had her fun she'll leave that man anyway. How do we know all these? Of course my resouceful grandma had a spy. It used to be their maid. Strangely she was sent back to her country for no reason about half a year ago by that man. One could only wonder why.         I tutor the older of the 2 cousins, though she's only in P2. Her results are terrible. My mum says it's because she doesn't have a mother to help her with her work. Which I agree, because her father says he doesn't want to stress his kids out and his new girlfriend doesn't interact with them anyway. So I did the sisterly thing and agreed to tutor them for next to nothing. But recently, that woman had started to show an interest in the kids' education. She bought loads of multiplication tables charts (I dunno why, since each chart says the same thing anyways) and loads of assessment books for her. It's alright actually, I mean, my cousin has been doing the books that I bought ever since I started with her. Except that that woman insists that my cousin does the homework that SHE gives her. So everytime I go over, the work I gave my cousin sits undone. That's still alright. Until today.      I went over in the morning and I see my cousin doing her school work at her table. I had given her some work to do last week, which was of course, lying there undone. Before I could say anything, she said       "I can't do your home work cuz I have a lot of work to do. [That woman] asked me to finish the work that she gave me and Papa asked me to do all these chinese school papers. Everyday must do. He said next time no need to teach me all those English tenses and Hanyu Pinyin already because waste time only. You just concentrate on Maths can already."       Waste time?! All those things I've been painstakingly teaching her til my veins pop out of my neck are a waste of time?! All those mornings I spent groggy and tired, having to drag my complaining body out of bed, sometimes even on weekends, were a waste of time?!  In the first place, it was my grandfather's request for me to find time to teach her, and even so I was very reluctant, for then I would have less time for myself. My mum had to practically bribe me to do it. I've never heard that man thank me for my efforts. Sometimes I even had to wait for more than half an hour outside his door for them to come from from their weekend trips to the market because he had overestimated the time. When I questioned my cousin if she had forgotten that she had tuition that morning, she said "I remembered! But Papa said never mind let you wait awhile won't die". The cheek!      I was so pissed today and had taken it out on my cousin, and that I regret now. After all it's not her fault that her father has sperm for his brains and a dick for his skull. I had thrown all the books that I bought for her onto the floor and then took them with me when I left. My parting words to her were "Since your father said that you're so clever you don't need these books I'll bring them home and burn them." Nah I won't. I'll keep it til that man dies and burn it to him.      I've never had such disrespect for anyone in my family before and I'm so disgusted that I had called him Uncle. For a long time I haven't greeted him nor acknowledged his existence. He could be lying there haemorrhaging to death for all I care.  I hope he gets some incurable disease that causes his cock to secrete pus whenever he ejaculates and hurt like 1st degree burns whenever even a finger strokes his cock.        That's for crossing my path.     
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       When I was 14, I had a major crush on  D .  D  was my senior in school and was quite a popular character. We were on friendly-acquantive terms, meaning : We'd talk on the phone like old pals but when we were in school,  D  would totally ignore me. The more  D  belittled me, the deeper I fell. By some stroke of luck (and some strategy on my part)  D  and I ended up together 2 years after. We went out, did all the coupley things, then 7 days later, I ended it. I had lost the feeling.  Before I turned 17, I met  M .  M  was a goalie in his sec school soccer team and also a drummer in a band. What a catch, I thought. A week after he asked me to be his girlfriend, I was having dinner with his family. 2 weeks after,  M  had given me a ring and told me that he wanted me to have his children (when we first met he told me he didn't like tots). 3 weeks after,  M  had held my hands, looked into my eyes and proclaimed that he never wanted me to leave him. By the end of 4 weeks, I broke up with him. Remember : I was all of 17.  2 years after, I met  R . I was already in a relationshp then but that didn't seem to deter  R .  R  was talented so he wrote me songs and sung them to me. He was good with words so he would often flatter me. He had many friends so all of them knew about me. He attended some of the same lectures with me so he would sneak glances at me. It's been 5 years and his love seems to have turned into hatred. I was touched, really. Touched with pity. My bf was less romantic but my bf wasn't psycho.  And it's not just me.  My friend  SF  was totally in love with her then bf  E . But  E  was a bastard who two-timed her.  SF  was willing to overlook that but he left her anyway. On the day he left,  SF  wandered the streets alone for 2 days before she could be persuaded to go home. After a while she met  DT . Though he wasn't exactly her type, he showered her with care while they were dating, and suffered silently her demands and tantrums. Now their marriage is on the rocks becuase she's having an affair. To this day,  SF  tells me she still loves  E .  My other friend  YY  had been with her bf  MS  for 5 and a half yrs. It was a comfortable relationship : dull and routine. It wasn't that  MS  was a bad bf, he was just... too domesticated and contented.  YY  was looking for passion. The breakup was brewing underneath for quite some time before it reared its ugly head when  NJ  appeared.  NJ  was (apparently) well learned and articulate.  YY  was hooked. But  NJ  was also an online flirt who seemed (to me) keen on cybersex, is as insecure as a mole-rat and as confused as a chinchilla. And his appearance... nothing to call home about.  YY  confessed that they had nil conversation chemistry. To top things up, he's not local!  NJ  has even casually mentioned that if anything were to happen between them he won't relocate. But dear  YY  has already made arrangements to meet His Egoness over the weekend.  What do women want?  I don't  fucking  know.      
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You know people will say anything just to come up with an excuse not to turn up for work. Well, if it's a Monday I don't blame anyone, or maybe the morning after Ladies' Night is forgiveable. I mean if the boss would rather you went to work with stale hair, breath like a rat died in it, eyes bloodshot and head spinning from a  massive  hangover and absolutely reeking of a lack of productivity - so be it. I have enough work experience to know what it's like to have to activate the muscles and bones that allow you to sit up from your bed at the sound of the alarm. Unless of course you're the sort who slithers out of bed like a backless snake. But then everyone feels like jelly in the morning.      Now it's those kids I don't comprehend. ( I call anyone even an hour younger than me, kids) You see  J  has run into some problems her workplace. Being the only full timer, and the most senior,  J  takes a lot of crap from the part timers, who are mostly poly students. The excuses they come up with... one can only marvel at their (un)creativity.   These below came from an ex part timer  Y . She always calls at the last minute to either say she'll be late or that she couldn't come into work. Then  J  would have to work from 0930 to 2130 alone.     My class will end late today, can you cover for me?    My class ended late, so I'll come in late.    My mother is sick. I need to look after her. (on a saturday)    My grandmother is sick. I need to look after her. (on a sunday)     [The ultimate]  I was getting ready for work and I fell in the bathroom and have bruises all over. So I can't work later. (on a saturday morning at 0800)     I had to scream at naive, softhearted  J  to make her see the absurdity of the excuses. C'mon, I cringed when I heard those lines. Aren't you shaking your head and smiling too? I had asked  J  to tell  Y  not to come back anymore but luckily  Y  wizened up and told  J  herself that she couldn't work anymore due to her "increase in school workload".     And now another part timer  T  has "returned from the dead", so to speak, after disappearing, no call no show, for a week.  J  tried calling him about 20 times, and he either didn't pick up or switched off the phone.  J  finally left  T  a message this morning on his handphone to tell him to return his set of keys or they'll report it to the police. Miraculously,  T  called back to say that he was in an accident last week, and fell into coma for a while. He explained that his handphone was with his mum all this while and she did call some of his friends to inform them, but had inadvertently not call his workplace. Then he said that he had only fractured his leg and that his cast would be removed this week, so he could come back to work this weekend.     J  was all happy about it but you know, being the suspicious person that I am, managed to spoil her mood. I said that doesn't explain why  T 's mother wouldn't answer the many calls that  J  made, and why sometimes the phone was switched off after  J  called many times consecutively.  T  said that he didn't know why his mum didn't answer the calls but that the phone was very old and had bad reception, so that's why it seemed as if the handphone was off.  J  decided to call the hospital that  T  claimed he was admitted in to clarify her doubts. Guess what?    The admissions office said that "the person of this I/C number has not been admitted here at all recently". Hmm. So I made  J  tell  T  that when he goes to have his cast removed, to get the doc to write some sort of letter of excuse so that "she could file it". Really funny business, isn't it?     Watch this space for second half of the saga.     
     

    
</post>


</Blog>