<Blog>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We woke up in room that looked like a hotel room. Neither Dave nor myself had any recollection of how we had got here. "It must have been that couple last night. The drinks?" Dave said. "But how?" I replied. "No idea". We looked around the room and drew the curtains open. The sun was shining, it was hot as always since we had come to Mexico two weeks ago. We were in a tall building, maybe on the 10th floor or so.  "This isn't exactly the place where I would've expected to be held by kidnappers" I said to Dave while I rubbed my shoulder. "I mean, there are people entering and leaving the building, I can hear noises, this is not a dark cellar somewhere in the woods". "There are no woods on these highlands" Dave replied jokingly. We were both laughing. I once again regretted that he was my sister's boyfriend, not mine. He was so handsome and charming and according to what my sister says exceptionally well built where it matters.  After a few hours there was still nobody who would tell us anything. We were certainly worried but on the other hand everything seemed so peaceful, calm and sunny. I was delighted to find that this hotel room even had an on suite bathroom. "Do you mind if I use the shower for a moment?" I asked. "Of course not, but hurry in case somebody turns up". The water was cold, it was truely refreshing and I felt my head become clearer. Only when I stepped out of the shower did I notice that there were no towels, so I just got into my blouse and skirt wet as I was.  When I opened the door Dave looked surprised. He basically stared at me and didn't seem to know where to look. It took me a few seconds to realise that my silk blouse was sticking tightly to my breasts because I had forgotten to put my bra back on. I hate bras especially when it's so hot but my size doesn't allow me to go without very often. "Ooops I didn't meant to..." I stuttered and tried to unstick the fabric from my body but to not much avail. "Don't worry I don't mind at all" Dave said and smiled. "Yeah, I believe that" I laughed "but you know, you're my sister's ...". "Sure, sure" he replied "but that doesn't mean I don't appreciate a pretty sight. I didn't realise before that you were that huge". "I'm doing my best to hide it you know. Particularly when my sister is at all part of the game, she's so jeallous". Dave laughed "Yeah you're right, let's just leave it there".   We both realised that we had been stripped of all valuables. "Do you have any idea what time it is" I asked. "No sure, maybe 11 or 12 o clock at night. Isn't it a pretty sight" Dave pointed out of the window where we had a wonderful view over the roofs on the city lights". There were still a lot of noises from the streets, so we concluded that we must have been somewhere pretty much in the center of this huge city.  We both had gotten pretty tired. I checked the bed sheets. They were not particularly clean. There was just a single large, thin bed sheet, no blankets whatsoever. Dave went to see if there was any way of locking the door from the inside to avoid having surprise visitors during the night. But there wasn't much he could do. He just moved a small cupboard in front of the door so we would at least wake up from the noise when somebody tried to enter.  I was hesitating. I hate to sleep in my cloths but then again there was already some sexual tension between us and I wouldn't want that to increase even further. Dave seemed to sense what I was thinking about. He said "Let's just pretend we were brother and sister otherwise our stay here could become pretty uncomfortable. There's no point trying to hide anything as you already found out. Who knows how many nights it's going to be". He smiled and I was glad he saw it this way, he was such an uncomplicated guy, I love that. So I shrugged my sholder and got undressed. He did the same but when we both turned around, I was unable to just ignore what I saw.  My sister hadn't exaggerated, quite the contrary. This guy had something unbelievable hanging there between his legs almost down to his knees. He was pretty stunned as well although he had already got a taste of my size today, he still couldn't help to stare at me. We stood there for a moment, then we laughed and got under that sheet we had to share. We said good night and each turned to different sides of the bed.  I wasn't able to fall asleep. It was so hot in the room and I couldn't stop thinking about our situation. Eventually I did fall asleep but I don't know how many hours later I woke up from the sound of voices somewhere on the same floor. First it was difficult to hear but then a door was aparently opened and the voices became much clearer. There were three female voices and one male. Two of the girls were speaking spanish and occasionally a few broken english words. The two were laughing and giggling all the time. The third female had a european accent. Maybe scandinavian or something. Her voice sounded fearful. At times she seemed to be protesting.  For a moment I thought about getting into contact with them but I wasn't certain at all what role they were playing. After a while the giggling mixed with soft moans. At the same time the european girl seemed to be weeping. As the moans became more intense, Dave woke up. He looked at me but I was acting asleep. He lifted the bed sheet a bit and I felt that he was watching my body. The voice of the girl next door became more shrill. She repeated something in spanish over and over again until she was interrupted by the other mexican girl. They seemed to argue about something, then it was silent for a while.   After a few minutes the moans started again but this time it was the other girl. Dave was silent. I blinked because I was curious what he was doing. What I saw was quite amazing. He was slowly massaging a massive erection. His cock reached up far beyond his navel. It must have been 12" or more. I quickly closed my eyes again but I couldn't hold back blinking from time to time. The sight aroused me beyond believe because big cocks were kind of a fetish for me but still he was my sister's boyfriend and I knew she was unforgiving in this regard. I realised it was dawn already. The voices from next door had died down. Suddenly our door was pushed open banging against the cupboard we had moved in front of the door. Before we could get out of the bed and into our clothes, the cupboard came crashing down on the floor and two females in combat gear armed with machetes burst into the room. For a moment I had thought they were here to rescue us but they immediately started to shout angrily in spanish, kicking against the cupboard. Then one of them went out again and pushed a frightened european looking couple into the room. They were both naked and had their hands tied behind their backs.  She was a tall blond in her 40s slim and quite muscular actually for a woman. Her hair was long and straight hanging down to her hips. Her breasts were medium sized and firm. He was much younger than her, maybe in his beginning 20s. Blond as well. Really quite handsome. Not too massive, slim, muscular and well equipped though not quite as well as Dave. He had duct tape over his mouth.  The woman was crying. I realised that it was the same crying I had heard during the night. Her crying angered the guards or whatever their role was. One of them shouted at the woman to stop and slapped her in the face. The other turned to us. She walked around the bed and seemed rather amused about our situation. Both mexican girls were petite and had exceptionally beautiful faces. Both had short very dark hair. The guard lifted the bed sheet at the foot end with her machete. She hesitated, then she looked again and laughed.   She said something funny sounding in spanish that made the other guard turn around to look as well. Then both laughed and signalled us to get out of bed. Confronted with two machetes and some other weaponry in the belts of the two girls, we did as we were told. All heads turned. Dave tried to quickly grab his jeans but one of the mexican girls kicked them away laughing while saying "no, no, no, no".   I folded my arms in front of my breasts which obviously wasn't very effective. I noticed the european guy eyeing me closely as my massive mammaries spilled below and above my arms. But Dave's features were certainly even more unusual. I could still hardly believe it myself. I was staring just as all the others hat his horse cock while we were standing by the bathroom door. The mexican girls were talking with each other, giggling and discussing something. Then one of them grabbed the blond womans hair and pulled her on her knees in front of her boyfriend. She grabbed the young guys flacid cock and slapped the woman on the back of her head saying "suck it!". It was quite humiliating. The blond looked up to us and lowered her eyes again. Then she did as she was told and soon we could see the young guy's dick grow in her mouth. But the mexican girls didn't care much about the european couple. They were more interested in Dave's reaction and I realised that this was the whole purpose of their little game.  They got what the wanted. It didn't take long until Dave's cock started to grow and point straight towards the two giggling mexican girls. It was truely immense. From my angle I had a good view on the full length of it and it was even bigger than I had thought the night before. Although it was such a precarious situation I couldn't help but think about how he ever managed to actually fuck a girl with that tool without hurting her.  Now one of the mexican guards started to talk to us with her heavy accent. "We are el frente national para la justicia and you are prisoners of war. We will not hurt you if your families pay a 100,000 US dollars within a week. If we don't have the money in a week, we will present your family with a little present and wait for another week. You will now be able to witness what happens if you let the week pass."   She smiled and turned around towards the european couple. She watched them for a moment. I was surprised how eagerly the blond woman was working on him. He was kind of close I thought. The mexican girl removed the tape from his mouth and kissed him deeply and aggressively. Then she said "thanks for last night" and smiled at him. The blond woman was furious, she looked up and shouted at the mexican girl "You fucking little slut get your hands of him!" Then as though she wanted to prove something she sucked him even more intensely. The young guy looked tense, he flexed his nice muscles, he opened his mouth and groaned "Oh yeah baby don't stop now!". But now the other mexican girl went over to him, looked him in the eyes and said "Too bad we still haven't got the money". Then she lifted her machete and drove it down between his belly and the blond woman's face. The blond was shocked. She fell backwards with his severed cock in her mouth. She spitted blood and started to scream hysterically. He just stared down along his body shaking his head silently.  It was a horrible sight of this young sexy guy having his cock chopped off. And I didn't quite understand the two girls. They seemed to have had so much fun with him last night. Why did they do it. I looked at Dave whose cock was still standing outwards like a flagpole and said "We should better get that money don't you think?". Dave was silent for a moment. Then he said "No that can't happen. It must not happen to me!".   The mexican girls pushed the european couple out of the room. They had given us the lesson they wanted and we certainly got the message.   
    
</post>


</Blog>