<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Last night, as I sat alone in my darkened house and watched John Kerry accept the Democratic National Convention’s nomination for the presidency, I wondered what his critics were saying.&nbsp; He made so much sense to me, sounded so reasonable and addressed so many issues that I think are important, that I can’t imagine something seriously negative.&nbsp; People criticize that he’s not personable enough, that he’s rather stiff, but that just sounds like nitpicking to me.&nbsp; My own mother told me yesterday that she didn’t think that Teresa was “first-lady material.”&nbsp; I thought that was completely ridiculous.&nbsp; First ladies have always been these demure followers, usually with their one “pet-project,” like Nancy’s “Say No to Drugs” campaign and Laura Bush’s push for literacy (which I was excited about, but which we didn’t hear anything about after the first year or so).&nbsp; Who better to be an ambassador for American women that someone who speaks her mind, is worldly, diverse and a leader in her own right?&nbsp; The woman told a reporter to “shove it,” for God’s sake.&nbsp; I would rather have her back me up than some figurehead or showpiece any day.&nbsp; Having a mixed first family is truly representative of this country, whether we like it or not, when percentages of broken homes and second marriages are so high.  I loved that Kerry’s crew from the war were there as well.&nbsp;&nbsp; Yeah, I know it was a publicity thing that makes him look good and honorable…but the thing is, I don’t think it’s just publicity.&nbsp; I think it’s a true representation.&nbsp; Plus, I loved his daughters.&nbsp; I loved that they told goofy stories about their dad, because that’s the kind of thing that I can relate to.&nbsp; I loved that Alexandra had her own agenda and mentioned people having freedom over their bodies, a choice.&nbsp; That won me over right there.&nbsp; In a campaign, I can imagine that sometimes, in order not to alienate voters, it can’t always be cut and dried and I understand that.&nbsp; It did make me feel better to hear her words though….because she said several times that her values were passed down to her from her father.&nbsp; I loved that Kerry emphasized women’s rights over and over.&nbsp; I loved that he supports small business.&nbsp; I loved everything about that speech.&nbsp; I’m not the kind of person that applaud in my own house, when the people on the little talking box can obviously not hear me or appreciate my reaction, but I did catch myself cheering last night.&nbsp; I don’t think it’s wrong to be excited about this – a chance at an America that I won’t be ashamed of.&nbsp; I WANT to be a part of something good and pure…someone who stands up for the underdog, instead of dominating them.   P.S.&nbsp; I know it’s corny, but I still get goose bumps… “America can do better.&nbsp; And help is on the way.”  

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So, last night, when I got home, I took the best nap.&nbsp; I know that sounds stupid, or juvenile, but it was so great.&nbsp; Well, initially, it wasn’t all that great.&nbsp; I got home, took off all my clothes (shut up, it’s my nap) and got into bed and closed my eyes…and then the dogs next door starting fighting and scuffling and making all sorts of noise.&nbsp; So, then I went into the living room and got on the couch.&nbsp; The only problem with the living room is that my ceiling fan makes a repetitive noise when the chain knocks against the light fixture….plink, plink, plink…you get the picture.&nbsp; So, then I had to go hunt up some ear plugs and in the process of doing that, discovered that the dogs outside had stopped fighting and got back into bed and went to sleep.&nbsp; I took great satisfaction in knowing, as I drifted off, that if I had not dropped my class, I would, at that point, still be stuck in traffic on 635.&nbsp; Ahhhhh…..  I think my blogging is going pretty well. &nbsp;&nbsp;I’ve been journaling since I was a little girl and am finding that blogging is just more convenient.&nbsp; I am a little late in my entry today.&nbsp; I usually do it as soon as I get to work, but today I was a little distracted because we are having a client visit, so I had stern email about cleaning up my desk when I got in.&nbsp; Whoops.&nbsp; Also, I didn’t log in until 8:01 today (1 minute late) because the frigging receptionist was not at her desk, so I practically had to empty my backpack out in order to find my keycard.&nbsp; Before that, I was even going to be a couple of minutes early….grrrr…  I have absolutely no plans tonight.&nbsp; I will probably curl up and eat dinner while watching C-Span or something.&nbsp; That’s what I’ve been doing lately, watching convention footage and whatnot.&nbsp; Have you read the quasi-debate between Michael Moore and Bill O’Reilly?? You can catch it on the Drudge Report, if you haven’t.&nbsp; I say quasi because it was really child’s play for Mike.&nbsp; He made O look like an idiot (not that it’s all that difficult to do).  Here’s the big thing that’s been plaguing me lately (other than relationship-py stuff which I have vowed not to discuss on this blog because it would take over and not leave room to talk about anything else) – I took about a three year break from college, which means that all my friends have either graduated or are nearing graduation while I am still 2-3 years away.&nbsp; Should I feel bad about that?&nbsp; I try not to, but it’s really hard.&nbsp; Yes, I know it was my decision to take such a break, but I really was trying to establish my life as a grown-up.&nbsp; I don’t get any financial help from anyone, and I just preferred not to struggle at minimum wage jobs and work part-time in order to go to school at the same time.&nbsp; I mean, people do that all the time and good for them….I just didn’t want to do that.&nbsp; I guess the other option was to take out student loans, but I have friends who will be paying off loans for like 10 years.&nbsp; I don’t want to start my life out that way.&nbsp; I already have shaky credit from lessons that I had to learn myself … I just didn’t want to dig deeper in.&nbsp; Anyway, so I’m finally motivated to go back to school again and all that good stuff so I can become a teacher and do something that I love….Only now, it’s going to take so long for me to graduate.&nbsp; Oh, well.&nbsp; As long as I stick my plan (see entry from 7/26) I think I’ll survive.&nbsp;   I plan to move to Denton in about a year, year-and-a-half in order to take all those upper-level courses that are only offered in the middle of the day.&nbsp; My plan is to find a decent job in the area where I can work weird hours…or marry rich by then so I can just loaf around and be a student.&nbsp; Both of these options sound a little unrealistic, but hey….stranger things have happened, I guess.  Anyway, I will try to do something exciting this evening so my entry tomorrow is not quite as ridiculously boring.  

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So I dropped this intense photo class that I was taking.&nbsp; I’m a little disappointed in myself, because I really wanted to finish it…good path to actually graduating and all of that, but it was just a little too much for me.&nbsp; It was a Summer II class that lasted from 6-11 Monday through Thursday.&nbsp; Come on, people.&nbsp; That’s ridiculous.&nbsp; We would get an assignment on Monday and have it due on Thursday.&nbsp; Now, tell me.&nbsp; When am I supposed to shoot that when I work from 8-5?&nbsp; I had been doing it on my lunch hour, but eventually one gets tired of shooting pictures of her cube and office building over and over.&nbsp; So, I dropped it, though I have residual guilt.&nbsp; I did buy a new camera, so I got that out of the whole deal and when I decide to take the class next time, I have all the stuff.&nbsp; So, I guess that’s ok.&nbsp; I just kept thinking that life is not life without free time and rest….things other than work.  I wasn’t going to get into this, but what the hell.&nbsp; I am so sick and tired of people asking me about “school.”   “How much longer do you have?” “What will you do with that?””Shouldn’t you be graduated by now?”  OK, listen up.&nbsp; It’s my life and I’ll go to school if I want to.&nbsp; It just so happens that I took a three year break.&nbsp; I know it’s not the best thing for my future, but damn….things are hard when you do them all alone.&nbsp; So, I have decided that whenever anyone asks any of the above questions, I’m just going to smile sweetly and inform them that I no longer answer questions of that nature.&nbsp; At all.&nbsp; To anyone.&nbsp; That way, when I finally do graduate, it will be a surprise.&nbsp; I mean, it’s not like I’m loafing around, depending on other people.&nbsp; I have a full-time job, with room to grow.&nbsp; I just got promoted.&nbsp; My boss told me yesterday that my new position is a springboard and will offer me all sorts of opportunities.&nbsp; I SHOULDN’T FEEL BAD ABOUT THIS.&nbsp; College is just harder for some people.&nbsp; I can’t help it if everyone I know is a genius and all graduated already.&nbsp; For God’s sake, that’s because their parents paid their way through.&nbsp; Take my ex for example.&nbsp; It took him 5 years to finish college and during that time, they paid for his apartment, his car insurance, his utility bills, his groceries.&nbsp; All he paid for was drugs and cable.&nbsp; I mean, come on.&nbsp; I had to struggle just to come up with my half of the rent.  Anyway, I’m still going through with my way-too-ambitious plans for the Fall.&nbsp; 17 hours, I think.&nbsp; Some online classes, so real-life classes.&nbsp; I am finally going to start taking some studio art classes because…well, I have to.&nbsp; You can’t so much be an art teacher without learning the art part.&nbsp; Anyway, I’m going to do all that I can to keep my current job and go to school.&nbsp; Towards the end, I will have to figure something else out, because some of those weird teaching classes are only offered in the middle of the day.&nbsp; So are the student teaching things at the very end.&nbsp; I have just decided that art education is the way to go.&nbsp; It will be something that I’m good at, that I love, that will make me feel good.&nbsp; Now the battle is getting there.  

						
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I had a pretty insane weekend.&nbsp; I stayed with a friend for several days and helped him set up his new house.&nbsp; It’s this great bohemian farmhouse in Denton on about an acre of land.&nbsp; The dogs all love it, they’re able to go nuts and run around without us worrying about them running into traffic.&nbsp; I wasn’t able to let them completely off of the leash, but I’m trying to wean them off of total dependence.&nbsp; Anyway, barring relationship complications, etc., it was pretty relaxing.   On Saturday, we went to see “Fahrenheit 9/11.”&nbsp; Now, anyone that knows me knows how liberal I am and how much I adore Michael Moore.&nbsp; Although I am very liberal, I don’t just throw my political views around.&nbsp; As passionate as I am, there’s nothing that I hate more than people who try to force themselves on others.&nbsp; I’m now trying to convince my mom to go see it, just so she can be as informed as possible when I attempt my next mission….to get her to vote for Kerry.&nbsp; It will be difficult, but I’m going to give it a shot.  I’m trying to sort out my feelings about a lot of things, because I mostly feel like I have too much crammed into my brain right now…too many things to think about and not enough time to do it.&nbsp; It’s like even if I am sitting still all alone in a room, there’s too much humming in my head for me to be able to think about any one thing.&nbsp; Everything just feels in a haze at the moment.&nbsp; That’s actually one of the reasons for me starting a blog.&nbsp; Maybe this way I can put some of my thoughts down on “paper.”&nbsp; This is totally geeky, but in the Harry Potter books, there’s a device where you can take thoughts and memories from your head and store them, kind of like a metaphysical Zip drive, and thereby clear up some much-needed space in my head.&nbsp; I need one of those.&nbsp; Maybe I’ll check Ebay.  

						
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   OK, so I NEVER do this, but I totally lied my way out of work on Tuesday and Wednesday, thus the no posting.  Tuesday I woke up at 7:30, which is normally the time that I leave and just made the executive decision that I didn’t want to go.  I seriously haven’t done this in so long.  At first, I was just going to go in late, but then I kept thinking about how many things I could accomplish if I stayed home, so I did.  I cleaned and rearranged furniture and worked on STUFF and it was great…until I made the fatal mistake.  I watched TLC in the afternoon.  Now, if you have never watched TLC in the afternoon on a weekday, you’re totally missing out.  It’s back to back Wedding Story, Baby Story, Dating Story, Makeover Story….four HOURS of reality television that doesn’t suck.  I’m not a big fan of the reality-tv craze that has swept the nation.  Now, the old-school reality-tv…I can get down with that.  The “stories” on TLC, the Real World (old seasons)…Anyway, so I watched all of that sap all day, while eating chips and drinking lemonade and started feeling all sorry for myself, firstly because I cried over something about every ten minutes or so and secondly because I worry about the whole un-boyfriend issue.  Will we ever be a real couple?  And get married?  Have kids?  It doesn’t seem very likely.  Anyway, so I did all of that…and then I did the STUPIDEST thing.  I called M.  I called and cried and sobbed about how I was his plan B and asked him what his intentions were and generally made such a fool of myself that in the wee hours of Wednesday morning, he showed up at my house and slipped into bed with me.  We slept comfortably together, as we always do.  We slept and slept and when the alarm went off Wednesday morning, we continued to sleep, among other things.  We ate and watched tv and went and had coffee in the middle of the day and talked about how crazy we are about each other and how much we love each other…and didn’t even TOUCH the whole commitment thing.  Didn’t even look in that direction.  I prefer to write off my hysteria to PMS and I think M. just prefers not to think about it at all, which is ok with me.  Status quo is ok.  Maybe he will just grow gradually into the other thing.  My new friend C. revealed to me via email that she sometimes wishes that she and her boyfriend were back in that not-quite-sure, everything-is-open stage.  That actually does give me a little comfort.  In other news, I watched Dreamcatcher, which is not a very good movie but did have one really, really neat part.  There was this guy, Jones, whose body was being invaded by an alien being (stay with me here) and in they had this great visual representation of Jones’ “memory warehouse”, which literally looked like an old-timey library with a spiral walkway down the middle and hundreds of thousands of crates full of files that represented old memories, all categorized and stacked.  I love that idea.  I wish that I was introspective enough to be able to just go cavort through my own memory warehouse….just think of the things that you would find!  

						
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So, I had a pretty good weekend, but it was only good for one specific reason, and that reason makes me feel pathetic.  I spent the majority of the weekend with M., and we had a really great time together.  A little too great, actually.  It was just a little too great for me to pretend that’s all it was – a good weekend.  Instead, it’s spurred me to start daydreaming about the future again.  Fact:  He lives in this crazy bohemian farmhouse in Denton with our friend J.  Fact:  I get along really well with J.  We could be friends even if M. wasn’t in the picture.  Fact:  There is a bedroom there that is totally not being used.  Fact:  Both M. and J. have dogs that love my dogs.  Fact:  I have to move to Denton within the next year and a half or so because that’s when I absolutely run out of classes that I can take at Dallas County and when I definitely have to live closer to UNT.   See the problem?  When I oh-so-casually mentioned to M. that I moving to Denton was something that would happen eventually, he actually got excited and said “Well, if I’m still here, then you’ll already have a place to live!”  As I am a girl, my immediate thought was “Yes, I’d love to marry you!”  Obviously, I didn’t really say that, but that’s how I felt.  It’s all confusing.  We just had one of those perfect weekends where we didn’t fight, but instead read to each other and went bowling and watched movies and played outside and made love and had tickle-fights and just generally enjoyed each other’s company.  And now I just feel kind of hollow, because I had forgotten what it was like to live with him and to remember is…painful.  In other news, the bitch-whore that he was previously dating is coming back to town to pick up her things this weekend, so I don’t expect to spend any time with him.   That is sad, on one hand, but also good because I’m trying desperately not to get my heart broken (again).  P.S.  I sort of have this internet thing going on, too.  More news on that later, if anything develops.  

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I am a terrible bill-payer.  I wait until the last possible second to do ANYTHING, which includes bills.  I have this whole package thing with SBC that includes phone, DSL and Dish network television.  I love being so connected, but I forget that since that is a combination bill, I really should pay it on time.  As a result of my procrastination, I have not had a phone for about a week.  This is interesting because my internet and cable had remained on, even though all of those services should be on the same schedule.  In the process of losing my phone capabilities, I have discovered something:  I hate the phone.  I hate that I run towards it whenever it's ringing.  I hate that I usually don't want to talk to the person on the other end...all of that stuff.  It has been amazing to just sit home and play on the computer and watch TV and not have to worry about the phone ringing.  I have a cell phone, too, but it's one of those that you have to put minutes on and come on....that is WAY too labor-intensive.  So, anyway, I will go online in a few minutes and turn all my shit back on, but I will always fondly recall the silence that was in my home for just a little while.  Also, just so that you don't misunderstand, I still talk to my mother, aunt, grandmother and not-boyfriend EVERY DAY from work lest none of them think that I'm dead, which they are wont to do.  P.S.  Happy Friday the 13th.  Kudos to those will watch horror movies in honor of the day.  

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today, I have been indulging in my very favorite hobby, pre-spending.  Payday is tomorrow and I think I have about $4 on my debit card and about $2 in cash, as per usual, pretty much just enough for lunch today.  Therein lies the beauty of pre-spending, which is spending the money that I will receive tomorrow, today.  Well, it’s not really spending the money…it’s more like window shopping, only over the internet.  Ebay is a great way to pre-spend…bid today, pay tomorrow.  It’s beautiful.  The only problem is that I’m more of an instant gratification kind of gal.  Ebay makes you wait until things are shipped, which can sometimes seem interminable.  Sometimes I would rather just wait and go to Target, so I can take my purchases home with me.  So far today, I have pre-spent on a twinset off of ebay, internet car insurance (as I currently have none, but that’s a whole other story) and bath products from Lush, my very favorite store that has just recently opened an online store and previously had to be purchased in bulk when I went to London.  Also, I have scouted out ticket prices for the ACL Fest in Austin next month.  I’ve been once before, with an old boyfriend and we had a great time, even though I got sunburned beyond belief.  Anyway, all sorts of cool people are going to be at this year’s show…like the Pixies and Modest Mouse and Wilco and Cake and the Old 97’s and Franz Ferdinand…totally fun.  My best friend lives in Austin and we always party like rock stars when I’m down there, so…good times.  In other news, I will purging my household this weekend…books, groceries, movies, linens…lots of stuff.  Spring cleaning, only in the summer because stuff is starting to get too cluttered and that just doesn’t work out.  Plus, it’s starting to look a little like Arachnophobia around my place, definitely time for some cobweb clearing.  I might even deep-clean the carpets.  I would then be VERY impressed with myself.  Hope everyone is having a great week:)   

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So, I don’t steal music.  When the whole P2P thing came out a couple of years ago (Napster and the like), I admit that it was cool to be able to go find anything, but I spent most of my time downloading the theme song to SheRa and that Chipmunks Christmas record, you know the one I’m talking about.  Anyway, it wasn’t long before I just decided that I didn’t like the way that made me feel.  Especially when I bought my iPod and the first thing that you see when you open the orgasmic packaging is “Don’t steal music.”  Now, anyone who knows me knows who the boss is in my relationship with my iPod.  What she says goes, my friends.  Anyway, so even though I hate those people who open their cd cases and have a hundred burned cds with a passion…it doesn’t seem to bother me to buy bootleg dvds from my friend at work.  I actually thought long and hard about it and realized that…nah.  I know I’ll get negative feedback about this, but I’m cool with that.  Now, to the point.  I watched Cold Mountain last night for the first time.  I bought it for $5 from my “connection,” and went home to settle down with it.  On Monday, I went to Bunko and then stayed the night with M., so I wasn’t back home until last night after work.  My dogs were, obviously, overjoyed to see me and we spent a quiet night at home.  I mostly cleaned up my computer (I had some kind of adware or something and it was driving me completely nuts) and then I watched “Secretary,” which I LOVE, by the way.  My mom actually called me at work yesterday to ask me what I thought of that movie because it had disturbed her.  I think it disturbed her even more when I told her how much I love it.  It’s hard to describe, but it’s something about people being true to their kinky desires, it just gets me.  Plus James Spader and Maggie Gyllenhal.  And James Spader.  So, anyway, Cold Mountain….The first 20 minutes or so were kind of disappointing because I wasn’t really in the mood to watch a couple hundred people be slaughtered, even though I wanted to go kidnap Jude Law (for several reasons), but mostly so he could go quote it in front of President Bush…all about being sent away and lied to, about the innocence of youth being wasted on war, about so many of his brothers dying.  It was pretty relevant to today, in other words.  Ok, and PS…Nicole Kidman is just gorgeous.  I know that I say that every time she’s in something else, but I just can’t help it.   Seriously.  Renee Zellweiger was amazing, too.  Did she win an Oscar for that role?  She should have, if she didn’t.  And the best part (other than naked Jude Law), had to have been Jack White as Georgia because…well, eventually we will of course get married.  How hot is he?  Quirky hot.  Yikes.  

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So, last night I went to play Bunko with my aunt.  She sent me an email yesterday and let me know that they had someone who couldn’t make it and they needed a substitute.  I’m usually up for anything, so I agreed.  Bunko, as far as I knew, was some kind of a dice game that large groups of suburban women gather regularly to play.  What she told me to entice me was that dinner was provided and candy was available to win as prizes.  That pretty much sealed the deal right there.  Anyway, I agreed to meet at her house, which is not too far away from my office.  Once the ladies started arriving, I realized a few things.  First, I have always longed to be married and have babies…really.  I was never at the point that I wanted to trick my partner into impregnating me…nothing like that.  I just have always wanted to have a family that was my own, with babies and things.  Anyway, I swiftly realized listening to all these women talk that I am SO GLAD I’M NOT THERE YET.  The main topic of conversation was the school system messing up and sending the wrong paperwork for all the parents to fill out through the mail.  Sure, I can understand that it put some people in a huff.  I mean, it’s someone’s screw-up that is wasting your time, but, really, people…is it worth talking about for an hour??  I just don’t think so.  The other topic that tops the list seems the be the incompetence of men.  Now, this one I can get right on board with, but again…not for an hour.  Anyway, the evening was really low key and I just kept thinking that if I had a group of Bunko girls in their twenties, it would have been pretty fun.  More liquor, more sex, far more profanity…the good things in life.  So, we’re sitting there rolling the dice (the endless, endless rolling of the dice) when someone notices a raccoon creeping around the backyard.  We all go and look because, hey, that’s pretty cute, right?  Small woodland creatures and all that.  So then the raccoon comes up to the backdoor and kind of taps at the glass.  Some of us (them) are still amused by this, while some of us (me) are totally freaked out because raccoons are wild fucking animals and it’s downright creepy that this one is so tame.  So then, all of a sudden, there’s ANOTHER ONE, just as tame as the first.  In my mind, I am spinning back to high school, where my best friend had reoccurring dreams that the monkeys of the world were trying to usurp the world order from humans and she was the only one that had figured it out, so they trapped her in her bed and held a scalpel to her throat and threatened her with silence.  Or something like that.  The point here is that there are now two, way-too-tame raccoons in the backyard, all pressed up against the windows on the porch and TRYING TO GET IN.  Fortunately, my aunt was just as freaked out about this as I was, so when her 14-year-old son stepped outside to take its picture and IT WALKED UP TO HIM, she yanked him back inside.  Anyway, totally freaky.  It made a great story when, after Bunko, I went to M.’s house and spent the night, reveling in the envy of the forty-year-old women that I spent the evening with.  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It has been forever since I have had a rockin good time with just myself.  This weekend, I vowed to spend the majority of my time alone, in my house.  The reasons for this were twofold -- first, because with that crazy-ass photography class, I felt like I never got to spend any time with my dogs, and also because I went to the Denton for the majority of last weekend, and the weekend before that, in order wot spend time with M.  I missed my house!  Also, I needed to save some money.  The only money that I have spent so far was on a box of Chex cereal and a bag of chocolate chips so I could make Muddy Buddies....a girl's gottat have some chocolate if she's not having sex.  Anyway, the snack turned out pretty well, but the by-myself weekend has been pretty rockin so far.  Last night, I came home and and surfed the net for a little while, watched some tv and then settled down with my Muddy Buddies and some wine and watched  13 Going on 30.  which, let's be honest, is the cutest movie ever.  Can I get a "Hell yeah" from all the girls that, once upon a time, rocked the side ponytail and blunt bangs.  I hear ya.  P.S....Mark Ruffalo is totally cute.  I timed the ending just right, popped a couple of Simply Sleep halfway through so I was ready for bed rightat the end.  See, this way, I was able to drop right into a ready-made Mark Ruffalo dream.  Totally rocked.   So far today, I have read my daily blogs, had some Muddy Buddies for breakfast and cleaned house...laundry, kitchen...you know, the kind of crap that you never seem to have time for during the week.  It's worked out very well so far.  I think M's going to drop by later so that will work out EVEN better.  Next weekend, I think I'm going to plan some kind of an event or something, because I will have just gotten paid.  I'm thinking dancing with all the friends that I can think of who get along, or a little gathering here at the house.  Let me know if you have any suggestions.  I hope you're all having as lovely of a day as I.   

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I went home last night with the intention of doing two things – searching my satellite dish programming for “Perfect Strangers” and going to sleep early.  While I did end up going to sleep early, my satellite search was a bust.  Can someone please explain to me why “Full House” plays twice a day as a syndicated rerun on some channel or another, while “Perfect Strangers” is nowhere to be found?!?  This doesn’t make any sense at all.  Mildly entertaining at best, one can only watch so much Bob Saget in her lifetime.  Ditto with Dave Coolier.  (As a side note, my toleration for John Stamos is MUCH higher).  Anyway, you could never call that show a classic.  It was just a sitcom.  The same goes for “Family Matters,” which was a SPINOFF OF “PERFECT STRANGERS” FOR GOD’S SAKE.  I mean, seriously, Harrriet didn’t even exist before working in the elevator at the paper where Larry and Balki worked.  Don’t be ridiculous.  I won’t go further into the intricacies that make EVERY EPISODE of “Perfect Strangers” a classic.  I will only tell you that crouching foreigners dressed as Ninjas who were goatherders in Mepose NEVER STOPS BEING FUNNY.  There are many websites devoted to the show, even petitions that have been signed to get it back onto the air.  USA Network, why have you forsaken us?  

						
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Why do things have to change? I know it's one of those cosmic questions that can't be answered, but it's really frustrating. Usually, I'm a big proponent of change, in the way of progress and all that. I used to have a teacher in high school and when the school year began, the walls in his classroom were bare. Every week or so, he'd put up a new poster or map and proudly announce, "Progress."  Anyway, so last night A came over and made dinner for me. I tried to just play it off like it was no big deal, but I could TELL that he was making his move, and that just made it worse. He just never does anything spontaneous,everything is premeditated. That's not the real problem, though, because let's face it. If it were M or that cute guy from work that made such a fuss over me I would be over the moon about it. It's just that I don't want it to be that way between us. I want to stay in our comfortable best-friend relationship, where we flirt shamelessly and talk about everything. Now, he's got all of these feelings involved, and nothing is going to be the same. I try not to lead him on. Like, last night, I put on my grubbiest clothes and sat at the opposite end of the couch than him. It just didn't matter. He kept trying to touch me and stuff and eventually I had to tell him that it was all too much and that it was freaking me out.  Yes, ladies and gentlemen, it's official. I am a huge spaz. What made it worse is that he was so nice about it, but you could tell that it totally hurt his feelings. He even said that when I was ready, I should go for it and that he would wait for me. Ok, listen up. What do you not understand?? I have told him that I don't feel that way about him, but he seems to think that I'll fall into line eventually and I HATE that. He has this attitude because he always gets what he wants and he just figures that I'll give in eventually.  *Sigh* It's just so complicated, but there is a bright side. My mom said that other day that she thinks that eventually I'll end up with either M or A, she's just not sure which one. Well guess what, Mom.  It ain't A. Strike three and he's out of the running. When I sleep with M every chance I can get and get all tingly when cute guy at work even LOOKS at me, then platonic friend from birth A doesn't stand a chance. Sorry, Charlie. Now I just need to cut down on the amount of time that I spend with him so he's sure to get the message. Plus, definitely no more alone time. I won't see him for a long time without F (for Fabulous...just kidding, he's my best guy friend) as protection. F has been warned and at the ready and actually was about to rescue me last night by showing up "unexpectedly" before I got the guts to just call the whole thing off.  So, anyway...if the universe wants to send some other hot guy into my circle, that would be great...or it could nudge the cute guy at work my way. That would be nice and much more fulfilling then IM flirting ALL day long. When I was in high school, that kind of flirting was cute, but now it's like extended foreplay that stops abruptly when it's time to go home and that SUCKS.  

						
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I was reading this article online yesterday,  urlLink http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/5583991/  where scientists are doing a study to determine what will make you happier, money or sex. Their tentative results indicate that people who go from having sex once a month to once a week are just as happy as they would have been with an additional $50,000 a year. I'm trying to figure out who these people are...And have come to the conclusion that it must be the wealthier people (John Kerry's 2%, if you will) that this information is coming from. I mean, seriously....$50,000 is almost twice what I make now. Surely that would make me happier than extra sex. I'm not sure. Still, to be on the safe side, I informed my...partner of this startling statistic last night and we enthusiastically went about...ensuring our happiness.  OK, and P.S...I was going to end my post here, but then I read it and "partner" makes me sound gay, which I'm not. Here's the situation: M and I are avoiding any kinds of labels, as when we get into boyfriend/girlfriend land, shit starts to hit the fan. It's a pattern that has something to do with his commitment phobia. Still...we are seeing/sleeping with each other exclusively...say the "L" word (although only occasionally) and talk in vague (very) terms about the future. So we're definitely dating. Still, I don't know what to call him. I guess I'll continue to go with M. *Sigh* Love is...confusing.  

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   When I was in the call center at the place where I work now, we had a crazy late policy.  If you were late (which is defined in the employee handbook as ONE MINUTE past your scheduled shift), your ass was grass.  Seriously.  I can understand this, because if you come in at 8:30 instead of 8, you've already missed 10 calls or so.  Anyway, this attitude about lateness has carried over into my current not-quite-defined position.  The problem is, since my shift changed from 10:00, so did the traffic.  So, lately, it doesn't matter what time I leave my house, I always log in to my phone at 8:01.  5 days in a row last week, I log in at 8:01.  I just kept waiting for the hammer to fall, because had I done this type of thing under previous managment, I would already be written up by now.  So...yesterday I started thinking about the fact that I'm late all the time and that no one seemed to give a crap.  I went into my new boss' office and talked a little with her about several things, one of which was micromanagment, or my day-to-day.  The greatest thing happened.  She totally doesn't care what time I come in.  She said that as long as I get my work done, she's not going to analyze any details.  It's like a total weight off of my shoulders, not because I plan on being late, it just allows me to focus more on my work and less on whether or not I am racking up "unauthorized" overtime if I stay late to work on something.  It's the best feeling ever.  Also, I have located my best friend from elementary school via Google.  How great is the Internet?!? I Google her every year or so...just when it occurs to me and I never got a hit before now, and then I got several all at once.  It turns out that she is listed as volunteer on the John Edwards page... and listen to what she has to say:  "About Me - I recently graduated from Berry College and now I am working at the Sexual Assault Center of NW GA. I am looking forward to someone beating Bush.Why I Support John Edwards - I think politics is often too negative and it is nice to see a politician with a positive vision for this country. In addition, John Edwards seems to be the only candidate who has addressed women's equality issues like equal pay for equal work, extended family leave, and ensuring freedom of choice for all women. As a woman, this is extremely inportant and the other candidates have failed to mention these issues and by doing so have alienated many young women voters who make up half the population. Edwards also seems very true to his word and sincere in his commitment to public service"  How great is she!!!  She has already responded to my intitial email and I am SO excited about the prospect of getting to know her as an adult.  P.S.  I bought three DOZEN tamales from a girl here at work and have now, offically, eaten them for 5 meals in a row.  I'm going to turn into a tamale. 

						
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So the next big plan is to set up a darkroom in my house, which is really half of a duplex.  I have had a darkroom before, but never when my space was as limited as it is right now.  My funds at the moment are pretty limited, too.  There are a lot of things that you need in order to have a successful darkroom, and what I’m trying to figure out right now is where all the darkroom accessories that I had in the past are.  I swear…I remember what happened to my last enlarger (most expensive item), when it bit the dust, but I’m not sure about all the rest of my crap.  I guess it serves me right for moving so many times in the past couple of years.  I think that this may actually be the first lease that I renew…hallelujah.  So…at the bare minimum, I need the following: chemistry, trays, thermometer, reels, tank, jugs for chemistry, graduated cylinder (or measuring contraption of some kind), funnels, enlarger, negative holder, timer, easel, black bag, safelight, grain focuser, tongs.  Additionally, any of the following would be lovely: film washer, film drying cabinet, light box, compressed air, paper safe, paper cutter, loupe, contact sheet maker, filter, analog timer, print washer, print dryer.  Photography is an expensive habit, but everybody’s got to have one.  For some people, it’s cars, for some it’s gadgets and computers, musical instruments, crack…whatever.  Generally, the things that you are really passionate about require some kind of an investment.  If anyone has any of these items just lying around your house (or now-defunct darkroom) and can spare them, shoot me an email, cause I can use anything that I can get.  

						
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Have you ever had a cell phone that was possessed by something terrible, and would answer itself at very inappropriate times, even when you, the master, did not instruct it to do so?  Yeah, so that happened to me on Saturday night.  I know that I said that I wouldn't talk about my romantic entaglements, but hey...I have to tell someone.  I have several guys in my life, but for the purposes of this post, we'll narrow that number down to two.  The first...M.  I met him in a club when I was 16.  We have dated off and on for many, many years.  Though the past year has been more off than on, the four years proceding that were pretty serious.  He is wholly inappropriate for me.  He has graduated from college, true, but he has almost no ambition, is ridiculously selfish and we have different tastes in most everything.  The problem is, I'm in love with him and have been for most of my adult life.  We try to date....we admit that we both love each other, are IN love with each other, but he is the classic committment-phobe, grass-is-greener, while I want to get married.  I know that is the biggest stereotype there ever was -- the guy being afraid of the committment that the girl wants so bad -- but there it is.  Anyway, we're in limbo.  After a few drinks, we always break down and cry about how much we're in love but in the real world, something keeps us apart, at arm's length (except that we still sleep wth each other every chance that we get).  The second guy...A, I have known since I was 12, when I had a raging crush on him.  We became good friends, and my crush grew and grew, but it was never reciprocated.  Eventually, as I grew up and met other boys, we remained close, but my feelings for him faded (the romantic ones anyway) until I was entirely comfortable with us both being with other people.  Anybody know what's going to happen next?  That's right.  Last year, he came home from studying abroad and decided that he was in love with me, wanted to date me, kiss me, sleep with me, marry me.  It was overwhelming, but eventually I decided that it wouldn't work.  The problem is, a year later, his feeling for me are even stronger and I'm still at the I-just-don't-know-stage.  He's great, he really is.  Smart and talented, funny and good-looking.  I just...can't.  Or something.  I don't know if it has to do with my feelings for M or not, it just doesn't seem right to me.  I really wish that we could go back to our raging flirtatious-but-it's-ok-necause-it-doesn't-mean-anything friendship.  I just don't think we can.  Anyway, if I keep hanging out with him, he's going to make his move and I'm going to have to turn him down and it's going to get ugly.  I can already tell.  So, the two of them hate each other for obvious reasons.  M thinks A is pompous and arrogant (which he is) and A thnks M doesn't deserve me, has hurt me too much in the past (which may also be true).  Anyway, M knows that I hang out with A, but A is not aware of my continuing relationship with M.   So.  Friday night, after work, I went to Denton to hang out with M at his new house.  We had a really great time, went to dinner, had a few drinks, played some video games and had lots and lots of sex.  It was a lovely, lovely evening.  In the midst of dinner, then in the midst of the car drive back to his place, the phone rang.  I glanced at the caller ID, saw that it was A and made the decision to call him back at a later time, as I hate it when people take phone calls in the middle of dates, etc.  Apppppppparently, the phone decided, by brushing up the side of my purse or somesuch, to answer itself.  Now, who knows what I was saying when that happened?  I could have been frustrated that A was continuing to call, only because I am frustrated with the whole situation.  I could have been talking to M about wanting to sleep with him...I could have actually been in the very LOUD process of doing that very thing.  Who's to know?  Anyway, A heard something he didn't like and the shit hit the fan.  Eventually, after muuuuuch backpeddling, explaining and out-and-out lying, I convinced him that things were cool and that I would go out with him tonight.....Ohhhhhhh, what a tangled web we weave....  *Sigh*  

						
</post>


</Blog>