<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Me to beat on him? It seems has though everytime my brother Dustin comes over he always tries to pick a fight with me so I can beat on him.  He should know that I am one tough girl and I leave him with bruises an what not. But it's really fun to show my strength,let some anger out, and I guess it doesn't bother him that much cause he stills visits. Yeah, in case ya didn't know I am the youngest of five. The oldest is John who is 36, Mark died at 24, but would be 34 (I think) , Dustin is 24, and then Leah is 18. So yeah, I have it good being the youngest.      Moving on, today I woke up before 12. What a shocker. Leah woke me up to get in the shower so that I could go run some errands with her. I took my shower and then we were off to Khols. Leah picked some stuff up and I saw some things I liked too. We were at the cash register and we got a $10 reward thing which is good Aug.1- Aug.7, she gave it to me so you better believe I am going back.After that was all done with we came back home and chilled for a bit. I waited for my dad to get home cause we were going to also run some errands. I told my dad about some things at Khols I saw, and I asked if we could go again tonight and then I thought or tomorrow so I could use the reward card. Anywho, we went back to Khols again tonight. So yeah, I got me a punkster purse and a black belt and saw also some even more cutesy stuff. I can't wait til my birthday and Christmas. I already have a list going. But after Khols my dad wanted to go look for some shoes for him. So we went into Finish Line. They had the tightest pink Nike's. I love them. But they are waaaaay over priced. I thought I was starting to run a fever. Well, he didn't find anything he liked there so we walked down to Old Navy. On the way, Bath and Body Works is there so I asked if we could go in to smell some stuff. Just a lil hint: My fav scent for now is Sheer Freesia..hehe. So we went in and I looked at some prices. The chic working there talked my dad into buying some room scenting stuff for my mom and then she put this lotion stuff all over my hands. I was like ok, I didn't really care for the smell. But when I came home my bro and mom were like mmm what's that smell?...so I was like hmmm maybe it's a winner. But I don't know. Well after my dad bought my mom some stuff we left to go into Old Navy. Nothing there that was of any interest so we left to make it back home in time for Big Bro 5. So yeah, that leaves me to sitting here. I did talk to my dad about gettin second holes in my ears,like either right next to the one hole I already have or up higher. Dad didn't seem to not like the idea. So maybe I should just add that to the list. I would like to get my belly button pierced. Mom doesn't like the idea cause she says I don't show my stomach and also hinting I don't need to. O well, at least I know it's there. Anyway, I doubt that will happen.      Ok, well now you learned a bit of the family history and the scent for now at Bath and Body Works. Moving rather fast in getting to know me,eh? Well, the typing is done for the night, so I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background:  She Will Be Loved-Maroon 5  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A tornado warning issued to another county on the radio.  The moment I hear any warnings or even watches gets my nerves a jitterin'. I am absolutely terrified of storms.  I know, that may sound childish, but I don't even understand why I am that way.  Sometimes, even when it just thunderstorms I rush everything into the hallway and just sit there and pray that the storm will pass quickly.  I do find it really embarrassing when it storms and I have guests over. Cause then I get into this like mean mode telling people to shut up so I can watch the weather station. Sometimes when it is really bad I freak out and start crying and pacing. And yes, I have done that even with a guest over. Thankful he was such a sweetie and just held me in his arms.   But yeah, I think that is also why I love the fall and winter so much cause then I don't have to worry about a twister or lighting scaring me.      Moving on, yes today was on the rainy side. I was awaken at 6am to take out the trash. Yeah, so that was weird, I was hardly awake walking all crooked and what not. So then after that I went back to sleep until 12. I sat around until 4. My dad came home and we planned on going to Khols. So I was like yay, maybe I can get a purse now.  But on one condition, that I take the empty trash cans back around to the back. Here my sis was already told to do that since I had carried them full out front in the first place. Well, her being the not responsible daughter  doesn't do what she is told and just leaves for work while she runs over the trash cans backing out...sheesh. So yeah, I did as I was told.  We finally left and went to Shoe Carnival and Khols. Shoe Carnival is having a sale on their "chuckies" , I so want a black and blue pair. But didn't get them. Then we leave to go to Khols.  Dad didn't buy anything there so since he didn't, I did not want to push it to get my purse.  We looked around a little more. But we didn't get anything there either so we left. By the way, when I walked it I saw some old Eagledalians. My boy Justin and then Jonathan. It was great to see Justin again. Brings back alot of memories. I did feel bad cause I wasn't looking my greatest  o well though, come on, it was an icky day out. So yeah, after all that I didn't get to see a radar yet so I asked my dad if we could just go home, and we did. Well, I came home got yelled at by Leah for not waiting for her to get off work to be able to leave with us. Question: Do I do anything right? So then sat around alittle more until Leah told me maybe I should apply at where she works, the Harrison. So I was like sure, I neeeeeeeeeed money. She says she will take me over there and fill out an application and then she can go pick up some dinner, I agreed.Question: Why don't people want me? I am someone who WANTS to work, yes...you read correctly, I WANT to work. Anywho,we were off. I got the application and sat in the car, filled it out, and turned it in. That application would be number 5. We went got her some Arby's and headed home. I walk in the door to find my mom sitting at my pc playing Literati. So, I give my mom a time limit for when she has to get off.  Mom was being sneaky, I think, and after one game she started another. I was like ooook, this IS your last game young lady. I thought I would be a really responsible person and I cleaned house while she played. That's so jacked. So yeah, I vaccuumed,puts some clothes in the dryer , and folded them.  By that time it was time for her to get off. I do so much, I need a break...hahaha. So now here I sit, I guess that is my break then.      Ok, well now the fun fact learned today was Brè is a baby, waw waw. But a cute one, riiiiiiight?...hehe. I do appreciate the comments by my peepos, I feel special. So anywho, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background:  My Worst Fear-Rascal Flatts     
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Seven&nbsp;cats. Yes, thats right 7. They go by the names: Murphy,Pooder,Tiger,Romy,P.J.(stands for some medicine that my dad thought of,weirdo),Gremlin, and Gretchen. I love each and everyone to pieces. What I find really odd is that the cats all have names given to them, but yet I can't seem to ever call them by their correct names. They all go by different names to me. So, I think I will just tell ya...&nbsp;&nbsp;  **Murphy-aka-Mr. Murph,Murpa Purpa, and Corpse (since he seems as if he is on his death bed) **Pooder-aka-Poot Ball and Lil Bit**Tiger-aka-Tiger Baby,Tigs, and Tiggy Wiggy**Romy-aka-Romy Love, Precious, Baby Girl,&nbsp;and Sweet Potatoe**P.J.-aka-PeePee, Peepers, and Chokes (since she has some choking issue, I just think there is a massive hairball inside her growing)**Gremlin-aka-Gremy Leonard,Gremis, and Raccoon**Gretchen-aka- Gretchy Sketch, Pookers, Mouser, Mouse Killa, Gertrude, and Geoffery with a G...insider..hehe. Also, poor Gretchen is a boy. But hey, he is neutered so he don't know the difference. I have had pupper doggies in the past. Poor little beagle Maggie-aka-Magger Wagger died about 2 yrs. ago, and then we had a black lab Shia-aka-Shi Pi which was too whack for the family so we gave him away.     &nbsp;   Moving on, the warm weather is returning, shucks.&nbsp; I did get out alittle today. I woke up around 11:30 and on the Sci Fi channel they had a marathon of Roswell. Since my sis loves that show and she had control over the remote I watched it too. I kinda like the show. I like the relationships in it,even though its all about aliens not letting there idenities known. But I am romantic type a gal. But to discuss all those issues, thats another blog, another time. So yeah, I sat an watched that til 3.&nbsp; Then I took a shower,yay me, and went to sleep some more until my dad asked me if I wanted to go to Steve and Barry's known to my dad as Ben and Jerrys...sheesh. So we went, he bought some pants and then me being the good girl I am asked to get the new Brownie Batter at Dairie Queen. So we got it of course. It was delicious for being the only thing besides a P.B. and J. sandwich I had today. Yes, once again I am going back to my no eating phase. I seem to have had&nbsp;alot of compliments of being skinny and so I want to hear it again.&nbsp; But I will eat, here and there, and watch what I am eating. So it's all good. Well, anywho, after that we came home quickly to watch Big Bro 5. My family (besides my sis) is like addicted to it. I know it is just another reality tv show, but this one I actually like. I hate the lying people though. It just shows how evil people are. Well, it was a good show and now its over. So here I sit telling all the nonsense of the day.     &nbsp;   Ok, well I am sure I just told nothing of importance to anyone today. But this blog is for me to say anything I want, when I want, or how I want. So if I want to ramble on about nicknames I give to my cats,well so be it.&nbsp; Until tomorrow, I am outtie!     &nbsp;   Music Playin' in The Background:&nbsp; Vindicated-Dashboard Confessional    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The great outdoors. Well, I don't know if you can technically call Eagle Creek the "great outdoors", but here in Indy it sure comes close enough.&nbsp; I love Eagle Creek. My mom and I go alot to see deer an what not. But tonight was a bit different. We went for some band called like Black Jam or whatever. Supposedly every Wednesday night they have some band. We first pull up and park, duh. Then as I am walking down to the Marina, some teenage guy comes up to my mom and I&nbsp;with a sign on his stomach and says I need a hug or I will die.&nbsp; I look at him with some freakish look and say "suuuure why not." And so I hugged the guy. Yeah, what a weird experience. Anywho, so my mom and I sit on a bench looking out over the reservoir. That was nice. The music they had was like a bluegrass genre. So, I enjoyed it. Then as the sun began to set my mom and I&nbsp;get up and leave so we can venture around the park before 9 when they close the gates in on us. Well, we are driving around and what do ya know, there are two deer just eating away,how cutesy. We conitnue the journey to find so scavangers-also know as- raccoons digging in the trash-can and the baby coon climbs up the tree. Such a Kodak moment. Then cruisin' more,some huge thing swoops in front of the car. This creature was an owl. So we pull over and I start hootin' at it. It was kinda scary. I thought maybe it would come peck my eyes out or something. So by that time its time to leave. We drive down 56th Street where we see even more deer,and they are even crossing the street. I sooo can't see Bambi getting hit. But anyway, overrall the outing was great. I really would love to live in the country just so I can have all the creatures living in my yard and then I wouldn't have to travel to a park to see them.     &nbsp;   Today, yeah, believe it or not, I did do alot. Not only did I have the outing at Eagle Creek, this girl got busy. Busy on searching for a job. I had previously applied at Petco. But those people must not have known what an animal lover I was since they never hired me. So, I have made it a goal NOT to work at fast food. That is when I come upon the sign at the Dollar Tree. Yes, I know its a dollar store and I won't get paid squat. But at least I will have more money than what I have now. So yes, I applied there. Then my neighbor works at Pearson Education. She explains what she does and says she makes good money. So I went there today also. I went in and the people at the front desk tell me I have to sit down to fill it out the application now. I was like uh oh. I need my mommy. But I was a big girl and sat and filled it out on my own. The questions asked were hard, well for me at least. So I finally get done and turn it in. But as I hand it to the lady at the front desk I ask&nbsp;" Do you have to be at least 18 yrs. of age to work here?" She replies with,"Yes". Then my next words are,"Well, then you might just wanna go ahead and throw the application away now." She laughs, I leave. Word to the wise: Ask how old you have to be to work anywhere, BEFORE you sit and fill out a huge application. But, good news, on the way to Pearson Education, I remember GFS (Gordon Food Service) was hiring. So I walked up there to get the application while 3 girls stare at me with disgust. They are just mad because I am going to take their jobs, well hopefully. So I sit and fill that application out, walk back in to ask this guy where I turn the application in at. He then says that he will take it. Good news, he was the asst. manager..hehehe. So I made sure I showed my pearly whites! He looked over it alittle while I stood there, and made some comments. So, I really think that place might be a winner. I did see a hiring sign at Tuchmans (sp?)&nbsp;Cleaners. They are paying up to $9/hr.WOWZERS Buuuut, you have to be 18, see..I asked first! So yeah that was my business experience.     &nbsp;   By the way, I kinda sorta found this new store. It's on 38th Street in the shopping strip where CiCi's Pizza is. The name is Total Fashions,I think. Anywho, I asked Leah to go over there so she said sure. Well, I am glad I did. They have some stylish clothes, some formal dresses, wigs, hats, and other accessories. Then they have like this wall of stuff for a dollar, yes, 1 DOLLAR! So I almost got nail polish and black eye liner..until I saw earrings, toe rings, and anklets. So yeah, I spent some money.     &nbsp;   Ok, well well well, I think I wrote an awful lot. But hope you learned something such as the 'word to the wise' part.But yeah, shoooo my wrists hurt so I am outtie!     &nbsp;   Music Playin' in The Background: My Happy Ending-Avril Lavigne     &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yes, that's right, I am admitting I hate showers.&nbsp; The showers I am talking about are not the lovely wedding showers, the poopy diaper baby showers, or even the calming rain showers.&nbsp; The showers I speak of are the showers where one must clean themselves.&nbsp; You might ask, then are you like some grudge bucket? Well, I can be. Showers are so time consuming and it just is such a hassel to take a shower and then put make-up on and do whatever else comes along with preparing for the day.&nbsp; Maybe that is why I spend so much time in my PowerPuff Girl Pj pants, and my o so comfy Cubs shirt. Cause I just don't feel like taking a shower everyday. I usually never have any plans anyway,hmm maybe it's because I am a smelly person?!?!..whoa, I hope that isn't the case.     &nbsp;   Moving on, today was a beautiful day! I love the colder weather in July, I could get used to it.&nbsp; It's so refreshing and it doesn't give me headaches like the hot weather does. Ahhh, just can't wait til Fall comes and then it will be like this everyday...and the smells, the yummy cider that goes along with it..ahhh. Ok, I better not say anymore,cause in all reality...its July,crud. JULY!? JULY 27th THAT IS! Getting closer to August which is when my dvd's for homeschooling come in.&nbsp; What is crazy is I am not supposed to start til September, but I can't wait much longer, I wanna start now.&nbsp; My brain must be fried or something. Did I also just admit to wanting to start school now? See, what this weather changing has done to me.     &nbsp;   Ok, well I hope that this blog of the day hasn't made anyone think less of me or differently that is. I have the right to express my opinion, so ya know what? I DID!     &nbsp;   Music Playin' in the Background: Kiss Me Fool-Fefe Dobson    
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well, I kept on saying I would start my own blog, so here it is! Let me first start off by saying... READ AT YOUR OWN RISK EVERYDAY ...Anywho, life is good (well yesterday and today at least) Yesterday, after church I travelled up to Borders with my mom to see the lovely and talented Emerson Drive. Ahhh, I thought I had died and gone to heaven. They sung two acoustic songs "Last One Standing" and "November" then signed CD's. Well, Me being the fan I am have both of there CD's and you better believe it, I got them signed. I even got to have the lead singer put his arm around me for a picture (that is when&nbsp;I just melted). I tell ya, that is such an experience. The only other autographs I have are from the Pacers back in the day of Larry Bird, Rik Smit,Dale Davis,etc. and then Chely Wright but I didn't get that one on my own.&nbsp; Not only is it an experience just to receive their autographs seeing the performance is breathtaking too. I went to the Country Music Expo earlier this year and that was awesome, and of course I have been to alot of the sporting events around the city.     Ok, well look for further blogging. Cause unlike some..no names mentioned..I will do my best to update daily!     &nbsp;   Music Playin' In the Background:&nbsp; Rescued-Emerson Drive      &nbsp;    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Some crazy dreams. Yeah, I have, of course, had the weird dreams of dating people who I never thought I would date. But in all honesty, dating those people in my dreams wasn't that bad. One dream which is somewhat reoccurring is a dream where my braces come off. It is so freaky and scares me to death. Yeah, I can't wait for the day I get them off, but in my dream when they come off my my teeth go back to being even more crooked and they also fall out. Ugh, just crazy I tell ya. I wonder what kind of weird dreams others have. Hmmm.      Moving on, today was like the most boring day I have had in a long time. I woke up early to try to accomplish whatever I wanted to do today. But nope, didn't do squat. Joshua did come over around 2 to fix the pc again and hook my printer up. Man, what would I do without him? After he left, I chilled some more and ate dinner. I did take a shower just so I could feel clean..haha. After my shower, I looked over how I want to schedule my homeschooling and then before ya know it, it was Big Bro time. So I watched that with my mom and now here I sit. By the way, I am curious where did everybody go? I receive no comments anymore, I feel so alone. Well not really, just want to know what's going on.      Ok, this blog was way to short. But like I said, today nothing happened. Hopefully tomorrow is better. Well, until next time, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background: Float On- Modest Mouse  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Raccoons. Driving down the street you can always find a dead raccoon on the side of the road. The other night I was trying to sleep when I thought I heard Gretchen eating outside. But I realized that is an awful lot of noise he is making just to eat. So I get up, go peek out my window and what do ya know, it is a raccoon. Not only was it one, but there were two. They walk so funny and they are like human size if they stand on their back legs. I always thought that raccoons would be nice, but I have heard Opossums are more friendly than raccoons. But I do think raccoons are waaaaay more cute. Also, not only have I seen alot of these creatures dead on the side of the road, when I took my little driving lesson through Crown Hill there was a dead one by one of the graves. Now is that like freaky or what? My family has had there idea that our cat Gremlin is part raccoon as well. He doesn't have the markings like one but he sure does walk like one and he makes noises that I believe a raccoon would make. So is it just me, or is there like a whole bunch of these animals?      Moving on,   today was my brother's 24th birthday. So that means my mommy made some of his favorite cookies and I ,of course, got to eat some too! So yeah, I woke up and went out to the cottage to wish him a happy birthday. He showed me all his gifts. His girl-friend had bought him twenty-four gifts. In the huge selection of gifts, he received Cubs tickets. Dang, I want them. He also got alot of other cool stuff, like a watch, cologne called Allure (which smells excellent), some cds, and more. After that I came back in and watched tv, chilled with Dusty some more, and did some chores. I then took a shower. After taking a shower I waiting around for my dad so we could go run some errands. We went to Sears, Foot Locker, Finish Line,Champs, Rack Room Shoes, and many more shoe places cause he is so picky on what he likes. I was tired of looking at shoes! Finally we made it home. Once I got home I looked up an old friend's number. The friend is Derrick. Yeah, last time I saw him was in 8th grade. That was 3 yrs. ago! I called him up and we talked a bit. I promise, that boy is going to be an NBA star..so keep your eyes open for him! He was shocked to know it was me. He seemed just the same has he used to be. I kinda felt dumb calling him though. O well, I did it. At least he knows I was thinking about him and that if he wants me he knows how to reach me. But yeah, that was fun. Now here I sit. It is hottttt. I am ready for the cold front to get to moving through, ugh! I can't believe school starts for IPS tomorrow. Ugh, that's a killer. But why do they only have half days and then start school on a Thursday? That is just gay. I tell ya, I find myself getting more grown up everyday, but also getting more childish everyday. Now does that make sense? I think not. I guess I just have my moments.Hmmm.      Ok, my mind is like bouncing like crazy! I have so many thoughts going through my head at once. I must control myself! Hopefully, I get some stuff accomplished tomorrow. I have so much to do. Well, until next time, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background: You're The Inspiration-Chicago     
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       When others make mistakes? I mean, if someone makes a serious mistake I know that isn't meant to be laughed at. But I always felt like when someone makes a slight error it is ok to laugh cause it usually is funny. Maybe I am wrong. I even laugh at myself at all the stupid things I do. Since when do people take that so seriously? Will people just lighten up and have fun? Sheesh, don't blame me for being the laughing person that I am.      Moving on, today was hot stuff. I woke up kind of on the early side just because I felt like it. I watched some televsion with my sister. My brother was getting ready for work and asked me to make him some grilled cheese sandwiches. For doing so he paid me $2. Yay me! Yesterday he paid me $1 just to get him something to drink. Well after my mom, Leah, and Dusty left I decided I would wash the dishes. So I washed them and then watched more tv. My dad came home from work and then I decided to take a shower. After I got out of the shower I ate some dinner and then in a few hours I was on my way to the Healthplex to play volleyball. While I was standing there waiting for the basketball guys to get done I realized I knew one of them. It was Terry Webster (an Eagledalian who left in the 7th grade). I kinda was hesitate to ask if it was him, but the moment I said his name he looked at me and said "Hey Brè!" I felt much better. We chit chatted a bit and then he left and I played some volleyball. Leah actually went to play with me tonight. She enjoyed it alot. After volleyball, Brad, Leah, William, and I went to Sonic to eat, duh. I had two hot dogs. I love hot dogs. Then we had an ice spitting fight and that was fun stuff. Now I am home finishing up my cherry slush. I am hoping there is a cherry at the bottom with a stem that I can tie. You have heard the saying, if you can tie a cherry stem into a knot with your tongue you are a good kisser? Well, if not, now ya know. I was amazed how little people knew of that. But keep in mind, I have done it more that once...hehehe, you know what that means. Ok, I will stop.      Ok, well I am going to get off here now and find something to do. Hmm, maybe I will eat some Runts. I love Runts! They are muy muy muy deliciouso. Dang,my arms feel somewhat tired. Me tired from volleyball? Man, that never happens. Well, until next time, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background: Toxic- Britney Spears  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Opened Memorial Day and then closed on Labor Day? Well, I guess what I thought was wrong. I went to go swimming and the pool was closed. So I looked it up online and it seems as though all pools closed yesterday. Now that ain't right. There is still a month left of summer and I wanna swim. Just because everyone else has to start school doesn't mean they gotta close the pools. Sheesh.      Moving on, today I woke up around 9:30. Yes, it was an early start to my day. I woke up to my mom saying that she found a gift for me in the mail-box. I guess before William had gone to work he left me some Jelly Belly's in the mail-box. They were yummy. But anyway, my brother had to be at work around 11 so I waited around and went with him and my mom when they went up to work. After my mom and I had dropped him off, we decided we wanted some double-cheese burgers. So we went up to the McDonalds in Broad Ripple since we were up that way. I love McDonalds only because they had a dollar menu. Thankfully Taco Bell kinda has the same thing, but yet they don't have chicken quesadillas on there. Bummer. After we ate we drove back down by home and went to Target. Mom got some pillows and my brother a birthday card. Then we came back home. While at home, that is when I discovered the whole pool issue.  I sat around and watched the Olympics volleyball. Yay! The USA beat the Germans! While watching that game, a Chilson came over. Yeah, Jason brought my mom some Starbucks...is he trying to be a suck up or just being nice? Hmm, I wonder. After he left, my dad decided he wanted to go to Dick's. So we drove out to Avon and he looked around. We finally were home around 5:30. Then I watched more television. Now I have decided to clean out my closet and drawers. I didn't realize how much clothes I needed to throw away. So yeah, I thought I would take a break and fill ya in on my day. Exciting huh?      Ok, nothing more to say today. O wait, I do want to complain about something else. I get so irritated when no one listens. I hate having to repeat myself or talk over others. I especially hate it when I say something and someone always has to question it or tries to think deeper into what I am saying which then leads to them getting way off the subject and leaving me even more confused. Sheesh Louise that was such a run-on sentences,O well..Now I feel somewhat better. By the way, I didn't get my DQ application today. Whoops, such a slacker. Well, until next time, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in the Background: Just To See You Smile-Tim McGraw  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sunday afternoon nap. After I have to wake up early to go to church coming home is nice so that I can sleep. The Sunday routine is usually go to church and then maybe out for lunch. Then I try to set aside time for me to relax, after all, Sunday is a day of rest.      Moving on, what a beautiful Sunday. Sunday should always be sunny. I did go to church today. It was nice. I am finally learning most of the songs they sing. I do love the traditional hymns, but thankfully I can learn the new stuff and still sing some hymns at the church I attend now. After church, my mom and dad, Dusty, Leah, her Josh, and I went to brunch at the Harrison. Leah usually works on the day of brunch, but today she didn't so she decided she should go since she actually is allowed to eat instead of serving the other guests. The Harrison is a nice place. The old people are so funny, and the food is yumilicious. Once we all had our stomachs full we came back home. Leah and Josh chilled at the house with Dusty, Dad watched the Cubs game, and I talked my mom into taking me driving. So yeah, we left to go to Crown Hill. She did take some flowers from the garden to put on Marks grave. So I went driving for about an hour. I do plan on getting my permit Tuesday or Wednesday. That is only if I past the test. We did return home around 3. The moment I walked in the door I put some comfortable clothes on and took a nap. I finally woke up from my nap around 8:30. Man, do I feel relaxed. I still have somewhat of a headache though. I think the crying I did yesterday still has my nose stuffed up in there,lol. I watched some of the Olympics with my dad. People do have some talent. It is amazing and they make is look so easy. So yeah here I sit. My room is still a mess. I can't believe I have slacked off from cleaning it. That so isn't me. Maybe I will clean it tonight or just wait until tomorrow, who knows. Tomorrow, I do plan on going to the Dairie Queen in Clermont to apply. Please, I NEED A JOB!  So yeah, that is pretty much my day.      Ok, I am one of those few teenagers who actually reads the newspaper. I think I took an interest in reading it when I had the privilege of being taught by good ol' Mr. Nitschke. He was like the least favorite teacher at Eagledale. But yet, I liked him alot. I think I gained most of my knowledge from him. I am going to miss him while I am homeschooled. But anyway, while I was reading it I read something about panic attacks. I have known a few people who suffer from these. My mom is one of them. It is crazy when she has one. Her heart starts racing and she of course gets all anxious and thinks the worst about what is causing her to feel this way. When she has these attacks, I feel like there is nothing I can do or say that will make her situation any better. She has found some ways to calm herself. She does take a pill for it, then she reads her Bible. Seems to work too. But what I find funny when she has these attacks is she seems like she has to brush her teeth. I wonder, does anyone else who suffers from these attacks feel like they need to brush their teeth? My mom did say that I might have suffered from a panic attack when we had taken our first trip up to Kenosha. I had the feeling of not being able to swallow. So in order for me to not get so scared about choking, the whole time we were on the trip I carried a bottle of water with me. I felt embarrassed and felt like I kind of ruined the trip for us. I guess maybe I got a little to excited or just too nervous about our road trip. Who knows, but I do not like the feeling that I can't swallow. Also reading, they gave a good tip on avoiding brain freezes : To avoid brain freeze when you're drinking a milkshake, keep the straw away from the roof of your mouth. To lessen the already headache-inducing effect, press your tongue or your thumb up there. I usually find myself pinching the top on my nose or squeezing my head really tight. Let me also say, a brain freeze and a brain fart are NOT the same thing. It irritates me when people call a brain freeze a brain fart. Brain freeze is the headache from drinking cold stuff to quickly and a brain fart is when you can't think of what you want to say or what you want to remember. So those people calling brain freezes brain farts, are suffering from a brain fart. THEY AIN'T THINKING! But ok, I think I got the point acrossed. One last thing before I go, I got my homeschooling dvds. I have a feeling I will really enjoy Consumer Math thanks to a good-lookng teacher. But yeah, it is weird to watch the videos and knowing that is how I am going to learn. So I just count down the days to when I start, fun stuff! Well, until next time, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background: Breathless- The Corrs  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Too good to be true. You would think that yesterday being Friday the 13th things would have gone bad then. But no, things went bad today. The little black kitten I mentioned in the previous post is no longer with us. We had found the kitten Thursday and discussed taking it to a vet to get treated and then try to have it adopted. But I knew that once the kitten got better I would want to keep it. So yesterday, I talked to my mom about it more and she agreed we could keep the cat, but we also realized we needed to get medical attention for it. Yesterday the kitten was starting to get playful. Even with only the use of three legs it jumped on and off my bed. I was so surprised. The kitten even try to race me to the door so it could go out into the living room with me. I fell in love with kitten. I was still undecided on a name for it though. But when I woke up this morning things had taken a turn for the worst. My mom woke me up saying I needed to meet her in the backyard and that we needed to discuss some things about the kitten. Once I made my way out into the backyard I just lost all happiness I have had for the past several days. Mom began to tell me that the kitten was using the restroom all over itself, it wasn't using the litter box, it didn't eat its food last night, it was breathing very hard, and that she would sit him down and he would just roll over and lie there. The kitten was sufferring. My mom then goes and calls like every vet there was in the phone book and every animal shelter besides the Humane Society. She didn't want to call the Humane Society cause there was more of a chance that they would put it to sleep instead of actually helping it. So I give the kitty one last kiss while my mom drives off to take it to this one vet to see what they said. The vetrinarian there said the cat had been attacked by another animal and that it was dehydrated. They said even if they did give the cat fluids there was a good chance it wouldn't live. After hearing that, my mom had no choice but to take it to the Humane Society. While being there, my mom asked for them to take the kitten. She knew it was going to be put to sleep. The people there asked for her to pay a $20 charge for allowing that. My mom said that isn't right and that the building was there for them to rescue animals and not to make it an issue of money. She then says I am not driving to Animal Control with this poor kitty. The manager comes out and says they will go ahead and take the kitten. My mom hands the kitten over to them while the kitty gives her one last meow. Like I said before, I didn't even give the kitten a name, but I grew close to the kitty. I thought that kitten was so lucky that it found us. Cause we being the animal lovers we are were glad to let the kitten feel safe with us. But now, I feel awful. I feel so hurt I couldn't have done more. All those "what if's" come to mind now. I just can't believe all the happiness I had, and all the happiness I had to look forward to with this kitten was just gone in a matter of seconds.      Moving on, if you can't tell this day just really was icky. Yesterday though was fun. I did end up going to the Fair last night. Leah, Josh (Leah's bf), William, and I all went at 9pm to 1am. From that time it was the all you can ride wristbands for $16. But me being a chicken that I am didn't get one. So yeah, I stood around checking stuff out while they all rode stuff. People problem think, "You went to the Fair and didn't ride stuff? You are weird and are missing out." But sure, go ahead and think that. I had fun anyway. Rides never excite me. So I made myself happy doing other stuff and just spending time with people. I did love petting the cows and donkeys though. Hehehe. O wait, I did ride the Ferris Wheel. Ugh, I was terrified just on that. I am so not cut out for that kind of stuff. But yeah, then around 1:30 in the morning I finally made it back home. My mom and Leah went to Steak 'n Shake when they were on there way to take Josh home. William stayed at my house for a few more hours and just chilled. He finally left and I went to bed. I just wish I went into like a coma or something. Cause I definitely didn't want to wake up to a day like today. But yeah, that is just all that has happen since my last post.      Ok, my head hurts from all my crying today. So I think I will go lie down or find something to do which doesn't allow my mind to go back to thinkin about the kitten. Well, unitl next time, I am outtie!       Music Playin' in The Background: These Days-Rascal Flatts  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       kitten go? Earlier today, my mom was sitting at the computer and then comes out to the living room and says there is an injured black kitten on the porch of our neighbors house. Well, we being cat lovers get a can of cat food and start meowing like kittens for it to come us. The poor thing came to us. Its front left paw looks broken. The kitten was hopping around everywhere. We took it into the cottage with some cat food and water. It's weird, the cat is so people friendly. It started purring. Well, since my brother is staying out in the cottage for awhile, we had to take it somewhere else. I could not allow that cat to not be in my possession with it being injured. So I offered to allow it to stay in my room. So here I have this little injured black kitten all curled up on my floor. My mom and I did manage to tape up its leg. But I have a feelin it will need to be amputated. The sex of the kitten is undetermined. I still don't even have a name for it. My dad suggested to call it "History"...haha, that's not funny. But yeah, any suggestions? I keep looking at it to see what names comes to mind, but I still see a blank. Anyway, I am just glad I could rescue it.    Moving on, today I woke up around 6:30am for my breakfast date with William which was supposed to be at 7. But the little meany showed up at 6:40. He brought me some breakfast which was delicious. So we sat and ate and then by 7:45 he had to leave to go to work. So yeah, that was thoughtful of him. Once he left I went back to sleep until 11. Then I just talked with my brother and sister for awhile. Then came 12:30 when I was supposed to be in the shower, but that is when my mom saw the kitten. I ended up taking care of the cat til 2:30 when I decided to get in the shower then. After I got cleaned up, my mom and I went over to Dollar General to get some gauze stuff for the kitten. Then we came back home and had dinner. After dinner, I sat around some more, took the trash out, and sat with the cat some more. Then around 7:30, my dad gave Leah and I money to go get him and my mom a milkshake. So when Leah and I left to go to Target we also stopped at Arby's to get some Jamocha shakes. Then I came home from that and baked cookies and watched Big Bro. Now here I sit. The kitten is still asleep. Aw, I love it already! But I shouldn't get too attached. Word has it, I might be going to the Fair tomorrow. If so, this would be the first time I have ever gone. Yay me! But yet, those plans could possibly change. Hmmm.      Ok, well I did something to my wrist and it hurts to seat here and type. I don't know if I slept funny last night or if he just hurts from beating up on people. But ouch, it's a killer. Might I also add, it is August and the temperatures are in the 40s. WOWZERS! I am loving it! Well, until next time, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background:  Here I Am(Come and Take Me) -UB40  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Naive. Lately during the observing of some individuals I realize how childish they can really be. I admit, I have my moments. But who doesn't? I am talking about naive people who just are always that way. The naive I am referring to  is not only in their actions, but also in there way of life in decision making. It's amazing how people can allow to drop themselves so low and lose what standards or goals they had for themselves. But maybe, the Lord will break them and all will be put "put back together".      Moving on, today was frigid feelin'. I woke up around 11. Did the normal television watching and what not. I did decide to take a shower earlier than the norm, go me! But anywho, nothing much was done today. I did talk to William around 5:30 and asked him to be at my house at 9 so we could enjoy a nice fire together. Well in between the time I was waiting for him to get here, Leah and I went to Target and Hobby Lobby. I didn't get nothing, bummer. But Leah got what she needed. Finally we arrived home around 8:15. I started the fire at 8:30 cause I thought I might have difficulties getting it going. Well what do ya know, I didn't. So I was stuck babysitting the fire til William showed up. We had fun. We roasted marshmallows and talked. So peaceful. Then the wood was all used and it was getting cold so we came back in the house. He talked to my momma for awhile then before he left, he reserved the rest of his time for me. How lucky am I?! Well, his dad actually gave him a curfew tonight so he left around 11:45. Now that he is gone, I have time to sit and fill you in on my day. Now who is the lucky one?      Ok, it's late and I got to get up early cause I am having breakfast with William before he goes to work. But before I go, have I mentioned how happy I am? Hehehe, I think so. Well, my bed awaits me, so I am gonna get all snuggly warm in it, so I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background: Grand Theft Autumn(Where Is Your Boy)- Fall Out Boy  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Energy once again! I have gone absolutely crazy. I am in a singing and dancing kind of mood. Too bad I can't do either one, but I try. I have had so much fun today. I love being in a great mood. It makes me happy and I can see others enjoy it too!      Moving on, yeah like I said, today was awesome. I woke up around 8:30 cause we had some tree trimmer guys cutting on the front tree.  They butchered it.The tree looks awful.So that wasn't too fun. Finally I got back to sleep for a couple of more hours. Then when I woke up I was asked to cut the watermelon. That is some difficult stuff. Thankfully, I still have all of my fingers. Well after I got the watermelon cut I planned on going swimming with my brother and sister. Well, before we could actually swim we all had some chores to do. Yeah, it was weird, my brother was told to do dishes. He hasn't washed dishes here at the house in like forever. Finally we got all the stuff done and by 1:30 we were swimming. It was chilly out, but I did manage to get some sun. Oh, there was a hilarious thing that happened at the pool. Well, we were all swimming and what not when they had some other life guard fake and engery so that they could tape the rescue. So the girl jumps off of the diving board and comes back up and says "O my neck hurts." Then the other life guard blows the whistle and says "Possible spinal cord injury and points then jumps in to 'save' the girl. Well while she is assisting the girl in the water, the other life guard is running with a stretcher and a medical bag. The poor girl falls. That is when I just lost it. The people video taping and the other life guards look at her and are like do we need to help you. It was just funny, I guess you had to be there. So much for there video taping rescue. But yeah, that was funny stuff. Then around 3 we left so Leah could watch Roswell and get ready for work.  Well then I sat around for awhile until Luke and Ryan (some Eagledalians) came over. I went and hid in my mom's room until they left. Once they left I took my shower. I felt so fresh 'n so clean clean...haha. The moment I got out of the shower the phone rang. It was good ol' Bradley (another Eagledalian). He called after his soccer practice to see if I wanted to play some volleyball. How could I resist?!?! I said sure. Brad then says well its just going to be the two of us cause William says he is too sore. So I call that boy up and telling I am going and that too bad he was too tired. He then says I told Brad I might go. So I was like ok. Well, I will see there or I will just talk to you later. Well, Brad comes and gets me around 6. We walked into the Healthplex, signed ourselves in, and then good ol' William walks in. I had a feeling he might show up...hehe. So we all played volleyball until 8:30. It was so fun. The Chineses guys kept picking on me. But thankfully, I just laughed and didn't overreact. After volleyball, I talked the boys into going to the park. They agree, I win! So we all headed over to the park and stayed until 9:30. W had so much fun there too. We were going to play more volleyball or tennis under the lights. But the Mexicans had taken over. What a shame. So we just did all the other stuff there until Brad told me he was ready to take me home. So I said my good byes to William, then Brad and I were on the way back to my house. Brad drops me off at my house and as we pull up I recognize Luke's car at my house. Sheesh. So I go to the backyard and find Luke,Ryan, Heather, and Tiffany (all Eagledalians). They all were in the backyard chit chatting with Leah. So then I call William to see if he still had some time to get back over to my house. But he was already home. Bummer. I talked to him on the phone a bit. I told him if he can't get on the computer tonight to just come back over. I have yet to hear from him. O well. So yeah, here I sit now. My room is messy. That ain't right. I have it cleaned everyday. Looks like I got work to do. Darn.      Ok, I am still full of energy. It is not like I have been drinking any caffiene either. It's weird.  Ahh, I hope the next few days are just as fun. School starts soon for everybody. Everytime I hear them saying about the new school year, I become more thankful that I am being homeschooled. Might I was add, I chose to be homeschooled, it was not something I was forced into doing. Well, with all that said, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background: Underneath It All- No Doubt  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Actually study to get my permit. Yeah, I have somewhat been a slacker in that whole driving area. But I have had the experience of driving through Crown Hill Cemetery. I don't think I am that bad. But then again, I haven't actually interacted with other cars, so who knows. I have really never had the need to drive anywhere anyway. My friends are all starting to drive now, Leah drives, mom will take me where I need to go, and then I always have lived right across the street from school and now that I am homeschooled it definitely doesn't matter. But yeah, I believe it is time Bre makes it out on the road!      Moving on, I have been one busy person the past few days. It is craziness. I see it now that the summer is slowing down to the end, I find I have so much to do. Like I said, craziness. Well, yesterday like I mentioned was Brickyard Sunday. Good ol' Jeff Gordon won. I don't really care too much who wins, but I find it exciting just to watch knowing that race is down the street from my house and is being broadcasted everywhere, well kinda. So yeah, as I sat and watched the race Leah and dad finally returned home from there trip. We all finished watching the race and they of course told stories about their trip. Well after the race was over I found I had so much energy inside me, I was ready to let loose alittle. I seriously was just running and jumping all over the house cause I wanted to so something, anything really. Well finally come 8:30 Sunday evening I IMed William and asked to do something. He agreed. So we went to Dairy Queen. I wanted to get the new Brownie Batter. THEY WERE OUT. So I wanted to get the Reese's Cup Blizzard. THEY WERE OUT. Was I cursed or something? How did an ice cream place be out of two of the top things on my list? So I was on my way to see if I was going to get strike three. But thankfully, they did have a Heath Blizzard. So after all that, we took our ice cream over to the park and sat and ate it. Being filled with the yummy ice cream we went and swang, slid down the slides, went on the merry-go-round (which I think he got sicky feelin' on).  The we decided to just sit and talk til my curfew. Yes, this time I made it home on time. I made sure to read my clock when it came close to 12.  So we came home on time. We sat around for while talking with my brother and parents. Then they left around 12:30 in the morning to go do some stuff.  So I told William he could just go on home and I would just go to bed. No way was that going to happen. He thought he should wait til the parentals returned. YES SIR! Such a protector. So they returned about 1:30. We all sat around and joked and talked more. Mom decided to go to bed, Dusty went to sleep out in the cottage and my dad stayed up with me and William for alittle longer until he was out. Yes, you could tell he was in a deep sleep from the way he was snoring. So William and I just sat around some more and enjoyed each others company. Finally around 2:30 he left. I went to bed and all was good.  I woke up today alittle after 11. I watched Breakfast at Tiffany's. I love that movie! They I chilled around the house. I talked my mom into getting me a chicken quesadilla too. Mmmmmm was it delicious! Then I decided I would take a shower and go do something with my dad. We went to Galyans to get him shoes, Dairy Queen again to get him a MooLatte, Home Depot to get my mom a back porch light, and Target to get my comforter, but they didn't have it so we went to Meijer and got the other one I liked. Finally made it home around 11ish. I chilled some more drinking a Dr. Pepper straight from the bottle. I love drinks that come from out of bottles. They taste so much better. Cause personally, Dr. Pepper is nasty straight from a can. It is so flat tasting.  But dad being a coke bottle collector, I get to drink alot from bottles. But he did get the Dr. Pepper ones while on his trip. I think that is why I like Jones Sodas too. They got yummy flavors that taste great. Root beer and Cream Soda in a bottle is awesome too. Ok,ok no more about bottle drinking. Just because I do say things taste better in a bottle doesn't mean I encourage any acoholic drinking from bottles. So yeah, today was fun stuff!      Ok, wow, I have typed so much it's amazing. I could so say more. But I have plenty of more opportunities to talk about other stuff, at another time.  Life can get pretty stressful. But I am learning every day to just at least smile and try to be happy. I just am soooo full of energy!!!! Well, so I can go let some energy out, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background:  Floor Filla- A*Teens  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       For being a slacker these past two days. I have been so busy and stressed it's unbelievable. So I will take the time in this blog to tell you about some of the highlights.       Friday, August 6, 2004       Well, Friday was good day. I woke up early so I could go get my hair cut. So as I was getting my hair cut my mom and I begin to talk like what should we do while dad and Leah are at Pensecola. My suggested we go to Evansville cause she has family their and she wanted to take pictures of some graves for her genealogy project. I then remind her we don't have that much money. She said we can just pack up the cooler and sleep in the car if we need to. Well, then I thought if we have enough money to do that in Evansville we can surely make it to Kenosha,WI. Kenosha is like home to us. The lighthouses there, the nice wavy Lake Michigan, and the yumilicious Jelly Belly Factory. So mom agreed. I WAS SO EXCITED!!!!! So we pack some stuff of use, pick up some ice, and get somemoney out of the bank...and we were off. While travelling, mom realizes we would probably hit Chicago during rush-hour. So she plans on taking the interstate a little farther out around the city. That was probably the biggest mistake ever. The interstate was crowded. I didn't know that many people could fit in such a tiny area. Not only was it crowded, there were like toll roads after toll roads. Mom begins to ask me to read the map in what roads she can get on to and then we can finally get to our destination.  It seemed like once I just said get off the interstate we were there in no time. Ahh, it was such a wonderful experience. Too bad we got there like at 6 that evening. So we cruised around a bit. Kenosha was having a tall ships festival. It was awesome. Those ships with all those sails, then the nice breeze of the water, and the sun setting. Ahh, picture perfect. So then after that we drove some more. I can't believe I forgot to mention this. But just south of Kenosha, and over the border to Illinois, there is the Great Lakes Naval Base. WOWZERS! That means you can see guys in uniform all the time. They are adorable. Even the Mexicans make the uniform look good. So anywho, we drove around checked that out. But back in Kenosha, we had planned to sleep in the car in this parking lot that overlooked the water. We had everything in the car situated and were just sitting talking until we got sleeping. Then all of a sudden my mom is like ugh what is that smell. I said it wasn't me. Come to find out it was a skunk. That skunky smell made us leave. So then we were confused on where we should stay. Mom did say we could get a cheapy hotel room. But every sign up there said no vacancy. So by that time it was 12:30am. We decide we will just come back home. So we drove back from there from 12:30am to 4:15am. Phew, what a long night it was.       Saturday,August 7, 2004         Well, around 5:30am I finally got some sleep. Some circumstances kept me up longer than expected. So then I slept until probably 11, got up and made a phone call to see if I was going to have plans later that evening. Finally about 2, the phone kept ringing no stop. Joshua calls to say he is on his way to get a disk, Asim keeps calling cause he has no life and wants his no in everyone's business, and then finally William calls to say we are going to a movie. I tell William to be here at 5. Before he got here, I managed to take a shower, and eat some pizza. Then he got to my house. We sat and talked for an hour and half. Then went to go see the movie. I got to see The Little Black Book. That was an interesting movie. Doesn't turn out the way you would have expected. But I liked it alot. Anywho, the movie ended by 9:30 and so we went back to his house to get some pictures that he had taken of me like months ago. He was slow at getting them developed. After that, coming off the interstate he asks if I would want to go to the canal. Of course, I agreed. We got to the canal by 10:15. The weather last night was gorgeous and being downtown helped me get away from the race crowd in the neighborhood.  We walked around, sat around and talked while we were at the canal.  Then around 11:45 (which I thought was what my watch said) we left and made it home. Well, walking in the door to my house showed I read my watch wrong. It was 12:15am. Curfew is at twelve. Oops! It was seriously a completed accident. It's not like I did it on purpose. So that led to my mom printing out another rules sheet. Sheesh.Well, William stayed and hung out for awhile and then left at 1. I went to my room at fell fast asleep. Ahh, it was lovely.       NOW, today...well it is Brickyard Sunday! Traffic is crazy, the people are crazy. But I love race days. Cause right over my street is where the military jets come by. It is an awesome sight. I have grown up getting excited for it. Today, Leah and dad plan on returning also. Things are a bit crazy around this Prosch house...sheesh. But I plan to make this a good Sunday!      Ok, I think you got the general idea of what I did on my days while I was absent. So sorry, once again for not writing on time. Well until next time, I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background:  If You're Not The One- Daniel Bedingfield  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Up and left to go on vacation together. Weird huh? Yeah, well we had kinda sorta planned to go on vacation this week. But Leah and dad wanted to go to Florida or South Carolina. Mom disagreed and wanted to head north so the temperatures wouldn't be so hot. Me, well I agreed to stay home or travel north also. So, we thought well why don't Leah and dad go on a vacation and then mom and I could. Well, probably is, dad is the money man. So yeah, they left and headed who knows where and will return who knows when. Just know that they have to return by Monday cause Leah works. Mom and I would love to go on vacation together up north, but dad just left us some money and then the car might be an issue on traveling. I just find it weird but yet nice. So yeah, tonight and all weekend mom and I will bond..hehe! I love my mommy!      Moving on, today was yet another nice day. Woke up before noon. I did lounge around most of the day, dusted my room, and watched has half of the family left. My brother John's ex-girlfriend visited today and she told me about this cool place where she gets her hair cut. So tomorrow, I am off to get this long stuff growing on my head cut off. Yay me! After Leah and my dad left I took the trash out and took a shower so that my mom and I could go look at a desk. We went and saw the desk, it was nothing special so we left and went to Meijer. At Meijer we got our fluffly lil fur balls some food, picked us up some yumilicious Jones Sodas and were on our way home. While at home, we realized that Gretchy Sketch was outside meowing its head off. So my mom goes out to feed him, when she realizes it's not Gretch its poor precious lovable ROMY! Aw, my baby got out of the house (most likely from being in Leah's room when her screen fell out of the window). She was out the whole time we were running errands. She could have been kitty litter, but luckily she stayed out of the street and just sat on the back porch. After that incident, I watched some tv. My television watching is over so that is why I am here. I have had alot to think about today. Some good thoughts, some bad. Life can get pretty crazy. I find I have alot to work on. I am on a mission. A mission which I am going to succeed in. But yeah, today was just another day, kinda sorta...hehe!      Ok, now you get the picture that my family must be a bit different. Sure we have the issues like most families have, but they just left to go on vacation. But why am I complaining? I love it, I really do...just as long as they are safe. Well, nothing more for me to say here, so I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background: Are You Happy Now?-Michelle Branch  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sleep in until 2 in the afternoon? Only occassionally do I ever sleep in that late. I had a really good excuse. I was online until 3 am last night and then the storm woke me up early so that made me even more tired. It is not like I had plans to do anything today anyway. I did want to go swimming, but Leah said no...bummer. I have to admit, I do feel like my day was wasted. But I repeat, I didn't have anything schedule for today anyway. So give me a break. (don't even start singing the Kit-Kat commercial.)      Moving on, obviously nothing important happen today. Well, kinda something did. Our internet was out all day until just about an hour ago. I thought I was going to die. I couldn't check my mail, I couldn't talk to anyone online, I thought I wasn't going to even fill out my blog for the day. What a nightmare! But thankfully, good ol' Joshua pulled through for me. He is awesome with his computer knowledge. Well, compared to me at least. Supposedly we needed to install some SpyBot thingy. Joshua had the disk for us to do so. So by 6:30 this afternoon, my mom and I were on our way over to pick up the disk at Joshua's house. As soon as we returned home my mom began to work on the pc. We first thought it wasn't going to work. But hours later it did! THANK YOU JOSHUA! So yeah, that is all I did today. It was a very short day, and nothing got accomplished. So now here I sit and probably will have another late night just talking to peoples online.      Ok, maybe you are categorizing me as a lazy person now. Sorry, I was just really out of it today. Trust me, I will not make it into a daily thing. Another thing though that has made me happy this evening is the weather is nice and cool. Ahhh, my fall temperatures return. By the way, today will mark the 1yr. anniversary of me having braces. Six more months to go, the countdown begins.Well, nothing more to say, so I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background: Day Dreamin'- Tatyana Ali  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Loving the chicken quesadillas that Taco Bell serves. They are so yummy and absolutely delicious.  The sauce that is put in it is fantastico! That has got to be one of my favorite sauces next to the delicious tasting steak sauce and chipotlè sauce.  I put those sauces on everything.  I know I said I am on a very strict eating habit now, but I was asked out to lunch today and Taco Bell was the place of choice. Eating out was nice. I was asked by an old classmate of mine at the not so lovely Eagledale. So today was a happy day, thanks to Taco Bell!      Moving on, I was awaken at 11:00 am by the phone ringing in my ear. Sheesh, I always think the phone is ringing in a dream until it keeps going on and on. Yes, the phone call was for me for my lunch date.  I made plans to leave by 12:30. After I got off the phone, I made my way into the restroom to take my shower and then get ready for my outting.  As I was in the process of that I got online to see if anyone was on. I got an IM from good ol' Jeremiah saying he doesn't have his surgery, CONGRATULATIONS....for now. After that lil chit chat, I finished getting ready and before ya know it I was on my way to eat one of my favoritest meals ever.  As I have said previously, it was great. Then I was brought home around 2-ish. I waited and waited for Leah to get off the pc but she didn't so I fell asleep waiting for her. Then I woke up and watched Roswell.  I was asked by my dad to go to the Indians game tonight, but I refused cause it's icky sticky hot. So Leah and him just went. I did go over to Big Lots with my mom to get a trash can and then we went driving. We drove to see one of my mom's many old houses off of Kessler. We also cruised around some other gorgeous houses. If I don't get to move to the country, I am moving into one of the ones I saw. Driving we did see some heavy trash pick-up stuff that had these old windows in them. Mom wanted me to put them in the trunk so she could hang them on the cottage since she loves that country,rustic look. So I did as she asked. I like digging through peoples trash, as long as they have some good stuff...hehe. After that we drove back home. I watched like one and half Lifetime movies. They were good. But then, you know what? Time for Big Bro. Sorry, Jeremiah, I like the show. But I am strong enough not to lower myself into being like them. Just because I watch it, doesn't mean I agree with it. Well, I watched that and then it ended which leaves me to sitting here.      Ok, I don't think I have much more to comment on. But as I am sitting here at my desk, I see some origami (sp?). Leah has been practicing and she left her mess in my room, sheesh. Looks like Miss Brè has some cleaning to do, again. Well, I am hot so I need to cool down with the fan blowing on me, so I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background:  Passenger Seat- Stephen Speaks  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Shopping at a thrift store. Yes, at one point I was one of the embarrassed ones to show my face in a store like that. But in all honesty, there is some good stuff there that is more in my price range. Leah and I went to a two thrift stores today, Good Will and Unique Thrift Store. She found some great stuff in good condition and it was even name brand items.  I was kinda jealous, cause the stuff she bought was cute. She did buy me some toe socks though which I am gonna cut the toes out and make arm cover thingys.  She found two pairs of capris and a nice shirt. We did find some cute skirts for church, but they had some holes which was a bummer. But the only probably there is the people speak Spanish over the microphone thing.Ugh, that also is another blog, some other time. GO BACK TO MEXICO!      Moving on, today was a good Monday. I woke up at a reasonable time. I had some errands I needed to run and I got them done. My parents were going to go up  to Noblesville to take a couch to my grandma's. Since they were doing that I was going to have Leah take me out to Khols. Yes, Khols is a store I shop at often. Anywho, she agreed to take me. But did she really have a choice? So after my parents left we headed off to Khols. We picked up what I wanted at Khols and then walked to A.J. Wright and Dots. Just looked around at some stuff. After that is when we headed to the thrift stores, and you all know how that went. We did manage to eat some Wendy's at the sickest Wendy's I have ever seen. Ugh, someone needs to clean the place. I hate it when someone working there has there friends in there too. Cause then they get distracted and don't do their job. I just had root beer and fries. No way was I going to trust them to make my hamburger. I was even caution about getting ketchup cause coke was all spilled,pickles were on the floor, napkins everywhere, straws all out of the wrappers. Disgusting. One customer came in and he said that he would have someone clean up the mess for me. I was like thank you. But he either didn't mention it to them or they just didn't listen. At least he was being thoughtful, I guess. Well, after all of that, we came home and the parents weren't home yet. But just about 5 minutes later they showed up. We carried some stuff they got to the cottage and decided to go out to eat. I was like ok, I only had fries anyway. But I am not trying to eat so much. So today was a bad day in that area. We went to Max and Erma's. I had cheese fries and some Rasberry Tea. Today was just a fries kinda day. It was delicious and the tea was awesome. I had like 5 glasses. I better wear my Good Nights tonight or my Depends. Hahaha, it's a joke ya'll. I can control my bladder.   Then when the meal was over we came back home. Leah asked me to rearrange her room with her. I helped alittle bit. But that is alot of work. Finally, I wanted to take a break which leaves me to sitting here.      Ok, this was a complaining kind of blog. I let out a bit about my dislike toward Mexicans and then I complained of how the Wendy's was dirty. Is that so wrong? I think not. I did put in a good word for thrift stores..hehe. Well, I think it is time for a restroom break, so I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background:  Dare You to Move- Switchfoot 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tell about my fear of going to car washes? Yes, of all the things I am scared of going to the car wash. My dad had asked my sister and I to wash the car today. But washing the car is really hard stuff for us. So I told Leah if she has $10 we could drive over to Mikes Car Wash and get it done and dad will think we did it. Well, she agreed. She agreed to it only if I go.  I was like ok, 2 minutes of torture isn't as bad as 1 hour or more. So my dad came in the house to check his E-bay stuff, and we made our get-a-away then. So yeah, we go through the car wash and I have my choking spells and what not. But I survived. Maybe I survived because Scooby Doo and Mickey were washing themselves too, so I felt safe. Well we make it back home to find dad hasn't moved from the computer. Mission accomplished. Leah finishes vaccuuming out the car and all goes well.      Moving on, today was an okay kinda day. I woke up a little after 9 to see if we were going to church. Mom said no, so I went back to bed til 12. Then I got up, looked through some ads and then that is when the whole car washing situation came. That got done and dad asked us to go get him some chicken at KFC. Of course, we did. Then I finally got around to taking my shower when I heard my brother Dustin was coming over with his girlfriend Krista. After my shower, dad said he had some places to go and if I wanted to go I could. I did, and so I asked Leah too. But as we were about to leave Dustin shows up followed by Krista. So Leah stayed home and my dad and I went out.  We went to Pep Boys and Meijer.  Dad didn't get what he was looking for a Pep Boys but he did buy some car air freshener that smells very good.  By the way, my dad did question what Leah and I wash the car with and thought maybe he should buy us  some special kind of soap to help us. I told him not to bother with it cause we dont't wash the car that much. Sheeeeesh, that was a close one. Anyway, we go to Meijer to see if they might have had what he was looking for, but no luck. So we went back home to find Leah, Dustin, Krista, and Leah's friend Shannon playing Phase 10. I just went to my room and slept. I thought maybe we were going to get ice cream but dad ordered them all pizza so I assumed ice cream was out of the picture. But o well, they ate all the pizza which helped me from the temptation to eat it. So now it comes to me just sitting here writing this out.       Ok, well now you know of another phobia of mine. I am a pretty strange individual. Well, nothing more to say tonight, so I am outtie!      Music Playin' in The Background-  All Cried Out-Allure  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>