<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Only 2 of the 23 Swift Boat mates support Kerry for President.  A new book entitled "Unfit for Command" is coming out soon, written by Swift Boat mates of Kerry telling the real truth of Kerrys vietnam tour.  They say that two of the three purple hearts received by Kerry were for  self-inflicted  wounds.&nbsp; LOL.&nbsp; What an idiot.  Also that most of his video from Vietnam is fraudulent, in that scenes were re-enacted.  The video put together by the Republican National Committee is priceless.&nbsp; Indisputable video evidence of Kerry going back and forth on issues.  Jeez, this guy is starting to look like a real flake job.  Yeah, this is who we want leading our country.&nbsp; A man that constantly changes his stance, a man that fakes war videos, a man that inflicts wounds on himself and gets medals for it, and most of all, a man that throws like a girl.  This guy should be running for President of France.&nbsp;  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Al Sharpton spoke tonight at the Democratic National Convention.  ...need I say more.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Apparently John "Nancy Boy" Kerry has acted before his sperm audition.  According to the man that took over Swift Boat charges when Kerry left:   " Kerry would revisit ambush locations for reenacting combat scenes where he would portray the hero, catching it all on film.&nbsp; Kerry would take movies of himself walking around in combat gear, sometimes dressed as an infantryman walking resolutely through the terrain.&nbsp; He even filmed mock interviews of himself narrating his exploits.&nbsp; A joke circulated among Swiftees was that Kerry left Vietnam early not because he received three Purple Hearts, but because he had recorded enough film of himself to take home for his planned political campaigns ."  WHAT A LOSER!!!!!!!!!!  The more that comes out about this guy, the weaker he looks.  The liberals hate Bush so much they are blinded to how much of a pussy their nominee is. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       >   &nbsp;  John Kerry once tried out for a part in a movie.&nbsp; Kerry, tried out for the part of a sperm on the old Woody Allen film, "Everything You Wanted To Know About Sex...But Were Afraid To Ask".   Kerry did not get the part.&nbsp; Casting directors claimed he lacked the testicular fortitude to accurately portray a male excretion.              
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Is Hillary a robot? or rather a fem-bot?&nbsp; Her loud, monotoned deliverance of her brief speech and introduction of slick willie hurt the Jimmys ears.&nbsp; After Bush is re-elected, this fembot is going to seek and most likely win the democrat nomination in 2008.&nbsp;&nbsp; Danger! Danger! Danger Will Robinson!   The Gorester is still living in 2000 as most of his speech contained references to the 2000 election.&nbsp; Get over it already Al, you lost dude, no matter how long you cry about it.   Jimmy Carter spoke...I nodded off on the couch.   Bill Clinton was his usual rousing self.&nbsp; Although I did not agree with most of his points, he is a great speaker and delivered his speech well.&nbsp; If this guy was running against Bush, the grand ol party would be in trouble.&nbsp; Fortunately, we have a dorky guy that throws like a girl and has taken no stand on any issues as the democrat nominee.   Dorks have no place in the white house, see Jimmy Carter.   An MSNBC poll suggests Kerry is losing ground to Bush because people have no idea where Kerry stands on many issues.&nbsp; Also, Kerry has no idea where he stands on many issues.   &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some official raghead in Iran threated to "wipe Israel from the earth" today if Israel proceeded with plans to attack Iranian nuclear development plants.&nbsp; He called Israel the United States' "wild dog".&nbsp;   Throw some milk bones in Tehran and let the dog loose.  Bring it on, camel jockeys.&nbsp; I would love to see Israel flex some military muscle.&nbsp; With America right next door in Iraq, now is the time.  Ive been wanting revenge on these fuckin raghead pussies since the hostage crisis in 80'.&nbsp; 25 years is a long wait for the Jimmy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The DNC opening tonight in Boston has signed a parade of weaklings, whiners and cheaters.  Former President Jimmy Carter will make a speech tonight.&nbsp; Jimmy is arguably the WEAKEST president of all time.  Al Gore will speak tonight also.&nbsp; Al, aka the King Of Whiners, will undoubtedly whine about something tonight.&nbsp; Hopefully, he will find that "lock-box" he spoke of so frequently in 2000 and put himself in it.&nbsp; Major pharmaseutical companies have been losing money on sleeping&nbsp;aides&nbsp;ever since the Al started selling his speeches.  Slick Willie himself will be on hand tonight also as the headliner.&nbsp; Bill is actually a very good public speaker, I will watch when he comes on.&nbsp; Guess he cant give advice to Kerry on how to get away with boning an female intern in the oval office.&nbsp; Bill: " I did not have sexual relations with that woman."&nbsp; Then again, with the way Kerry throws a ball, he may be looking for a male intern for oval office interludes.&nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Whats up peeps?&nbsp; My name is Jimmy.&nbsp; Ive been around before.&nbsp; I grew uninterested in the news for a while, but now that the election campaigns are heating up, I figured the Jimmy should return.  Jimmy is a republican that enjoys slapping the face of the liberal idiot.&nbsp; You know the liberal idiot dont you?&nbsp; The ones that blame the president for every bad thing in their lives.&nbsp; Attention liberal idiot: nobody forced you to drop out of high school, have 6 bastard kids and live off welfare.&nbsp; Yeah I know this doesnt apply to all liberals, but it does comprise a hefty portion of them.  If Jimmy has offended anyone, please tell someone who cares. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Throwing like a girl isnt a bad thing, if youre a girl.&nbsp; Perhaps John Kerry took throwing lessons from his wife.&nbsp; She showed him how to pitch once, then when he asked again, she told him to shove it.   As a republican, Kerry wasnt getting my vote anyway, but seriously, do you liberals want someone who throws like a girl to occupy the white house?&nbsp; How embarrassing.&nbsp; Hopefully AHHH-NULD will call Kerry a girlie-man too, after last nights limp wristed toss, the moniker applies.   Theres just something very untrustworthy about a man that throws like that.&nbsp; In my opinion, the way a man throws a ball, any ball, tells you a lot about him.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Top Ten McGreevey jokes:   10    New Jersey state bird changed to the swallow   9    New Jersey turnpike renamed Hershey highway   8    New Jersey raises terror alert level to lavender   7    we know he didn't like bush, but this is ridiculous   6    now we know why mcgreevey enjoyed "polling" so much   5    what does mcgreevey and the Israeli navy have in common? Jewish seaman.   4    New Jersey dept. motor vehicles to now call rear end accidents, a mcgreevey   3    gives new meaning to stuffing the ballot box   2    Post headline...mcgreevey goes down!   1    Shouldn't take mcgreevey long to get out of the governors mansion, he's already got his shit packed! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Kerry is so incredibly boring, dull, and uninspiring.  I cant believe this guy is running for President. You democrats are really reaching with this idiot.  I predict Bush wins in a landslide. Some may be unhappy with his iron-handed or unilateral decisions. But in times like these, that is exactly what we need; and the people of the U.S. will realize that come election time. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>