<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      According to an article published in Aljazeera Kerry didn't have anything new to say about the situation in Iraq.&nbsp; He vowed to maintain troops in Iraq, which is what Bush has vowed to do as well.&nbsp; Kerry does stress acquiring more help and international participation.&nbsp; This differs from what the democratic party would like, which is the immediate and full withdraw of our troops.&nbsp; More and more of the companies involved in rebuilding Iraq are having their workers kidnapped.&nbsp; This has caused several companies to pull out.&nbsp; Unfortunately this has sent the signal to all of these fanatic groups that this type of operation is working and will only encourage them to do more of the same.&nbsp; They want all foreign occupiers out, no matter if they are here to help rebuild Iraq or trying to get a new government setup.&nbsp; My guess is these are the people that want to setup another dictatorship.&nbsp; As far as the companies rebuilding efforts go I could see some frustration over why all of these companies were offered the work instead of local contractors.&nbsp; They may not have all of the modern equipment, but it's just something they may be thinking when kidnapping these workers.&nbsp; It's obvious we need another plan.&nbsp; Our allies are backing out one by one and pulling their forces out.&nbsp; Pretty soon we will be the only ones left and the beheadings will continue without our withdrawal.  Falluja has heated up again as well.&nbsp; US air strike killed 13 Iraqis.&nbsp; We have injured civilians with these air strikes and flattened homes.&nbsp; This is just another wrench in the works.  Bottom line is there is no magic cure for this situation.&nbsp; It's going to get worse before it gets better.&nbsp; We have to get a native security force together as quickly as possible so we can start our withdrawal.&nbsp; We are obviously not helping the "peace" process and getting an interim government in place that will work.&nbsp; We simply can't force our will on them, it's obviously not working.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been thinking and looking back at previous wars and what the people of the nation were doing.&nbsp; I read something that disheartened me in one of Howard Zinn's books; "Howard Zinn on War".&nbsp; He's talking about the Vietnam war and how it was started.&nbsp; It's all summed up in one short paragraph: "Congress -- with its traditional cowardice, and based on lies told by President Lyndon Johnson, Secretary of State Dean Rusk, and Secretary of Defense Robert McNamara about the supposed attacks on American vessels in the Gulf of Tonkin in 1964 -- had given LBJ a blank check for mass murder."  Is the scenario sounding a little too familiar?&nbsp; Those that don't learn from history are bound to repeat it.&nbsp; Now the question has to be; why are we back here?&nbsp; Why did we let Bush get away with everything when he gave us so little to go on?&nbsp; The frenzy of 9/11 clouded our mind at first so Afghanistan was a given.&nbsp; The pain was much too real yet and it gave us an enemy with a face.&nbsp; Something we desperately needed or at least needed to believe at the time.  Now what about Iraq though?&nbsp; No hard evidence, intelligence briefings that were years old, no ties to al-Qaida; there were talks between the two but Saddam looked at al Qaida as the biggest threat to his regime.&nbsp; They hated each other from what I've understood.&nbsp; Was 9/11 still so close to us that we were still blinded by rage?&nbsp; Are we still too close to that point and if so who will be the next target?       
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have to give credit to Israel for at least one officials willingness to exhaust all diplomatic solutions regarding Iran's nuclear program.   "All diplomatic efforts should be&nbsp;exhausted before considering more drastic measures to stop Iran's nuclear programme." said Army chief of staff General Moshe Yaalon. &nbsp;"Political pressure certainly has potential, just as it worked on Libya. And this must be exhausted first of all, in my view."&nbsp;   Is there any way for Bush to classify them as terrorists?&nbsp; Afterall some al-Qaeda members have been allowed to pass through. According to resent inspections there is some evidence of a nuclear weapons program that could be used against Iran.  Iran has denied that they have any nuclear weapons programs and that their program is strictly for energy research only.&nbsp; They said they signed the NPT and would allow UN inspectors in as they have signed for that as well.&nbsp; Afterall Israel has not signed the NPT so I don't know what they're complaining about.  Now here's the way I see it.&nbsp; Israel and the US will push for more UN inspections.&nbsp; I don't think Bush could do the same thing he did in Iraq which was accusations without anything backing it up, even if he did declare it a terrorist regime.&nbsp; Iran is not on the 'Coalition of the Willing' list which puts them in a unfavorable light in Bush's eyes.&nbsp; Afterall if they're not with us, they're against us, or something to that affect.&nbsp;&nbsp; The trick will be to keep the hard liners in check.&nbsp; Should they take control it may cause Iranians to flock to their country in a patriotic surge, similar to what happened in the US after 9/11, and back any actions they may deem appropriate, again such as 9/11.   Here's some additional information on the evidence that has been gathered:   urlLink http://www.cfr.org/background/iran_curtail.php         
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The latest buzz going around is not only do we plan on still occupying Afghanistan and Iraq, we now may go after Iran because "U.S. 9/11 commission. It claimed Iran allowed eight al-Qaida future airplane hijackers to pass through Iran from Afghanistan between seven and 11 months prior to the attacks on America."  Here are some excerpts from the report:   "In late 1991 or 1992, discussions in Sudan between al Qaida and Iranian operatives led to an informal agreement to cooperate in providing support if only training actions carried out primarily against Israel and the United states long afterward, senior al Qaida operatives and trainers traveled to Iran to receive training in explosives."   "Our knowledge of the international travels of the al Qaida operatives selected for the 9/11 operation remains fragmentary. But we now have evi=dense suggesting that 8 to 10 of the 14 Saudi “muscle”operatives traveled into or out of Iran between October 2000 and February 2001.121."   &nbsp;There are many more that point to the cooperation of al-Qaida and Iran.&nbsp; Now to throw fuel on the fire, get a load of this from the NY Times:   "Iran has broken the U.N. nuclear watchdog's seals on centrifuge equipment and resumed building the devices, which are key to making nuclear weapons, in a show of defiance against international efforts to monitor its program, diplomats said Tuesday."   Now the magic question is are we going to do anything about it?&nbsp; More appropriately is Bush going to do anything about it.&nbsp; Is he going to&nbsp;ride the fear of terrorism and gamble that people won't want to switch presidents if there is another possible threat or even put off the elections?&nbsp; I don't think Bush will be able to pull anything off this close to election and would more than likely have to go through "proper channels" this time such as brining it to the UN and making the case Iran is breaking the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty.&nbsp; I'm sure&nbsp;the US Jewish population and Israel will start putting pressure on&nbsp;their buddy Bush since Iran is a regime that denies Israel's right to exist.&nbsp; Does anyone think they can convince the UN to do anything?&nbsp; This will be the next hot spot to watch out for I'm sure.       
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here is one of many horror stories you read about in some political discussion groups.&nbsp; I do not agree with them on many levels.&nbsp; I believe they have the right to defend themselves, but no right putting the security "fence" where it currently is.&nbsp; Can you imagine waking up one day and finding out that your whole neighborhood has been "fenced" in and you now have to go through a checkpoint to exit and leave your home?&nbsp; Cut off from everything you know and what little "freedom" you did have is now gone.  Here is what I received in the good 'ol inbox today:   In one day, the Israeli occupying forces (IOF) arrested two young girls, after raiding their homes and terrorizing them and their families, leading both girls, younger than 15 years of age, into the military jeep in their pajamas, despite the begging and cries of their families. Aseel Al Hendi, born on October 10, 1989 and a ninth grade student at the Al Fatemiya School in Nablus, was arrested on the dawn of June 16, after large forces of the Israeli occupation surrounded her family's house and ordered all dwellers to come out barefooted with their house gowns. Aseel begged the soldiers to give her time to wear proper clothes and some shoes, but they were deaf to her cries. Then the barbaric interrogation of the mother and Aseel's young siblings, the oldest is 14, with the soldiers shoving the mother's shoulder with the butts of their rifles and shouting at them. The horrified children were too afraid to even breathe. After checking everybody's ID card, they found out that Aseel was only 15 years old, but that did not prevent them from leading her into the military jeep along with her father, leaving the mother behind crying and begging the soldiers to let her child wear at least some shoes. Al Hendi's mother said her daughter is considered one of the best students in her class, enjoys reading and has interests in computers. She was hoping to travel abroad to pursue her postgraduate studies. At the same night, the Israeli forces had a date with another young flower to pick in the middle of night, and in the same cruelty, they advanced to the Rafidia neighborhood, where they surrounded the house of Al Kokhen family and arrested their 15-year-old daughter Majd. Majd was born on April 7, 1989 and with her arrest, she was deprived of participation in the honoring ceremony of her scout group at the Al Fatemiya School. IPC correspondent said that the Israeli forces surrounded the Al Kokhen family house and then ordered all the dwellers of the house to leave immediately. Afterwards, the soldiers barbarically checked the family members' ID cards, before asking about Majd in a sharp tone, as the Israeli soldier was holding a list of names in his hand. Majd, who was arrested by the occupying forces and thrown into the military jeep along with her father, is under the international standard of childhood, so she is considered a child. The IOF troops argue that she was two months older than 15! Majd's mother watched in silent tears as the jeep that has her daughter and husband drive away to the western part of the city, praying that it won't be the last time she sees them. According to Al Kokhen's teachers, she was also a top student, and led the basketball team of her school. She has also artistic and sports interested, in addition to her preparation to join the "Seeds of Peace" international organization for her beliefs in the virtue of peace. After 24 hours of detention and interrogation at Howara military base, both Aseel's and Majd's fathers were released, but without their daughters, and later they were both transferred to the notorious "Al Ramleh" prison, according to the complaints office "Hamoked" in Jerusalem. The Association of Prisoners and Ex-Detainees "Hossam" says that the Israeli occupying authorities torture even the children inside the Israeli jails and concentration camps, pointing out that child prisoners are frequently tortured, and this was particularly obvious in the "Etzion" prison, where children were being beaten and placed in solitary confinement cells, after being stretched all night on barbed razor wire in the prison's yard. Also, the children are also deprived of hot water and bathroom visits, due to which hygienic problems spread among them, especially when treatment is not provided and cleaning materials are not present. According to a report by the Palestinian National Information Center (PNIC) in Gaza, the number of children that have been imprisoned in Israeli jails has reached more than 2,500 children, 463 of them are still inside prisons. The ratio of children among the Palestinian prisoners is 7.6%. 243 children are still detained pending trial, while 22 others are "administratively detained" without charge or trial. As for the female children, they are sent immediately to the infamous "Neveh Tirtza" prison, which has frequently witnessed since April 2001 attacks on the Palestinian female prisoners there by the Israeli wardens and shock troopers. During these attacks, their personal possessions were confiscated, and some of them were placed in solitary confinement, such as the prisoner Soad Ghazal, 17, who was placed in a solitary confinement cell of two square meters. PNA Internationbal Press Center   This story can also be found on Aljazeera.net.&nbsp; Note you will not find anything on the Haaretz.com site...funny that.&nbsp; Now one could dispute the security fence all together and argue that England had no right to declare Palestine to become the new state of Israel.&nbsp; They didn't own the land so it wasn't theirs to give.&nbsp; There are only two reasons why the US government and Israel get along for now.&nbsp; The US goverment is using Israel for it's purposes and Israel is using the US for it's own&nbsp;purposes.&nbsp; What exactly do they think is going to happen when we're through with each other?&nbsp;&nbsp;I guess we all can be happy here in our safe and secure homes knowing we're very lucky not to be 15 year old girls in the West Bank.    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last night Catherine watched "Uncovered: The Whole Truth About the Iraq War" by Moveon.org. The effect was as expected. We all know Bush and crew lied about the circumstances getting us into the war. This just sheds some light on what exactly was lied about and how the language and intelligence changed as the war progressed. It goes though why Iraq was not and immanent threat to the United States. Saddam was smart enough to destroy his weapons of mass destruction as he wanted to keep his regime in place and him at the head of it. Why would he do anything so stupid as keeping the weapons around to jeopardize that? As time went on the language changed from 'they have weapons of mass destruction' to 'we know they had developed programs for weapons of mass destruction'. The video takes you through their change in language as the war progresses and there are no weapons found. Now here's the other thing that gets my blood boiling. We impeached Clinton for lying about sexual acts while he was in office, not to mention spent a ton of tax payer dollars on it because Star had a hard-on for him. Bush lied to congress and us to get into a war with Iraq that wasn't necessary. Which here seems to be a more sensible thing to impeach for. Lying about sexual acts that had no repercussion or involved anyone getting killed, or getting us into an unnecessary war causing the death of our troops, damaging the already fragile view of America, and making us look like the terrorist. Now lets look at the definition of terrorism, well...at least one version of it. Terrorism is defined by the FBI as: "Terrorism is the unlawful use of force or violence against persons or property to intimidate or coerce a government, the civilian population, or any segment thereof, in furtherance of political or social objectives." Now lets look at this. We unlawfully used force against Iraq and it's civilian population as we lied about the reason to go to war and without proof of Saddam's involvement with Al Qaida and other terrorist organizations. As a matter of fact Osama and Saddam hated each other. Saddam didn't like giving up his control for anything. Saddam viewed Osama as the grates threat to his regime. I'm not saying Saddam wasn't an evil man, but just want to put things in perspective. We did use it to coerce the civilian population, to overthrow Saddam, even though we're still fighting some of the civilian population. We did it to further our political and social objectives, i.e. there is a lot of oil and money for US contractors to be made there. If you think no one is getting kick-backs from it you're nuts. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Is Bush going to bring the draft back to active duty or worse?  A scary thought that’s already down on paper.  Did you know that out of all the congressmen only one has a son in military service in Iraq?  This explains why they don’t think it’s a bad thing.  They have nothing to risk.  They have the money and the pull to keep their children out of harms way.  For poor America there is no such luxury and many sign up for the benefits of training because they are so poor it’s the only way for them to get out.  This is especially true for young black men. There have been web sites that have been pulled down because they were drawing negative publicity.  There is a copy of one here:  urlLink http://www.thememoryhole.org/mil/defendamerica-draftboards.htm . As stated on the site they are looking for volunteers “If a military draft becomes necessary.” There are also two bills in the Senate (S.89) and House (H.R. 136) that would require military service for all men and women between the ages of 18 and 25 for a period of two years, but at the discretion of the President the period of military service may be extended. S.89 right in the first paragraph it states “…defense by requiring that all young persons in the United States, including women, perform a period of military service or a period of civilian service in furtherance of national defense…” S.89 requires anyone between the ages of 18 and 26 perform a period of national service.  “Service” refers to one of two things: 1. “as a member of an active or reserve component of the uniformed services” 2. “in a civilian capacity that, as determined by the President, promotes the national defense, including national community service and homeland security” Selection for military service is based on the needs of the uniformed services and states “the President shall—“ 1. “determine the number of person covered by subsection (a) (referring to the age) whose services is to be performed as a member of an active or reserve component of the uniformed services…” 2. “select the individuals among those persons who are to be inducted for military service under this Act.” For civilian service “Persons covered by subsection (a) (again referring to age) who are not selected for military service under subsection (d) (see the above 1 and 2) shall perform their national service obligation under this Act in a civilian capacity pursuant to subsection (b)(2) (referring to the form of national service; civilian or uniformed)” H.R. 136 is pretty much identical in content.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is a copy of a letter regarding the security monstrosity that Israel is constructing illegally. The response was basically put they supported the construction of a wall. I e-mailed back with my arguments and they chose not to respond to them.  Supporting the construction of Israel's security wall is a step in the wrong direction if there is ever to be peace between the Israeli and Palestinian people. The wall violates international and humanitarian law and has already been condemned by the United Nations. The path of the wall goes beyond Israel's borders, cutting off the most fertile land from the Palestinian farmers. This has robbed them of their Livelihood and ability to take care of their families. They are forced to go through security checkpoints if they are even granted the documents to do so, which in many cases they have not been given to the farmers that need them. Even with the documents they are forced to wait for hours before they are even let through and may end up not gaining access at all. The precepts of democracy demand that we condemn land expropriations, home demolitions, illegal arrests, beatings, torture and the continued Israeli defiance of UN resolutions, the flouting of the Geneva Convention; and decades of legal and social discrimination against the Arab population. The UN and World Bank have issued reports about the rampant malnourishment and the epidemic of anemia in the territories caused by the strangling of Palestinian society by the Israeli Occupation Forces.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Iraq. Let’s talk about Iraq. I’ve had discussions about the occupation and more fighting. I hate to say it, but I think we should just pull out now, or we won’t anytime soon. The longer we stay in, the more intense this is going to get. It is speculated that Muqtada al-Sadr's forces used the cease-fire to stockpile weapons and prepare for this new round of violence. They are attacking U.S., British, and Iraqi security forces. According to Aljazeera’s correspondent in Najaf fighting broke out when mortar rounds, killing one and wounding four others hit the hospital. Apparently the casualties were all hospital staff. The body count was at least 15 Iraqis killed and 102 wounded. On the US side 1 soldier was killed and 5 wounded. There is more violence to report on in al-Mahawil, the road linking Al-Adhamiya and al-Mansour, Balad, and last but not least, Falluja. Let's look at both sides of the coin. Interim Iraqi interior minister Falah al-Naquib issued a statement that his government would not negotiate with al-Sadr and would continue fighting against him. Now I don’t have exact quotes here, but wouldn’t “the people’s” government sound better than “his” government? I mean if I were an Iraqi citizen and someone came up on TV declaring it “his” government I’d feel more excluded than I already would be that I didn’t select the government in the first place. That’s just me though. Not surprisingly a senior aid of al-Sadr’s stated that they will resort to military operations if the siege of Najaf by US forces is not immediately lifted. Knowing us, as in U.S., do I really have to say what’s going to happen next? O.K., I will. The interim government (our government) isn’t going to back down and neither is the US. Now the longer this drags on the more and more people will sign up for al-Sadr’s side (if they don't sign for Al-Qaeda first.) This is going to turn into Iraqi was take two. Vietnam anyone? 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      According to the "President" we are much safer than we were on 9/11 of 2001. Is this really true? How are much safer are we? Better airport security with still underpaid people? These same airports that now tell employees to shuffle people through at a faster pace to keep the line moving instead of causing delays for more secure checks? We keep hearing we are safer, but somehow I find no comfort in that. Even going to NY Grand Central you see the national guard there, but they really aren't looking out for anything? It didn't appear so when I was there. They were more interested in talking with other workers or security. OK, they may have been discussing something of importance, but anyone could still walk in there and blow it up. All they would have to do is wear the bomb and be willing to die for a cause. Now who would be silly enough to do that? It wouldn't even have to be grand central it could be on a train, and why not hit a few key bridges on I95 and 15? That would put a huge blow on CT/NY's transit systems and make life really unpleasant for a lot of people. It's easy to say we are safer than we were on 9/11, but I want the proof. We won't have that until these new systems are tested by another attack.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Has anyone noticed this campaign that women's issues have taken a back seat? Not only on the Republican side, but surprisingly on the Democratic side as well. So what do we know about our two candidates and where they stand on womens issues? After a lot of digging this is what I came up with. To me it seems like George wants to model today's women after the oppressed women in the middle-east.  Bush: 1) Wants to ban abortion. Sabotaging Policies that Protect Womens Health and Reproductive Rights 2) Rolling Back Policies That Guarantee Equal Opportunity for Women at Work 3) Backtracking on Policies That Guarantee Equal Opportunity for Girls and Women at School 4) Shortchanging Child Care and Other Supports Women Need to Maintain Self-Sufficiency 5) Starving Programs Women Need to Pay for Tax Cuts for the Wealthy 6) Weakening Efforts to Combat Violence Against Women and Help Its Victims  An excellent report can be found at: http://www.nwlc.org/pdf/AdminRecordOnWomen2004.pdf   Kerry: 1) "Clearly, this White House is more interested in appealing to its electoral base than it is in protecting women's health." 2) Voted repeatedly against the Partial Birth Abortion Ban 3) Will greatly expand after-school programs to serve 3.5 million children and fund a historic increase in the Child Care Tax Credit to meet the needs of overstretched parents. 4) Believe that we must make equal pay for equal work a reality, not a slogan. 5) Was an original co-sponsor of the Women's Health Equity Act, which ensures women's access to the highest quality and most advanced health care available. 6) Title IX has helped extend opportunity in education and athletics to millions of girls and women. John Kerry and John Edwards will defend Title IX and work to expand college opportunities for women. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>