<Blog>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I've had a pretty bad stomach virus for the past two days. I have like 0 strength and can hardly get out of bed. It really, really sucks. I've caught up on TV watching though. I can't eat anything substantial because it doesn't stay down. It's horrible.  Other than that, nothing's really been going on but I figured I'd update.  Maybe some more later.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It rained all day. It was one of the most miserable days I've ever known. I hated it a lot.  I'm not sure why, but it feels like something big is about to happen. I don't know whether it will be good or bad, all I know is that whenever I get this feeling in my stomach it means something is gonna happen. I guess we'll see.  July is almost over, which means soon there'll only be part of a month left until school. That isn't a good thing. However, for whatever reason, I have a good feeling about this school year, even though with my class as seniors the drama will inevitably be even worse than it's ever been. My schedule is insanely easy though, so that'll be a plus. I just hope it goes fast. I'm not really one for proms and parties and whatnot, and I probably won't even go to such things, so whatever. I haven't done much of my English work for the summer, I need to get on that.   I've been staying up until really early in the morning lately. I just sit on my computer and watch Full House. And I leave my fan on at night so it gets really cold in my room, and there's something comforting about it. It reminds me of fall, and I like fall.  Well that's all for now.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, today, I decided to start one of these things. I'm not sure why. I guess it's a combination of boredom and the fact that  urlLink Hey Mercedes  has one. Well, seeing as how I'm starting this kinda late into the summer, I will recap a little.  I am one year away from being done with high school forever, and thank God for that. My junior year was pretty enjoyable, however. I met the most amazing people ever and they know who they are (I love you all).I got to meet and become even better friends with people as a result of playing in the Talent Show. This year's talent show was one of the best experiences of my life. Then, Renaissance Night. While I still consider the night a joke and question its existence, I got to hang out with Ed for the whole school day and then perform with him in the night. With this Renaissance Night performance, a new acoustic band was formed (watch out for us, kids). That's really all there is to know about the school year.  The summer has been a pretty good one. I went to parties for the first time in a long time and I had such a great time (Thank you for everyone who invited me to graduation/birthday parties). I went on vacation, nothing eventful there. I played my "last" solo show in New Jersey on July 15, 2004 which was fun even though it didn't live up to my expectations. That pretty much brings us up to date.  I'm really tired of the drama that seems to radiate throughout this town. Everyone needs to either be nice or just leave. And threatening people isn't cool. It doesn't make people like you.  So, someone needs to go with me to see  urlLink Rilo Kiley  with me.  Oh, and check out  urlLink Grandaddy . They are better than most of what you listen to. Actually, that's just my opinion, but they are good.   Well, I think that's about it for now.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey  Just a quick little update.  If you want to listen to the songs from my solo show back on July 15th, I threw together a quick little site to host them. You can find it  urlLink here  Now, before you say, "Hey that looks like crap" (which some of you will anyway), realize it's only temporary so that people can hear the stuff because the site I'm making for real is pretty involved so there's no telling when it'll be done. For now, I'm gonna use the crap angelfire one to host songs. I'll post here when it's updated so you know to check it.  [rant]  Oh, and if you know in advance that you're not going to have anything nice to say about my music because:  A. You don't respect me  B. Your friends say I suck C. You don't like my kind of music D. You're just an all-around asshole E. All of the above  Then don't even bother listening and get yourself onstage and do better.  [/rant]  Later.  PS. Thank you to everyone who continues to support me and my music. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This post is meant to coincide with my previous post about Warped Tour.  Today, I went to my first ever Warped Tour. The bands were simply amazing but it would not have been the same if I was not in the company of two of the most amazing people ever.  Ed and Kelley are two of my bestest friends and I was so honored to be in their presence and to share such a wonderful event with them. They are the nicest, coolest, most amazing people I've had the pleasure to meet and it would not have been half as memorable a day if they were not there. I am so grateful for their friendship, and I don't know what I'd do without them.  I don't know many, if any, people that would put up with me and my idiosyncrasies for a whole day. I've said it once and I'll say it again: I   Seriously, these are the textbook definition of true friends. Take notes, kids...I mean it.   I could write so much more but I'm very tired.  Thank you both so much.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow. What a day. So we left for Hershey Park this morning. I didn't know what to expect, this being my first Warped Tour. All I can say: Wow.  The first band we saw was The Casualities. I have never heard anything worse than them in my life. Their rants about punk and what's not punk and how they're punk were boring. Hearing "I wanna see the biggest circle pit ever" a million and one times was boring. They annoyed me a lot.   The second band was *faints* Matchbook Romance. So unbelivably good. The bassist is officially my favorite person. So good. I loved them before but I don't think there's a word for how I feel about them now. I can hardly remember any of their set so I won't even try.  Then, came Sugarcult. I like them, not as much as the other bands but they were pretty good.  Then, was New Found Glory. Oh...my...God. I didn't expect the crowd to go half as crazy as they did. Set included Hit or Miss, Something I Call Personality, Understatement, My Friends Over You, All Downhill From Here...I don't remember anything else. James from Get Up Kids/Reggie and the Full Effect/some New Amsterdams joined them onstage which was awesome. The crowd though. Insane is the only word  Then, was Coheed and Cambria. We discussed on the way home how we didn't know whether they'd live up to their fantastic albums in a live situation. Boy, did they ever. Set included: Everything Evil, Favor House Atlantic, That song that starts "New Jersey bound..." (I can't think of the title). I don't remember what else they played.  Then, was Taking Back Sunday. Oh my. So amazing. Set included Set Phasers to Stun, Bonus Mosh Part 2, Great Romances, Cute Without the E, You're So Last Summer, Decade Under the Influence...Again, I can't remember anything else. There was something so healing about screaming along with Adam and Fred. I don't usually get that emotionally into it, but I felt so relieved of all the shit that's happened in the past from their performance.   After Taking Back Sunday played, Yellowcard came on and we left :-D. We walked around for a bit, got some free stuff and various merch. Good stuff. I got my program signed by the bassist and drummer of Matchbook Romance and by The Matches. As we were walking I hear "Giving Up" by Silverstein and I looked over and they were playing one of the smaller stages so we went over. After "Giving Up" they played their last song, which happened to by my favorite: "Bleeds No More". Then we sat on the bleachers and watched the insaneness of some not so good bands.  Ie. Lars Fredricksen and the Bastards, Tiger Army, Story of the Year, etc.   After waiting, more walking, we went to see Fall Out Boy. Oh my God again. They were so so so so so so so good. Again, they were a band that I loved before but can't even describe how I feel now. They were joined onstage at one point by Matchbook Romance's drummer and later Matchbook Romance's bassist. Needless to say...amazing.   Fall Out Boy was the last band that was worth seeing so it was then that I bid my fond farewell to the 10th annual Warped Tour.   This was easily, not only the best concert I've been to, but also the best day/night I've had in a long time. I feel like I'm forgetting so much so this post may be edited in the morning.  Later. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm bored so I stole this from Nick.  LAST PERSON WHO...  x. Slept in your bed: Me x. Saw you cry: My mom x. Made you cry: Elliot Smith x. You shared a drink with: I drink alone (like George Thorougood) x. You went to the movies with: My family x. You went to the mall with: I don't even remember x. Yelled at you: I don't know x. Sent you an e-mail: Some guy that I won something from on Ebay  HAVE YOU EVER...  x. Said "I love you" and meant it?: I've never not meant it...seriously people who throw around "I love you"s aren't cool. x. Gotten in a fight with your pet: Sure? x. Been to California: No x. Been to Hawaii: No x. Been to Mexico: No x. Been to China: No x. Been to Canada: No x. Danced naked: all the time (read: no) x. Dreamed something really crazy and then it happened the next day: Not recently x. Wish you were the opposite sex: No way (read: yes) x. Had an imaginary friend: Yes. Still do...what now  RANDOM TID BITS...  x. Do you have a crush on someone: Yeah x. What book are you reading now: A Man For All Seasons (for school) x. Worst feeling in the world: Being woken up before you're ready, or in the middle of a good dream x. Future son's name: Octavian x. Do you sleep with a stuffed animal: Nope x. What's under your bed: Shoes, games, one of my guitars x. Favorite sports to watch: I don't watch any really x. Siblings: Nick x. Location- PA x. College plans: ESU x. Piercings: Nope x. Boyfriend/girlfriend: Nope  EXTRA STUFF...  x. Do you do drugs: No x. Do you drink: No x. Who is your best friend: I have multiple, I'm not gonna bother listing them so no one's feelings get hurt...everyone whom i love knows it x. What are you most scared of: Rejection and/or death x. What clothes do you sleep in: Lately, long pants (cause it's cold) and random t-shirts that i would never wear outside the house x. Where do you want to get married: I dunno. I would want an outdoor wedding with only the closest of family and friends. And Saves the Day would be the band.  x. Who do you really hate: Again, I don't want to say it here because I'm all about the love x. Do you drive: Yeah x. Do you have a job: For my parent's business x. Do you like being around people: Yes. Unless they annoy me x. Are you for world peace: Yes, but it won't happen  STUFF...  x. Have you ever liked someone you had no chance with: Well, there's no point in telling the story if you know the ending x. Have you ever cried over something someone of the opposite sex did: Yeah... x. Do you have a "type" of person you always go after: I don't think so x. Want someone you don't have right now: Yeah x. Are you lonely right now: Kinda but not really. Not as much as I've been in the past. x. Song thats stuck in your head a lot: Right now, Floater by everytime i die x. Do you want to get married: Yeah x. Do you want kids: Eventually  FAVORITE...  x. Room in house: mine x. Type(s) of music: Almost everything x. Band(s): I'm not gonna list my favorites, cause that'll take forever. Let's just say I am in love with Saves the Day. x. Color: Black x. Perfume or cologne: Banana x. Month: January x. Stone: My pet rock  IN THE LAST 72 HOURS, HAVE YOU...  x. Cried: No x. Bought something: Yeah x. Gotten sick: No x. Sang: Yeah x. Wanted to tell someone you loved them: Yeah x. Met someone new: No x. Missed someone: Yeah
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey.  I'm getting a haircut. Just so you know. I'm tired of my hair being crap.   That's all.  Oh, and I guess I lied about putting some songs on here. I never got around to it. Maybe at a later time.  Thank you.  Goodnight.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey.  Today was a good day! Unfortunately, I was unable to go to Gleni's graduation/going way party which I was sad about but I did get to hang out with Ashley, Mike, and Kelley and it was a lot of fun. Anytime spent with them is awesome and I was honored to be in their presence today. The only thing wrong with the day was the fact that Ed was unable to be there and he was missed. I felt really bad that he couldn't be there.   I'm not doing anything for the next two days, but then it will be time for Warped Tour. I am really looking forward to this (if you can't tell from my previous mentions of it). It's going to be a good time!  After that, I really have to get my English work done. I told myself I wouldn't put it off this year but this is the longest I've waited. So far, I've read 2 out of 3 books but really need to get my essays done.   Later on tonight or tomorrow I'm going to put the audio from my "last" solo show ever from July 15, 2004 in New Jersey on the internet. I also have DVD's of the show made (I don't know why anyone would want such a thing), but if you do let me know. I also have a surprise bonus song that I just recorded recently that I will also post eventually. I'm really starting to like keeping my solo career a more internet-based one with song random shows here and there. That way, in the time I'm not working on The Swingset Kids or The Frequency, I can post songs and whatnot. Also, with TV and Video coming up I can work on doing some crazy music videos and whatnot. I've also been known to do some (read: 2) solo shows via live audio stream on the internet so I may start doing that again. Should be fun.  As for The Swingset Kids, we're gonna do that EP and play shows and just be plain amazing. It's simple as that. I'm telling you, watch out for us. I started coming up with ideas for guitar for Ed's songs which we will work on the next time that we practice. I'm so happy to be working on originals. Covers are fun but originals are just so much funner. Good times.  Oh well, that's all for now.  Later. 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello.  So tonight Ed and I had band practice after a long long time. It was good. I'm really happy with the direction things are going. We worked on one of my songs (I'm really liking the bass Ed came up with for it) and he showed me some of his songs and I'm working on putting guitar to them right now. Should be awesome. Pretty soon we'll have an EP, or demo...whatever it's called nowadays. I'm really excited for that as well.   I'm also considering starting a website or something for my solo work. I would post songs and stuff. I don't plan on doing many solo shows, only a few every now and then because A.) I want to focus mainly on The Swingset Kids and The Frequency, and B.) I would rather the few solo performances I give to be special and not something that happens every week. I do plan on doing one before everyone leaves for college though so I'll keep everyone posted.   I still haven't even touched my English work. I really should get on that. The summer will be over before I know it and then I'll be screwed.  Warped tour in 4 days!!! Woooooo!!! I am really, really excited.  Well, that's all I have right now. I plan on going to bed early tonight. I'm always so tired lately.  Later.  
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey.   I haven't written for a while. I'm not sure why...not much to say I suppose. Well, I've been doing basically nothing except work lately. I'm really bored. I've been writing a lot of songs lately too.  I'm really tired of everyone being so two-faced and hypocritical. People in this town can be such jokes a lot of the time.   5 days until my first ever Warped Tour. I am super excited!! It is going to be a lot of fun.  School starts in about 25 days, which seems way too soon. I really don't want summer to end, even though I haven't really done much with it. It's gone wayyyyy too fast. Oh well.  I really don't have much else to say.  Later.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm feeling a little better. I'm still kinda sick but I'm well enough to at least move around the house.   I need money. I'm selling off some of my possessions (on Ebay, of course). If this doesn't work I'm either going to have to resort to auctioning off my organs or male prostitution.   I really don't have much to say today.   Be prepared for a Swingset Kids computer game. Oh my, it is going to be the best thing anyone has ever seen. I would explain it but it is more than worth the wait. I'll let you know when it's done.  I'm missing some people a lot.  Okay, I'm just rambling now so I'm gonna cut this off. Maybe more later.
    
</post>


</Blog>