<Blog>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      no more no cd key. lol  look for us, b/c we are coming in strong. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome our new member, FS-SproXy, he is from sweden.  "Hello my name is Fidan and i live in sweden. My clan name is FS-SproXy. I  think it will be fun and exiting to join and play with FS. I think we got  a good team and i hopes that we will be a great playing and famous   Halo clan in the future." -FS-SproXy           
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi, my name is kevin welcome to FOUR SPARTANS even tho as of right now theres only 3 of us im shure well become one of the greatest halo pc clan. so thanks for joining peace magic chef aka kevin  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello, my name is Trevor and my clan name is FS-03. If u have any questions, just leave a post. We also have FSmagicchef. If you would like to post here also, just leave a post. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just leave a post and we might let you join. lol. 
    
</post>


<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i saw the village it was great until the end it sucked but i wont spoil it for u even tho i still dont think any one reads this. I also tried red bull for the first time today it actually works suprisingly, but it tastes like cheap champagin they serve at new years or at a indian wedding with a ton of people going to it. Even tho it cost me 2 bucks and i had to smuggle it in just to drink it, it was worth it. it kept me awake and elert.  i also found out that were getting cable internet friday coming up and were only going to hook it up to my computer so its not going through any routers just a direct line to me :) but it sucks how long itll take, 6 days and conting. any way its worth the wait ill have up to 3 mb/s download so thats superfast even if i get half that.  so thats it for now peace some guy named kevin aka MAGIC CHEF aka FS-02  
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I was playing halo last night as usual and i went in to this room and this guy said he was a mapper and he was testing somethings they were actually pretty coo. the first one was if you shoot the sniper rifle it spawns a invisible warthog that kills you instantly the second one was if you run outta amo you can shoot invisible ammo and the guns just klicks as if it is out of ammo but it still hits stuff. anyway the guy said he wanted to test these things out and said would put my halo name MAGIC CHEF as a batta tester so look out for it in some future halo thing even tho i think he was lying cause i have the copied .exe file for halo so i could play with my cousin cause he has a copied ver and you can pnly play with people who have the copied .exe file or the copied game.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; After i got board at halo&nbsp; i was flippin threw channels around 1:00 AM and on tlc had this documentry about the first g1 or a1 or some letter followed by the #1 race in america they were 2 american teams i think one had the new gto and the other had a supra they had a lot of teams that came from japan they had crazy cars like s15's 350z's and and even eight sixes and a whole lot more sadly the two teams from america didnt win they got in the top 16 which is good and one got in the top 10 which means they could go to japan to compete. It was also a documntry about the gto and about drifting they said last year a guy with a 200 horse power 87 (corrolia) over here beat the rest of the cars worth oat least 80,000&nbsp;U.S. dollars it was awsome. it makes me want to try to drift when i get a car but ill prob crash my first try and i dont have enough money to do that after abot 15 min of drifting the guys tires were completely tore up and they werent cheap tires they were $200 a piece so ill prob get gran turismo 4&nbsp; and the steering wheel for it which is almost acurate to the real thing it turns as much as the real steering wheel but theres no clutch or the it only shifts up and down but i can still do heal and toe with it and the game is really a simulater so its the closest thing to the real thing for me anyways.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; So thats it for now i still dont think anyone reads this crap so i dont know why i wright it but it still kills time&nbsp;&nbsp;and its alot better then &nbsp;vacumeing the house, doing the dishes and cleaning &nbsp;my birds cage.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; So peace, some guy&nbsp;named kevin aka MAGIC CHEF&nbsp;aka FS-02&nbsp;aka only South&nbsp;American &nbsp;indian guy at pghs.    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Im really bored now so im gonna write crap   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I cant wait until thursday and friday. i cant wait until thursday because were gonna order cable modem. And on friday the village comes out and im gonna go and see it with my brother and maybe my cousin if he can go. also a game ive been waiting for more than a year comes out street racing syndicate its like nfsu except more advance and its been in production longer than nfsu so it has to be atleast alittle bit better if not being the best street racing game.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I'll probally not buy the game just rent it and play it for a week. im getting tired of halo because i keep on getting kicked off and when i dont get kicked of i lagg and i cant move so when we get broadband hopefully that will all change and ill be able to play all i want.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I still dont know what blog stands for and i dont think anyone reads what i put up mainly because i dont know how to read what other people put up so all of this is pointless except to kill time and get better at typing.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Well thats it for know 2 blogs in one day thats like a record or somethin i already forgot what i talked about so im not going to review it so  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; PEACE for now, some guy named kevin aka MAGIC CHEF&nbsp;aka FS-02 aka the only south american indian guy at my school PGHS.   
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My dad still didnt call about the cable internet thingy, he said he wont call until thursday so thats like 2 days away then probaly another week so i have like 9 or 10 days until i actually get it then i have to by a freakin router for my dads computer and it has to be wireless so my brother can get it to even tho he dosent have a computer yet and he wont buy one. I dont see why i have to buy a router im paying for the cable internet thinggy with my own money so no instead of 20 a week im gettin10. atleast its something my cousin is soposed to get 25 a week but his dad hasnt paid him in like 3 weeks so im kinda lucky there.  today so far sucked my mom woke me up at 8:30 AM and i didnt go to sleep until 2 last night so i was really tired. i had to go with her to the hosipital so she can get x rays for her check up or something. that sucked the most i was sitting in the wating room like for a hour or so and everbody that walked by looked at me all weird and i dont even know why then i had to drive home cause she wasnt felling well and i was all tired and hungry cause i didnt eat anything yet so today prety much sucked and im going to sleep now cause im still tired................................................................................................................................................................. .......................................................................................................................................................................... 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; First of all wtf is a blog what does it stand for who made and why?  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;After thats answered im just writing this stuff cause im bored and i have nothin better to do except playin halo on pc with my crappy vid card and crppy connection which is crappy because ever other half an hour i get kicked off. hopefully thatll change when we get CABLE INTERNET or what ever its called :) . Then i wont get kicked off or lagg in halo and i wont have to evade my parents each night as i go on the internet to&nbsp; play halo.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Enough about halo and the internet for now, this summer as last summer and the summer before suxs the main reason i think is because we moved from branchester lakes to cedar creek west. the only thing good about the move was the house i like this one better than the old one but the location sux alot of my friends live in branchester and i know nobody here cause everyone close to my age are all "gansta" or "preppy" so i dont like them at all. also branchester which is like 10 min away get every thing before us like cable channels and prob dsl so I HATE THIS PLACE.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Now that im done BSing about stupid crap ill talk about gold fish, yes gold fish&nbsp; i have a couple of questions  &nbsp;1.were do they comefrom do they live in some creek or pond some where picking on leaves that float in the water.  &nbsp;2.in the wild what do they eat?, nobody feeds them flakes of food so what the hell do they eat there really stupid so why are they so popular and still survive and im tired of numbering shit so im gonna make on lon paragraph from now on so here i go as i continue i tink gold fish live in petstores only because we feed them if they werent so popular they would be dead which is kinda better than 500 golfish in a 10 gallon tank shitting on each other and runnig in to the glass   &nbsp;   ok so heres my so called Blog what ever the hell it is. it was mainly about stuff im looking forward to and stuff i hate and stuff im wondering about basically all stupid things that&nbsp;no one else cares about  hopefully the next one if there is a next one will be better then this bunch of crap that i just wrot cause im bored and also makes u think how i got all a's in english last year.   peace, some guy    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi  I was playin halo as usual :( i play it to much anyways i was blue and the room i was in was also blue in the game i mean for any of u tards out there. i said out loud u cant see me im blue and my cousin who i was playin with busted out laughing and then he killed me, i guess he could see me same thing happend with blood gultch and red u can still be seen in the rocks and with the camo on can also still be seen so i've decided halo i gay and i will never talk about or play it agian ( i didnt say halo 2 tho)   so if u know me and i say something about halo u can slap me if u wish but beawre  i will slap u back then kick u. :) -_- (:                                                ll   peace, some guy named kevin aka FsMagicChef aka last indian or something or only indian i ,forgot oh well cya    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi there  its been a while since i last blogged nothing much has happened except i got broad band and ive been downloading like crazy, ive downloaded all of the red vs blue episodes theybve made and anime with bit torrent. and ive been leavin my computer on all night which is getting me scared of over heating so i bought a pci fan and thats about it.  peace, soem guy named kevin aka FsMagicChef aka the only west inidan guy at my highs school.  
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In less than 12 hours i will have highspeed internet i know that most of u (if any) dont reall care about me getting broadband but i am so "shove it". any ways ive been looking forward to this for more than a week and now its less then 12 hours away i could really care less if i get it or not mainly because i have to pay the bill and thats half my income for the month and next year i have to buy gas money and car related junk and also i plan on buying a radeon 9800 pro video card but the cheapest price i can find it is 250 and so far i got like 31 i got a long ways to go which sucks alot.  my work in our house is steadly increasing, in the begining i was a lazy bum who did nothing then came summer and then the chores at first it was ok then it got boring and tireing but its the least i can do so ill do it i guess heres the work and order i recived the orders to do them every week empty the carbage pails in each room every thursday night, empety the kitchen carbage every night but my brother kinda took that over, vacume the house every friday afternoon, wash the dishes every morning from my working family members, mop the kitchen once a week but my mom helps to so i do like half the work, vacume the living and dinning room ever tuesday or wensday im not really shure, vacume before and after company comes for a party or something big like a barbecue, water the house plants once a week, and do the laundry when my mom tells me to except she puts the bleach and other junk im comfused about in the machine for me. and it looks like ill soon will be cutting the grass which is bad cause my dad dosent want to cut the grass short so he cuts it ever thursday and sunday so i might have to do that it makes me sad :( well if you were stupid enough to read the second half of this para graph your just stupid.  well thats about it for now so cya, some guy named kevin aka FsMagicChef aka the only south american indian blah blah blah who cares were im from. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3 days until i get broadband and then my downloading and halo playing will increse alot.  My cousins halo clan is starting to be pretty coo at first it sucked alot it had four memebers but my friend tim lied by saying he has halo and even if he gets it now it wont work on his crappy computer hes has a celeron procesor and intergrated video with i think  a 28k modem or the one closest to it he lies a lot so i just stop trusting him. Another member that is in the group is my cousins friend but he emits that he dosent have it but my cousin is going to give him a copy soon. now we have 3 playin members me my cousin and this guy i think his name is tom hes actually pretty coo he lives in swedan and his connection is awsome we had 9 people playin at once and their was no lag at all. when we play with my cousin as the server if we get more than 4 people it starts to lag and when we get 6 it lags alot but it maynot be his connection he has dsl but this one guy said that home networks may slow it down. but halo is alot more fun now that im in a clan if u ever play online look for FsMagicChef (four sparans magic chef) or any one with FS infront of their name.  So thats it for now peace, some guy named kevin aka FsMagicChef 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well 5 days until i get cable modem i cant wait for that to happen but im kinda beginning to think its a bad idea mainly because im gonna get 10 dollars a week instead of my usual 20 because i have to pay for the cable modem. i was gonna buy a bunch of crap with my money but now im thinking i should use my money the smart way like not buying stupid gameboy advance game ill only play for like a week or 2 and not getting red vs blue dvd when i can download really fast hopefully by friday. I decided to save up and get a good video card for my computer im deciding on 3 radeon 9600xt with 128mb Xtasy9600xt with 128mb or Xtasy9600 with 256mb all are agp 8x if any body actually reads this and has any of these cards tell me how it is  Peace some guy named kevin aka MAGIC CHEF aka FS-02 
    
</post>


</Blog>