<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Well tomorrow is my last day in California and then Friday morning I leave bright and early!!   Can't wait to get home, there's so many people I miss.       Like Brent.. Okay so we're goin out for a couple of months now already and he got home from Atlanta and had 2 days untill he left to go to D.C. We planned on doing something at least one of the days before he left again. So he gets home and calls me at like noon.. We keep talking for a while and then he says hes really tired and hes gonna take a nap unless I wanna do something. So being the kind person that I am (haha) I tell him that he can go ahead and go to sleep and we will just hang out the next night. So then the next day he calls me a couple times and then around 4:00 he says hes goin over to his friend Brandon's house and then they are both gonna come over and then we can kick it. So I'm like okay just call me when you get over there. So he says okay.. and then..  HE NEVER CALLS BACK ..Not even before he leaves for D.C. the next morning. I was really upset.. Actually I still am as you can probably tell.. So then hes gone for two weeks and I think he is coming home in like 2 or 3 days.. I'm not even sure. We'll see.. He probably won't even call me when he gets home again, ever. What a  greaat  boyfriend huh?       Whatever, now I'm all upset. Gotta get him off my mind- PEACE.     
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Well today nothing is going on, again..As usual...   I'm thinking that in like 20 minutes I'll go outside and lay out by the pool with my book. Right now I'm reading, The Healing Time of Hickeys.. Haha Yeah it's not REALLY good but it's okay so I just keep reading it.      I haven't read any books in a really long time so I am kinda proud of myself for actually doing it now.My step-dad Jerry just told me he needs to use this computer in a couple minutes. Haha, more on him later.All I'm gonna say right now is that he is an ANNOYING Shit.   I think a little later I might kinda explain my family situation and everything.   I don't know why I feel like I'm writing this to someone, because no one ever really reads my posts as far as I can tell. If you read my posts will you please Leave a note because I'd like to see what's goin on.      Yeah, thanks.   
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         I just recently wrote that song.. Any suggestions would be greatly appreciated. I also need to figure out a title.      I close my eyes every time your face comes into view  You don't like the way I look, you don't like my attitude  I think your pretty different from the way you used to be  You wanna make it seem like you still have feelings for me     Chorus:  But I'm gonna tell you  This is not how it should be  You coulda saved me  Don't show a bit of sympathy  Cuz I'm goin nowhere  Yeah, I'm not how I should be  You coulda saved me  Do anything you want just don't breathe     So we both know things might be better left unsaid  I don't want to ruin that, But I'd rather see you dead  Sometimes I wish that things could go back and just rewind  And I know this isn't the place, and this isn't the time     But I'm gonna tell you  This is not how it should be  You coulda saved me  Don't show a bit of sympathy  Now I'm goin nowhere  No i'm not how I should be  You coulda saved me  You can do anything you want, Just don't breathe     When people ask me how you're doin baby I just laugh  It's nice to know they wanna break me and bring my memory back  If you could just take the time to grow up we could be  But untill that happens baby, I'd like to ask you to get away from me  Cuz you coulda saved me  This is not how it should be  Yeah, I'm gonna tell you  Don't show a bit of sympathy  Now I'm goin nowhere  Oh I'm not how I should be  You coulda saved me  Do me a huge favor.. Don't breathe   
      
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Okay, so here we go.. First post ever on this thing. I'm kinda confused about how it works, even though I had a similar diary on Diaryland.com..  Diaryland.com sucked ass actually. It seemed really hard for other people to end up reading your posts and posting back in reply their thoughts. I hope this one is a little better. Also, I don't really see how other people get hooked on these things. I mean its writing down meaningless thoughts, (at least mine are meaningless)... But i have to admit sometimes I actually like reading what other people are thinking about.. Even if it is pointless.  Soo, my first post is pretty weak and I have absolutely nothing to say. But I'm finding that I am typing really funny and this is not how i speak in person at all. My writing hardly shows what kind of person I am. I'll write more later.. This is kinda tiring.  
      
</post>


</Blog>