<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Yes, it's been confirmed, I worry way too much.    So, I went to Stef and Juan's trailer last night after work. I was originally planning on going home, but Stef wanted me to stay the night. I knew if I stayed the night lastnight I definitely wouldn't be allowed tonight, but he still wanted me to stay. But when I called the bitch she wouldn't let me: "he's 21, we haven't met him and you're going to sleep with him!" Yeah, so what if that's all true.    We started off by finishing a movie with Juan & Ali (some girl Juan is crazy about apparently, however Stef hates her). And soon enough I ended up laying on top of him underneath a sleeping bag. It was so nice. It felt so nice to cuddle with someone and give them sassy kisses and nibbles while staring into their eyes. I guess I believe that he likes me now. :D He's so cute, he loves my "angry" face, which is really just me scrunching up my nose and burrowing my eyebrows. But I love how he loves it. He makes me feel special and beautiful, he's not a testosterone driven macho man, he talks with a cute little baby voice to me sometimes and is constantly playfully teasing me. I love it! I love every second of attention he gives me.    So we cuddled like that for a while, teasing and playing and biting! But it got to be too much, we were both getting much too horny and couldn't do anything about it. I just wanted to rip all his clothes off and go wild, but Juan and co were just above us on the bed. So Stef came up with the idea of going for a "walk"...He's so bad.   He took me up to this weird little tepee and we got in on ;). haha it was awkward and wet yet still fun.   However we couldn't really have sex properly because it was hurting him, he has a really sensitive penis, it's kind of weird. So it kinda hurts him to have sex with me, which makes me kinda self-conscious, cause I'm still afraid maybe I'm doing something wrong. But he's basically convinced me it's not my fault at all. So I gave him head and let him cum in my mouth and I swallowed it for him. I don't mind doing it, I've only done it for a certain few people. He said I was the first person who has swallowed for him.   I'm a little shy about my body infront of him, cause I don't like my body and he's had a lot of girlfriends and he's probably use to girls with nice little bodies. I'm taller then him and bigger boned, so I feel a little weird, but I'm soooo attracted to him.   He wants me to stay the night tonight, so I'm gonna have to go work on the parents. I figure I'll be able to do it...I might have to get Juan to pretend to be his dad or something embarrassing like that. I mean embarrassing for me, they're not use to having to deal with parents so much and I hate dealing with parents then having to get people involved.   He has to work at four and I work at five, so this kinda works out good. I just wanna go to his trailer and wait around for him and sleep with him all night...it'd be so nice. Very enjoyable...   I'll write again.      By the way, I found out the correct spelling of his name: Stephane   so short for should be Steph, that's what I'll use form now on...  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Stef just called me, like 5 minutes ago. Band practice plans fell through for him, so he invited me over after work. He also bought a bass amp, which I want to watch him make love through. I guess I should be excited now. ;) Again something to look forward too. I guess he wouldn't invite me over if he really enjoy me. :D I guess my mood is looking up. However I should go vacuum my room and prepare for the grind. The faster it's over the sooner I see him, right? I wonder if he stayed the night at Sheila's...blah. I should go. I can't get started on this again.  I'll be back.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I saw around lastnight! I was really excited and happy to see him. I got stoned earlier in the night, which made me pretty quiet around them. I felt awkward cause I was so quiet..But I guess it doesn't matter. He invited me to go for a walk with him downtown to get a drink, so of course I accepted. But with my 2am curfew about 10 minutes away, I knew I was either going to be very late, or I should just invite him to my house.    I love his flirting methods, they're so cute. When we were walking, we both kept bumping into each other as an excuse to hold hands. It was cute and sweet and made me smile with delight. This bumping shoulders also became and excuse to start a passionate kiss, right on the sidewalk! We got into it and couldn't stop, he tasted so good. His lips are gorgeous and delicious and I can't help but kiss him and kiss him, every chance I get. We were finally interrupted by the sounds of drunkards wandering the streets.   So we snuck into my house and worked our way through foreplay to sex. I was nervous and self-conscious about myself and my ability to be completely honest. It also didn't help that my parents were in the house, above us.    But then again it was our first time together, it's a new body with new likes and dislikes and it's hard to master someone in one sitting! But there's another aspect of me that is really self-conscious, where I feel like he actually wasn't having a good time, but was just being polite. I am deathly afraid he doesn't actually like me and just wants sex. However he hasn't quite displayed that complete mind set. He has been very sweet and he cuddled a little after sex. But I still feel he is one of those completely polite guys who thought he was interested in me, but after having bad sex with me, in uninterested. Maybe I'm worrying too much. But I can't read him, it's so difficult to tell if he's being truthful.   I'm also scared that he went back to sheila's and told everyone how horrible it was. Thinking about all of this makes me even more self-conscious. Maybe I'm not very good at sex, I thought I was...But....   I really wanted to pleasure him and I really wanted him to cum...But it wasn't happening through sex, so he asked me to trying sucking him. But it didn't seem like I was doing it right, he wanted me to go as deep as possible, to use tighter lips, and to play with his balls. And even though I tried meeting these requests I don't think it worked. I suppose I could argue that it was our first time and we need to get to know each other's pleasure requirements...But I felt bad because I wasn't masterful.    So we switched back to sex again, of course the problem is he has to pull out...So that can be argued as an underlying reason for his prolonged cumming. But why do I still feel it was my crappy ability that was the problem? Am I really bad? I'm kind of upset now. Maybe he doesn't want to try with me again. Oh man, maybe I'm just being too drastic, but I'm so scared!   I really want to see him again and I can't wait to show him what I'm made of on Saturday. But I wonder what his intentions are? Does he want to just "see" each other and have sex and a friendly relationship? Does he want a relationship? Or does he just want to fuck, cause he's decided he doesn't like me or my body?   I've been reading sex tips since I got up...I want to hit him hard with some really good sex on Saturday, so I'm shaping up. :P   Apparently he's calling before 5...Thinking of work - I have to clean my uniform and I'm probably going to be working upstairs tonight. Damnit! I'm going to be pooched. I want to talk to Sheila...See what went down when he left my house for Sheila's. Did him and Juan go home? Did they stay till 5am? Did Danielle and Stef hook up or flirt or talk about how bad I am? I need to talk to Sheila. I'm sure things aren't as bad as I think, but I can't help but worry.   I can't stop thinking about it.   I wonder what he's doing tonight...I think practicing with the band? Who knows. I wish I could see him, but I've dated musicians before and it's not cool to interrupt band bonding sessions. Not that I care that he practices, I'm glad he's playing his bass. It's just that I'm selfish and want him all to myself to give him a real taste of my real skills. I can be quite crazy and fun, so I'm told and I know I can show him a good time. I just have to build myself up a bit, I suppose.      Anyways, off to prepare for work.      I'll write again.     
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink      Stef. *drools uncontrollably*&nbsp;  urlLink         I can't stop looking at this picture. He looks too tasty. I just want to scramble up that tree and ravage him, right there on that branch. There's something about the makeup, the&nbsp;strapping red suit, and the elegant black dress that I find very sexy. Maybe it's because, despite his formal wear he is savagely perched in a tree.    The picture and his look reminds me of Pyxis, if I was ever to bring that character back to Ruby Grail, I'd get Stef to model for me.    &nbsp;      urlLink      I love the bands style, Plastic Action Star. It's so hot, look at Stef.*&nbsp;  urlLink           &nbsp;   I can't wait to see this boy again. I must admit I really like him. He told Jaime, and I quote: " She's gorgeous, she's really cool, and I want to see her again soon." My heart jumped with extra eagerness. I wish I had a webcam in the privacy of my own home :P, things would probably get pretty heated.    I spoke to him for like four hours yesterday, it was so much fun. He should me this site where you can make your own south park characters, it's super fun. I think his looks exactly like him, I made one for myself too. If this stupid blogger bot and picasa hello thing wasn't so retarded and difficult to use..Maybe I'd be able to post them.    &nbsp;                        
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       salutations, &nbsp;    &nbsp;   welcome. this will be my first attempt at a journal. I'm curious and excited to begin writing more of my thoughts down. it feels thrilling and dangerous, to open up my mind and my words and expose them&nbsp;bluntly for all to read. however it will be benefiting.    i'm patiently waiting for stef, pretending there is still a chance he might show up, come online rather. we were suppose to meet at 2am but there's been no word and it's almost 4am. i feel like giving up, because its the obvious thing to do. but i've started this journal now, why not write it.    ahhh stef. i can't help but laugh at my own antics when i find a new crush. its been a while since i last had a crush on someone...i just haven't met anyone i can be around in a relationship type of way. maybe i'm too picky or perhaps too fickle? i've felt very free and independent lately, and i must admitt i quite enjoy it. I love being on my own schedule with lots of random fun with different people all the time. i feel like a true air sign - a free individual flying the sky.    but it feels good to have met someone i feel very interested in. and especially fidning out from jamie that i "sparked his interest". it made my heart jump, as i had been thinking about him&nbsp;all saturday, trying to figure out how to see him again. my first impressions seem to feel he's a sweetie pie with a heart. but still a stable individual with substance and being. i can't wait to talk to him about politics and conversations that get me excited.    it's 4am, he's definitely not coming on. i probably tired him out from lastnights' game of questions that lasted til 5am.    I love his subtle, but very impacting ways of flirting. I've never met someone who is so careful and precise with their courting. i enjoy the anticipation of feeling vibes from someone as they begin to put more moves on you. midnight madness morning (haha) being the perfect example as stef offered me smokes and sips of wine. it started off slow and friendly (like when he came to sit near me at the fire)...That's where i think his flirtation began. he says it was when he found out i was of legal age, around the time we had a smoke or something, but that was so much earlier in the morning (technically). so after we retreated to she's bedroom (conrad, she, juan, danielle, stef, and i), i developed a seat on the floor (eventually beside stef) with the three on the bed and danielle perching over us like a stubborn bitch. i wish she would have just gone to bed. it would had made this so more relaxing and comfortable for me. but it was obvious to her that stef and i were sending out vibrations. ;)    whatever...its over now, i've ranted enough of the danielle torment.    its time to gets back to the amazing feeling i have for stef right now. i feel so good, happy, excited, raw, hyperactive, alive, full of expression.    oh and despite the mother problem...which i don't even feel lik getting into right now. That's a deep, black wound no one wants to start in on. it will just consume you whole until your existence is bare and naked. like its been combed too many times. and massive, red welts will form on your skin until you become paralyzed and throw yourself onto a sheet of blazing hot razor blades.    anyways...    i better go off to bed so i'm well rested to face to fiery dragon slaying festival tomorrow.    I hope stef comes home on wednesday, that would be a pleasant surprise.      &nbsp;   i will write again.      
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I'm back...   It's 3am and I'm still up. I couldn't think of anything better to do.    I suppose I could sleep?   So I won't write for too long...   Nothing too exciting is going on. I bought some pot today with Fish. I went to work tonight.    Mike comes home tomorrow!!! I'm so excited! I can't wait to see him. I'm gonna call his house tomorrow and see what time he gets home, I'm also gonna go out and get a little gift for him, cause I can't help but love the guy. Hehe.   I might have a little party for him on thrusday night...or hell, maybe he'll wnat to have one tomorrow night.   I was thinking of calling Lysan, but I dunno. I think I want to just chill with him and Fish. We haven't had some time together in a long time and we always have so much fun together. Just the tree of us, Fish and I always talk about how complimenting we all our to eachother as friends.    I'm excited for the upcoming year, grade 12, wow. It's going to be a lot of work, but a lot of fun at the same time. Yearbook, driving, turning 18, new freedoms, gr. 12 status...oh man...so much is happening, so soon.   Well, I guess I'll be on my way.   Oh. Ben leaves for Guelph soon...I should call him and see him. I miss him. I love that guy, he's my sweetheart, we can't help but love eachother so much.   Anyways...   I'm off I suppose...   Goodnight...til we meet again.  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Okay, so I haven't written in a week, and a lot has happened. But sometimes I just get too wrapped up in everything to sit down here for a few minutes and write. I suppose it's like building a habit...Or an addiction (for lack of the use of a better, descriptive word). They do call it "eating habits", I suppose this is why I also believe eating meat lifestyles or vegetable lifestyles is just habit...Anyone can train themselves to one or the other. You need determination and you need some wallpaper and reason for action....It's not that hard..:P   I enjoy my eating habits now. I enjoy being a vegetarian and discovering all the interesting snacks and foods that are friendly to me.    I love how I started talking about this...I was told in a writing workshop that sitting down and just letting your mind flow where ever it likes is very good practice. Even if you start thinking about thinking nothing...They even said to write that down.    So here I am, mumbling on...Sporadically interrupted by the consistent blinking of boxes at the bottom of my screen. Demanding my attention at once. At this very instant. I suppose it's the price you pay for having a live, instant message conversation with your friend, while trying to type in your blog. Hah.   Well, to be quite honest, there is not conversation. We're just sending random emoticon symbols back and forth, oh, and we still are. I just choose the one that looks the most appealing at that moment. But I suppose I was complaining more about the blinking flash that turns into a constant, lit up box. Piercing me and hanging over me like a dark, microsoft blue cloud, urging me to raise my hand and click it free. But some how I'm lost in the rhythm of my keys. It's keeping me focused on this flow...This breath.   Ahh, but here we go again, another one has messaged me, so urgently, it seems. Summoning my attention and typing skills. Which usually come in at full in intervals.   So I'm back. I was just speaking with John, from 3 Guys.   We went to the Purple Pig today for lunch, in Bracebridge. I drove them (the parents) down there, so we could go to home depot to buy some supplies for my room. :D It was pretty enjoyable...I got to drive and we picked up this cool laminate hardwood floor for my room, a night light, a plant (i love it)...And some other stuffff...but anyways, to get back on topic...   We stopped there for lunch, it sounds like quite the meaty restaurant and it is, but they did have a veggie corner. So I got a veggier burger, with really good fries. It was cool...when we sat down there was a table of kids behind us and a table of four in front of us. Its strange how I remember those details. I think it's cause I'm use to doing table checks and seeing how many chairs, people, plates, kids, high chairs, etc. Hey, it's what being a busser turns you into, I'm a table hawk.   So ANYWAY...The table in front of us got up to leave and this weird, bleach blonde, scrawny coke addict came up and asked if we mided if she joined us. We were all so startled and shocked that my dad and I didn't say anything, and my mom just barely squeezed out a "no"...then she started rambling on how she had a rough night and that she just needs someone to harass...I don't know...It was very strange. She was obviously piss drunk and screwed up....she told us her boyfriend beat up her dog. I don't know, she was pitiful and rude, but I still felt bad for her, cause she was drunk. It gives me a ha  rd feeling, one I can't quite describe. I feel awkward, I'm put in an awkward position to choose either side...And I suppose I decided upon, "I'm going to ignore you and distance myself from you". But what did she expect us, complete strangers just sitting down to enjoy a lunch to do about her, the sympathy, drunk, stranger cause, invading our personal table.   Anyways...Moving on   I went to WARPED TOUR! Wow! WOW!!!   Fuck man...it was so awesome...I really enjoyed it..so worth it.   I met this guy, I moshed in the pits, felt the wrath of it's depths, became dehydrated, inhaled dust, had to pee badly, got all burnt, got bruised, was cold, hungry, filthy...Everything..it was what I needed...to let lose in those pits and just give Everything up. I lost a bracelet, She lost my aldo shoe. I dunnoo....it was just overall crazy and awesome. Saw lots of Huntsville folk "punkers" from HHS there.   It was a sweet time...I'd go back next year for sure...It's just such a crazy, different type of atmosphere and party, essentially. It's insane, you feel so connected to everyone and so alive, the excitement and the crowd drives me nuts.   Stef and Danielle. Fuck em'...yeah fuck Jamie's girlfriend too, while your at it. That's really I'll I have to say about that situation now. I know I had quite a lot to say about Stef early..but whatever. I don't spell his name right either...shit.   Anyways...what else..   My room is almost done (finally)...I suppose it's my own fault it wasn't done earlier, but it's coming along and looking good.   MIKE COMES HOME ON WEDNESDAY (which I could get the day off for)...oh well we'll still party hard, for sure. I love that guy!!!!!   But I suppose i'll be off to slumber...   it's about that time. I did I fair amount of catch-up...      Until we meet again, invisible friend, who so jauntily dances this sidewalk with me. So close, you peer through this dancing fools' own typed words.   Goodnight.      
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A lot happened last night; the condensed version of the situation is everything involving Steph blew up in my face. Bloody, teary, and no shame are also descriptive words. So many emotions overwhelm me right now, I couldn't possibly describe them all. For starters, I feel like fucking shit. Simple. I had about 3 hours of sleep since last night/morning, I feel malnourished, and my arm hurts. I also feel like a used, general whore who trusts much too easily. I feel retarded, embarrassed and most of all stupid. I'm a stupid girl. A stupid brat. There were warning signs and I didn't properly acknowledge them, I guess? Well that isn't true, I did acknowledge them (see last posts), it's HIM that didn't do anything really.. I'm sick of being at the butt end of things and getting screwed over, blown off and abused by people who don't put in any effort to communicate or just act fucking mature in a situation. I'm sorry, but I expected a 21 year old with lots of girlfriend experience to have a little more communication skills then what was displayed last night. It was rude to just totally ignore me and go off with Danielle for the night. And that's just putting it simply, it was also hurtful, very hurtful. The only way I know how to describe this feeling is, heartbreak. I feel heartbroken. Apparently we're not right for each other and he wasn't feeling right or whatever... Well what the fuck, we talked on the internet while he was away, for like 4-5 hours at a time, getting to know each other. Maybe we jumped into sex too soon, but it was damn fun. I let him do things to me that I wouldn't just let any random guy do. I've never been tied up, I don't let just anyone go in my ass and I don't let just anyone cum in my mouth or all over my face. Jesus Christ... Honestly, I feel used...I feel like someone took advantage of my trusting and loving nature. Because it's true, I trusted him and I really like/d him. Even though we weren't in a relationship I enjoyed his company, I'm extremely attracted to him... and it killed me to watch him flirting it up with Danielle all night. I couldn't stand it. It was like knives slitting my wrists, coincidental? I was drunk, but that made it worse of course, my emotions started flying off the wall. But I know even if I was sober I would have been feeling the same way. I really thought he was interested in me and it made me so happy. I was so happy to have met someone I felt I could get close with and share something with. I've said it before, I'm god damn sick of emotionless relations with people. I want there to be something more then just sex, I want to meet someone new and be totally taken aback, like how it felt with Steph. Where all I wanted to do was kiss him and cuddle with him and enjoy him. Because I did. I'm not meaning to blame anyone, but I'm sure Danielle assisted in planting some message in his head that we were NOT good together.  But, sorry, ya know...Love isn't for everyone.   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Well, here I am again, just as confused as before. I'm really not sure what is going on with Steph and I. I'm beginning to realize maybe we're only close friends who fuck. Which wasn't exactly what I was going for...But... Also, what the fuck is with Danielle staying overnight there? Obviously she would have had to sleep right next to him, there isn't any other space. I haven't really ranted about that yet, but it really pissed me off to know that. Maybe they're just friends, but they always seem to flirt a lot and I wouldn't be surprised if something happened. I want to ask him, but I know he's not mine, and I don't want him to even get the sense that I'm jealous or trying to be possessive at all. Because really I'm not, I'm just damn curious...Cause I really don't want to be just another girl he fucks. I'm god damn sick of that nonsense. Maybe it's too much to ask to be the only current fuck friend. Whatever...  He did in fact call me Thursday and came and saw me and stayed overnight on Wednesday after work. But he obviously was too busy last night, our days off to do anything. Whatever, again. But I must say it was pretty fun when he stayed over, we had a threesome with Sheila. I must admit it was very interesting, I've never done it before. I was a very spoiled brat, because they bother we're just going nuts for me. And I was a little jealous when Steph and Sheila kissed and when he started doing stuff to her...But I guess it didn't really bother me, it was only Sheila...I would have been hurt if they had sex though. But anyways, there are other things going on in my life besides the rantings of boys... The situation with my parents is a little better...I don't really know what to say about this topic. There is soo much to go into about that they think, my "behaviour" and such. They're constantly rhyming these behavioural things I'm doing that they dislike, but I'm hardly caught in the act doing them, in my opinion. Like the last thing they got pissed off about what that Steph and I were up at 5am still and they were pretty pissed off. I don't know...I don't even feel like getting into this, it's stupid. It's also boring to rant about... On the upside, I plan on getting smashed tonight...I haven't been really drunk and much too long. So tonight, I won't have any weed, (although I'll be jonzin' for it, I can tell already) I'm just going to drink, cause She is having a little shin dig. Wooo! Now, next issue, whether to call and invite Juan and Steph....? I probably will, I don't want to disturb him and his girl of the day though... He is really sweet to me when he's around, but I can't tell whether is fake or forced....Who knows. Some guys are very smart like that, they know acting like they like you and being sweet with gestures and words will make most girls very attracted to them and more open for sexual activity..Which in my case is true. I'm not embarrassed about it either. It's not like it's a bad thing.... anyway...I'm very into my Nirvana and Kurt lately... Courtney Love was lucky, or was she? I can't quite tell. I shall write about the aftermath of this party...Of course I will.  Until then...   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>