<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So I received the first comment of my blog. Now blogging seems to be interesting. If you are in Mumbai as a tourist, then a cab is probably the best mode of transportation, unless your hotel can arrange a vehicle for you. There isn't much to do in Mumbai, per se. I mean there is a museum, and pretty cool lounges & pubs, but don’t expect any great public space. Do see Gateway of India and Marine Drive, but avoid the zoo. If you are interested in wildlife, you can tour the National Park –most people visit to see the tigers and lions, though I think they arrange bird-watching, trekking etc.(Mumbai is the only city in the world, to have a proper national park within its borders). But I would suggest you spend more time outside, than in a city like Mumbai, Delhi or Calcutta (now called Kolkata). If you are looking for sun n sand, then head to Goa. For backwaters, lagoons, and ayurvedic treatment, go to Kerala. But my favourite state is Rajasthan – famous for its forts, palaces and havelis (beautiful houses of rich merchants). If money permits, be sure to stay at the Lake Palace hotel, in Lake Pichola, Udaipur. (you have heard of Lake Palace right?) Ask anything that you may want my opinion on.  I started the painting, but decided that it wasn’t going to have six squares, what I decided was that after I finish my work, i'll work on that painting with the paints remaining, if any. So today, after I finished working on my copied-miniature-Mughal-painting, I had some really nice pink paint left in my palette, so I painted a pink square. Tomorrow may be another square, or may be I’ll start detailing the pink one.    &nbsp;  Wondering if there is any way to reply to comments...  
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I am just exploring different things here. For instance, what appears between two posts. CSS is a really powerful tool to change my blog page as per my choice of colours, text etc. &nbsp;It doesn’t seem difficult to grasp, at least up to the level I need to know. The six square painting isn't going to happen tonight. I have just been reading about CSS all evening.    &nbsp;  I’ve got to repair my cycle soon. It had been lying unused for more than a year, when I repaired it last fortnight, but haven’t touched it since; so its flat all over again. Speaking of cycles, I was reading about these cycling clubs in London. It seems to be a pretty cool concept to hook up people together as cycling buddies, tell people about cycle-only routes, which actually cut down travel time to one’s destination. I don’t see this happening in Mumbai for quite some time. It is pretty dangerous to ride cycle on Mumbai's street. There are those really friendly rickshaw-wallahs who seem to emerge from every possible direction and place, in no time at all; not to mention those BEST bus drivers, who feel they own the roads.  
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Well, I've just created not one but two blogs for myself. I really dont know why I did this, but I suddenly felt the urge to blog. I have really nothing to do for another two weeks or so.       &nbsp;   College will start after that. I am starting first year architecture. Any tips for me?       &nbsp;   Im going to paint something tonight, though its not going to be anything original. I saw this painting on a wall in the background, during a television   serial. It was divided into about 6 squares, 3 in each row, and therefore 2 rows. And all that was there in those 6 squares were circles, or rather rings of different colours. Is this some kind of abstract art?     
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       “JACK AND JILL WENT UP THE HILL, TO FETCH A PAIL OF WATER. JACK FELL DOWN AND BROKE HIS CROWN, AND JILL CAME TUMBLING AFTER”. We had to sing this as loudly as we could – and no, this was no ragging, just a workshop. I think the main aim of all these workshops is to make us interact with each other, and to make us more comfortable around one another. After all, we are going to be spending the next 5 years with this group only.  The ragging starts: I am being asked to walk down the ramp. A big smile of surprise on my face. Then the fellow (he goes by the name Yogi, very familiar to Yogi bear, na?), tells me that its walking down the ramp as a female model. The smile quickly gives its way to a (supposedly) very indifferent “what ever”. To which our dear Yogi gets really angry, and asks “What’s with the attitude ?”. Come on, what did I say, just a ‘what ever’. I happen to say that really often. Anyway, then some one asks me whether I want to be ragged or not. My answer is: definitely not this way. I mean its too much to ask to do that, isn't it? Other ways of ragging seem to be fine (which btw is not referring to the kind of stuff that seems to go on in many medical colleges). Just that guys should not be asked to act like girls, and girls shouldn’t be asked to act like guys.  
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Most of our day was at the stilt area. Had a few interactive games.  We have a canteen uncle, and also a canteen dog. The dog just roams there all day. He some how never barks.  The seniors (except the TAs &amp; their batch) are desperately trying to rag us. They haven’t really been successful so far.  
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       So we are not supposed to address our professors as ‘Sir’ or ‘Ma’m’. Apprently calling them by their first name will do. Also wishing the prof. entering the class ‘Good morning / evening’ is “the last thing we do here at KRVIA”. This seems kind of awkward at first. I mean we have been wishing teachers and sirs, since the time I can remember. Some of them would actually got wild, if we did not wish them; notably Mrs. JRD who had once phoned me a few months after the SSC result, and when I said “yes ma’m” she goes: “Is this how you address your teachers? Where are your manners Kunal?”. Now to get used to this new informal atmosphere will take time.  But the biggest surprise in this regard, is how the Dy. Director Mr. Anirudh Paul is referred to as ‘Paul’. So we had “Paul is going to have a small talk with you all after some time”.  
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       We all got ragged. This was a day I can probably never forget. We (or at least I) knew that we would have some kind of Introductory Workshop, for the first few days, and this would probably be taken by some TAs (Teaching Assistants).  So we are all sitting in the ‘Lecture Room’, waiting for some one to come. Then these 2 guys come in, and strat introducing themselves. They go on to say that they are going to be our TAs in so and so subjects. And then we are all asked to stand up and introduce ourselves – name and from which college or school are we. One by one all of us diligently stand up and introduce ourselves, and meanwhile one of the guys starts video taping up, which at that moment seemed strange, but possible. Then they go on to ask us, if anyone has ever ‘built’ anything. Some one answers: a few projects involving models, in school. But one student, says that he has helped building a wall when he was in college. That was really surprising.  Just a few minutes later a professor appears outside the lecture room’s door. And all of a sudden so many people start clapping. It turned out that the two guys claiming to be TAs were in fact only second year students; as were some people sitting along with us – notably the guy who had built a wall. All of them of course ran out then. So the second years had a good laugh on us. They were all in it together, all of them were standing outside and laughing.  The first prof. we met was Mr. Kausik Mukhopadhyay, accompanied by a group of about 10 -12 teaching assistants. 
      
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Went to Haveli today. They had Independence Day theme. All saffron, white and green colours. Really delightful!      I am really excited about tomorrow – it’s going to be the first day of FYBArch. I don’t think I have ever been so excited, and looking forward to it something so much, except maybe for the time when I visited the CEPT campus for the first time.  
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Today’s day should probably recorded in our group’s history. The messages started with Deep claiming that his poll is missing. This was followed by a rather long and deeply written message by Anish, asking that I should stop deleting stuff that I don’t like.  Reading this, I think I must have got really bugged up coz I immediately replied back saying that I had deleted only 3 things. And then I sent a message showing what all had happened in the group during the day. Then it seemed that Deep had himself deleted the poll.  Meanwhile Rounak started writing in asking everyone to cool down. Then Kshitij wrote in, again asking everyone to cool down. Then Deep sent a message saying that it was his fault that the poll had been deleted, and Kunal had nothing to do with it. Then Anish wrote in to say that he did not mean to accuse anyone. Then iposted a message saying that even I had gone a bit over board, especially with deleting the SRK-look-alike poll, and the capital letters in my message weren’t really necessary. Between all this, Vivek wrote in again asking everyone to calm down, and Rounak defended me claiming that while “The next princi” poll was a bit relevant, the “SRK-look-alike” poll made absolutely no sense.  The best part of all this was that people were writing so much stuff in their mail. I mean no body must have said so much on one topic in school, let alone try to cool down others.  Here are the messages, in the order of posting, from first to last:    From: "The greatest guy in the town"   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 5:03 pm Subject: Hello ppl  Hi, somehow i donno the poll results have been deleted.well as last seenKunal got 1Nikunj got 1Sunil got 10 to be Nare's jasoosMihir got 1 Signing off Deep Garg    From: "The greatest guy in the town"   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 5:11 pm  Shocked by the results well this wasnt true actuallyKunal got 3Nikunj got 1Rama wid the max no. of 5and donno y Mihir got 2signing offDeep Garg    From: "Anish"   urlLink  heatednemz@hotmail.com   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 6:05 pm Subject: Kunal wat are u doing?  dunno if its u..but evrything we upload is mysteriously disappearing from evrywhere!this place is becoming a mess! make someone a morderator (if not me) to handle the lot in ur absence and PLEASE give us the freedom to POST ANYTHING WE LIKE EVEN IF IT IS A POLL.... DOESNT NECESSARILY HAVE TO BE RELATED TO SCHOOL ISSUES!try not deleting matter that u think is rott!one persons garbage is another persons gold!    From: “Kunal"   urlLink  kunal_kunal_2002@yahoo.com   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 6:08 pm Subject: Re: Kunal wat are u doing? WHAT IN THE WORLD DO U MEAN  ANISH,THE ONLY THINGS I HAVE DELETED UP TO NOW:POLL ON SRK LOOK ALIKEA PICTURE OF UMA (AS PER RESULTS OF POLL)A PICTURE OF MYSELFNOTHING ELSEI HAVE NO IDEA WHAT U R TALKING BAOUTI HAVE JUST LOGGGED ONKUNAL    From: kshitij deulkar   urlLink  thegreatkyd@yahoo.co.in   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 6:12 pm Subject: Re: [hmps2002] Kunal wat are u doing?  hey guyz,i, sriram n ramu totaly agree wit andy. man v need more fun here man no serious crap!!tc guyzluv kyd    From: "Kunal"   urlLink  kunal_kunal_2002@yahoo.com    > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 6:14 pm Subject: WHAT HAPPENED TODAY IN GROUP  I HAVENT DELETED ANYTHING TODAYTHIS IS WHATHAS HAPPENED THE WHOLE DAY:       8/14/2004 9:51 am rounaks   urlLink  rounaks@yahoo.co.in   >   Deleted file: "/RonWalking.jpg"  8/14/2004 11:24 am gargdeeps   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Edited poll: "Who was the most famous guy from A division ? "  8/14/2004 11:24 am gargdeeps   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Edited poll: "Who was the most famous guy from A division ? "  8/14/2004 11:46 am smartsunil911   urlLink  getscared666@hotmail.com   > Post sent via web: "Re: Hey sunil"  8/14/2004 11:51 am smartsunil911   urlLink  getscared666@hotmail.com   > Post sent via web: "Re: Hey kaamu!"  8/14/2004 11:51 am smartsunil911   urlLink  getscared666@hotmail.com   > Post sent via web: "Re: Hey kaamu!"  8/14/2004 4:48 pm gargdeeps   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Edited poll: "Who was the most famous guy from A division ? "  8/14/2004 5:01 pm gargdeeps   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Deleted poll: "Who was the most famous guy from A division ? "  8/14/2004 5:03 pm gargdeeps   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Post sent via web: "Hello ppl"  8/14/2004 5:11 pm gargdeeps   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Post sent via web: ""  8/14/2004 6:05 pm anish11.rm   urlLink  heatednemz@hotmail.com    Post sent via web: "Kunal wat are u doing?"  8/14/2004 6:08 pm kunal_kunal_2002   urlLink  kunal_kunal_2002@yahoo.com   > Post sent via web: "Re: Kunal wat are u ..."    IF DEEP EDITED THE POLL (CHANGED OPTIONS)THEN POLL RESTARTSKUNAL    From: rounak shastri   urlLink  rounaks@yahoo.co.in   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 6:16 pm Subject: Re: [hmps2002] Re: Kunal wat are u doing? WHAT IN THE WORLD DO U MEAN  you guys are seriously making this a personal thing more than anything... the point of this group rore-unite and all (although that sounds corny, when I say that... it IS true)... so just relax... the stupidpoll was indeed stupid, the uma pic... I dunno anything abt that... and I had posted up Kunal's picw/o asking him, and he didnt like it, cuz of certain reasons... so he deleted... so just chill...RounakSHIT HAPPENS... TIME TO GET MOVING!    From: kshitij deulkar   urlLink  thegreatkyd@yahoo.co.in   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 6:34 pm Subject: Re: [hmps2002] WHAT HAPPENED TODAY IN GROUP  kunal chil man!!! v wer tokin bout d srk lookalike poll. it wuz stupid bt it wuz meant 2 b fun. datz wat d grpz all boutrite? n man if nethin shld go itz d stupid who wil b d next princy poll. man d options dnt mak no sense.peons b'comin principalz?? man dat dsnt make us laugh man. srk hope u read this. d teaching staff n dclerical staff is totally different. n guyz wateva v say on d grp itz no personal thing. guyz dnt take thm 2 personaly. jus read n **** it man. n if v wanna make ne personal comment v dnt need d yahoo group man. i think v r here 2 have fun so juz chill!!! hey n these r d viewz of sriram n rama 2. thy r sitinrite here.tc all    From: "Kunal"   urlLink  kunal_kunal_2002@yahoo.com   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 6:40 pm Subject: today's drama  What do u mean things are disappearing? I just checked, all photos are there. All rows in the database are present. 8 files are there, and there are 3 closed polls and 1 open poll. And all the 7 links are present.The most famous guy's poll disappeared coz deep himself has deleted it (see the time in my precious mail): 8/14/2004 5:01 pm gargdeeps   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Deleted poll: "Who was the mostfamous guy from A division ?"Don't tell me that u saw "new within last seven days" and came to conclusions. Im sure u know that , that are only the number of knew things , and not the total.Anyways, I think the capital words in my message weren't all that necessary, so ya sorry man, was just a bit furiousC yaKunal    From: Kunal Bhatia   urlLink  kunal_kunal_2002@yahoo.com   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 6:43 pm Subject: Re: [hmps2002] WHAT HAPPENED TODAY IN GROUP  yeah maybe i went a bit over board in deleting that srk look alike poll    From: rounak shastri   urlLink  rounaks@yahoo.co.in   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 7:07 pm Subject: Re: [hmps2002] WHAT HAPPENED TODAY IN GROUP  na man... seriously... the new princi poll is decently funny... it at least makes sense, we've been talkingabt Mehr being prici and all, so it makes sense... the peons bit is suposed to be a funny, although if youthink about it seriously, sitaram WILL be better than Mehr ... who looks like shahrukh khan, thats justplain dumb... that poll didnt make sense in any way...came outta no where... and yea, it might've been funny to a few, but overall, a lot of the pplfrom thegroup found it making no sense, cuz ... it just didn’t aanyway, chao for nowRounak    From: "Vivek"   urlLink  vivekprabhu13@excite.com   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 7:32 pm Subject: Chill out!!!  Hi Guys,Relax everyone,dont fight about the stupid poll or other stuff.Let one put what one wants to put and vote who all want to vote.do what u want.Chill...But please dont include my name In the srk poll!!! Man!!!I was shocked!! Dont spoil my name!! .Poor Shahrukh....What has he done to deserve this...ME??? Pls...    From: "The greatest guy in the town"   urlLink  gargdeeps@yahoo.com   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 8:12 pm Subject: Hey guys my explanation regarding deletion of poll  Hi,Today I went to one of my frnds house and jus left logged in on his PC and he made the mess by deleting the poll and Kunal is not at fault.Well I jus edited be4 left and so poll did restart.But I sentthe results to everyonecoz it was my fault.Regarding deletion it was my mistake and dont worry next time I'll remember to log off be4 I leave.And the change in poll was bcoz Sunil was not willing to connect him with Nare.So I thnk everything will be fine.Signing off.Deep Garg    From: "Anish"   urlLink  heatednemz@hotmail.com   > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 8:36 pm Subject: WHOA BOYS!  Chill guys!i didnt mean to start a mahabharat over here! First of All ,kunal am sorry if i hurt u personally...didnt have that intention! For the polls, its just a case of different veiws( thats why we have VOTING?!?!) ..coz everyone does'nt think alike..its all abt majority!similarly some of us found the srk thing funny...while some of us thought it was bullshit! no probs dudes! coz thats the fun part of it!secondly... none of us want to hurt each other..so if ur name is included in any poll..or ur pic has been uploaded (manupilated) then dont be surprised or take it seriously !!! coz its a joke ...maybe a bad one ...but it still is a joke!so i hope no more kaboom's on this topic! tc guys! and chill (have some beer)by the way...how many of u do have girlfriends? i had 2 ;)    From: rounak shastri   urlLink  rounaks@yahoo.co.in    > Date: Sat Aug 14, 2004 8:46 pm Subject: Re: [hmps2002] WHOA BOYS!  smartass, all of a sudden you change the topic to how many girlfriends ppl have... NO ANISH! You're not forgiven... yes you're "Unforgiven tooo"(hetfield style)... lol jk... its all good, hope everyone's oknow, namely anish and kunal... (kyd shut up, dont create more confusion, yaar)... aaand yea, lets carryon... you had 2 gfs, is it? well thats nice... I still have the stupid HMPSness within me, sala boys school got me scared of girls... if not scared... a bit too shy... so yea... anyway what abt the rest... Deep I'm sure has like 20 by now (the self proclaimed pimp, as mentioned by someone earlier)... well, glad its all sorted out now... good luck, talk to y'all laterRounak    
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          The long coats that people seem to wear are not meant for protection against rain, but rather against wind. So what I found in Bombay Store was of the same size as my current one, though I had hoped that I would find some longer ones. But of course the make of this macintosh (or was it mackintosh?) was much better. May buy it later.  Khadi Bhandar was disappointing (again).  Had lunch at Cafe Samouvar at Jehangir Art Gallery. It's a nice little place, though a bit pricey. Saw some art after lunch.  Returned home by the A2 bus. This air conditioned bus to town is really convenient.   I don’t think that the book-wallahs atfort should be evicted. Yeah they are hawking, which is illegal, but then they add such a charm to the area, giving it its own distinct feature. We really don’t have many such places in our city. I feel that the existing condition should be improved, but they should certainly not be removed.  
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I went with nana today to a few shops in Santacruz. They (nana and nani) are going to leave for the US in a few weeks, so they have tonnes of things to do. We (nana, nani and myself) had a Maharastrian thali for lunch at Parle (E) with papa. I somehow seem to prefer either Rajasthani or Gujarati thali more. Am I being too biased? I mean, I know one thing for sure, Rajasthan’s forts and palaces seem to be much more interesting than any found in Maharashtra.    I need a better quality wind sheater (or rather rain sheater) to save my self from getting wet. My current wind sheater (thought it is meant to prevent u from getting wet in the rain, we tend to call it a wind sheater) is really no good, I end up quite wet. Another thin is that no matter how good the wind (rain) sheater may be, my legs are always going to end up getting wet, coz there is nothing to protect them. So I was wondering if one of those coat-type-things that they always seem to wear on streets in American TV serials, will do the trick. Apparently they are called mackintosh, quite familiar to Apple’s Macnitosh, eh? So I thought I would ask nana to bring me one from the States, but they are apparently available here also. Some good ones can be found in Bombay Store. Nana has to go to town and I was going to accompany him in any case, so I was hoping that we could go tomorrow itself and get my mackintosh.      There is one call centre guy Rahul, handling Air India’s queries. Nana has become very friendly with him. He is of some reserved class, so his English is very poor. And now nana is guiding him to improve his English. How very interesting! Apparently (now don’t I use that word a bit too often?) nana had asked him to write an essay on any topic, every day for thirty days a week. And the guy actually wrote it for 7 straight days. Now that’s what I call a sincere person. And this essay writing seems to help him. (Of course it will, if you write one every day sincerely). Well good for him, he seems to be doing great.    Signing off now, have to copy a Hindi poem for Tarun from a book, plus have to get up early tomorrow, so that we may go to town, provided of course that it does not rain.  
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       It was raining all day yesterday. Plus there was a strike of BMC and BEST workers, so you can imagine the condition on the roads. Thankfully I didn’t have to venture out anywhere. It seems to be a very clear sky right now, but who knows what can happen after a few hours. I mean Mumbai's monsoon is really unpredictable, though it may be the best rains in the world.  Just 4 days left, before architecture school starts. I’m wondering what I should carry to school on the first day. I mean this ain’t engineering where you know for certain that there will be this subject in this class with this professor. While here, as per what the school’s website says:  “  FIRST YEAR INTRODUCTORY WORKSHOP      Do you remember the song,”mera joota hai japani….ya? c'mon sing, sing it”, these were the words said to us on the first day of the workshop, after a few introductory exercises. And my reaction to this, 'are we being ragged by the Profs and the TAs itself!'.     But later we all realised that there was something lot more to it. This song lead to the theme of the workshop, 'Phir bhi dil hai hindustani'. Within a span of three weeks, we were put to think, imagine and visualise ideas things on a much larger scale.     The strange contraptions we imagined amazed all of us, of course with the help of our Profs and TAs. Groups of students came up with huge props in relevance with themes. All of our work was exhibited before the college and our parents, in the form of a small performance, in which all the students participated. That day definitely made us proud of ourselves.     To add to the excitement, we had a MUMBAI DARSHAN trip, which ended with a stay at Gorai beach. This trip was a learning experience about Mumbai from a different viewpoint. With this came an end to the first workshop, which began to get us thinking and model/prop making.     The very next day started the second workshop, which basically aimed at improving our sketching skills. We were given exercises that helped us understand human figures and spaces in their surroundings. It included some collage making and video shooting, in accordance to the theme of 'Contradictions'. We also shot on some of the roads of Mumbai.     By the end of these two workshops, we were just a month into college but we felt like we could understand many more of the varied ideas that were thrown at us in the past few weeks. ”  Sounds interesting, na?  
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Its been exactly a week since my last post. The main reason for this was that my monitor had shut down, it just wouldn’t turn on. I mean for the past few weeks, the screen had been flickering a lot, but last week it wouldn’t even turn on. Now I have a new Samsung monitor. It is supposed to be 15”, but no matter from which end to which end I measure, it isn't 15”. The picture clarity is really good, much better than my old View Sonic monitor. It was 8 years old. Apparently View Sonic monitors aren’t made any longer.  I got into KRVIA, the architecture school of my choice, in the first round itself. I’m really happy, but it seems that the DTE has really messed up the admissions. The interim fees have been fixed, but these may increase. Mrs. Lalitha (the registrar), wishes me all the best upon submitting the fees, and asks me to work hard, and try for the scholarship. How nice. College should hopefully start on the 16. Wonder what I should carry on the first day ?  The HMPS group on Yahoo! is proving to be a success. We have 25 members within 10 days. People have been very enterprising in posting pics and starting polls. I have started the database, hopefully people will start filling in their info.  I was sorting out the folders on my computer, and came across this diary I had started when I first got a computer at home. Mind you, this is Feb & Mar 2003 and NOT 2004 :    February   2003 :    Tue 18:  The PC finally arrives. The black coloured CPU, keyboard and mouse seem very odd. We have got 242 songs!!! This is cool.   Wed 19:  I am addicted to the PC already. The multiple-users facility is great. I am going to need some time before I can understand Office XP completely. I have decided to start writing a few lines about my day, at the end of every day. Eleventh standard final exams are just a week away, and to be honest, I am not prepared at all.  I need to study, so I am going to close the PC right now.      Thu 20:  Its 12:30 am. I have just finished studying some Chemistry. Tomorrow is my Chemistry practical exam. I shall start studying it in the morning. During the last few days I have been sleeping nearly 10 hours everyday.  Chem. pracs. were ok. Papa’s office is going to be renovated soon by Susan. He is moving all his files, etc home. Our kitchen is looking like a ‘raddhi-wale ka dukan’.    Fri 21:  Physics pracs. were not so great. I nana moved a lot of things, from papa’s office to nani’s house. I really have to start studying for final exams.    Sat 22:  Susan’s workers started their work this morning. Tarun has his ‘Dyanpeeth Exam ‘tomorrow. He says he is nervous. This is the first time I’ve heard him using the word ‘nervous’.   Sun 23:  Paid a visit to papa’s office twice. I met a couple in pap’s building. Couldn’t recognise them. Apparently there is some connection with BCTS. Their son is also with Dagli and Lakshman sir. Final exams on Wednesday!   Mon 24:  I really need to finish off what I aim to finish in a day. A lot of studies are left. I did some skipping today.      Tue 25:  I am not fully prepared for maths.   Wed 26:  Maths was ok. I think I’m getting a new tooth! It hurts if I put on my braces. We may have a major problem here. Today, nani forgot to give Tarun his tiffin-box, and didn’t realise it till Tarun came and told her that somebody had stolen his tiffin-box. Only then did she check in the fridge, and find it there. Tarun had thought that somebody had taken it out from his bag and thrown it away, while he was playing in the silt area, before school begins. So, he went and told this to his teacher, who gave him 10 Rs. So that he could buy himself something from the canteen. He wanted a vada-pao which costs Rs. 5, but since he didn’t have 5 Rs. And only had 10 Rs. So he decided that he would not be able to buy his vada-pao!!!   Thu 27:  English was good. Chemistry tomorrow.   Fri 28:  Rahul and I actually finished one entire Chemistry chapter on the phone in 10 mins!. I think ill make a listof the things I’ll do during the one month break, between 11 th  final exams, and restarting of 12 th  classes. Chemistry was quite good, but I need to avoid silly mistakes.      March   2003 :    Sat 1:  I thought, I would be able to study today. It is quite impossible to do anything else when you have an India-Pak cricket match, especially at the world cup. India won the match handsomely. You should have heard the fire crackers all around!!! No physics today.    Sun 2:  I did study physics today, but not much. Tomorrow’s physics paper is going to be tough. I am thinking of giving tuitions, rather a ‘crash course’ and ‘revision lectures’ in Social Studies for std. V to IX, during the one month break that I have. Let’s see what happens.    Mon 3:  Physics was quite good. I am staying at nani’s house today. I went to papa’s office.   Tue 4:  Computer Science I was ok. I am right now struggling to study flip-flops. What I actually did, was to connect to the net, go to Google and search for flip-flops. After viewing the very first page, my problem was solved. (Actually it had nothing to do with the page itself, but I suddenly understood the part with which I was having a problem.) Anyway, so I then decided to write my own notes about that topic. I did the same on MS Word and then printed it out. You will not believe the amount of time it takes to format (subscript and superscript) words!   Wed 5:  Comp. Sci. II was good! I again messed up that topic on Reserved and Conventional Memory! I went for a movie with pap tonight. We saw ‘Two Weeks Notice’ at Fame Adlabs, during the 10:30 show.   Thu 6:  I saw another movie today! There were 10 of us. We saw ‘The Ring’, a horror movie, at Movie Time, Malad. We ate lunch out. In the evening, I accompanied papa, to the wedding of his friend’s daughter, at ‘The Club’. It was a Marwari wedding. For a moment, I actually thought that I was in Rajasthan.    Fri 7:  I had my Computer Science extra practicals today. I had nearly forgotten about it! They had combined 2 batches, so there were 24 of us. What chaos!   Sat 8:  The idea about giving tuitions/ crash-course/ revision lectures, during the one month break, has now officially been discarded. The main reasons that led to this step are as follows: too short period to give tuitions, revision lectures and crash courses for lower classes are not very popular, lack of adequate means to advertise, enough of twelfth standard work.    Sun 9:  Amma and daddy have gone to Lonavala, with chcha, chachi, Mamta and their servant Archana. I didn’t do anything much today.   Mon 10:  Pap’s office is finally shaping up. Touch wood.   Tue 11:  The computer fellow came today. He put up C++ (though there seems to be some problem in starting it), he took back the speakers(well get a new set), and we are now connected to the internet (finally!). We’ve got a net connection through MTNL. Here, all you need to do is to hook up the line on your PC without having to bother about going to VSNL’s town office (though now days this can be done online), filling up forms, applying for specific hours, etc. We still use dial – up, but it connects quickly, and also seems to be much faster.   Wed 12:  Vivek’s b’day gift--- write more    Thu 13:  Vivek’s b’day --- write more    Fri 14:  Kishor uncle is coming tonight, and bua is coming on Monday night, along with Rohini and Amol.    Sat 15:  I went to papa’s office and then to nana’s house.   Sun 16:  Stayed at nana’s place. Papa’s office’s work got over today. I went to ‘Haveli’ today, after quite some time. They were paying holi with Shri Nathji. I missed the actual play (I was at pap’s office), but I did have a nice darshan. There was so much gulal all over the place. They had live music and songs. The atmosphere was very enthusiastic, merry, and ecstatic.   Mon 17:  Holi hai! Nani had told me that today holi will be played in Haveli at 6:30 am. So I got up at 5:00 and reached Haveli at 6:30, by bus. They were lighting the Holi-fire. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I started a yahoo  urlLink group  of my school mates. Wondering how people are going to respond. We’ve all gone in absolutely different directions. We have many guys doing B. Com. , some along with CA, some are into hotel management and catering, most are waiting for engineering admissions to commence. I think I’m the only one who is going to do architecture.  Speaking of architecture, the allotment of colleges is on the 4th. Wondering which college I will get. I hope I get into  urlLink Kamla Raheja Vidyanidhi Institute for Architecture and Environmental Studies . DTE has really messed up the admission process. This is the first time that they are conducting architecture admissions. I sincerely hope they stop doing it next year. But again, if JJ handles the admissions, then surely they aren’t going to display results or allotment on the net. We would have to trek all the way to CST for everything. Come to think of it, I think  urlLink DTE  is doing a good job. 
      
</post>


</Blog>