<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Waiting…. alone. Not exactly my favorite thing to be doing, especially when everyone is staring at me, like I’m some kind of idiot. It’s amazing… this ability people have, to make you feel inadequate funny thing though, it’s not that they’re trying to, it’s just the shadows, the phantoms in my mind… my own inadequacy rising up to unrealistic proportions, creating monsters from unperceivable fleas. How to change it? Breathe… look around slowly, deliberately. Done… the world is somewhat back to normal with it’s obnoxious people and pleasing climate. Pleasant interruption… she’s finally arrived, I’m not alone anymore… the world fades out with background music. Apologies are made, gracious smiles given, conversation begins.. the phone rings…I’m hungry.The modern conveniences of telephones are sometimes a curse, it adds to the rudeness of the insult created by an ignored conversation… but then, for young love much must be endured, every little details counts when physical distance is involved… and so I graciously reserve my opinion and continue to wait… patiently. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Happiness is rising up within me and yet I cannot relish it, not because I do not want to, but because experience has shown me that if I enjoy my success there is something lurking in the shadows to crush my enthusiasm and my triumph will go unnoticed. With this in mind, this joy is already poisoned. Cynical aren’t I? A true product of consequences arranged and angled to sober my thoughts and to make serious my understanding. Foolishly I cling to childish fantasies but reality has taken care of that error… for the most part.Having prattled on so, I am thus a half baked being of muddled thought, diction, coherent or otherwise, and so, confused I pause for breath and try to remember what it was I was trying to say in the first place! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       List of things to do today      Shoot myself  Call Sabrina  Make payments…  Sometimes it’s hard to be brave and face the music, it’s so much easier to go out into the desert and die. Sometimes it feels like nothing is worth the butterflies that seem to flutter around ceaselessly in your stomach, increasing the tension and the nervousness. Sometimes you need to count the cost before you put it all on the line. Sometimes it takes a lot of courage to put things into perspective. Sometimes it’s so much easier to quit than to push forward.     I came, I stood, I shivered in my shoes….   I’m still standing...because i'm not alone. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yelling… lots of it, voices carrying over from the next room, bringing back childhood memories of loud noises that made you cry, because it was scary and you couldn’t understand it.  The door swings open, he seems relatively unscathed, I’m amazed, if it were I, I’d probably look a little grim at this moment and consider quitting. He hurries to his cubicle and answers his phone. Hmmmm seems to have thicker skin than I imagined.  Nerves are raw, they have been for the last week, it isn’t surprising that the slightest mistake could provoke the most dreaded reaction. Of course this was no little mistake. I’m relieved because for once it doesn’t involve me… Shamefully, yes gleefully even, I secretly rejoice because it doesn’t involve me.  I know the explanations, the answers, yes it’s the stress, yes it’s the tension, still…understanding as I am, I would rather be standing two feet away than be the recipient of this rather unwelcome blast. However no comforting shoulders seem to be required today, no sympathetic ears. Good…. There are other things on my mind ...so many things.  The day is drawing to a close, everything is relatively calm, it is the weekend, silent prayers of thanksgiving are going up all around. One last effort is made to be sympathetic… how else will I win the Nobel prize for being the world’s greatest humanitarian?  Raising my voice I point out that today is supposed to be an unlucky, it is Friday the 13th… we all know what that means. The few words I receive confirm that, that hide isn’t as tough as it pretends to be, men will be men… you know how it is. They’d rather die than let anyone know that they have feelings, well that’s all I’m going to get for today.  That’s all that is required… for today.  Moving on... boy friend trouble, insecurity, job pressure etc..etc.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Weariness seeps in as the phone rings, is it another customer? Maybe it's my workaholic boss? with a lethargic hand, the result of a good book and a late night, I lift the receiver to drone out the mandatory greeting and am pleasantly surprised to find the almost but not quite chipper voice of an old friend, she wants to meet, coffee or tea? Both sound good, she says the choice is mine but I feel her strongly hinting at the tea shop, as I am of a similar inclination choosing to stay away from my beloved dose of battery acid for the sake of unblemished skin, I suggest that we be civilized and English for the evening.  As the day draws to a close, the sky is a radiant orange, with streaks of pink, making the clouds look like exotic cotton candy, the wind picks up, I love that, to my mind a sharp strong breeze makes the air clean, crisp, that's when I'm alive. I head out of the office passing the security guards who never seem to realize that I don't have to pay for parking, one of these days they'll remember. Carefully guiding my middle aged scooty into the Tuesday traffic of buses, auto rickshaws, cyclists and the rest of the mobile monsters, meandering in and out, trying to reach my destination without incident, I feel the tiredness, the monster within howling to be fed.  Ignoring the pleas for pity as I would a prosperous beggar, I look to the pavement to find her standing there, cell phone at her ear, jabbering away. Typical I think to myself as she raises her hand in salutation, she probably after some story or some fact of life that nobody's going to give a damn about tomorrow. Sure enough as she puts away her brand new Motorola and glides her 59 something kilos towards me I wickedly consider if she's still dieting, but right now I don't really care. She tells me that she wangled her way into meeting the West Asia correspondent. Cause for joy. She gets on and we're off, the added weight makes balancing a little difficult specially as she's leaning to one side, however remarks in that direction are unwarranted as they would probably encourage strenuous cursing and would end up being more of a nuisance so I wisely keep my own council.  As we cross over to this so called haven for the crème della crème of Bangalore's future hot shots, (Yeah right) we find it surprising empty, save for a spattering of people, but then, it is a Tuesday night. Oh joy, the most coveted leather couches are finally available, my pounding head rejoices at the prospect of a comfortable piece of fluff to rest upon. As expected she opts for the masala chai and I scan through the herbals settling finally on the chamomile, at that moment I can hear my stomach butting in claiming attention and so to pacify it, the quiche is also ordered. I think that did the trick because my stomach seems to have quieted down.  While we wait, the usual subjects bubble to the surface and of course we have to beat them out as only two women can. Covering the usual range of topics, work, life, love, dreams, plans, ah grateful interruption, the phone rings, I can lean back with my eyes half closed and watch the grains of sand trickle down, the hour glass, letting me know that my five minutes are up so that I can proceed to pour myself a steaming cup. It is time, the tea is poured the sugar added, no milk, the rebel in me refuses to be that civilized.  She seems to be excited about something, she'll let me know soon enough, happy people never seem to be able to keep things to themselves, I can see that she's dying to tell, might as well speed it up, "Who was that?" I ask, "Debashi" and here it comes, "He wants me to go on a road trip with him to Iran to cover the anniversary of the revolution!"  Already I can see the wheels spinning and she muses aloud, "Getting leave won't be a problem, I can sell the story to my newspaper, but how do I convince my parents that it's safe?" As most good little south Indian Brahmins go, she fits in quite well, says her shlokas, doesn't eat meat and is exceedingly intelligent, but otherwise quite the rebel, However I would put today's boost of enthusiasm down to having met the American woman Michael Jansen, that is, the above mentioned West Asian correspondent. I never knew that riding in a jeep with soldiers having bullets flying over your head, could actually inspire people.  Again my mind is drifting, desert sands, heat, the sound of goats in the distance, childhood memories, perhaps better forgotten. Fatigue is starting to kick in, I can't seem to listen to the babbling anymore, we're done anyway, they're clearing the table and we're paying the bill, I drop her off at the bus stand with promises to go book shopping. I have to pass through a muslim inhabited area to get home, it's the shortest route. Taking a deep breath I head towards the market, passing swarms of people, who seems to be walking aimlessly, crowding up the narrow streets, making it difficult, I'm praying that my breaks hold, should have got them checked last week. Women in their burkhas pass by with their children, like jeweled crows. Men are calling to each other across the road, spitting paan, talking, laughing. The smell of unwashed flesh is overwhelming; the thought of getting out of there becomes more and more appealing, finally breaking through, I reach a broader road, only to discover that it has been blocked off.  With no other choice left open to me, I turn to the road on the left and keep going straight, more houses, more people, it's a large locality I think to myself, I have no idea where I am, all I know is that I have to take a right soon or I'll be completely lost. Beginning to feel uncomfortable and a little scared, it's not good to be out late in an unknown area. There, just a little ahead, there seems to be an intersection, at least the road looks broader than these gulleys, might as well take that one. I'm still going straight, according to me I should take one more right to get back to the road I wanted, but something tells me to keep going straight. Everything looks strangely familiar. I'm heading towards the end of the road, I'll have to turn either left or right, what do I do, I hope there's a sign. Thank God! I know where I am! I take the left and I'm home in no time.  In the absence of fear and worry, weariness returns, but I'm home I can rest, or so I thought, but it seems that it's not time yet. I belong to a family and therefore have to be prepared to assist when called upon. Tonight is one of those times, big sister needs to go get some things of a dead friend, her mother is waiting, she's leaving in an hour for America, we have to make our good byes. So I'm on the road again, the wind has picked up, it's a biting cold, should have brought a thicker sweater I lament as I shiver. As we enter the apartment complex the watchman gives us strange looks, we're not suppose to park inside, we're visitors, but you can't always follow the rules, sometimes it's just not safe. Climbing up the stair, I consider doing it everyday when I go to work and then I laugh, me? Climbing 9 floors? Everyday? So not happening.  Pati opens the door and smiles at us, we see aunty crouching on the floor, a moment's puzzlement crosses our faces, till we realize that she's trying to disconnect the telephone cable. After the usual pleasantries, she sends us to buy currency for her phone, she's unfamiliar with it and would rather that the Airtel office recharge the phone. We're out of the building again, walking down the broken pavement, "Do you know where the office is?" I ask, "No" I look in disbelief; she had just told aunty that she knew where it was. So we walk down the road and stop at the first shop, the man sells currency thankfully, so we recharged the phone. Slowly we make our way back up the road, cockroaches scurry across the pavement, hoping not to be trod on, shadows hide them well. Everything is done now, we have what we came for...shoes.  As we make our way back home, I think to myself, it seems wrong to keep these shoes, they were never worn, all of them bought for the day she would walk again, but that day never came, she died before that. It doesn't feel right to wear what was meant to be hers, funny, I didn't feel that way when my grandmother died, nobody seemed to have any qualms about taking her things. And therein lies the tragedy, I knew her better than my own grandmother, I miss her more. Does that make me a bad person? Maybe, at this point it is irrelevant.  Weariness is creeping in, I can feel it, seeping into every bone, it's time to pay the piper, it's time to rest.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Climbing up the stairs to one of the few remaining traditional coffee houses left in Bangalore, I glanced up at the sky, thick clouds of grey floated by like cotton balls, peering down, almost like little children threatening to drop little water balloons on my head. Thankfully shelter was near and time to get there abundant.  As usual the intimidating group of young professionals gathered outside the door, to share their witticisms, news, cigarettes and of course coffee.  They probably don’t realize it, but their formation outside the entrance, resembles something of a human scanner, scrutinizing each person as they pass by, observing possessions, clothing, hairstyles etc. Quite frankly it’s a little unnerving to new comers and being of the easily intimidated sort myself, I tend to proceed with some degree of discomfort.  All that aside, I pass by relatively unscathed, greeting the few familiar faces that graciously tear their noses out of their books to acknowledge my appearance for all of two seconds.  Settling in, I wait for my companion to call of a cup of the usual steaming battery acid as we pull out our own books, either to write or muse over. This place is famous…definitely not for its coffee, or the food for that matter. Maybe people enjoy the fact that they can come to one of the most expensive shopping areas in Bangalore and still get coffee for Rs.5.00/- I cannot be over critical, after all I have enjoyed the convenience of  its presence for a number of years, its rustic feel, the buzz of creative minds flitting in and out like bees in search of wild flowers.  Of course these days the so called creative minds and artsy crowd have meandered their way over to Koshy’s due to certain political reasons (Bah politics!) namely the inability to smoke within the premises of the seating area. Hence the few loyalists resign themselves to enjoying the fresh air outside the entrance therefore intimidating all new comers earlier mentioned.  The coffee arrives with the required 2 glasses of water, the rain has begun, all smokers stroll inside to reclaim vacant spaces and continue a discussion on an idea for a prospective business venture, requiring some knowledge of clay and 2D animation.  Pausing in my writing to consider the proper application of “sollecitare” I take in the sight around me, surrounded by a melting pot of creativity in the form of artists, writers, sculptors, designers, I realize how insignificant my talent is, how lacking in depth, how raw and unrefined.  Smiling, I continue to write, disregarding the insignificant interruption, my writing is my pleasure and if it amuses another soul then I am grateful for a kindred spirit, if not, I am grateful of the opportunity to be unique. Why does this coffee house, inspire my thoughts more than others, why does it signify, this anachronism?   Perhaps, it draws us, because it symbolizes something we all look for, this kaccha structure of brick and mortar, unrefined and very 50’s in appearance represents a beginning, a starting point.  I won’t romanticize on the structure, suffice to say that it’s rather old-fashioned walls; fans and paintings bring to mind an era, a culture that is quickly growing out of fashion.  The rain has stopped, the crowd is still moving like a lumbering beast on the pavement, it is difficult to press on without banging into another person. The wind has picked up, it will be a cold night.  A sense of peace pervades all senses; there is a feeling of well being, of purpose fulfilled.  Ah the joys of musing for the sole purpose of self-entertainment on a fine Sunday evening, these are the days we live for… for the few and far between. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting back I admired the latest addition to the office curios, a 12”x12” knots and crosses board, ‘something to do if I get bored’ I smiled. Out of the corner of my eye I could see someone approaching the office, the lighting outside the door wasn’t all that great and it was causing glass to reflect of glass, providing a very distorted view.  The door opened, forcing my head to the side I noticed my boss’ driver entering, he seemed to be carrying a lot of food from Coffee Day, ‘boss must be hungry’. Not thinking much of it, I returned to my pleasant occupation of admiring the board, vaguely registering that he stopped to talk to the technician.  All adoration duly paid, I turned back to my computer and continued to make out the invoice that was going to bring us some more money. (Don’t really hear cash registers going off in my head.) The man was now standing by my desk, ‘God’ I grumbled, ‘hope he doesn’t have some idiotic thing to say today.’ The man, according to me thought he knew everything about everything and even if he didn’t, there was always an opinion about the subject. On most days we ignored each other, pretending to be exceedingly busy, but today was not going to be one of those days.  Looking up a hint of a smile graced my rather sarcastic lips and of course didn’t quite touch my eyes (could it be otherwise?) He pulled out a box from the bag (there was a huge piece of chocolate cake in it, pity I’m not fond of chocolate.) and handed it to me, for a moment I was confused, did my boss think I was hungry and had ordered for me too? Giving the driver a rather puzzled questioning look, he took his cue and explained in a matter of fact tone, “It’s my birthday.”  Of course, were I a sensible person I would have politely wished him and thanked him for the gesture. But being the hapless wit that I am, I creased my forehead and demanded no less than three times, “Really?” The surprise gradually fading away I blurted out, “um happy birthday.” “Thank you” he mumbled and went in to suck up to the only person who really mattered… the boss.  I did, quite naturally I might add, pause to reflect on the situation and of course feel the pricks of conscience for the earlier snubs, for not being more patient and understanding. Perhaps I shouldn’t have snitched on him in the beginning, he could have been a good ally. Perhaps he would have taught me the mysterious art of sucking up. I must confess I just don’t get it.  After mulling over these thought for all of a few minutes, reality filters in, I refused to let this piece of cake be my poisoned apple. If it must be food, then let it be something of greater consequence. I know that this breed of human is dangerous, because he is genuinely good natured and yet there is something, a certain cunning, I cannot place it exactly but I know it is there. My inner warning bells indicate a requirement for caution.  True I might be overreacting; it is in my nature to do that, genetic legacy I believe. By this time reality is at maximum saturation and all sympathy forgotten, quite literally. And so I go back to my cake. We will continue as usual, I will find him annoying and he shall continue to annoy me, (on purpose I’m sure) I shall however do my best to be kinder….  After all, that was some good cake! 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Owning up to a screw up, is a difficult thing, especially when something greater than a frown is at stake.   You can hear the words, "it's not your fault..." somehow you know it was meant otherwise, "it's entirely your fault." You sense the frustration, you see the restraint. So many words... sticks and stone, sticks and stones...  There's that sinking feeling, the one that lets you know that pond scum has better days than you. Your head is hot, everything seems fuzzy, emotion clogs up the oxygen pipes, decidedly denying your brain the opportunity to think.  A tear slips down, you can't stop it... there's nowhere to hide, the shame burns on your face. Desperately you look around, the bathroom! you run... almost.  Inside... the tears roll, flowing fast and free. Times up, got to get back to work. The air comes more easily now, rational kicks in.  You're not entirely to blame, your share is not as big as they would like it to be... relife.  The repercussions are easy to bear, because they are left to be fulfilled in solace, although not completely deserved, but that is of no consequence now.  Perfection leaves no room for error, no room for second chances... 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was like watching a sheet of paper being knocked down by a steam roller. The chain jingled as Brandi rushed towards the gate, she loves getting out of the house, anything to get a whiff of that garbage. As expected she dragged me around the block, refusing to use the abundance of nature's providence, otherwise known as dog's Facilities. The air was a little nippy, it had just rained after all. Brandi headed to a favorite corner and my heart beat with anticipation, perhaps I'd get lucky, maybe, just maybe she'd potty outside today. That's when it all began. The old lady got out of the car, leaning forward, she said a few words in malayalam and waved good bye to the old couple in the car, looking both ways she wrapped her shawl around her and began to cross the road. I watched her go, not really paying attention, Brandi was trying to eat something off the road... A whimper of brakes reached my ears and as I looked up I saw the old lady crumple as the motorcycle hit her. " Oh my God!" I whispered, people were coming from every direction, Moni ran to help her, I wouldn't expect anything less, he's the good Samaritan of the neightbourhood. People stopped, there was Glenn with his wife and child, somebody helped the man on the motorcycle up, he seemed stunned. I stood rooted to the spot, instant flashback held me there for a second, I had been hit by a cycle at the same spot when I was four or five, I could see the coins that I was taking to a beggar scattered everywhere, I saw myself howling not because I was hurt rather because of the sudden shock, besides I think by then I'd been well trained to cry when confronted with the unknown. The situation seemed to be under control, Moni had gone to get her family, the other man seemed to be feeling better, there were enough people around to argue the case, to defend and accuse. Slowly I turned around and tried to keep pace with my 3 month old Lab who raced back home. That was a somewhat unexpected end to a rather nice day. Talk about a memorable 24th. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This afternoon, I was talking to my  urlLink sister  she was telling me about something she remembered as a child, the conversation went something like this. Sister: I remember when I was small, people would pick me up by holding me under the arms and that hurt, I'll never do that to a child. Me: Yeah that's not the way you do it, the right way to do it is to gently hold the loose skin at the back of their necks and lift them up, unless you prefer to lift them up by their ears... Sister: What?! Me: Yeah, that's the right way to carry puppies.  Yeah, i know what you're thinking....   
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A couple of years ago a worked for a printing company that pretty much drove me up the wall, to save my sanity, I wrote little notes about things in general, mostly for fun.  Much ado is the fashion of the day... Much ado about nothing.  Many a word needs be said upon this special eve but actions they say carry a much better tune.  I chance upon a time to ponder in the shadows of the dawn by fortune's fate, good thoughts evade me and I am left staring at a cold stone floor.  The uncertainty of time and the certainty of its abundance has left me with more than a few choice words and a complete lack of expression.  Before action there is thought and between the two is a varying amount of courage to combat the hesitation.  Ambiguity is the thought of the day and yet I would not wish such singularity of thought Not because it is wrong Simply because it is lonely.  Long live the foolishness of thought that causes us to live in peace and teaches us to love.  All work and no play makes Jack a "very" dull boy why doesn't anyone get that?!!  Too much is said and I would that much were unsaid that however is something only the blessing of a bad memory can achieve.  A horrid cold in the middle of summer is one of nature's more ingenious pranks.  Words always stay etched in your memory never forgotten only buried and although you may not remember them precisely it's the feeling they carried that you won't forget.  Passionate speeches and long winded sermons may be a bore, but a tolerable banter will do.  I supposed to reciprocate a feeling one must first stimulate it.  Some words could be better spoken and others better written but if a lack of refinement pleases just as well if not more then the absence of eloquence is of little import.  What would life be without these moments of lameness where humour is found in simplicity itself.  Sometimes being alone is stomach wrenching specially in a room full of people.  One's strength grows off another's weakness human nature I guess...or is it divine?  Not always getting what you want can be a pain in the ass!  Contemplation is a funny thing, the more you think the less sense things make. Is it the discovery of individualism or just discovering that your opinion doesn't always co-exist with everyone else's  They say that there is a time for everything I believe that now is the time to eat.  I have learnt that you can never judge another till you walk in their shoes. God only knows what your response would have been in the same circumstances.  Ever notice how we're reminded of the right things when we're doing the wrong things.  I admire people who can work even when there is no interest or inspiration.  To pick on the weak is detestable even if it causes great amusement.  Never underestimate the power of concentration it is essential to achieve perfection.  Asking for help is not such a bad thing after all...  The most idiotic situations can cause one's confidence to fail.  Dissatisfaction can lead to self sabotage.  What punishment can torture more than guilt?  Always running with no place to go.  They say that if you love somebody you should be able to let them go....you're kidding right?  Life is full of ups and downs, who knew it would get this bumpy.  One of these days there will be a tongue to express what we really want to say.  Sometimes time gets down on its hands and knees and crawls.  Specialization is for those who have a single talent to improve upon.  You maybe great, but great isn't good enough.  History is as short as memory.  Thinking and then believing are all that's needed to achieve anything.  Strange how the absence of one can make a difference to all... and this case that's not a very good thing.  Changes are occurring all around in everybody's life and the questions yelling in my head is, when will the right ones happen in mine??  One of these days I will remember that it is my duty to come late!  At times like these sleep is a wonderful thing and killing Edward the next best thing.  The mask of a diplomat is a difficult face to wear.  Haste leaves no room for error.  Induced boredom is a fine way of killing any inspiration for work.  Alone and yet...full of myself!  All dressed up with nobody to see...nobody that counts that is.  Disorientation is good...for about 5 minutes.  If you're doing a job you don't like is it because your the kind of person who can't say no...or are you just that stupid?  No matter what people claim, in the end it's all about survival.  Silence and stillness can lead to madness a little noise never hurt anybody.  Breaking a person's spirit is devastating... Why are we so cruel?  If you're always striving to be more than you are will you ever be content?  One thing I've learnt from Peter Pan is that everybody needs a happy thought.  When in doubt..ask for directions!  They say, " whistle while you work." I'm not sure that's such a good idea.  When doors close, windows open, there's always a plan B.  Doing a job that entails constant rejection is not very healthy.  Predefining personal space is essential for healthy work relationships.  You know cursing really doesn't improve one's disposition at all.  Everybody wants to be appreciated, that's why we show off.  Staying focused on the path is not easy, specially when there are so many pretty things along the way!  Uniqueness is a vanity we cannot do without!  You cannot undo a wrong, but you can try to make up for it.  Sometimes it's good to hesitate.  When the dust rises, cover your face and duck!  Trying to fly only to discover that I don't have wings.  What excuse can pardon a short temper and mean disposition? I need one!  When people are talking at you from all directions, don't you just feel like telling them to shut up?!!  When you mentally alienate yourself from someone, physical distance makes no difference.  Eagerness can make you slip, learn to be patient.  When you can't hear people you forget that they're there.. sneaky huh?  For a moment time stood still...I can still see it in my head  My world is at peace, don't disturb me! I want to savor this moment for a while.  It's not what you say that makes a difference, it's how you say it.  Sweet words, valueless except for their sentiment and yet, they might as well have been gold.  Blank...I need to jump start my pen.  Wants are like weeds, no matter how often you pull them out there are always more.  The definition of right and wrong is continuously changing someday we're not going to recognise the difference at all.  Pensive moments, times of trying too hard isn't it nice to just let things go?  I feel like an object out of time apprearing to fit in, and yet, appearances are so deceptive.  If one must look back, let it be in acknowledgement of something learnt and not because of a desire for something lost.  The ancient Egyptians threw out the brain because they believed that it had no value... not much has changed since then.  Look past the end of your nose, there is another world besides your own.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>