<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Unfortunately, I don't have much time to post today but I did want to share this site that someone sent me.&nbsp; It the  urlLink Animal Rescue Site .&nbsp; Go to it, click on the purple button.&nbsp; For every click the site's sponsors donates food to a animal shelter or santuary.&nbsp; Bookmark it!&nbsp; It's something simple you can do to help.&nbsp;    
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was talking to my sister on the phone last night and telling her about something that happen to me at the mall.   Picture this: I'm at the mall and I haven't eaten all day but I'm going to dinner with friends in an hour or so. I decide to get a snack so I stop at Mrs. Fields and get one of those yummy toffee cookies. I'm eating my cookie and walking to go to my car and I notice that people I pass are smiling at me, even giggling a little. Do I have something on my face? Hmmm... I get to within 5 steps of my car and I realize that I have my Cookie Monster t-shirt on&nbsp;(yeah, I know, I'm too old) and that's why people were laughing at me. Uhg. How embarassing.  Anyway, I tell my sister this story and she says, "I can just see you now, ponytail swinging, all hunched over and doing that little shuffle you do and eating a cookie."   What? Ponytail? Hunched over? SHUFFLE?!  "What are you talking about?" I asked her.&nbsp; "I don't do those things."  "Uh, yeah you do but it's cute! When you walk your ponytail swings from side to side. Violently. It could be used as a weapon. I think its because of the way you walk, you know, how you don't really lift your feet you just...shuffle. Don't get me started on the hunching, you have terrible posture."   Yeah, sounds real freakin' cute. Why am I picturing the hunchback of Notre Dame?  
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I guess I could tell you about myself.&nbsp; I'm&nbsp;a 26 year old, flight coordinator&nbsp;(don't ask) who is&nbsp;experiencing what I like to&nbsp;call a quarter-life crisis.&nbsp; A quarter-life crisis&nbsp;hits when you're in you mid-20's and&nbsp;it's when all of a sudden&nbsp;you&nbsp;have&nbsp;no idea who you are&nbsp;or what you want&nbsp;to be.&nbsp; That's where&nbsp;I am right now.  I&nbsp;noticed&nbsp;I was&nbsp;experiencing a quarter-life crisis when I was getting dressed to go out not too long ago.&nbsp; I have this&nbsp;Miller High Life trucker hat that I adore.&nbsp; I had my hair in pigtails, put the&nbsp;hat on and cocked it to the side.&nbsp; I looked in the mirror and it was then I realized that I can&nbsp;NOT pull that look off anymore.&nbsp; I'm simply too old.&nbsp; When&nbsp;did that happen?!  Then I started noticing other things like going to bed&nbsp;BEFORE midnight, talking constantly about the weather and gas prices, calling the teenagers at the mall "those damn kids"...&nbsp;  *gasp*  I'm&nbsp;my mom.  So, here I am,&nbsp;keeping a blog and letting you experience this quarter-life crisis with me.&nbsp; Aren't you lucky?  &nbsp;   
      
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been having some very weird dreams lately.  My mom says, and Korean's believe, that you dream more when the seasons change which for as long as I can remember I've found to be true.  For some reason my dreams are always really weird and get weirder as it get's closer to the time when the seasons change.  The other night I had a dream that I was back in Germany and some friends and I were out going to the bars but at the same time we were looking for something.  We went to our usual place in Kaiserslautern called the Harp.  We had a few drinks but didn't find what we were looking for so we moved on to the next bar, the Hannen Fass.  We walk in and there's a bunch of people gathered around someone near the bar.   As we get closer we realize that it's John Stevens, the red head from American Idol, and he's drunk off his ass, sitting on the floor, singing Irish drinking songs.  That's all I remember.     Weird huh?  I think we've still got some time before the season actually do change.  I can't imagine how much weirder my dreams will get. 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've been having some very weird dreams lately.  My mom says, and Korean's believe, that you dream more when the seasons change which for as long as I can remember I've found to be true.  For some reason my dreams are always really weird and get weirder as it get's closer to the time when the seasons change.  The other night I had a dream that I was back in Germany and some friends and I were out going to the bars but at the same time we were looking for something.  We went to our usual place in Kaiserslautern called the Harp.  We had a few drinks but didn't find what we were looking for so we moved on to the next bar, the Hannen Fass.  We walk in and there's a bunch of people gathered around someone near the bar.   As we get closer we realize that it's John Stevens, the red head from American Idol, and he's drunk off his ass, sitting on the floor, singing Irish drinking songs.  That's all I remember.     Weird huh?  I think we've still got some time before the season actually do change.  I can't imagine how much weirder my dreams will get. 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Our company has a suite at the MCI Center and sometimes we can get the tickets.  Saturday night I went to the Prince concert.  If he's coming to your city anytime soon, definately go.  He's amazing in concert and I have to say there's something incredibly sexy about him.  Usually I'm not attracted to short men who wear high heels and more make up than me but this man just oozes sexuality and confidence.   So I have two new obsessions: 1.) Prince 2.) The Olympics.  I can not get enough of the Olympics.  I watched synchronized womans diving the other night for like and hour.  Those Chinese girls are good.  I was glued to the tv watching sailing.  Sailing?  Who watches sailing?  Me, that's who.  Water polo - love it.  Woman's field hockey?  How did I live without it before?  I tell ya, I'm obessed. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday my mom nonchalantly asked about my love life. I told her that it was, at present, nonexistent. Boy did she look disappointed!  Being a modern girl who doesn't see myself settling down anytime soon can be hard with old school parents like mine. My mom is Korean and thinks I should have been married years ago. My dad is from Idaho. Need I say more? Most of the girls in my family on that side get married and have kids barely out of high school.  I keep hoping my little sister will get hitched to someone soon so it'll take some of the pressure off me. 
      
</post>


</Blog>