<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        She's the one you call when you're bored because she makes you laugh. She's the one you talk to when you're feeling down because she's willing to lend an ear and be a friend. She's not the one you call when you need a date to your company's Christmas party, or to go dancing with on a Saturday night. She's the one you spend time with between girlfriends, before you find "The One". You know, the one who you keep around in the meantime.    She's not one of the guys, not a tomboy, but you don't look at her as a "real" woman, either. She's not bitchy enough, moody enough, or sexy enough to be seen in that light. She's too laid-back, too easily amused by thesame things your male buddies are amused by. She's too understanding, too comfortable - she doesn't make you feel nervous or excited the way a "real" woman does. But she's cool, and nice, and funny, and attractive enough that when you're lonely or horny and need intimate female companionship, she'll do just fine. You don't have to wine and dine her because she knows thereal you already, and you don't have any facades to keep up, no pretenses to preserve.    You're not trying to get anything of substance out of her. She's not easy, but you know that she cares about you and is attracted to you, and that she'll give you the intimacy you need. And you know you don't have toexplain yourself or the situation, that she'll be able to cope with thefact that this isn't the beginning of a relationship or that there's any possibility that you have anyreal romantic feelings for her.    It won't bother her that you'll get up in the morning, put on your pants, say goodbye, and go on a date with the woman you've been mooning over for weeks who finally agreed to go out with you. She'll settle for a goodbye hug and a promise to call her and tell her howthe date went. She's just so cool . . . why can't all women be like that?! But deep down, if you really think about it (which you probably don't because to you, the situation between the two of you isn't important enough to merit any real thought), you know that it's really not fair.    You know that although she would never say it, it hurts her to know that despite all her good points and all the fun you two have, you don't think she's good enough to spend any real time with. Sure, it's mostly her fault, becauseshe doesn't have to give in to your needs - she could play the hard-to-get bitch like the rest of them do, if she really wanted to. But you and she both know that she probably couldn't pull it off. Maybe she's too short, or a little overweight, or has a big birthmark on her forehead, or works at Taco Bell. Whatever the reason, somehow life has given her a lot of really great qualities but has left out the ones that men want (or think they want) in a woman.    So she remains forever the funny friend, the steadfast companion,the secret lover, and you go on searching for your goddess who will somehow be everything you ever wanted in a woman. You'll joke to her that she should be the best man at your wedding, andshe'll laugh and make a joke about a smelly rental tux. She doesn't captivate you with her beauty, or open doors with her smile.Mainly she blends in with the crowd. She's safe. She doesn't want to be the center of attention and turn the heads of everyone in the room. But she wants to turn someone's head. She wants to be special to someone, too. We all do.She has feelings. She has a heart. In fact, she probably has a bigger and better heart than any woman you've ever known because she's had a front-row seat to The Mess That Is Your Life, and she likes you anyway. She obviously sees something worthwhile and redeeming in you because although you've given her nothing, absolutely no reason to still be around, she is. Anyway, yeah. I'm a Meantime Girl.    Been one more times than I care to admit. I don't know the reason, really, and at this point I don't even care. I just want to let every guy know who's ever had the good fortune to have a Meantime Girl that we may be a lot of fun, but we cry, too. A lot. And someday we won't be around.....     
    
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        i never expected that you'll text me back cuz i have been texting you before but i wasnt getting any answer, so your reply took me by surprise and you even did replied again and again that night. but only that night... i told myself not to linger anymore on things that i cant have, i'll just think happy thoughts. not think of you, not even talk to you but i cant help it. i cant even help not feel missing you. i know i know it's wrong but, well sad me then...       in my phone...   text-unsent message-just wanna let you know i miss you.     
    
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
           WAAAAAAAAAH!!!!  is this nice ..what else can put in here? what kind of pictures can i attach here?          
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          My Element is Light. I am friendly, happy, social, bubbly, and can brighten up any one's day. I am very kind and a real people person because you have several friends (or atleast should). And cheery nature makes me lovable and my stunning looks are sweet and stand out.     
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          "Virgo"       August 22 - September 21Try not to be so much of a stick-in-the-mud today, dear Virgo. Other people aren't going to want to take the time to pull you out and drag you along with them. Take the initiative yourself. If you want to have fun, you need to create it for yourself. The biggest part of this equation is simply your attitude. Realize that other people can sense your jealous nature, so don't think you are fooling anyone. Let others live their lives. You need to concentrate on your own.....   
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        last friday... Ivo (my friend) and I went to Greenblet 3 to watch a film... The Village, last screening at around 12am. the film was quite stressful because of the sound effects that makes you close your eyes but still nothing happens. Though the story was not that really scary if one will base it from the trailer. the movei do have this twist about a village that a group of people created because of their horrid past.. and they want to keep innocence intact... there are lines in the movie that one will find corny and too deep to absorb as mushy but well after a little while one will think that it was nice and ironic... " you stopped touching me or holding my hands" ...    
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I can sometimes see myself up inside a lighthouse. 
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         some nice things and places that we can connect to the 80's    1. Astroboy!! ( I love astroboy)   2. sybelles ( i hope that i got the spelling right, this is where my mum use to buy her shoes)   3. fairmart ( do we still have this one?)   4. rustans makati with a nice park outside so that one can eat their waffled hotdog on stick   5. fiesta carnival with waffled hotdog still ( i think that was my favorite food then) ... enchanted kingdom of the 80's kiddos    6. waffled hotdog and snow cones    7. Aga dancing the moonwalk...bwahahahaha   9. student canteen    10. uncle bob's lucky 7 club    11. SM toy store (toy kingdom? blah!)   12. bazooka bubblegum and their comics    13. tarzan bubblegum nyahahahaha!!!    14. george estregan.. porn king of the phil. movie industry together with his softdrinks sarsi and pepsi...coke? there's no coke?    15. john and marsha    16. tito pepe and his kwarta o kahon    17. kuya germs and his bellstar dancers    18. yellow cabs...not the pizza but the yellow cabs, plus the love bus    19. makati atrium, posh place before where you can have chit chats and coffee..though still standing there, my mum use to take me along with her there before    20. micheal jackson and his thriller mtv       well i still do have alot to add on my 80's list and am loving doing this list but am tired now so i'll just go home for a the meantime and get a good nigth sleep, but what really makes me feel 80'ish is that when i look into old pics and see my mum posing in our old house in the province with me and my brother beside her and she's wearing short shorts...hehehehehe        
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          I am what people call an "unica hija", the first child and the only girl. my dad considers me a gift cuz he doesnt have any girl sibling and am so close to him, although my mumsie is my bestfriend and my brothers are my barkada. my dad was able to take care of me when i was still small but because were not rich and my parents wants to give the world to us, when i was three, he went to work abroad, first was to saudi, he would go home once a year then will stay with us for like a month which we consider lucky us or just a week. then after 5 years of going out, my parents decided to go home to mumsie's province, bacolod, and just put up a small business, we had then a small rice store but after three years before edsa 1, fire ate up our business... we didnt have any choice then but to go back to manila and for dad to go abroad, this time off to the land of milk and honey and lotsa dumb people (whahahha). he worked for disney world's luxury ship, "the big red boat", as a chief butcher, he'd go home to us once a year a again and this time were lucky if he stays with us for 2weeks. he do spoils me, educated and sent me good school, gave me material stuff, my classmates then even tease me, what manel wants manel gets. happy? me? yes i am somehow, but i do sometimes wish that i do have a complete family, complete in the sense that my mum, dad, brothers are there everytime i go home... that when someone courts me then i got this dad who can bully the guy and tell him not to hurt my li'l girl, that when someone breaks my heart i can go home crying and that i can cry on his shoulders, not just cry but whail my heart out till i get tired and fell asleep. i know he tries to see to it that he's there at every significant occassion in my life like my first js prom, though he missed my debut. he did called, yes, i know he can feel that his li'l girl misses him alot. i cant remember how many xmas's that we missed having him with us. it's been five years now since he last went home, he do calls us up, we do send text messages once in awhile, he is still the best provider ever materially but still i know that he is aware that we are longing for him to be with us so much and that how he wish that were still li'l kids... corny it may sound but while doing this one, my eyes are in tears. miss you dad...soooooooo much!      
    
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Time can never mend the careless whispers of a good friend     To the heart and mind, ignorance is kind     there's no comfort in the truth pain is all you'll find ....        lines from george micheal's song  careless whispers ..that was song that blurted on me when i turned on my radio this morning, then it brought me back to memory lane... the 80's..( baduy! mag reminisce ba?)..  i was born at the dawn of the 80's, basically grew up listening to chicago, rolling stones, pink floyd, metallica, queen, bob marley, aerosmith, kiss (courtesy of my uncles and my dad), but then i cant help but love madonna and george micheal (which i find very very sexy and i dont care if he's gay) eventhough then everytime i wake up in the morning i can hear mama i killed a man in our radio... and my lullaby is color my world by chicago.       The 80's are the days of big hair and shocking colors, corny it may look but i listed down things that i was able to pull up in my cerebrum hehehehe:    1. shocking hairs courtesy of aquanet    2. sneaker,trets and high cut converse   3. tight fit jeans for men    4. trapper keepers for school    5.rainbow brite    6. striped blouses ( my mum and i used to own some then hehehe)    5. white pants (baston dapat!) and the GET USED prints on your pants    6. big belts    7. walkman    8. beta max (laser disc and vhs came on the later part i guess and early 90's)    9. Gabby Concepcion and Aga with the bagets are your kind of man (i find herbert bautista then cute)   10. short shorts for GUYS!!!   11. pair it with long socks    12.COD every christmas and the big xmas tree in araneta    13.ice cream parlors are in not coffee shops (lost ang starbucks!)   14.G.I joes and transformer    15. family computer, you're a hit if you know mario bros and you already have beaten king koppa and also that you also know battle city like the back of your hands    17. Papa dont preach!!    19. the seiko wallet jingle every afternoon in your t.v.    20. See True (i forgot the shampoo jingle they use to play there hehehe)      to be continued....          
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        My shift ended at around 5am this morning, and after eating brunch with a couple of friends, went home at around 12, was not able to get sleep right away cuz got some visitors a home. the boogieman visited me at around 3pm and my clock shouted at me at around 5pm... but still i was able to find energy to pull myself up and go to work. funny though, i know that am so tired and all but still i feel so high, my energy level is way up on ten... why do i feel so perky perky today? am i trying to hide something? i know deep down inside me i am covering up for something.. i am in denial, i just wanna look happy but i know am not... this is hard but i am enjoying it, it makes me look stupid and it makes me feel weak, i know i am weak, i am a coward, i am nothing... aaaaaarrrrgggghhh!! i dont wanna feel so damn depressed so i guess i'll just go on with this "joke" i have going on..    
    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Love is never easy, butIt turns life into song.   There is no bit of circumstanceThat love cannot transform.    There is no weary momentOf anger or despair   That love cannot convert to graceAnd render whole and fair.    How passionate the paradiseThat comes from knowing wellThat someone in your happinessFinds pleasure for himself.    How sweet the gift of giving toSomeone who gives to you,   A selflessness that gives to self   More self than self is due.    With all the searing madness ofThe world from day to day,   And all the dreary sadness thatNo joy can take away,    There is one truth more beautifulThan anyone can bear:   That two can trust that when they turn   They'll find the other there.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Through the fireTo the limit,      to the wall     For a chance to be with youI’d gladly risk it all     Through the fire     Through whatever,      come what may     For a chance at loving youI’d take it all the way     Right down to the wire     Even through the fire     
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          I am going to  Marry Josh Hartnett according to this blah site. He is really shy, but don't let that fool you. He is really outgoing and sweet with those he loves and will be loyal to them for the rest of his life. Congrats!! for me..dream on!! but i really like him..soooo sexy!!!    my type of guy?..someone fun to be with.. not dumb, not that sexy, and will love me..for who i am..who doesnt want that kkind of kind of guy huh?!       
    
    
</post>


</Blog>