<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whether it is or isn't really fat is irrelevant.  I couldn't get it up off the mat to save my life.  I guess eating that birthday cheesecake wasn't a good idea.  C'mon, tina, get with the program.   Are you going to take fighting seriously, or not?  It's time to make a real change, and I mean for real, this time.  Really.  I mean it. 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today, I actually got myself out of the house and out to Krav Maga class.&nbsp; I almost talked myself out of it 'cuz I was feeling so lazy.&nbsp; Definitely not one of my psyched-up days.&nbsp; My mind was asleep&nbsp;so I wasn't putting forth the best effort.&nbsp; I made it through without even thinking about quitting, well except for the the short time Paul was throwing knees into my abdomen.   
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night, I went to Jiu-Jitsu class and got psyched.&nbsp; I felt so good and charged up, like I could take on the world.&nbsp; I had a good spar, and even though I couldn't tap him, he couldn't tap me either.&nbsp; I started thinking, "I can do this!&nbsp; I can get good at this!"&nbsp; I was so revved up.  Then, this morning happened.&nbsp; I'm gonna have to make myself go to class tonight.&nbsp; It's the only way I'm going to improve.&nbsp; But, I can't understand why I don't feel as good as last night.&nbsp; If only I could stay on top of the world... 
      
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wasted.  That's how I felt last night at training.  I have been slipping up in every way - eating too much, sleeping too much, and just being lazy as hell.  I can hardly even stand now I'm so weak, much less put up a fight against the 200 pounder with his knee on my belly. 
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah.  Allen was no pushover, either.  So what if he's only been training for one month.  I tapped him 4 times in a row.  I'm just glad he didn't start crying about it like the last guy. 
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's what I told Jeff when he was about to choke me. Okay, that is cheating, but at least I escaped! Ha Ha! But I really did feel like puking for a second. It's not my fault he went all soft on me when we're supposed to be sparring. Sooner or later these guys will stop being so nice to me, and then I'll be sorry. Maybe. 
      
</post>


</Blog>