<Blog>


<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         me, lizelle, joanna     me, lizelle joanna     joanna, lizelle, me 
      
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      RULES: Write a statement intended for&nbsp;14 different people. NEVER TELL which one is for who.   1. we known each other for 2 years now when i met you in high school.... even though we may not be best of friends anymore because of many disagreements... im still here for you as a friend.. i learned many things from you... and i dont regret any of the agruements we had because i learned something new from all of them... hopefully we will have a better school year next year... see you soon... lylas   2. ive known you since the 9th grade by the one above.... even though you thought i didnt like you as a friend you were really nice... now that we got so close... so close that your the first thing i see in the morning... my roomate!... cant wait till you come back.. its kinda quiet now that you went to your moms.... luv ya!!   3. ive known you for a loong time now.. youve been there whenever i needed someone... when i was bored you would always find something interesting to do... you're my dieting partner... you did it but not me... you we're always there to give me a lift.... you're my chubby partner! love you!   4. we havent had a deep conversation in a long tiiimme... you left for the summer... and i havent seen you in a long time... hopefully the next time i see you we could catch up on all the things we missed out on... you need to sleep over sometime... i hope everythings going okai with you... call me sometime.... miss ya! 143   5.&nbsp; i know things between me and you are different.... different then before... you were the person that i always turned to and you would&nbsp;always make me smile and you still do...&nbsp; you would always make me laugh my head off because of the silliest things.. i dont care what other ppl think of you or what they say.... you will always have a place in my heart... i hope you know im always here for you if you need anything... im only a phone call away..and dont worry.. im not mad at you... i never was...&nbsp;i still love you.......   6. my parnter in crime... my buddy... where u at?!... mayn i miss those days where we would just chill.. when you were down here in fort washington... we have some many laughs together... and we think alike... your my twin!.... lolz... we still need to change our handshake.. we had that one for like 2 years already... well i mish you!! come back.... 143   7. ive known you for like 2 years now? i dont know... but to me it seems like i known you ever since we were little... you were always there for me through anything and everything... even though your like 8932 hours away you still seem to keep in touch.... thanks for the everyday phone calls and saving me from boredom... remember you have 2 phone numbers! 215 and 267....you know im always here for you... hopefully we could chill soon.. k?! love ya!   8. my laughing partner... we would laugh at anything even though there would be nothing to laugh at... i would just make fun of your high pitch voice.... lolz remember the time where you couldnt find your milk?! lolz where my milk?! you bout to flip out at me and raisha... rememeber playing that name game at like 2 in the morning... YENNIS! YODEL!... lolz funny... i hope u know im here for you.... luv ya !   9. make her have big boobs and big hips&nbsp; " I'm calling my dad!" awwwww... lolz ive known you ever since you came here... and you&nbsp; used to talk about me when you used to speak tagalog... you&nbsp; made me cry!..... but know your a young adult and your so pretty.... thanks for all the deep talks we would have.. its good to know that little adings like you can give great advice.. thanks for everything... i love you!   10. i want your phone! lolz remember that... you always seem to always know whats on my mind... or if something is bothering me... you know what lets go skiing... lets see if you got better.. lolz... erry body in dis club gettin tipsy.. havin our own club... and slumber parties.. but you only showed up.. hahaha.... thanks for all those convos... even though i didnt feel like talking to you! jk... luv ya   11. ive known you all my life... and you are one of my closest cousin.... maybe cuz you live close by... well just wanted to say thanks for everything... and even though we argued just a bit... we always seemed to kiss and make up..lolz... im always here for you.... and maybe starting next year i could ride with you! lets get icecream! 143   12. i see you everyday.. and i spend most of the day babysitting you...... even though you always annoy me... you always seem to make me laugh... good luck i n the last year of elementary school... and can you please leave me alone... your bothering me right now... but i still love you!   13. ive known you all my life... and you seem to&nbsp; understand me more than mommy... thank you for everything and i mean everything... even though i know i annoy you all the time.. i try not to... it comes natural... you still owe me!..... i didnt forget... hopefully we could diet together... hmmm ill think about it....... i cant fit your clothes anymore!... luv you!   14. yo my nigggggaaa.... lolz mayn now that you work.. its been so boring in the house... i dont know who to cook for... and we need to work on our dance rountine... and our cheerleading... i cant wait when you have a day off so you could take me out.. lolz... but seriously.. thanks for everything...even though i dont call you ate.. you already know that you play your role as a big sister......... cant wait to see you!.... love you!    
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       SECTiON 1 [»] ABOUT YOURSELF name: you could call me LeiLa... or Lei sex: female  age: 15 birthday: december.30th.1988 height: 5’3? hair col0r: aurburn with blonde streaks eye col0r: dark brown location: eMDee 'b0o' stats: just chillen fears:god above all. snakes. little insects. blood. the doctor.   SECTiON 2 [»] THiS OR THAT? &nbsp;pepsi or coke? pepsi lefty or righty? righty chocolate or vanilla? vanilla dog or cat? Dog  girls or guys? Guys  black or white? depends innie or outie? innie third boob or third buttcheek? what da heck?! freak dance or slow dance? depends mcdonalds or burger king? mcdonalds boyfriend or best friend? bestfriend lizzie mcguire or even stevens? lizzie mcguire VMA`s or grammy`s? VMA’s   SECTiON&nbsp;3 [»] ON THE OPPOSiTE SEX...  turn on`s –>funny // good looking // sweet// caring  turn off`s–›&nbsp;negative attitude&nbsp;// yellow teeth // lies d0 you have a BF/GF –› no. are you allowed a BF/GF–› nope  SECTiON&nbsp;4 [»] THiNK FAST!  color_ Pink d0rk_ Chanel butt_stinks suicide_ you need help auto_ shop yummy_ yummy carry out scary_your face night_sleep day_eat!  SECTiON 6 [»] HAVE YOU EVER peed your pants?when you`re small. Don’t we all? cheated on s0meone?nope fallen off the bed? heKk yeah. fallen for a relative? ew no been KiSSED: no had plastic surgery? no failed a grade? no been c0nstipated? Eeeyeww!  br0ke someone`s heart? i hope not had y0ur heart br0ken? you could say that had a dream c0me true? yup asked someone out? no picked y0ur nose? whatda hanky-panky?!!? lol been in love? what's love st0le anything? yup done s0mething you regret? Yup [a lot of those] had a wart?&nbsp; no g0ne streaking? whats that br0ken a b0dy part? i jammed my middle finga and it looked broken.. but nah dont think so  SECTiON 7 [»] CURRENTLY  wearing – Shorts and a red tank listening to – nothing eating – nothing.. just finished eating dinner feeling – confused... crappy... blahhh!! reading –what im typing located –my brother's room chatting with – no one watching – nothing craving -sushi should REALLY be – getting ready to go to the GEM  SECTiON 8 [»] DO YOU...  brush your teeth?yup like anyb0dy?not shure yet have a BF?nope have any piercings?yup wear th0ngs?nope wear glasses?yeah have braces?nope drive?nope believe in Santa Claus?nope wear de0dorant?yup sing in the sh0wer?helll yeah ever get off the damn c0mputer?yup  SECTiON 9 [»] FRiENDS  who is your best?they know who they are who is the loudest?chanel who is the shyest?danica who laughs the most?muah who have you known the longest? Lizelle who have you known the shortest?i dunno do you only hang out with a certain `type´?naw i like being with everyone do you belong to a crew?dont think so do you hang out with the opp0site sex?yup do y0u trust yours? my what? can y0u keep a secret? you tell me  SECTiON 10 [»] THE LAST PERSON YOU...  hugged –my momma gave epr0ps -- Genny IMed – Adrienne talked on the phone – Grace yelled at –an Jr tripped – myself lolz laughed with – my brother and momma  
      
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i have no clue what im doing... hopefully ill get used to it.. =) 
      
</post>


</Blog>