<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm not really sure  why  I started this blog.&nbsp;Maybe,  just  maybe, I'm putting this out there because I want people to be able to know me. . . People may listen. But of course that is just a hopeless dream and no one will ever find this. Which could be a saving grace. In some ways, I think this may become more safe and private than a traditional journal. There are infinite places I could hide this on the web, but there are only so many places to hide a book in your bedroom.   Thirty-one days until I'm back in a school desk, back to friends, and back to my life as I know it. It's so strange. . . I want to go back and I don't, but I have to go anyway. But school is school and you just can't change that.   Well, now this window is open, and hopefully the breeze will start fluttering in, and I'll get some fresh air.   &nbsp;  P.S. This game is completely out of game, ARG people.    
    
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I just realized. . . in twelve days, I'm going back to everything that basically makes my life. I'm trying to prolong living. I realized that I don't really do anything other than school. All I've done is read, babysit, see a few movies, and gotten together with my friends three or four times. Going back to school signifies returning to my life, and some less-than-appreciated components of it (a.k.a. a certain someone).  He's a good kid. . . one of the smartest ones I know, but he just does  stupid , stupid things sometimes. He spends more time trying to "fit in" than he needs to. He has started way to many fights (with one specific person, I may add) to get in with his friends and that annoys me. He's so smart, but he just does these things that good kids don't, all in the name to be funny. It wouldn't bother me so much if A) he wasn't my friend or B) he wasn't a good kid. He acts  so  immature sometimes, it really bothers me. Like ripping up the whole entire cover of a bus seat to throw them at other people. . . that's not something I thinks someone like him should do. Call me biased or stuck-up, but that's just how I feel. He could be doing so many other things than being the way he acts sometimes.  Another thing that bothers me is his cockiness. He's always like, "I could build a fingerprint scanner if I wanted to." And the only thing I've seen him do with electrical things was a little kiddie experiment set. He thinks he's a master engineer at age fourteen, a seasoned pro that can do anything, and that bothers me. It's the same thing with sports and music. I remember that at the beginning of seventh grade that he told me how he was one of the best trumpet players, and he turns out to be second trumpet. In sports, he thinks he is amazing at soccer and baseball, and blames other stuff on everyone else. Never once does the selective hand of blame fall upon his little head. He just thinks he is the best (not so extremely though. He isn't as bad as some other people I know of).  If you ever read this (part of me wishes you will, another part wishes you won't) just think about you are going to do or say, and examine the repercussions it could create. You don't "need" to say mean things about your recent ex-girlfriend in order to "fit in."If you want to be thought of as a gentleman or good boyfriend material (whatever that is), you should realize that saying horribly mean things like that (even if you apologize and they accept it) should  never  happen, especially if you want to pursue a friendly relationship with that person. And don't use the "fitting in" excuse anymore, it's cheesy. I'm surprised she believed that. . . saying such nasty things so your friends will like you. Not to sound cliche, but if they make you feel that way, they aren't your friends. And remember that people don't just forget things overnight. . . sometimes things you say can cause big-time trouble and you should always try to uphold your honor, no matter what. Once your honor, decency, or dignity is gone, you have nothing else to build a life on.  Wow, that was a lot of venting. . . I guess it just built up a lot. I hope that person will clean up their act a little. You're going to be in high school. . . we all need to mature a litle (some more than others. . .  ahem, ahem ).  As always, More later,  John   "Time and time again we fall in to the depths of who we are,   But you can't keep running away from what you're trying to find."   
    
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Where does all the time go? Just a month ago, I was a month out of school, so blissfully bored and useless. Now, I have thirteen days to finish my math packet, and try to finish two good-sized books. I hope I can do it.  I got my backpack today. You know it's back to school when you have a backpack all ready. God, I can't believe that in four years, I am going to be plucked from my little safe haven, my  bubble  for God's sake, and just dropped over one of the many colleges in this country. I really give props to the college students who get the college they want, etc. It looks like one logistical and financial disaster. It's funny, you never really realize how much trouble an education can be. . . It's like an accident on the highway. All you hear are horror stories about them, and you say to yourself, "Wow. But that would never happen to me."  College, college, college, college, college. Where do I want to go? I've told my mom that I want to go out into a city . . . which one I don't know. I've always had a dream of going somewhere like UCLA or Harvard, or some other school. And now when I'm a little more reasonable, seeing that unless I get one heckuva scholarship, I really won't be able to afford it. Well I've got one thing on my side. My money. I bet that forty-five percent of the money I have now (right now, at age fourteen) will be used for my college education. . . I never spend my money, which can be a gift  and  a curse, I guess.  Well, changing gears a little. In the past week or so, I've realized to things: A) I'm am seriously thinking of wanting to be a writer for my profession (if I can make it, that is) and B) I want to go on Teen Jeopardy. I know, I know, two totally different things. For the first one, it just feels right. I like writing, and I'm good at it, I think, people say so (except Jon Balanoff, who thinks I'm bad at creative writing. I'll show him). I just don't know what I would take in college for that. Or which college to go to, for that matter. Would it be like one of those liberal arts schools or something like that? Or can you go to a university and get qualified there?  The other part, about Teen Jeopardy, is that I'd  like  to be on it. I watched the teen semi-finals yesterday and I knew a lot of the answers, sometimes when the high school seniors on the show didn't. It would be a good way to get exposure, and for people to notice me, and to raise money for college. It would be fun too. I think our culture should put more importance on competitions like this, that showcase the young mind and knowledge, proving that we aren't just beer-drinking, pot-smoking, ecstasy-snorting, rebellious teenagers. Some of us can do amazing things, and everyone's vision is clouded by the stories they see everyday on the news. There are good-teens and bad-teens, just like everything else. Those "surver-makers" who are just trying to make awareness better are part of the problem too. I understand they are just doing their job, but seriously their  jobs  have come back and bit teenagers in the butt. Now everyone's like, "Oh my God, it's a teenager, give him a drug test!" As I said before, not all of us do drugs and drink.  Back to Teen Jeopardy. I could raise a lot of money for myself and my education, and that's something good. Other than the problem of how to get to some big city to audition, there's really nothing to lose.  Wow, that was a big post. I'll write again as soon as possible. Later.  John    "Time and time again we fall in to the depths of who we are    But you can't keep running away from what you're trying to find"    -- Chronic Future, Time and Time Again   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jeez, only a week left on AWARE. I really don't get that. . . how can the game end before the bomb is set to go off? Well, I guess I'll just have to wait and see.  The silver lining to that is that it will end before I'll have to go back to school.  Speaking of . . . I got my schedule a little while ago. I got all the classes I asked for, which is good. I still have to finish my math packet. . . darn it.  And I thought I would have my book done by the end of the summer. I don't think I've written anything in two weeks. I think I need to just write it down and get it down before I start fixing  anything . What I plan on doing is writing the last chapter now, I have some really good words in my head for it. One problem I'm having is trying to make is as far away from Alias as  possible . I've already gotten enought ideas from them, I think it's time I got my own.  Well, I'm off to do that now.   "Time and time again we fall in to the depths of who we are   But you can't keep running away from what you're trying to find"        
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's so weird. . . When you are trying to get something so bad, once you get it, it's cool for a few days, then it's gone. It's almost like . . . You like wanting it more than having it.  Like with the cable Internet we got last night. We had been  begging  my dad for months to let us get it (we've labored over inferior dial-up for longer than any person should have to). But now that we have it, it's like "o.k." It's great and all, but it just feels so weird finally having it.  I saw The Bourne Supremacy on Friday. Good movie. I read the book too, but, aside from the title, they don't share anything in common. Here are the differences between book and movie:  1. Location; Book: Bourne and Marie live in Maine, not in hiding. Majority of book takes place in the Orient. Movie: Bourne and Marie live in Goa, India, in hiding. Action takes place all over Europe.  2. Marie; Book: Marie is  kidnapped  and is rescued by Bourne. Movie: Marie is  killed  within twenty minutes.  3. Characters; Major characters in book aren't in movie, major characters in movie aren't in book.  4. Plot; Book; Marie is kidnapped, and Bourne must catch a Bourne imposter to get her back. Movie: Bourne is framed for a crime and is pursued by the CIA for arrest.  The book and movie both had their ups and downs (i.e. the book was  incredibly  dry at times, the movie didn't follow the book, etc.). Both were good, though.  Tonight we are having dinner with our aunt who came down for a few days. Yum. Steak tips.  Only. . . shudder . . . fourteen days until we have to go back to school.   Sometime we all just need to take a step back   And look at eachother. . .   And ourselves.   
    
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, a lot of changes have gone on in AWARE this past week. We are all forming an alliance! (Bar The Restorers, who plan on detonating a nuclear bomb and throwing a major hissy fit if Congress doesn't "reassemble" the Constitution by September 5th for their sick twisted endgame).  I was really disappointed to see Omniscient Eyes' posts. I thought with their previous nefariousness would be plotting the assassinations of all Ideltech employees, but it turned they were just solving the same puzzles as us mostly. They didn't even know the solution to their own puzzle!! Alecia even said that we would be "shocked" to see what had been discussed in their forums, but really there wasn't anything too surprising.  Some people are angry with the whole Hidden Alliance thing, but I like it. It's forcing us to join forces to fight a greater evil. Maybe it will all work out... I don't know.  I'll write more tomorrow or Thursday.     
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Have you ever noticed when you are anticipating the inevitable things in life that really hurt, that all you do is postpone it to the end? I had an experience like that. We had all known that Gizzy wasn't going to live very longer, and then we got a date, and I just basically kept it all bottled up until the day of, the hour of, the quarter-hour of... It was like that if I didn't think about it, that it wouldn't come. All the big doggies are gone now :( . . . Just the puppies are left.  My mom and brother went out back and made a nice memorial for Stubby, Gizzmo, and Yogi (the hampster). It was nice with bark mulch mounds and stone around each one, along with a stone with their name on it and such. It was pretty...  I got my high school schedule this week. I got all the classes I wanted. Woo-hoo. I still have to finish that book and my geometry packet. It'll probably be done by next week. Probably.  This is my first blog post on my new computer! Yay! Now all we need to do is get that cable internet and we'll be set.  Dinner time's coming soon, and I have to feed the dogs, so I'm out.     
    
    
</post>


</Blog>