<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hawaii is the best place that you could ever go. I started going to hawaii when I was 3 years old and I still am with my family. they take us every year for my dads bank vacation, my dad works at The Bank Of Willits. He rocks. I love to surf whenever I go there and I love to meet all of the hawaiian boys THEY ARE HOT. lol. Anway surfing is really fun, you should try it sometime. I go to hawaii every year and it is always a different smell different breeze and many different sound of the earth. It is great. Night time is so beautiful I can stay up all night and necer get tired. I always feel so far away in my own world when I am in Hawaii it is great. I dont have to think about anything important when I am there. Just GUYS. lol  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hey I am learning to drive and it is easy, but I only know how to drive automatics they are the easiest. I am going to drive on are paved road tommarow and I am so excited I hope that I dont crash. I drove up to are house and backed out of the garage and into the garage it is so fun. I am the only one who is excited about driving I have&nbsp;17 year old sister and she doesnt want to drive, plus she doesnt have time. She swims.    
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Yeah swimming. Swimming is a great sport and hobbie to do, I have been swimming for nine years aand it has gave me a great tan and make me strong. Everyday I try to get faster, it isnt that hard to get fast you just need to go to practice and that will help you. I love swimming becasue I meet a lot of new people, they are all the best people I met. When I&nbsp; swim I feel so good and I love it and I hop you people will join. You will have fun.  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hey I love food. FOOD.FOOD.FOOD.FOOD. I love fooood. The food that I ,love is Top Ramen, Mangos, Popcorn, and everything else you can think of. I also care about CHOCOLATE how ever you spell that, I love chocolate and YUM. How many of you love food?  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hey I love the friends that I have. I had a really bad life when I went to school in Willits at the Middle School. I hung out the with the wrong people. They made my life miserable. I joined the Ukiah Swim Team and I made a lot of friends there they all convinced me to go to Ukiah High and I said yes. I met all these nice people, I met Tess Pasternak, Wiltly Sassen, Jeremy Pollard and alot of nice and great peopl, the person that I think really inspires me is Elley Cannon she is the greatest frined ever and she is always making you laugh and well she always makes me laugh. Ilove her to death.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>