<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     The daily news where I see faces of Laloo,Mayawati,Mani Shankar makes me sick !! does it do the same to you?? We are talking here about a supposedly great country which seems to have forgotten everything bout itself and probably has the worst leaders in ages.I am obviously talking about political leaders here. The last month I was in Pune for my summer internship.Oh sorry!! let me tell something bout myself.I am a student of a prestigious b-school.we call ourselves wimwians.Dont try to understand it as most probably,u wont be able to :)). so back to the pune thing.yeah!!i was there in pune for my summer internship and i heard about their Mayor Arun Bhatia contesting for the elections.He is a government employee and that too, a honest one as per media reports.Obviously,he doesnt have the financial resources to contest against heavyweights like Kalmadi.However,he seemed very confident( I heard one of his speeches there).He was campaigning mainly with support of his friends and wellwishers who probably want someone honest and more capable to represent and work for Pune.I even saw ordinary government employees posting posters of him(asking for votes) in local buses and other places.I even asked one of them what is he getting out of it?? He said he is not getting anything out of it.However,he is a local and wants Pune to be a better place.and he wants Arun to win.Although,I am not from Pune,I felt interested in the elections there and tried to browse though some articles on it(atleast some,considering my time constraint).I even queried my guesthouse boy and others and they all thought that Arun should win but he wont because he is against a very strong Kalmadi.and that was ultimately the case.Why is that we dont get good leaders elected to parliamentary positions??any comments.Are we so engulfed with our petty interests that we totally forget about the general wellbeing of the society and end up voting for the wrong person. take bihar for example.one of the most highly endowed state in terms of natural resources and even agriculture(north bihar).The leaders for almost 3-4 decades have been raping the state while it has slipped down to the lowest ranks in terms of development.Is it because of the people?? I dont think so!! Bihar has given some of the best scientists and other intellectuals(remember Chanakya!!),bihari workers are one of the most hard-working.then is lallu or rabri devi the best that they can send to the parliament?? take mayawati.an ordinary teacher rising to become a parliamentarian is good.but just look at the way she did it ?? hinge on to one kanshi ram,raise emotive issues regarding the caste system ,abuse the father of the nation...thats all about it.per se,i am not against politians raising this issue.a nation cannot progress if such a large no. of people live under such conditions facing both social and financial deprievation.However,what the Mayawati brand of politicians do is to ride on emotions...abuse the higher castes.. any leaders from the higher castes.... its ok ... everybody has a right to say but India could very soon face a civil war if these emotions are continuously flamed.Moreover this does not benefit anybody.Instead of economically empowering them,making them literate enough so that they can ask for their rights ,what this has done that it has brought bitterness within the upper castes while repeatedly benefitting the cream/elite of the backward/scheduled castes.What is more worrying that these brand of politicians are increasing. Hope, the young sons/daughters ( although i am against dynasty rule very prevalent among COngress leaders) of Congress leaders bring some fresh ideas/thoughts .Our political leadership really needs a revamp. Ok,i am done for today. Open to the public for comments :)) 

						
</post>


</Blog>