<Blog>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well,  what can i say. a 9 hour shift done. probably one of the busiest weekends in a while (with riverboat days and all). it was interesting. almost fun. learnt lots, as this was kinda my 'training' also. but, both CSM's i worked with thought i did good, so that's good. there was only one 'incident' and that was when, well, i kinda let all but one cashier go for their break all at the same time.........whoops. so there was some problems. but it was alright. you learn from mistakes right? no body took too much offense from me asking them to do stuff and all that, i know there's gonna be some issues with some of the older people though, just with a younger person telling them what to do. oh well. they [the cashiers] we're all very supportive and helpful, considering half the time they told me what to do. oh well, it was a good experience. no real stories i can remember, but if i do, i'll post 'em  keeping you posted,  jared - red vest - euverman   feeling : not stressed anymore, my legs are tired  quote of the day:    "You did good, seriously"                                          - Jacky, CSM  listening to : 'King for a day' - Crush 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      welcome back.    well my night was interesting. did some training as a CSM. it wasn't as hard as i thought, but who knows what it'll be like when it's busy. oh well.  i work my first CSM shift saturday. that'll be fun, with riverboat days and all. well three 'memorable' moments happend today (memorable meaning i'll forget them tomorrow).  number uno:  CSM training , well it was kinda boring. i learnt the basics though, and on saturday i get thrown a red vest and keys and a nice pat on the back.  number 2:  Vacuum cleaner  well, Robert told some customer today that we'd have a vacuum cleaner ready for him by 830ish. well, it wasn't ready, and chances are it wasn't even off the truck. after searching 20 minutes, no luck. i climbed over the boxes. brandon helped, but we couldn't find anything. the 'do not climb on bins' sign were kinda avoided. oh well. no body died.    number 3:  Mr. Wilson  well, i've seen this guy in a few times at the store. who knows if his name is actually mr. wilson, but he looks like  urlLink mr. wilson  (click on his name) from denace the menace. seriously, without the mustache, this guy is a carbon copy. he talked about how he bought a  urlLink '55 chevy  (again, click on the link) for $2900 dollars in '55. he used this analogy to relate it to inflation; but i didn't really pay attention after that part.  oh well. good times.    well, those are my stories.  Thank you for your cooperation and thank you for shopping at wal-mart,  Jared "the menace" Euverman   quote of the day :   "do NOT climb on bins"                                            - Wal-Mart saftey sticker  listening to : "Fade to Black" - Metallica  feeling : wound up      
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      good morning and welcome to my boring life.   work starts in a few hours. i really don't wanna go. it's an 8 hour shift, meaning the only good thing is you get an hour dinner/lunch break. unfortunately, nine times out of ten i buy something.&nbsp; oh well, atleast when i stop working in electronics i won't be so 'prepared' on what to buy. i swear, being in electronics for me is like a starving person in a grocery store. everything i need and ahhh. oh well. money's just.....well, money. interesting thing about work: it never suprises me how &nbsp;stupid sometimes people can be. seriously. not only customers too. but i know i'm breaking lines and rules with this blog. i can just imagine somebody releasing this site at work and i bet you woooooosh there goes my job. but we'll see how it goes. if i need a littler disclaimer this it it:  disclaimer :  everything portrayed in this blog is not a representation of Wal-Mart but rather an employee (hopefully not former) who is talking about his experiences in a fun, satirical matter. people portrayed on this website are real, but i assure you, all is in good fun. i apologize at any problems this may of occured.  well that was easy. lets not hope this gets me in trouble. ah oh well, what can ya do. live goes on. to be honest though, wal-mart is a great place to work. without a doubt. and i sure as heck hope it doesn't get unionized. that's another funny thing. about a month ago, this union thing was such a worry and a concern. now it's as mentioned rarely. *sigh* i'll never figure out this adult stuff. unions suck. its hard to believe in one year, i'm done high school. then i will be an 'adult'. oh well. life goes on. you live with the good and with the bad. but, work is now close and i need to shower. i'll blog after work tonight, take it easy, jared 'still a kid' euverman   listening to:  "Wild Honey" - U2  quote of the day:   "To err is human, to forgive is divine."  - Huggy bear on Starsky and Hutch  feeling : tired 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah, that's right, 3 posts in under an hour. this just *shows* the rocking life i have.   well, I'm currently working in electronics at Wal-Mart. Man the stories i could tell. I work with 6 people in electronics.    Tammy  - she's the department manager, i don't really work with her much, cause she just came in after the whole ricky thing, but i'll describe that later.&nbsp; she's full time,&nbsp;i don't know her age.   Edwin &nbsp;-&nbsp;i've never seen somebody do so little work, honestly. i've tallied up some of the times he's been gone, it's been hours of a shift he won't be in the department. oh well, what can ya do. something like 23 or something. he always asks me how old he looks. i dont know.   Effie  - she seems to do her own random projects, she keeps busy. she's nice and supportive. she's a full timer. i don't know how old she is.   Robert  - i work with him quite a bit, fun guy to work with. i've had my share of good times with him. robert just graduated this year.   Rav  - Rav use to be my next door neighbour when i was like 3. he's great. the acclaimed 'beast from the middle east' is a riot. good times good times. rav's 22 or something.   Kegen  - i don't even know if i spelt his name right. i use to work with him lots, but he has a habit of giving away all his shifts for one week. so it's kinda sparatic when i see him.&nbsp; he's going into gr. 11.    people who i use to work with:    Chad  - well, this guy, without a doubt, was the best guy to work with while i was in electronics. unfortunately, he gave his two weeks notice days after tammy was named department manager. it's a pity. not only was he a great worker he knew how to make it relaxed and fun too. it's really a pity. i haven't seen him since he quit, so i don't know what he's up to, but i'm sure he's having fun. he's 18 or something.    Ricky  - well, i never *worked* with him. so i can't really say much. i'm not here to point fingers just from what people say. but whatever. i've heard good and bad. i won't even comment, he just doesn't work at walmart any more. (maybe people will stop asking me that now)   Well, my stay in electronics will be over in a few days. I recently applied and recieved a new part time position as a Customer Service Manager. that means a pay increase woot woot. I get to wear a red vest, not a blue one. so now the customers know who to hunt down. *sigh* oh well, maybe the extra 30 cents will be worth it. i get to job shadow the head CSM, Jane, on thusday the 29th, so, that'll be interesting, i still don't know what i have to do for a CSM though. oh well, it'll be fun. i got to do some more training on the computers last night. so now i can officially be a people greeter and i know how to delegate. it's funny how i didn't even know what delegating meant before last night. oh well, get off your butt and stop reading this. see that's delegating. well, i gotta go do some cleaning,  sincerly,  people greeter jared  oh by the way, i got 59% on my chem 12 provincial. but that's not important.    listening to:  'back home' - yellowcard     quote of the day:   'varsity sucks ice'  - someone's msn screen name i don't even know what varsity is. i don't know how it can suck ice. it's just a quote, and i haven't had any new quotes in 20 minutes since my last post.     feeling:  ready to shower    &nbsp;       
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      since i did my nice welcome message, i'll cut to the chase and give you an idea of what i plan to have in each blog post.   Three main things:    listening to:  this will say what songs i've been listening to while i write whatever post.    quote of the day:  a quote from anyone who i've talked to today, and i'll probabyl give some of the background behind that story. i will only use tv quotes and stuff if i can't dig up anything good from anyone. there might also be more then one quote of the day.    feeling:  i know i know, this is so cliche, but oh well, it's fun.   So, without further to do:    listening to:  'View from Heaven' - Yellowcard   quote of the day:   'it can be yours if the price is right'  - Price is Right   feeling : bored   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       welcome to my blog!     &nbsp;   well, if your here, you probably know who i am. so i'll cut the personal crap. this blog will be my rants and raves for Wal-Mart and other thigns in my life. nothing to special, but hopefully you'll enjoy it.    
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, it was an alright day. it was rough at times, but it was good. i was scheduled to close by myself, but thankfully jacky had to come back to help with the courtesy desk so she helped me out. well, there was one certainly scary incident today. i won't mention details, but let me say, it was one of the 'scarier' things that happened with my times at walmart. a walmart associate complained of light headness and nasuea, and things got worse, with the associate going in and out of conciousness. parmedics arrived and left with flashers and sires on. i won't mention anything more as this is quite a personal issue. it was a scary thing to see, and that's why i question my future, it turned my gut to see a person like that, but i still did what i had to do and helped the paramedics out. but this certainly was a new and unique experience. i really don't feel like posting anything funny that happened today.  that's all and my prayers are with that associate and the family of the associate.  jared "questioning" euverman  listening to:  nothing  feeling : torn about my future  quote of the day : "The best moment in wal-mart history happened today." - A cashier who was referring to two ladies who shopped in their bikini's today. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      what's up? well, today was interesting. we had some liars and some honest people. we had three 'trainees' on the tills today, and of course, they had a CSM trainee helping a cashier trainee....badddddd idea lol. well one of them accidently gave a $10 dollar bill instead of a 5, and thankfully, this guy came back and said he noticed the mistake. phew. cause that wouldn't be a good way for this girl to start her cashiering 'career'.  oh well, i think she made more then that mistake. and then i had a not so nice girl come in, saying she didn't get her money back on saturday after she went through a newbie cashier. of course, i'm thinking this could be legit after my previous incident. well after checking it out with a manager, it was ALMOST impossible for this girl to be telling the truth, so the duty manager talked to her, and she then proceeded to change her story, at that point her father said 'well make up your mind on your story' and he proceeded to leave. thankfully the father atleast saw the hole. cause it would've made it a helluva lot harder to deal with if he was supporting his daughter. well, another rosemary story arose today. she filled out one of my audit sheets, and she did it totally wrong and she even DENIED she did it. man alive. talk about liars.  thank goodness i work with jane tomorrow,  jared "honest" euverman  listening to : 'open your eyes' - alter bridge  feeling : ready to goto edmonton  quote of the day :  "I'm not lying. Seriously" - Customer complaining about not getting change. 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey,  well, today was a day i've dreaded ever since i heard i got the csm job...no not training....rosemary. this elderly lady who is another CSM. seriously, maybe a handful of people like her. she's so snappy, and i feel bad for the people she talks to. she bossed me around, and i can't wait till i'm gone for 10 days.  seriously, i woudl've cried if she said some of that stuff she said to the other cashiers to me. i apologize if your a cashier when she's on. seriously. you guys take alot of sh*t that i don't have to take as much of.  well, no real stories today. except rosemary. but i mean, how much can i tell?! she questioned everything i did, she has to make sure EVERYTHING i do is perfect, while meanwhile she barely does any of the stuff i 'have' to do. oh well. life goes on, and thankfully i have alot more of it left besides working at walmart,  jared 'i don't like the colour  rose ' euverman   listening to : 'everybody' - stablio  feeling : wound up  quote of the day :  "Are you sure you did that Jared?" - Rosemary 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well,  It's official. I'm now an 'official' CSM. awesome. i'm glad to get out of electronics, it started becoming a hell-hole to be 100% honest. it was so 'oh ok i'll do that' but it never gets done. ah, oh well, it's no longer my worry! well, it was an interesting day. it was probably the one day i accuatly worked hard enough to earn my money. after removing all the movies from the "summer sale blowout" bins and organizing them by their own companies (Fox, MGM, Warner Brothers, etc.) then boxing them and putting them to claims. I did that all day. looked on the side of dvd's and vhs's to find out who made the, and put them in their appropiate spot. for 8 hours. 8 hours. not 1, not 2, not 7, 8! oh well. atleast CSMing is something new everyday and everyminute, which will be a nice switch. well, the one funny story that happened at work was this:  Some guy and his family came in and he asked if we had little speakers. i hesitated.  little speakers? what the hell is that  i asked my self. i presumed he meant computer speakers so showing him the speakers he said "those are nice little speakers". i chuckled, i was accutually right. well, he asked if they'd connect to a discman, and i said yes, i knew that for a fact (unlike everything else i b.s.) from previous basketball trips. he then got all complainy and asked why i had an attitude. he was like 'i know your lying to me' and then he left. usually, stuff like this you ask yourself why your doing this. then you remember it's your break, and you forget about it. and now i'm writing this out and asking myself wtf was he talking about. oh well. and on a lighter note, i saw mr. wilson aka the customer who looks like mr. wilson. i saw him driving. a nice gray GMC astro van. i guess he wasn't driving his '55 chevy. meh oh well. lies die quick.  jared "100% pure CSM" euverman   listening to : "Everybody" by Stablio (best song ever)  feeling : excited....nah who am i kidding i'm bored.  quote of the day :  "I know your lying to me"  - an angry customer 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      meh,  nothing to say really. another day done.  i plan to buy some guitar stuff tomorrow so that'll be nice. i got jelly belly's today. jacky found out i'm younger then her, which she just couldn't believe. and work was almost fun. learnt some new stuff, and finally people stopped asking me how things are going and how i like the job....well the story of the night would be this one for me...going home. yeah that was about it.  jared "i'm too lazy" euverman 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well,  after watching 5 000 rubber ducks dumped into the skeena river, my 5 hour CSM shift was about to begin.  there wasn't much that happened. it just sucks when the cashiers know more about my job then i do. ahhh ohwell. i guess i'm still in training. i'm sore and tired though. not just from volleyball either, all that walking sucks. *sigh* well, i only had one 'interesting' story really. a customer found a blank cheque from somebody (signed and everything) for 'dog chippers' and that was it. so after reviewing it, i got an associate (delegation in effect) to phone the person's phone number on the cheque. After speaking with the person, they didn't want the chequed ripped up, thus voiding it. No, they wanted the blank cheque mailed back to them. Why, you ask? I'll never know. Oh well, it's on its way to Hazelton tomorrow.  and i'm out, 8 hour shift tomorrow is gonna be killer  jared "insert witty remark here" euverman   listening to : the TV i'm too lazy to turn off  feeling : tired  quote of the day :   "It's raining"   - Daniel as we started to play beach volleyball at 8 am.    
    
</post>


</Blog>