<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok - so those of you that  really  know me know that I am completely obsessed with hurricane season. I check the satellite of the Atlantic and the Gulf every day. The season started June 1st, it's been very weird this year- it's been very slow.  Let the tracking of TD#1 begin. According to the National Hurricane Center, at this time that the the depression will likely intensify into a Tropical storm in the next 24 hours and reach landfall somewhere in the Carolinas in the next 2 1/2 - 3 days. Looks like South Carolina. But, remember these storms can change from day to day.  The wind speed has to reach 74 mph for one consecutive minute for the storm to be a catagory 1 hurricane and 39 mph for it to as a named tropical storm, at that time (if it gets there) It will be tropical storm Alex.  Another area that needs to be monitored closely is an area of low pressure in the south east Gulf of Mexico by the Yucatan pennensula, this will more than likely be TD#2. Being on the Texas Coast, I should watch this one very close.  Keep checking for updates. (if you give a shit). I could post satellite pics, and probability charts if I could just figure out how to put pictures on here. I really need to just try - I'm sure it's not that hard, right?    
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is turning out to be a very bad day. I was supposed to have 3 closings. As of 1:30 today, only one looks like it actually going to close- in about an hour. Thank god my client already moved to Atlanta - They will email him the docs, so I don't have sit in at the closing table. Somedays I wish I would have stuck to being a "doggy nurse". It doesn't help that I sat up until 2 in the morning with my neighbors girlfriend, Amy drinking beer and smoking cigarettes. Why do I do this to myself????? I have an extra heartbeat in my head and I have had about 6 tall glasses of tea and still haven't peed. I also have whore voice ( the horrid raspy voice after a night of smokin' and drinkin') My liver/kidneys/lungs will never forgive me. I just have to get past 2:30, then I can go and lay out with Tammy by her pool and sweat this hangover out.   
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's&nbsp;late morning/early afternoon&nbsp;and I am still in my pajamas. &nbsp;Hey, I've&nbsp; been working all day- I love my home office! I tried some trading spaces ideas&nbsp;with it. I pulled up all the&nbsp;carpet and&nbsp;sponge painted the concrete floor to look like sand. Then I painted the walls a brilliant blue (Ralph Lauren's Mediterranean Blue) I even put new fat white baseboards on myself. I had to borrow my neighbors&nbsp;machine saw thingie-&nbsp;I think it's called a skil-saw???&nbsp;I even got a fish tank for the corner of the room - it's very tropical and relaxing.  It's raining, today I love the rain - I usually like it to be very warm and sunny - but today the rain fits my mood, I hope it rains all day.  I watched the Democratic convention on TV last night. What a joke.  I can't wait until August 30th - The Republican convention is in New York that week.  I also need to learn how to post pictures on this damn thing. I'm not very tech-savy.  Well, I guess I should get in the shower and run to the office-office to check my box, I hate my office-office now, too much drama - too many people working under the same roof will totally cause that.  &nbsp;Or may be I'll stay in my jammies, the dogs will come in here soon for there afternoon nap, they will&nbsp;sleep under the desk and keep my feet warm.  I think I'll stay here and continue to work in a comfortable environment for the rest of the day........    
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Natalie&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are dead bees' every where in a vacant listing I have. I think there is a wasp nest in the attic or something. It's horrid. It freaks me out. At least they are dead..... Of course they are dead, there is no a/c on in the house and it's about 100 degrees.&nbsp; The seller won't turn on the power. He yelled at me today when I called him to tell him about these problems. He's an ass.  I am thinking about breaking up with him and taking my sign out of his jungle that he likes to call the front yard. It's humiliating to have my name on a dump like that.&nbsp;      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know I had to do it....... I need to know what clothes to pack. OK fine... I'm obsessed with weather. Anyway here's what it's going to look like while we're in Vegas. What a temperature variation! Lower 70's at night? I'm gonna freeze! Upper 90's in the day.... I can handle it, that close to the weather we've been having in Houston lately.... But, we also have the humidity that makes it worse. At lease Vegas is dry heat. I can handle it!  MONDAY...MOSTLY SUNNY... HIGHS IN THE UPPER 90S MONDAY NIGHT...MOSTLY CLEAR... LOWS IN THE LOWER 70S TUESDAY...MOSTLY SUNNY... HIGHS IN THE MID 90S TUESDAY NIGHT...MOSTLY CLEAR... LOWS IN THE LOWER 70S WEDNESDAY...MOSTLY SUNNY... HIGHS IN THE MID 90S WEDNESDAY NIGHT...MOSTLY CLEAR... LOWS IN THE LOWER 70S THURSDAY...MOSTLY SUNNY... HIGHS IN THE LOWER 90S  I am crazy today, it is the last day to get any deals closed before we leave. It's hard leaving your job when it's a one man show. I have 2 closings while I'm out of town, it looks like I'll have to work a little while I'm there.... That sucks. All I can do it tie up any loose ends today and hope for the best.  Also - I just want to let everyone know- my dogs staying in the "doggy hotel" is going to cost more than our hotel room. WTF????? This is 3 nights of boarding as pampered pets, which means they get walked 3 times a day, and a bath before we pick them up. The bath is one of the most expensive items...... But, I don't want to pick them up and have them smell like a boarding kennel (piss and ass). My 2 boy dogs will have a blast at the kennel - they love it! It's like a little vacation for them.  My girl, Guenivere, is a total bitch in boarding. She HATES it, she'll try to bite the girls when they take her out of the cage to walk her. She is very sweet otherwise - she just really, really hates boarding and she gets scared. Hopefully she won't bite the shit out of anyone while we're gone.   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took Jeanette's Lip test What do your lips say about you?  Results:  Natalie, you're all about Tight Lips    Do you tend to play it safe? Hedge your bets? Keep a stiff upper lip when it comes to sensitive matters? Nothing wrong with that — don't your friends tend to confide in you more than others? You're honest and trustworthy, and you logically think things out in order to come to a rational, smart conclusion.Your mouth doesn't get you into trouble too much, and you can be choosy when it comes to when, where, and with whom you open up. There's a simple elegance to your quiet ways that allows you to stay in control of situations and, in the end, hold all of the right cards. After all, a little mystery makes everything more interesting.   urlLink take This Test   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took Jeanette's Lip test What do your lips say about you?  Results:  Natalie, you're all about Tight Lips    Do you tend to play it safe? Hedge your bets? Keep a stiff upper lip when it comes to sensitive matters? Nothing wrong with that — don't your friends tend to confide in you more than others? You're honest and trustworthy, and you logically think things out in order to come to a rational, smart conclusion.Your mouth doesn't get you into trouble too much, and you can be choosy when it comes to when, where, and with whom you open up. There's a simple elegance to your quiet ways that allows you to stay in control of situations and, in the end, hold all of the right cards. After all, a little mystery makes everything more interesting.   urlLink take This Test   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took Jeanette's Lip Test. What do your lips say about you??  Natalie, you're all about Tight Lips    Do you tend to play it safe? Hedge your bets? Keep a stiff upper lip when it comes to sensitive matters? Nothing wrong with that — don't your friends tend to confide in you more than others? You're honest and trustworthy, and you logically think things out in order to come to a rational, smart conclusion.Your mouth doesn't get you into trouble too much, and you can be choosy when it comes to when, where, and with whom you open up. There's a simple elegance to your quiet ways that allows you to stay in control of situations and, in the end, hold all of the right cards. After all, a little mystery makes everything more interesting.      
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today Tonka had to go the vet. He needed his 6 months injection for heartworm prevention. We also picked up his vaccination records along with Merlin and Guenivere's for when they board and the doggy hotel while we're in Vegas.  Going out with Tonka is always unpredictable, you never know what your going to get. He is just so damn cute, everyone wants to pet him. He's still very puppish so he can be a bit wild. But, he loves kids and is always gentle around them and willing to roll over and let them rub his pink tummy. So, we're in the vets office waiting our turn and there is this little girl making Tonka sit for treats. Oh, and by the way my Tonka Truck is very good when he knows he will be rewarded with a cookie. He was taught at "puppy pre-school" and in basic obedience. Anyway, the little girls mother is sitting there with her cat in a carrier smiling at Tonka and her little girl playing. she says " He looks like the dog from " The Little Rascals", He's so cute, what a good dog" I say, "yeah, he does look like that dog a lot of people say that" She says, "What kind of dog is he?" I say, "He's Mixed with American Pitt Bull Terrier and American Bulldog Her smile drops, she grabs her kids arm and pulls her away from Tonka, gives me a dirty look, turns her body position like she is protecting her kid and stupid cat from my vicious pitt bull that might bite her face off. What a bitch. It drives me crazy! This is not an isolated incident, Tonka and I went to get a fish from Pet Co, and lady about freaked out because there was a "Pitt Bull" in the store. One time there were two ladies together in the parking lot at the vets office and one of them screamed at me "shame on you for owning that vicious dog" Tonka was only like 5 months old then. These people are so swayed by the media and think that just because criminals use American Pitt Bull Terriers in backyard fights and backyard breeding that all of them are the same. Tonka is the absolute sweetest dog you could ever meet. Merlin and Guenivere, my other 2 dogs are Boston Terriers. I trust Tonka around children more that I do them. It's unbelivable and breaks my heart for my poor Tonka. I was raised with German Shepards and have had Boston's up until we brought Tonka home. I will never have another breed again. (although Richard want's a Boxer, that's what he was raised with). He is not only sweet, but he's cool, he's funny, he's smart, he's athletic, and the best damn snuggler EVER! He never leaves my side, he is the ultimate "velcro boy" even when I'm in the shower he lays on the mat in the bathroom and waits for me, occasionally sticking his head in to say hi, he's done this since he was 6 weeks old.  My dog's are like my children and are treated as such. So, for these horrid people to insult me this way gets under my skin.  So please, if your one of those people reading this, and you judge a dog by it's breed and all the bull shit you see on the nightly news - please don't. Visit  urlLink www.badrap.org  for information on the breed. They are great dogs and I am sick and tired of the fucking media making them out to be monsters.  I'm so mad - i'm not doing spell check - so sorry if everything is misspelled. I suck at grammar and spelling. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A HURRICANE WARNING REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR THE FLORIDA KEYS FROM THEDRY TORTUGAS TO THE SEVEN MILE BRIDGE...AND FOR THE FLORIDA WESTCOAST FROM EAST CAPE SABLE NORTHWARD TO THE STEINHATCHEE RIVER. A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTEDWITHIN THE WARNING AREA DURING THE NEXT 24 HOURS. PREPARATIONS SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION. RAINFALL TOTALS OF 4 TO 8 INCHES ARE LIKELY ALONG CHARLEYS PATHACROSS THE EASTERN UNITED STATES.  THESE RAINS COULD CAUSELIFE-THREATENING FLASH FLOODS. ISOLATED TORNADOES ARE POSSIBLE ACROSS PARTS OF SOUTHERN AND CENTRAL FLORIDA INCLUDING THE FLORIDA KEYS TODAY.   ..TROPICAL DEPRESSION FOUR DEVELOPS IN THE FAR EASTERN ATLANTIC.. . THE DEPRESSION IS MOVING TOWARD THE WEST NEAR 14 MPH...22 KM/HR...AND THIS GENERAL MOTION IS EXPECTED TO CONTINUE FOR THE NEXT 24HOURS MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS ARE NEAR  35 MPH... 55 KM/HR...WITH HIGHERGUSTS.  SOME STRENGTHENING IS FORECAST DURING THE NEXT 24 HOURS...AND THE DEPRESSION COULD BECOME A TROPICAL STORM LATER TODAY ORTONIGHT.    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hurricane Charlie is gonna be a big one. Catorgory 3. That's pretty scary. Looks like the swell will make some good surf tomorrow - Richard is happy. He is sitting here trying to make me look at this stupid squirrel cartoon on illwillpress.com his name is foamy or something like that. I think it's stupid. I want to go to see The Village. All the plans for the schedule for the reunion are final. We only have 1 1/2 weeks to go. I am starting to get excited. It's been a long time since I have been out of town.  I got a big tip on a transaction that I closed from the seller today. I think I am going to buy a bunch of shoes with it. I love shoes. May be I'll  get a pedicure too - this way my feet will look cute in my new shoes.  Ok - Richard is rushing me now he wants to go somewhere - apparently, it's boring in the house. Maybe he wants to go fly a kite. buh-bye.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took Marigolds ink block test. Here's my result.  Natalie, your subconscious mind is driven most by Peace  urlLink   You have a deeply-rooted desire to make peace in the world. Whether through subtle interactions with loved ones, or through getting involved in social causes, it is important to you to be able to influence the world in a positive way.You have a deep respect for humankind. You care about the future of the world, even beyond your own involvement in it, and you inspire others to feel the same way. Your innate drive toward peace guides you in daily life towards decisions that are respectful toward yourself and others. Your psyche is very rich; the more you learn about it, the more you will understand who you really are. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...BONNIE FORMS FROM THE REMNANTS OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION TWO IN THE SOUTHERN GULF OF MEXICO... AT 4 PM CDT...2100Z...THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM BONNIE WASLOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 23.2 NORTH...LONGITUDE  88.7 WEST OR ABOUT 410 MILES SOUTH OF THE MOUTH OF THE MISSISSIPPI RIVER. BONNIE IS MOVING TOWARD THE NORTHWEST NEAR 12 MPH...AND THIS GENERAL MOTION IS FORECAST TO CONTINUE TONIGHT.  A GRADUAL DECREASE INFORWARD SPEED AND A TURN TO THE NORTH IS EXPECTED ON TUESDAY. MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS ARE NEAR  45 MPH... 75 KM/HR...WITH HIGHERGUSTS.  SOME GRADUAL STRENGTHENING IS FORECAST DURING THE NEXT24 HOURS. Interests on the Gulf Coast should monitor this system closely. Looks like this one will head to Florida/Alabama. Looks like it will not strengthen into a hurricane at this point.  Also - TD#4 is in the Carribean - it is forcased that Saturday it will be Hurricane Charlie and entering into the Gulf of Mexico. This could be a big one.  Keep posted for updates.   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The time is correct on my computer. The time reflected on my entries is wrong. - Why??? Help- it's really bothering me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Finally it's Friday. My crazy week is over. I am going to try my hardest to take this weekend off. Yesterday was NUTS- I had to leave work early before I went postal on some mortgage companies. I left and went to Target to go shop - Target Rocks! I just wandered around for about an hour and all I bought was a $8 tank top that I now think makes my boobs look saggy.  Helen has to go back to work on Monday after 3 months of maternity leave, so she came over to my house with Samantha and Mason. We took samantha to the Kemah Boardwalk (it's so tourist ridden - but fun). They have a new exhibit at the aquarium- Stingray Reef - it's a huge tank full of stingray. Kind of like a big swimming pool. You get to feed them fish, you put the fish inbetween your fingers and stick your whole arm down in the tank and they will come over and suck the fish out of your hand, it's pretty cool. Helen went to do it and Samantha who is 3 went hysterical, she thought the big ass stingray was going to eat her mommy. That kid is pretty cute. After all the excitement with the stingrays we let Samantha play in the sprinklers on the boardwalk, she had a blast while Helen, Mason and I melted in the hot sun.   Also - my "career listing" finally closed this week. This is a home that I had on the market for over a year. I sold it 4 times, yeah - every time it would go to close the buyers mortgage would fall through or something like that. So - finally after all the hours and hard work I put into it, I get paid and get to put a sold sign in the yard. I am truly excited . Richard is taking me to our favorite Italian restaurant to celebrate tonight. So much for dieting. It's getting too late for me to lose some weight before Vegas.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tropical Depression Number Two has formed east of the Lesser Antilles. T.D. #2 was centered at 13.2 north, 54.2 west, as of 11 AM EDT. It was moving west at 21 mph, with maximum sustained winds of 30 mph.A strong tropical wave and associated area of low pressure is out in the eastern Atlantic, west of the Cape Verde Islands.  Looks like it will also head up the east coast. (North Carolina, again???)  Hurricane Alex is now a Cat 2 storm traveling up the coast of North Carolina. In the next 24 hours it will move away from the coast and move in to unfavorable waters and more than likely dissolve.  I have got to get the U button fixed. I can't work like this. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Looks like Alex will become the first hurricane of this season. The weather dudes predict that he will strengthen into a Cat. 1 storm. I hope everyone has their bottled water / batteries ready on the coast of North Carolina. I'm not sure why I am so attracted to the weather, I think I should have been a meterologist (or learn how to spell). I should go back to school, how much money do they make???? I should look into this.  I read a good book yesterday/today, it was so good I couldn't put it down. it's a Mary Higgins Clark murder/mystery - "who done it book". I have not read any fiction in a long time. My Mom gave it to me, she is BIG on reading romance and murder mystery. The book is about a lady who's husband is murdered and she goes on a quest to find the killer. Little does she know, it was all a huge setup - her husband really is not dead, he faked his own death. He planted a bomb on his boat and blew it up and had his scuba gear on board for his escape. He had been laundering money from his construction/real estate company and was going to flee the country with the secretary who was his secret lover. That's until little smartie-pants wifey figures it all out and kills them both.  The U Button on my lap top is malfunctioning. I have to hit it like 2-3 times for it to work. It's bugging the shit out of me.  Today is our friend Keri's birthday, she is 32 today - she's a little depressed - she thinks she's getting old. We are going to meet her at Molly's pub (this is like our Cheer's Bar). I am going on an anti -beer diet. I am starting to grow a beer belly- it's not pretty. Last time I did this diet I lost 4 pounds in a week, then I quit. This time I must stick to the plan. NO BEER FOR ME TONIGHT.  I am making Sweet and Sour Chicken for dinner tonight if anyone wants to stop by, we always have left overs.  I might even make some brownies.     I 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect from South Santee River South Carolina to Cape Hatteras North Carolina. A tropical storm watch is in effect from north of Cape Hatteras to Oregon Inlet North Carolina, and from Edisto Beach to South Santee River South Carolina. Tropical Storm Alex is located about 90 miles south southeast of Charleston South Carolina. Winds are sustained at at 40 mph. The storm was nearly stationary and will probably resume a northward drift later Sunday evening and Sunday night. This could bring the storm along or over the northern South Carolina or southern North Carolina coast later tonight and on Monday. The immediate affects from this storm will be an increase in winds and showers along the South and North Carolina coasts during the next 12 hours. Dangerous rip currents are already being reported and these very dangerous ocean currents will increase as Alex increases in intensity.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>