<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I just woke up, and I feel real yucky. I dont even want to go to work today. But I have to so that my pay check comes in decent...well atleast today is the last day. Im going to ask Sharim about tomorrow's Boxing match. I wanted to invite my dad and monstro. But Im not even sure if my mom is going to let me attend. Bleh. What else is new?  I cant wait till Im 18  Any way yea. Last night I wrote a letter for Jason, telling him how I feel. But I doubt Im going to even deliver it. Maybe Diane is right, maybe we should spend some time apart... bleh. But what else worries me, is I have a funny feeling that this "Online crush" she has is in fact Jason. And I think Jason encourages it. But I dont know, That could just be me assuming things. I find her really annoying. And Jason says he does too... so maybe not. Im just so tired of all of this. I want to ask Pam, my shrink if she can give me some anti depressents or something. I wouldnt mind seeing the world in rose colored glasses right about now. You know what else is bothering me, is that I used to be suicidal, and depressed all the time, and didnt care about anything, my body went entirely numb. That feeling is comming back. I barely feel human contact anymore. All I feel now is tormented love for Jason, btu its more like Im feeling teh pains of love more than enjoying it. I can be laughing and smilng, and then a second goes by and I begin to think. Why do I bother laughing, no one even notices my smile. Bleh.         
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Lets see, What happened today? At first today I was suppose to go to the zoo with my job. I was goign to take Giselle along, but the trip got cancelled due to rain... I didnt really want to to go to work after that, I went to Jason's house being he wasnt going to school. I spent the day with him. You know I realize, Im a very depressed person. I look at him and he seems so distant to me. I love him with all my heart and yearn to be loved in the same way. But that will never happen. Hes not even in love with me. Which is messed up because Id do anything for him, and he knows it. Instead he loves two other girls who he's not even with.          Did they give him the love he deserves? Did they change their entire lives around to make him happy? Did they put their family and friends aside to be with him? Did they do his essay for school for him because he was having trouble? Did they sit him down to work on a report that he kept putting off? Do they worry about him the way I do? Do they wish they can take all his bad memories, fears, pain and put it into themselves so that he wont have to feel it? Do they make sure that everything in his life is going okay before they even think about themselves. Do they cry at the mere thought of him being in harms way? I do. WOuld they take a bullet for him? I would.          And all I really want in return is to be loved by him, for me to be the only one in his heart. For him to think abotu me throughout the course of his day. For him to not even feel the need to look at otehr women because he knows he has me. For him to respect me as a person.           It hurts being with him. But I guess theres nothing I can do, I  am a slave to my love and to all of my emotions. There is nothing I can do to change that.            People I feel threatened by in my relationship            1. Kristie         2. Vanessa         3. Karen aka Toby Wan         4. Thin and beautiful young ladies that I know he'd be attracted to.           People ask me why? And Ill say it.  I am ugly.  I am fat.  I have messed up hair.  I am depressed.  I am dumb.  I am not feminine.  I complain.  I am often sad.  I am spiteful.          All things that make me unattractive and unwanted.          I wonder if he'll ever love me the way I love him.          You know what hurts most, is the fact that I am not important in anyones life. I mean nothing to everyone. And then the one person who is my everything, and I beg that he feel the same, will never love me the way I wish he did.          I feel used sometimes... and it hurts. I dont know what Im suppose to do anymore...           If I die, would n e one cry?       What if I commit suicide right now, how long would it take people to realize Im dead. What is I fell into a coma, when I wake up, who would be by my side. A worst thought is, Jason, the person I would love to waken up my eyes to seeing, if I had been asleep for too long, he would probably assume its okay for him to date others. And would have moved on by the time I woke up.           I hate sex. It makes me sad.  I hate liquor. It makes me mad.  I hate drugs. It makes ppl bad.  I hate myself. And the life I have. 
    
</post>


</Blog>