<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Waking up to the sunrise. Looking out the window seeing my future. Far away dreams going to come true. Feeling the butterflies in my stomach. Feeling all warm when I lay in my bed and dream of you. Seeing your beautifull eyes as I stare into your soul. Wanting to taste our first kiss. To feel your skin against mine. To express my love to you. Smiling so much in my life. Knowing Im wanted from you. Being taken to a place I never been to before. Being welcomed in open arms. Your voice calms my heart like the waters crashing into a sea. You are the one you takes away my dying tears and makes me feel alive. You caress my lips with a explosion of beginings. You make me want to live and walk on this earth together. As we become one and grow old together. This is how love reflects me from my soulmate. Paul, I love you. You are my angel who has rescued me and took away my darkness. Gave me wings to fly. Gave me a meaning to breathe. You are my desires, dreams, and future. Everynight before I go to bed, I hear your voice whisper in through the wind sleep well my love. Watching the palest moon shine above our bodies. Falling asleep, knowing soon we will be together.  
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hot liquid explodes in the depth of my soul Burning sensation comes over my pale skin Melts my inner mind Hot coals twine through my veins Closing my eyes Pleasured by the pain Myself flickers against the flame Becoming one with the dark fires that ravish me  Listening to the rain that pours  Around my body Not even a drip Just a puddle of me In the middle of the thunderstorm Traces my hands down my warm flesh Lost in this moment  Opening my eyes Looking over my skin Seeing the rain has baptized Me into a pure shade of silver Becoming a sharp blade Lying across the stonewall Waiting to be in the hands of My Lord To be pressed up As he shatters me into his soul And I become one with his heart As the silver breaks into his self And we become a reflection in the Sky, creating an overcast of clouds. 
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Standing at the window And looking out at the black sky Seeing the darkest moon Turning around and seeing my love Staring deep into my  eyes   As we both walk too the bedroom Listening to the sound of a blue sea Hearing the waves crash against the reefs My back against my love Listening to his voice That is calm has water His hands so warm and soft Gliding down my skin Feeling his body against me.   Crawling into his bed Two naked bodies lying so close Closing our eye's Feeling the red fire Our love starts to stain Our flesh As we become One Sleeping. Waking up to the Rising Sun. 
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ~~TimeGlass~~ Taking the time to solve the puzzle The sand covers the ground A empty glass to be filled Broken mirror of the past lies on the floor To many saved memories were in that jar  A stranger enters my life causes me to forget the darkness shares his wisdom and guides me to the light brings my knowledge to the paper wakes my mind  Sends me his smiles and words of forgiveness Allows the poet in me to take many challenges fighting the fears and forgeting the demons  His hands touched my inner beauty allowed myself to be seen the scars were healed He has saved my soul in many ways Our lives have been taken to the highest tale The illusions of our history will forever be sealed.
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    ~~WingedIllusions~~ Addicted to the liquid that floods my soul with passion. I'm leaving this dream for a true emotion. Wrapped in a silent cold dark night and keep loosing the track of time. Winged illusions haunting me day and night. Blinded by the darkest past and guarded by the palest moon that shines upon my tears. I have to drink from the drought that burns my heart. Feels the wind against my skin, smells the air, lies in the sand and falls asleep to the sound of the rain. And I always knew the answer is the same: sweet bullets. Gun powder all over the ground, strangers surround me, feels so alone, missing her eyes looking into mine, needing her love that keeps me safe in my mind. And who knows why I always get the second chance: the hell of an eternity. She does something to me, keeps my heart from being broken, keeps my mind from shattering against the glass, she will be the answer and take away the pain from my past. And never mind the broken glass I walk on, my soul would laugh seeing your icon: the sweet imagine of a flame, my frozen soul can't even claim the hope I've had and lost.
    
</post>


</Blog>