<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Hey ya all!! How was your day? Mine was good! I hung out with the coolest gal- Jen Jen!! First, I woke up and made macaroni and cheese then Jenny came over and we watched Legally Blonde! Great movie! Then we took Lou Lou and Snickeys to the park and met up with Evan and his dog Jack then my stupid dog Mickey flew into the NASTY dirty pond with the ducks and so i went chasing in after him and had to clean him off at Evans. After that issue we just chilled at Evans for an hour or so then Jenny came back to my casa and Chris, Robin and Mark came over to pick us up and we went to Chris's house. At Chris's house we played Wiffle Ball and then we jsut chilled in his room for awhile. IT was so much fun!! After Chris's Jenny, my sister Natalie and my dad went to Suzette's Creperie for din din! It was scrumpious! Then we came back to my casa for like 10 mins. then met up with Chris, Mark, Robin, Craig and Evan at Fox Bowl to go bowling! It was fun but Jenny left at 10 to go to Boston! I miss my baby already!! So yea now I am at home just chilling out waiting for Nick to call from Colorado. Oh well! TOmorrow I  am going up to Lake Geneva to Aunt Becky and Uncle Bob's house!! Yea!! It is going to be so much fun! I'll be there til Sunday. If you need anything just call my cell! I love you all! Sorry to bore you out with my day to day life! Much Love! Have an AWESOME weekend! LINDSAY AND NICK COME HOME SUNDAY! YEA!!     
      
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey Everyone! My friends are AWESOME! They are amazing! I love them to death!!     &nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; * Jenny, Lindsay, Rachel, Brie, Lauren, Christina, Haley,   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; &nbsp;Mary, Kayt, Marlee, Liz, Nick C., Nick N., Nick E., Tom,    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Evan, Craig, Mark, Mike, Joe, Matt G., Chris S., Matt C.*  
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey!! Yesterday  was my birthday!! HEHE! Well let's see I woke up at the crack of dawn (9;05) to go to tennis at 9;15 and I played til 11:30 which sucked the butt and he wouldnt even let me out on my birthday!! So after tennis, my mother, me and Nats went to the Farmers Market and I got a dozen of assorted pink roses which by the way are gorgeous! Then we got back to my moms apartment and just chilled then went back to my dads house to get my presents from my family and all the cards and stuff which was cool. Then back to my Mom's house and Lindsay came over to straighten my hair and then i got ready for my party! At 6 I met, Lindsay,Jenny,Evan,Sam and Tom at the train station and we took the train down to Chi-town to eat at the HArd Rock Cafe. We had to take seprate taxis to get to the restuartant and of course i got stuck with the boys and Sam was up in the front seat taking to the Cab driver and it was hilarious! Then after a 2 second cab ride we got the restuarant and ate a whole lotta food and my daddy surprised me with Roses and was there for about 30 seconds and left but it was the thought that count and we finished having our dinner then my waiter grabbed me, took me on stage and the WHOLE restuartant shouted "HAPPY BIRTHDAY!" to me and while i was holding this giant dessert thing with a candle. It was cool though! After dinner my mother and devil child decided that they should all go to the Rainforest Cafe to by me plastic snakes!!! (For any of you smart people out there know that I am deathly afraid of snakes!) So when my mom walked outside with a bag I began to ball because I was so scared and pissed at her. So then the limo came and picked us up and we had a long ride home listening to a bunch of remixes, it was fun! We dropped of my mom at the train station to get the car and then we dropped off the rest of the people in the limo while my mom was getting us amo! Then on our way home to my moms apartment the limo driver had to come fix my window casue the crappy thing broke and i seriously thought he was going to rape all of us! I was freaked out and he was stupid cause he doesnt know how to LISTEN to directions from Captian Lindsay who was navigating us home adn the guy went back on Naperville and got lost and then we finally got home at 11:15 then did some work and got back at 12;30 then watched Dirty Dancing twice because Lindsay wanted to watch it again but i fell asleep. So that was my Birthday! IM FINALLY 14!! WOHO!! Much Love!!    
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey!! Today Lindsay and I went to the Wheaton Sports Center at 11;15 and worked out til 1;15. Then we took showers and then the blow dryers sucked- Lindsays was smoking, mine didnt dry. Then my mommy came and picked us up and we went to Jewel to grocery shop for my mom and Lindsay and I bought bread. IT was scrumpious! Then we dropped Lindsay off then Natalie at cheerleading and my mom and I came and picked up the dogs and went to 7 Gables to walk them. Mickey passed out! haha! Then I came home and went on the computer, answered the phone about a 100 times and then I began to read the book Feed. I dont like it at all and my dad is MAKING me read it! Stupid books that we have to read for school! It's so stupid! Anywho, after reading for all of 10 mins. I went outside and watered all the plants for an hour so now the plants look BEAUTIFUL! hehe! And now I am trying to figure out what I am going to do tonight! Much Love!  
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hey ya'll!! How was your day? Mine was dandy! Lets see, first I was rudely woken by Natalie and Emily with louie on top of my head scurrying around like a bangee. Then at 11;15, Kim Lee pick me, Natalie and Emily up and we went to Houlihans- I HATE THAT RESTUARANT excecpt for hte Fruit Fizz's those are grand! Then I came home and chilled and watched A Baby Story, painted my nails and watched the Ashlee Simpson show ( hehe! Nick) Then at 2;45 I headed off to Dr.Bob's office for fillings and sealinse on my teeth! I got happy gas! It felt good! HAHA! Then I came home and just chilled then went back to my Mom's apartment she was moving into. Then got home took a shower got ready for the night and went to Sam's house with Lindsay, Rachel, Nick, Nick, Evan, Craig, and Mike. It was bundles of fun! A LOT of stuff happend! After we dropped off Rachy and Linny- Me, Molly and Natalie went on a run to McDonalds and I got my scrumpious meal! 2 hamburgers, fries and a medium Coke! HEHE! Evan you should be proud.... Now I am home and typing this and tomorrow Lindsay and I are going to the Wheaton Sports Center to work out then make breakfast! Sweet Dreams! LOVE YOU ALL!  
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey everyone!! I hope your weekend went well-mine did!! hehe! Lets see.... Friday afternoon Me, my dad and Natalie went up to Lake Geneva to Aunt Becky and Uncle Ozzy's ( his real name is Bob but I call him Ozzy because he reminds me of him!) lake house which is GOREGOUS! I cant even tell you how pretty it is. Anywho we got up there and ate dinner and Skinny's then came back I showed my dad how to make a good fire thanks to Honey Rock Wilderness class! HAHA! LINDS! Good times in that one! and we made s'mores then I painted up in the studio then went to bed. Saturday Uncle Ozz came and woke me up at the crack of dawn- 9;45 and we went ot breakfast at Kent's which is a little shack that has the best french toast, then we went across the street the Paradise Miniture Golf thing were i lost because i suck at putting- oh well! Then we went back to the house and went golfing at Lake Geneva Country Club right across the street thing and played about 5 holes of golf and then i quit cause it was WAY to hott out! Then me and Natalie had a HUGE golf cart war with the golf carts! IT WAS SO MUCH FUN! We went through like weeds and crap and totally messed up the carts and natalie flew into mine and then i flew out of it cuase i did a donut and flew out! it was so scary! then natalie ran into me and ruined hte front end of the cart cause shes a moron and doesnt think. Then after 2 hours of that we went into Fontana and looked at beautiful houses then went Gordy's then to the grocery store.THEY HAVE THE BEST GROCERY STORE!! We came home, made a scrumpious din din then Natalie and I had another golf cart palooza! Then I came home and painted and then went on a night cart ride to look for dear or whatever then watched the fireworks down on the pier. It was amazing! It so sereal and peaceful! Came home- painted some more then went to bed. Sunday- I was woken up rudely again by Natalie and Louie and we went to starbucks but I was in my pajamas which included basketball shorts and a little tank top with no shoes and my dad wanted me to get out of the car and go and get stuff from Starbucks! I THINK NOT! Then we went down to Gordy's again to get the boat and my dad wanted me to get out again in front of a bunch of normal looking people. SOmetimes I think he doesnt think. We drove home- correction I drive home! hhehe!! I am good! And got in our bathingsuit adn packed up for the ghetto pontoon boat! LET ME TELL YOU! IT WAS TRUELY GHETTO! We didnt even have seats, we had lawn chairs and mine kept moving and oh man it was horrible! Then we "dropped anckor" to swim and it took us about 20 trys because my dad didnt think that we were stable but we were cause you could tell when i brought the anckor up and a bunch of nasty seaweed and rocks came up. Then finally we were stable and i jumped into a pile of seaweed then got back on the ghetto boat and went cruising back past beautiful homes that i would die to live in. Got back to the house, showered and off back to go ol' Wheaton, Illinois! Of course we stopped at Frateillo's though! I love that place and across the street there is a boat on a giant stick! ITS SO COOL! Then we got home at around 7 then Nick and I talked on the phone and came up with the plan of playing tennis since there is nothing better to do so me, Rachey, Nick, Evan, and Craig went and played tennis! It was fun except for the fact that i slid into a pile of piss and the kid was laughing at me then i fell off the rock climbing thing, yea i wasnt laughing! Then Rachy's dad came and picked us up at 10 and I came home and now Emily and Natalie are annoying the crap out of me!! I gotta go! I love ya all!    
      
</post>


</Blog>