<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this morning i woke up at 11:30am or so.  younok's cleaning lady was here and she was super nice too...i should just say that EVERY person i have met is incredibly nice and helpful and i'm sure every person will be so i don't have to type that anymore.  anyhow, youngok and i have bad jet lag, so we just lazed around for a while then went grocery shopping.  there is a new beautiful grocery center with a nice food court and starbucks right by her condo...instead of having super high aisles with huge boxes of food, they have like 6 foot ailses made of black wire, kind of like closet organizers and on these shelves are small bags of noodles, sauces, everything.  it's really cute actually!  and they have so many free samples!!  i love it here!  i bought some food and youngok and i ate some really good chinese food at the food court.  where she lives is comparable to the gold coast in chicago, so everything is kind of expensive but very nice and clean and new!  then we came back and lazed around some more and ate some fancy cakes we bought at that bakery where i dropped the tongs.  they had free samples too...i learned that free samples are kind of universal, no matter where you are in the world, you can still understand what is a free sample and what isn't...but the used toothpicks aren't thrown away, instead they are put in a small tray right next to the fresh ones.  one is in red writing and one is in black...i just have to remember which is which when i'm on my own...oh well..i'll remember later.  thanks for reading!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i was so tired on this flight...i sat next to a really nice man who was from canada on business and told me how i should get into stock anaylsis because then i could travel...pretty good idea i thought.  to bad i forgot math and hate to read.  this flight had the best food, sushi!  and you know, i probably should have questioned all raw fish that i ate, but since my stomach was okay from that other sushi in tokyo, i thought i would be fine.  you can't have fun unless you try i think!  or get sick... hey!  youngok's mother just brought me yello melon...it's like honey dew and cantelope mixed together and looks like a giant cucumber.  anyhow, i slept hard core on this flight and woke up to the painful pressure in my forehead from the landing...i'm sensitive to change in pressure for some reason...but it's fine when i land, so no big deal.  anyway, i got off the plane and waited in a HUGE line for customs...i was glad at this point that i had already gone through all that trouble before becasue i got into korea with no problem...ha ha, suckers...just kidding, i'll probably get deported next month...  and there waiting for me was the very kind and generous J.H. Kim, youngok's father!  he held a sign on it with my name, i've ALWAYS wanted to be in that situation!  he already knew about my luggage problem and said it would all be taken care of.  we got into an SUV and he drove me to his beautiful condo.  youngok and her mother and father live in an awesome condo!!  it has all hardwood floors, 2 bedrooms and a master bedroom, 2 baths, a spacious living room, wonderful high tech kitchen with a flat stove, and a closed in balcony that stretches the length of the condo.    he gave me the tour of the condo and offered me anything i wanted to eat or drink or watch tv...but i just crashed on my bed.  i was exhausted.  J.H. Kim went to work and i slept.  he came back in an hour and him and i went to another airport in seoul to pick up youngok and get my luggage.  before we left youngok's mother (who is so nice too) made a little bag up for me with juice and snacks in it.  then J.H. Kim took me to this pastery shop to get some bread to eat.  this was the best bread i've ever eaten in my life!    i slept on the carride to the airport and totally drooled on myself.  oh yeah, i also totally dropped these tongs to grab the bread with at the bakery, i was a mess.  at the airport, which was clean and beautiful and high tech, we got my luggage and picked up youngok.  i was so excited to see her!  we came back and her sister met up with us to help us carry our luggage to the condo and unpack.  her sister helped me unpack every single thing!  she was so nice and funny too...youngok's family is just wonderful!  that night i completely crashed again.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my friend Yusaku Toh, from film school, met me at airport and i was SO GLAD that he did...japan was really confusing and not that many people speak english like they do here in korea.  so we met up and he walked with me to my free shuttle to my hotel, the Sky Court.  we rode there together and do you know what?  they drive on the other side of the rode like europe, but in korea they drive on the side like in america...wierd huh?  but i was bizarre and so many times i thought we were going to get into an accidet becasue we were on the "wrong side" of the road.  the sky court was nice but SO SMALL!!  not necessarily the cubical i imagined, but it was about 9x9 feet.  all it fit was my bed, a dresser and a bathroom!  it was so cute and actually, my size!  i actually felt of normal height in japan, it was nice.  it was also cool to keep up on the olympics...i noticed that now only the japanese competitors were being covered by the news and there were some pretty awesome japanese athlets, like the girl who won judo!  i saw her interviewed on some japanese show later and she was so shy, but not a shy competitor...she was awesome.  anyhow, yusaku was going to take me to where they shot "Lost in Translation", but it was an hour away from my hotel, but the train was so cool!  we didn't take the bullet train cause it was more expensive, but just the regular subway train was awesome!  it was so clean and very colorful!  all the ads were hanging from the ceiling and EVERYTHING had a cartoon character. and EVERYONE was on their cell phones...but they are much better than we have in america...our most high tech phone in america is the old model in japan.  they can look at each other while talking to each other!  as well as full internet access, 2 mega pixel cameras and video capabilities.  we went to two little cities, one was Shinju-something and the other i forgot...but they were amazing!!  everything was lit up with colorful neon signs and everyone was dressed super hip...everyone was out and everyone was having fun, shopping and eating.  i saw a KFC with a life size, plexi-glass colineral (how do you spell that?  the KFC kernal)...i guess when japan hosted the world cup, a bunch of people stole the 'kernal' so now he had a chain around him like a dog.  it was really funny.  everything was so clean!  the bathroom at McDonald's was amazing!  a computerized toilet that was clean!  and the doors to the bathroom were about 2/3 of the size here.  yusaku and i ate at a sushi resturant though, and it was pretty good...i had so much fun there!  everything was so easy to do and we didn't have to wait for anything...like the sushi resturant, we just sat at this counter and waited for the sushi we wanted to eat to come to us.  it was already made on plates that were on a conveyer belt type presentation and you just picked up what you wanted.  and every one gave me a warm wash cloth to wipe my hands with...mom and dad, i know you would really appreciate that!  ah ha...  every shopping center was in the street, so we didn't really have to "go into" a mall...i bought some really cool vans for about $20.00 with my new yen!  i love japanese money....they have $1.00 and $5.00 coins...it was very convienent.  and you can buy anything in a vending machine; pop, tea, beer, cigarettes...no one cared who you were or how old...it was all there in a vending machine!  yusaku was so helpful and nice to me...he carried my shoes around the whole night and translated everything for me...i would have been so lost with out him!  we then played darts and met up with his friend from work...she was SO NICE too, but i forgot her name...i always do that!  forget names, not play darts in tokyo.  but we went to this really cool photo booth place where you go into a booth and with all touch screens, choose different backgrounds and make your own picture stickers!  it was so much fun, after you pose with the backgound you can use a computer to write stuff on the photo and add little pictures that go along with the background.  we choose a haunted house background and i added fangs to yusaku and blood to me...then they printed out and were only like 1cm x 1cm!  everything was so small!!  and everything had music and lights and cartoon characters!  even the older men had cartoon characters hanging off of their cell phones!  then we went to a rasta bar!  i actually listened to bob marley and other japanese-rasta music and drank some japanese pop and ate this japanese pickel with a plum sauce and jelly.  jelly is like a softer jell-o in thick juice.  do you know what else is popular in japan?  is having a sunny-side up egg on your hamburger!    so THEN we played pool at some other place and ordered more food!  we had these chocolate covered cracker sticks in pinapple sauce and fried octapus hush puppies with mayonaise dipping sauce.  it was actually really good!  it's definitly a different cuisine there!  i was getting tired, but had to wait until 4:30AM for my train...so it was finally time and we all got to the train.  at the station, everyone who had been up all night was there...it was so clean and safe!  no "shady" people asking for money or people trying to mug you...it was a really nice time.  one business man had too much fun and was lying in the subway moaning, then he passed out, so i took a picture of him...i can't wait to show it to you!  yusaku rode the train all they way back to the hotel with me!!  we both slept and no one cared  everyone was sleeping...japan seemed very laid back to me, surprisingly enough!  no one cared if you bummped into them or were really drunk...it was kind of like, "hey, it happens!"  at the hotel yusaku and i said goodbye.  i was so blessed to have him show me around and take care of me...thank you yusaku!!  my plane for seoul actually left from Hanada, Japan which was 1 1/2 hours from my hotel...much farther than i thought, so of course i was late.  i rushed to take a shower and got into the shuttle bus who only took me to Narita!  so the very kind bus driver, who spoke VERY little english, carried my luggage all over the airport to help me find another bus to Hanada.  i had spent a lot of money in tokyo and was worried that i wouldn't have enough for the bus to Hanada, but i had the exact amount left!  phew!  so i boared the bus to Hanada where i found a nice man who spoke english to talk to...now Hanada has 2 large terminals and it seems to me that the english words "right" and "left" get confused in japanese because i was given the wrong direction every time.  i was so confused!  i got off at the wrong terminal...i had about 45 minutes to my flight and wasn't even at the right terminal...so i had to take another bus to terminal 2 (the international terminal).  i was finally at the right terminal and had to check in.    here i found out that my luggage was lost in Narita.  at this point i didn't care, but it took a while for the flight attendant to explain this to me...so i just smile and bowed a lot and everything was fine.  (i think i bowed more in my whole life in tokyo that day!)  THEN i had to go through security and of course they did a special check of my carry on luggage and caught my nail clipping scissors...but they let me keep them...which was nice.  so i literally ran to my gate only to find out that the boarding was delayed.  ha ha!    so i finally boared my final flight to Seoul, super tired and a little delerious. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so tracy and i woke up at 6:00AM so that she could drop me off at the airport and get to work on time.  LA traffic really is pretty bad, but at least you get to look at mountains while you drive...we circled the airport twice and i finally found where to get out.  my bags were so frick'n heavy!  i was so happy to get rid of them...but i had to wait 3 hours for ANA (All Nippon Airways, my airline service to Korea) to open, so i hung out with all the other international flyers at the overpriced McDonalds with my dumb heavy luggage.  finally ANA opened and i waited in line to check my luggage.  it was funny because i was the only caucasion and after a while i thought i was asian.  i'm just so used to looking like everyone else that i really thought i was, but then i would go to the bathroom and be surprised that i am not asian!  ha ha...  so what happens next is another (and really scary) point in which i almost couldn't go to korea.  so in order to stay in korea for over 30 days, i needed a visa.  to get a visa, i would have needed an employer to sponser me, or say that i will be working in Seoul, not just hanging around.  so i didn't have a visa, cause i don't have a job yet, but my return ticket was in 5 months, not 30 days.  so after about  an hour of explaining myself to 3 people, a REALLY nice man understood my story and got the ticket date to be changed for 30 days...so now either i find a job or get deported!  but God will get me a job, so i'm not worrying...but at that point i was definitly worrying and i must have looked like it because 3 different foriengers asked me "are you okay?"...ha ha  so i finally made it to my gate and i was one of 3 caucasians!!  and again, i thought i was asian anyway, so i didn't feel that out of place.  the plane was HUGE!  and had these great television screens behind the seat in front of me, so i had my own personal tv!  i sat next to two older japanese women who were like any old women i know...  they saved everything wrapped, the rolls at dinner, the salt, pepper, plastic silverware...they had all these "comforts" for plane travel like head rests and foot rests...  i was laughing at them until 8 hours out of 10 total hit and i was wishing i had all of those nice pillows and foot rests!  it was a LONG FLIGHT!  i slept on and off and watched Shrek 2 in french, then figured out how to in english.  it was a really fun experience though...the "crash instruction" was a video rather than a demonstration and a little animated "do not" symbol pointed at things not to do and got angry!  my lunch and dinner were alright...my lunch was wierd though...i had a tray of cooked vegetables, some noodles, a roll, 2 milano cookies THEN a tray of a piece of deli ham, one black olive, potato salad and 2 pieces of shrimp.  i called it "the sea meets a picnic" dish and of course ate everything because i was so curious about it all.  when the flight ended, the whole plane stretched together!!  there was a video of different stretching exercises and we all did them together!  it was so cool!  and funny for some reason...i laughed a lot.  i offered the two ladies some gum and hand lotion and they were really nice and gave me some cracker wrapped in seaweed and i ate it.  they kept speaking to me in japanese...yet another reason why i think i'm asian.  we landed in Narita Japan safely and this time i got to leave my heavy bags. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      at 3:00AM on monday morning my mom woke me up to get ready to go to the airport.  ken stayed the night so that he could join my mom and i to the airpot and say goodbye...we had stayed up almost all night trying to figure out this crazy speaker system my dad bought for our tv in the basement.  it's cool when it works, but otherwise it's like an invasion of speakers.  we tested it with LOTR (for all you non-geeks that = Lord of the Rings) and it was pretty awesome.  anyhow, ken was on the couch with the movie still playing and i woke him up to go...i said goodbye to my sleepy dad and we were off to Midway in Chicago.  this is pretty much the begining of my several set-backs to korea...you'll see a theme here in the next couple blogs of how something went wrong which could have totally prevented me from korea...but God pulled through and now i am here.  so anyhow, on the way to Midway, we almost got lost.  but we didn't and got to the airport.  my friend Lori met us there just as the lady at the luggage check was yelling at me cause my bags were too heavy...i had to pay a $25.00 fee for one of them, but it was better than not going with them i guess.  we walked to the point where only i could go on alone and took some pictures (i'll post them later) and lori gave me this bundle of notes folded in a really cool way!  they were all goodbye notes from everyone at Bible Study...it was SO NICE to read them on the plane!  thank you everyone!  so then i hugged everyone goodbye and proceeded to my plane...i ended up sitting next to this really nice 16 year old girl named Heather (my sister's name!) who was from CA...she wants to attend Trinity College in Illinois and likes to eat food too!  wait, i guess a lot of people like to eat food...but she liked to eat even when she wasn't hungry, like me.  anyhow, we talked a lot and i slept a lot and drooled on my new jacket.  i arrived in LA safely and Tracy, my good friend from film school, picked me up on her lunch break.  it was so cool to see her out in LA with all the other film industry folks being successful and having fun...she took me back to her awesome apartment (get this...for $450 a month per person she has a great 3 bedroom apartment with a pool AND a parking space in a gated garage!!) then left to go back to work.  her super nice roomate Mandy took me to Hollywood Blvd. on her way to a meeting...but first Many and i ate at In and Out Burger!  it was one of the best burgers i've ever had and one of the shortest menues i've ever seen.  there were lots of beautiful people at In and Out and i spilled dr. pepper on myself.  i hung out around the Chinese Man theater and saw some CRAZY things like:  super posh shopping malls, spiderman, jimmi hendrix, a really good magic show, the gap, over priced suviouners, holloween costumes, wigs, homeless people and abaondoned stores.  LA was fun, but kind of dirty...i'm glad i live in Chicago.  Mandy picked me back up and took me back to the apartment.  when tracy got off work, tracy's BOYFRIEND KEITH!  (really nice guy) and tracy and i went grocery shopping.  tracy made us all dinner and some other film school friends of mine came over and we all watched the olympics.  it was SO NICE to see everyone!  they even came with ballons!  my friend Chris Cline works for a special effects company and builds a lot of stuff, so it was cute that the balloons he made me had a huge lugnut tied to the bottom to weigh them down.  we all reminiscent about SIU and Loren Cocking (for all those film SIU people) then i went to bed at 2:00AM, making my official awake time 23 hours.  thanks for reading!  i'll post pictures later!   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello, sorry that last picture was SO HUGE...was it HUGE on your computer too?  It didn't even fit on my blog window...ha ha.  Anyhow, I just wanted to talk about my last week in Chicago.    So friday night was my last Bible Studay, then saturday I went to Lawrence beach with Ken.    Ken is my very special friend.  He's not "special", but he is special to me and I will miss him very much.  Anyhow, we went to the beach together and man oh man, it was dir-tey.  First of all, there was a dog beach filled with like 70 dogs in a 20 square foot area.  I even saw a three legged dog.  Then walking along, was the "to be cleaned beach" where we saw a stagnet pool of lake water with two hazard garbage cans sitting in the middle.  Finally, we got to the "good beach" and played this football game that we made up.  I lost horribly and had egg all over my face after gloating how I was finally going to beat him.  Then I made the mistake of going in the water.  After taking giant leaps to avoid the alge, I made it to the "clean" water where I smelled ecoli to the max.  Gross.  Sunday I came to drop off my first "load" of apartment stuff at my parents home and had dinner.  It was really nice and I ate some corn.  Monday night I went out to dinner with my friends from church.  Lois (the girl just to the right of me on the HUGE picture below) bought me some wonderful tank tops from Forever 21 (thaks Lois!!) and I bought some more so I can look as hip as possible overseas.  Maria (the girl kneeling at the right of the HUGE photo below) came with too and we all went to eat at this pub which name I forgot...but it was great.  I had a pepper burger and it was delicious and we met up with Chris, Charlie and Anthony (Anthony is pictured below, he is the non-asian guy on the right...sorry Anthony, it's just the easiest way to explain it) and Chris and Charlie aren't in the photo.  Well THEN we went to Margies Candies and that was even better!  I loved the pecan rolled ice cream.  Needless to say, I won't be able to fit on the plane to Seoul.  Thank you everyone for the wonderful night!  Tuesday night I joined my two good girlfriends (and former roomates) Kris and Kate at the Movies in the Park for "Invasion of the Body Snachers" which wasn't as good as I thought it would be.  Not cause it's old, just cause it was so sad.  But they had a great place in the park and our friend Aaron from SIU also joined us!  THEN we stopped in Millinuem park and it was AWESOME!  I won't even explain it, just go.  Then we went back to thier apartment and I met Kate's adorable new puppy tucker.  I wish them both a lot of luck this next year...they're going to be missed by me...  Wednesday I was sick to my stomach all day.    Thursday was my last day of work.  That night I drove Ken to his home in Coal City to pick up his new computer.  His mom got us dinner and I spent time with his family and two dogs.  It was so much fun!  His family is very funny and I also watched a little bit of that creepy VH1 movie about Michael Jackson with his older sister.  Creepy is the perfect way to describe it.  That's all I will say.  Friday I spent the morning moving out of my apartment with my mom and Ken.  With out their help, I'd still be there eating ceral in a corner not knowing what to do next.  I have a lot of stuff.  Saturday is today and I am at my parent's house in Fox Lake and my brother is here with soon to join my sister, her husband and daughter Ava for dinner.  I'll take pictures with my NEW DIGITAL CAMERA and post them later.  Have a wonderful day and thanks for reading!
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This is a picture of my Bible Study group...well, most of them.  Do you see the cupcakes in front of us?  They were made for me by the girl to the left of me (i'm wearing the ET t-shirt) and they said, "We'll miss you Shandog".  It was such a special night to me.  Everyone in the group spoke about some memory they had with me and gave me some advice for Korea.  I didn't realize that there are aren't any dryers in Korea, as in the machines that dry your clothes after you wash them.  Oh well...I guess you'll see future blogs of a sopping wet Shannon looking confused.  Thank you Leonard for heading the study that night and thank you to everyone for what you had said and for the advice.  I will miss you all SO MUCH.  (all caps = a lot!)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        urlLink Youngok's Screening     Originally uploaded by  urlLink I like to take pictures .      Hello!  Thank you for visiting my blog...I thought since I am going to Korea because of Youngok Kim, I should introduce who she is.  She was an intern at the animation company where I work.  We became good friends by working on her animation that she was having this screening for.  SHE did the animation, I was just the voice of the cat.  It's a REALLY good animation and in one week she'll be heading out to SIGGRAPH in L.A to accept her first place award for the student animation competition...this is a HUGE deal.  Tons of students enter this in this country and only 4 winners are selected and she was number 1!  So that's really good....After Youngok's screening, we all went out to celebrate...that's Youngok on the left (holding one of her animated characters), Roy (who also helped with sound), Heidi (Youngok's old roomate), and myself...see how much I look like my drawing?  (that's sapposed to be a sarcastic comment) 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>