<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I bought a used X-box yesterday. I was trying to decide if I should spend my money on such an unnecessary thing, when I remembered my instant purchase justification system: "Dude, it's not like I'm buying crack or something.". 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To deal with the problem of birds using my receivables area as a commode. (What the HELL birds?) I just purchased the  urlLink Ultrasonic Bird Repeller Quadblaster Qb-4 ! Only $495 per unit. I did a cost benefit analysis and bringing in a Falconer was deemed too short term a solution. I don't know that Health and Safety would have approved it anyway. Essentially, what I am doing for these birds is hosting a dinner party and cranking up some  urlLink Venom .
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I zinged the Intern pretty good yesterday. At our office a guy from Donato's pizza comes to sell his wares every Friday.&nbsp;The&nbsp;Intern&nbsp;said that this wasn't fair because he didn't work Fridays. I pointed to my eye and said "Can you see? I have a little teardrop."   David Spade called, he wants his zazz back.   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hi,   I think&nbsp;am going to use this site to make public my brilliant observations, and maybe write some snack reviews.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Burger King Angus Burger is excellent. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If you have lots of time to read at work, like me, I recommend the book "Jennifer Government" by Max Barry.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Did you know that Hyde from "That 70's Show" and Francis from "Malcolm and the Middle" are brothers? Weirdly, Hyde isn't related to Malcolm, Reece or Dewey and can time travel. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey Mark, I beat Splinter Cell last night. The end was kinda bogus.   I'm sold, I want a  urlLink Robosapien  this Christmas.   Check out this giant  urlLink Robosapien!    
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This  Miami Redhawk player has the worst/best name ever.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink AandE.com Store - Product Detail   I love me some Tv. Dangerman is a show I rented and now love. Lots of old-school brainy spy action and it's never corny or campy. Everytime I turn on TV and see Poker being played a little piece of me dies. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I have the new Mooney Suzuki song Alive and Amplified stuck in my head. It's a fun song, and anything that breaks up the "Any Way You Want It"/"Facts of Life Theme" medley in my head is welcome. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I don't want to hate Carlos Boozer since he left the Cavs, but I also can't lie to myself and deny that I would enjoy seeing a dog clamp onto his testes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am going to "Fruit Punch" whoever decided to stop stocking Orange Juice in the vending machines. AVI vending, this cancels the goodwill you built with the AVI-Q Barbeque Chicken Sandwich. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>