<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I love their new song  Vindicated  it something that comes from his own soul. Just emotional music that describes that indescribable feeling gets to me. Thats what my lyrics are about. Music we can all relate to right and sing along with. 
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I went to see Spider Man 2 on the Twenty-nineth and let me tell you, what an a amazing web slinging movie. This is proably one of the best action movies that I have ever seen. It has everything you could want: huge suspense that had up jumping in our seats, Laugh out loud comedy and an impossible romance. After I saw this I coouldn't shut up about it. Amazing acting and choreogaphrey in fight scenes. It was very incredible. Wowza!    Very funny," Spider man ,Spiderman does whatever a spider can, Spider man Spiderman, Watch out here comes Spiderman"!       The writings the color of web, yay!    
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Have some fun and dont be afraid to joke around because when these slow times of summer roll around I dont want you wearing a    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Tom Welling is very hot. Maybe its just the Superman thingbut man I would let him rescue me any time. He does look hotter as a bad boy though. Hmmmm. Ethier way very fine, fine&nbsp; hmm that doesnt work with me does it?Mmmmm just sit back and enjoy the scenery. Wow, what a view!   
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        OH Orlando is super fine, I really wish he was mine. Ok stop this before I get a restraining order. But I just go all giggly if i see him in a movie or on tv or beside my bed just ahhhhhhh. Take a deep breathe and relax so I dont get myself wound up in his gorgeousness. But I cant help myself just lalalalala I want to sing and dance around and run to him in  a field of daisies in slow motion while dramatic music plays in the back ground. There I go getting obssesive again. Im very sorry!  DAMN ! He's Fine. 
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Summerland is a great show. I like the dramatics of it that you can relate to and the factor that its supposed to be on the coast of Southern California. Not to mention those hot actors. Jesse Mccartney and the actors who play Jay and Camryn. MMMMMMMMM. But seriously a really good show.Check it out. WB 5 Mon 9:00 pm Tues 9:00PM Season Finale. Bye Summerland!  urlLink http://www.thewb.com/Shows/Show/0,7353,1849,00.html  
    
</post>


</Blog>