<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						                      I know what you people are thinking.  And your right.  God forbid, this man, of all men should have an outlet for speaking his mind and shattering the peace.  Yet, I am here with my knowledge, intermingled with the pathos of opinion to create the most engaging, entertaining and stimulating blog on the internet. I ask only that in this blog's infancy you permit time for the requisite growing pains, the struggles of infancy. In that time, my views and your participation will hopefully not only promote and explore current ideas, but also breathe life into new ones.                 First, what the heck could be so interesting that this clown wants us to pay attention?  Simple, my most esteemed colleagues and friends. The same topics that have always moved us.  Initially. The passion of politics in all its forms invades every fabric of our life. From our own general election or the election of your local politician, to the ever changing sovereignties both in our immediate vicinity and across the globe, issues are constantly arising and metamorphing into policies and decisions that shape the world.  The players with the power also have the not so trivial affect of changing you the observer.  I want to hear those changes and guess what, you have to listen to mine as well.                 Second, the film industry that shapes our culture.  Full length features are a billion dollar industry with a workforce of over a quarter of a million strong.  Hollywood's reach extends to every hemisphere.  I plan on rambling on all facets of this booming industry where budgets balloon, egos dominate and eccentricity reigns.  Anything goes here, I will be sure to touch as much as I can.               Third, the business of business will be a focus.  This country has incorporated corporations into every facet of existence.  Companies large and small will swallow chunks of your waking life and I think that is a worthy area of discussion.  From stodgy CEO's stock options to Grandma Bagliani's Italian grocer, the business that shapes our enormous power is at the same time a source of despair, loneliness and questions our purpose.                 Finally, I hope to talk about the dreaded miscellaneous.  Anything else that comes to mind including but not limited to the law, art, literature, relationships, taxes, women from Venus men from mars and basically anything to be left on the table. A beginning point for this indomitable quest is the most logical of all. A question posed before cracking any good book asks 'Who is the author'? More to come  .            

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Michael Mann is good. The Mann that brought us the disappointing Ali and the groundbreaking Insider has always wanted to tackle heavy subjects. Mann tackles these subjects with such style and panache that you can't help but call him good. So when I entered the theater to see his latest, Collateral, I expected to see quality work.  Collateral is led by a villainous Tom Cruise as a hitman for hire and the sometimes bumbling, sometimes striking, but always engaging Jaimie Foxx as the lucky cabbie chosen to help Cruise make his "stops." Collateral was shot mostly at night in the City of Angels. Mann savors the night life as most of the movies run time follows Cruise and Foxx through the LA darkness. The gun shots, the camcorder feel and the grainy video all speaks to Mann's strengths. While Mann's style is on display, the usually immaculate Cruise is the centerpiece of this picture. As Vincent, this cold calculating killer steals the screen. You look forward to more Cruise, from the dispatching of no name thugs to point blank head shots of targets on his list. I never thought I would say it, but I wanted more Cruise. The times when we shifted to the local and federal officers on the chase was too often. I found myself thinking "come on" so we could get back to Vincent on his hits. Foxx and Cruise are almost teammates and they have chemistry in both the violent moments and in the dialogue during cab rides. Jada Pinkett also has some of her best work in a limited role as a prosecutor riding in Foxx's cab.  She makes an important appearance later in the film that has consequences to both our main characters.  Her presence on the screen is solid and you can't help but genuinely like this Will Smith sidekick  There are some cons in this movie too. Too much of the cops, not enough Tommy. There are some formulaic events and dialogue that add a sort of cheese factor to the movie that wasn't necessary. but all too often found in films of the thriller genre. In the end, the Mann power here is overwhelming and the eventual product is satisfying, but fails to cross over into the realm of true masterpiece. Yet, an average Mann is better than most.  *** of out 4 stars  A compilation of reviews.  

						
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    British law enforcement officials yesterday arrested 13 suspected terrorists responsible for the heightened terror alerts in major U.S. cities this past week. One suspect, Abu Musa al-Hindi, was the mastermind in charge of the survellance of U.S. targets. The apprehension of these suspects is another positive step for those engaged in the fight against terror, but this is not the only answer.      Terrorism, as we know it, is a clash of culture. Basically, our way of life is envied, distasteful or otherwise despised by a great many people throughout the world. I see this war on terror as a temporary solution for a systemic problem. The U.S. wields too much power and the rest of the world just doesn't like it. The U.S is a nation based in Christianity, the rest of the world is not. The U.S. has the initiative to solve the worlds problems, by force if necessary, the rest of the world does not. So, who is to blame? Obviously, we all are. If that's the case, why aren't we thinking creatively as we try to work through these issues?       I heard a disturbing discussion on talk radio this morning. If the U.S. is attacked again, the Muslim citizens in this country may be subject to ridicule like those in another period of great fear in this country. A time during WWII when tens of thousands of Japanese Americans were placed in internment camps. A similar possiblity is very real, and we must take all the steps to avoid that event. The truth is force only serves to contain...or exterminate. The Bush administration should remember that our  urlLink homefront  is the first priority.  So far, we haven't done what is needed to protect it.       I support force being used around the globe, and I commend the Allied Forces for making progress, but I fear that if force is the major tool here then we may see barb wire fences not far from our homes filled with men, women and children who dress differently and have different skin color than the rest of us. Sound familiar?          AP article   

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    The Fed is looking to raise rates next week amid some sobering new job data. The labor department found only 32,000 new jobs were created last month, the fourth straight month of decline. Obviously, the burning question reamins whether or not the economy is heading in a postive direction. To that question, I answer in the surprising positive.....maybe.      President Bush has rarely pointed his focus on economic concerns. His tax cuts meagerly benefited the average American while creating larger benefits for the wealthy. The problem is the tax code has always benefited those with more money, a fact little acknowledged by most Americans because of the complexity of the tax code. Who can blame them! The truth is President Bush has done nothing but sit on his hands on the most vital economic issues in the private sector. My view is to commend President Bush (did I say that) for not tampering with the economy. There are times when a President must instill policy to stabilize our financial way of life. The President has backed away from that urge and let the markets, he has let competition do what it does best. The result is a stagnant economy that may not be helping, but it isn't hurting.      Does this mean I am voting for Bush based on his-in my view- laissez faire view of the economy. That answer is a resounding no, but what I do propose is that this President has not shaken the private sector to the ground because its not his stregth. Of course, the public sector and the governments trillion dollar deficits is a somewhat different story. The man likes to spend, but that is the subject of a different article. I just don't blame him for losing jobs, which is a small step for me.   CNN Article   

						
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The art of the deception is just that, an art.  So when I walked into the theater this weekend to see The Village by M. Night Shyamalan, I expected to see someone at the very peak of his profession. What I discovered was a different monster altogether.   A short synopsis goes as such.  A small farming community located in western Pennsylvania has an isolated way of life.  The town's citizens never venture past their own borders for fear that the creatures living in the woods might attack them.  The creatures, M. Night doing "creature" better than anyone else, are shrouded in the unknown and evoke fear as well as any of Night's previous creations.  The cast including Adrien Brody William Hurt, Joaquin Phoenix, Sigourney Weaver and newcomer Bryce Howard all give focused performances.  Howard, basically the main character in the film's second half, is the reason to go see this film.  She is striking and powerful as Ivy Walker, although someone forgot to tell her she was blind in some of the movie's earlier scenes.  As a movie, The Village is a transition work for Night.  Not his best because it strays from the singlular conventions that made him the moneymachine he is today.  Yet, this is not a negative in my opinion.  The acting here flourishes where the sublties of Phoenix and the strength of Howard carry the depth of emotion that is necessary for an audience to root for the characters instead of merely passing time to see the twists and turns Night delivers at the end.  Brody, playing a mentally disabled villager, may seem underused but rather his simplicities are some of the best examples of deep seeded envy and love in the film.  The one failure here is Weaver who with her limited screentime didn't seem to make an impact opposite Hurt.  There seemed to be a storyline there that Night never bothered to explore.  The other part of the film, the part we know Night from, where he uses his Hitcockian flair is surprisingly just a diversion in this film, a tool at his disposal.  A few brilliant scenes from this mode only appear sparingly throughout the film.  When Night wants to scare and decieve he can do so at will, but here it seems he did so only to draw in the audience to his character piece.  It was as if Night couldn't decide what he wanted his movie to be.  In Night's wake is a puzzle of parts that some audiences will determine is worth the price of admission while others will feel they were cheated.  The true result, however, is a director growing beyond his boundaries and for the first time taking his actors along with him.  He only asks that you join him on the journey.  Rowland's review     ***  out of 4  A compilation of reviews from The Village.   urlLink http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/village/  

						
</post>


</Blog>