<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      what a fucked up morning.woke up eager to watch the man u/ ac milan game only to see man u play brilliantly the whole game but end up losing on penalties.  pissed me off and am still pissed of and i dont feel like doing anything today. i dont even feel like typing any more 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    this is how i seem to see myself in the next 10 years..preety fucked up aint it&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hello my name is aamir....why i started this blog? dont ask me even i dont know the answer...shows that i have a very fullfilling life dosent it 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok to raise money i have come up wiht an idea to get rid of the many cds i dont listen to. if any jackass wants to buy used cds. TALK TO ME!!!   current guitar fund: $5 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well went down to tom lee music in downtown with matt today and saw the perfect guitar. a black fender stratocaster. i must buy it. i have come up with a proposition where i save every single dime i have to raise money to buy the damn thing.    Current Amount In Guitar Fund: $5 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well it wasn't a spectacular day today just got back from watching the england game. they finally produced a convincing display against ukraine. not bad. went down to rogers today to rent the exorcist but found out that it was out. fuck. ive been wanting to watch that damn movie for so long already. oh well. the new exorcist movie just rekindled my desire to watch the damn thing. i managed to get from hell though so i think imma gonna go watch that now. so ciao till then. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    oh no...its lana lang.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i finally got around to restoring my computer and its as good as new again. hell yeah.... but than again i lost all my mp3s. now thats not good. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey!!!!!!!!!  scotty dosen't know that fiona and me do it in my van every sunday  she tells him shes in church but she dosen't go still she's on her knees, and.......  scotty dosen' know, oh scotty dosen't know-oh so don't tell scotty scotty dosen't know scotty dosen't know SO DON'T TELL SCOTTY  fiona says shes out shopping but shes under me and im not stopping  'cuz scotty dosent know scotty dosent know scotty dosent know scotty dosent know so dont tell scotty scotty dosent knoooooooooooooooooooow......... SO DON'T TELL SCOTTY  i can't believe hes so trusting while im behind you thrusting  fiona's got him on the phone and she's trying not to moan it's a three way call and he lnows nothing NOTHING!!!!  scotty dosen't know scotty dosen't know scotty dosen't know don't tell scotty 'cuz scotty dosen't know scotty dosen't knooooooooooow........ SO DON'T TELL SCOTTY!  we'll put on a show, everyone will go scotty dosen't know scotty dosen't know scotty dosent knooooooooooow......  the , parking lot, why not? it's so cool when you're on top his front lawn, in the snow laughing so hard, cuz...  scotty dosen't know scotty dosent know  i did her on his birthday  scotty dosen't know scotty dosen't know scotty dosen't know scotty dosen't know don't tell scotty scotty dosen't knoooooooooow...  scotty will know scotty has to know scotty's gotta know gonna tell scotty gonna tell him myself  scotty has to know scotty has to know scotty has to, scotty has to, scotty has to go!  scotty dosent know (don't tell scotty) scotty dosent know (don't tell scotty) scotty dosen't know scotty's gotta go 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well woke up to day and had to rush to granville for my eye check up.  i found out my eyesight is worse than i expected it to be. it nearly doubled. fuck. came back home because i didn't feel like doing anything much today. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    this my friends is classic maiden. from their '82 video, number of the beast.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      shit its so early. why the fuck did i wake up so early today?  well since the day hasn't even started as yet, im going to comment on the teen choice awards i ended up watching last night. well first of all that show was total crap. from start to finish. im afraid it was a FOX idea to strengthn the stronghold they have on the north american teen audience by attracting a few hot celebraties and promoting an overall crappy effort in portraying an award show for teens. im afraid less then 40% of all teens living in north america will find the show of any relevance. it could go to show the strong grasp the media has on the youth of today. but fuck it its  just a crappy award show.  If some dick head from FOX is reading this i hope you don' t sue me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      check it out i changed the template. still looks gay as hell though. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "people say cherish the school life for you'll only realize how good it is when it is gone but i dont care fuck off you stupid stinky school, with your restrictions and gay uniforms and gay rules and gay culture and gay girls who don't wanna fuck, just fuck off."  -cheenu a.k.a. maddy   haha linus where the hell did you find this. i leeched im not sorry though. 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      don't wanna be an american idiot don't want a nation under the new media and can you hear the sound of hysteria? the subliminal mindfuck america  welcome to a new kind of tension all across the alien nation everything isn't meant to be okay television dreams of tomorrow we're not the ones meant to follow convincing them to walk you  well maybe im the faggot america i'm not part of a redneck agenda now everybody do the propaganda and sing along in the age of paranoia  welcome to a new kind of tension all across the alien nation everything isn't meant to be okay television dreams of tomorow we're not the ones who're meant to follow convincing them to walk you  don't want to be an american idiot one nation controlled by the media information nation of hysteria it's going out to idiot america  welcome to a new kind of tension all across the alien nation everything isn't meant to be okay television dreams of dreams of tomorrow we're not the ones who're meant to follow convincing them to walk you.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    here is another picture to satisfy those needs.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well another fuckin' hot summer day.*shakes his head*could the weather get any hotter?  so i woke up this morning and stumbled across the new green day song. i have to say it was preety good. the damn things stuck in my head to. well i recommend you listen to it, American Idiot- Green Day.  ended up in pacific center mall somehow this afternoon and stuffed myself silly. ahhh the effect of good food on humans. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well what a day. managed to do lots of stuff today. went down to metrotown to pick up some stuff i needed, came back ate and then started cleaning out my desk and shelves. damn i never knew i had so much junk in there. im still not even done and im getting sick of it. oh well back to work i guess. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      another sunday morning and another fuckin hot day.  i feel very much like an intellectual today but for some reason am in no mood to start with my anti-capitalist rants. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    the gibson voodoo, now this is one heck of a crazy guitar.&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      here are a list of albums you must have in your collection-  1)Number of the beast- Iron Maiden 2)Battle of Los Angeles- Rage Against The Machine 3)Appetite For Destruction- Guns 'n Roses 4)Black Album- Metallica 5)Back In Black- AC/DC 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    now this is one fine looking babe...;) if you  dont know who this is, its kritin kreuk..now you know.  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      yes i fukin rule.i just checked my maeks and found out that i owned the provincials. thank you very much. hahahahahahaha............ man my marks just seem to good to be true. i was sweating over nothing. haha more reasons to party. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well today didnt do much besides going out to dinner with my parents. dinner wasnt to bad but was still preety hungry. to day i have decided to include a list of 5 albums which should never appear in you CD collection. should it be in your collection my advice to you is to burn it or flush it down your toilet. (you dont want other people hearing it...not even your worst enemy) they are in no particular order.  1)Linkin Park- meteora 2)Hillary Duff- metamorphisis 3)Simple Plan- No pads, no helmet, just ballzz 4)Nickelback- The long road 5) The Ataris-( cant remember album name)  there are alot more but just cant get myself to type them out. just thinking of them scares me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i just heard a song on the radio and i am in disbelief. the spider-man 2 "song" by dashboard confesssions or something or another is by far the gayest song i have heard. i am sad to say it seems gayer than the"hero" song on the first one. i never thought that would be possible .......  what is the world coming to... 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      well lets see...woke up today and heard maiden(dance of death). man that album just never gets old. its brilliant. felt quite bored and lazy. wanted to do something but just didnt feel like moving. i somehow managed to get my ass of the couch and get a couple of dvds. couldnt bear to watch all that crap they were showing on tv. it seems as though every channel is showing the same boring shit.  note to self: stop leaving guitar picks on the friggin' floor after jamming. can never seem to find it later on. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>