<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      she said, "go get yourself a blog!" ... so I did...  Once I started quoting Carrie Bradshaw, we figured it was time for me to start putting in diary entries... I only have to wonder... shall I make these entries similar to "sex and the city?"  I certainly have enough material to do so....   
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    yup... it's me...  Posted by  urlLink Hello  
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Excerpt from “Women Who Run with the Wolves,” by Clarissa Pinkola Estes…………….  The archetype of Wild Woman resides in the guts, not in the head. She can track and run and summon and repel. She can sense, camouflage, and love deeply. She is intuitive, typical, and normative. She is utterly essential to women's mental and soul health.  She is the female soul. Yet she is more; she is the source of the feminine. She is all that is of instinct, of the worlds both seen and hidden -she is the basis.  She is intuition, she is far-seer, she is deep listener, she is loyal heart. She encourages humans to remain multilingual; fluent in the languages of dreams, passion, and poetry.  She is the voice that says, "This way, this way." She is the one who thunders after injustice. She is the one we leave home to look for. She is the one we come home to. She is the things that keep us going when we think that we're done for.   To adjoin the instinctual nature does not mean to come undone, change everything from left to right, from black to white, to move the east to west, to act crazy or out of control. It does not mean to lose one's primary socializations, or to become less human. It means quite the opposite. The wild nature has a vast integrity to it. It means to establish territory, to find one's pack, to be in one's body with certainty and pride regardless of the body's gifts and limitations, to speak and act in one's behalf, to be aware, alert, to draw on the innate feminine powers of intuition and sensing, to come into one's cycles, to find what one belongs to, to rise with dignity, to retain as much consciousness as we can.  go see:  http://www.elexion.com/lakota/textos/texto31b.htm
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear Cats,  When I say to move, it means go someplace else, not to switch positions with each  other so there are still two of you in the way.  The dishes with the paw prints are yours and contain your food.  The other dishes are mine and contain my food. (Please note, placing a paw  print in the middle of my plate of food does not stake a claim for it  becoming your food dish, nor do I find that aesthetically pleasing to the slightest.)  The stairway was not designed by NASCAR and is not a racetrack.  Beating me to the bottom is not the objective.  Tripping me doesn't help  because I fall faster than you can run.  I cannot buy anything bigger  than a king-sized bed.   I am very sorry about this.  Do not think I will  continue to sleep on the couch to ensure your comfort.  Look at videos  of dogs and cats sleeping.  They can actually curl up into a ball.   It is not necessary to sleep perpendicular to each other, stretched out to  the fullest extent possible.  (I also know that sticking tails straight  out and having tongues hanging out at the other end to maximize space  used is nothing but sarcasm.)  My compact discs are not miniature Frisbees.  For the last time, there is not a secret exit from the bathroom. If by some miracle I beat you there and manage to get the door shut,  it is not necessary to claw, whine, meow, try to turn the knob, or get  your paw under the edge and try to pull the door open.   I must exit  through the same door I entered. (In addition, I have been using the  bathroom for years....feline attendance is not mandatory).  The proper order is kiss me, THEN go smell the other cats' butt.  I cannot stress this enough.  It would be such a simple change for you.  To pacify you, I have posted the following message on our front  door... Rules for Non-Pet Owners who visit and like to complain about our pets:  1.  They live here; you don't.  2.  If you don't want their hair on your clothes, stay off the furniture.  3.  I like my pet better than I like most people.  4.  To you it's an animal.  To me he and/or she is an adopted son  and/or daughter who is short, hairy, walks on all fours, and is speech-challenged.  Dogs and cats are better than kids.  They eat less, don't ask  for  money all the time, are easier to train, usually come when called,  never drive your car, don't hang out with drug-using friends, don't drink  or smoke, don't worry about buying the latest fashions, don't wear  your clothes, don't need a gazillion dollars for college, and if they  get pregnant, you can sell the results.  
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My parents had three children – one of each.   The day we got our wings:   There was a box factory in our home town, and one of their specialties was fabricating airplane wings.  For those small planes they used during the war for reconnaissance. (I say that as if there were only one war.)  My brother Bob, our pal Frank and I planned the trip  to the factory to purchase two wings.  They were about 20 feet in length and covered in canvas.  They charged fifty cents per wing, and we were ready!  Well what can three boys do with a couple of airplane wings?  As you can imagine, it was a sight to see, two outspread airplane wings going down the road, with three sets of legs propelling them.  Quite a mutation.  We took our “bird” down to the pond, which was in a park at the end of the road.  Only it wasn’t a park back then, it was just a place.  Up on one side there was a hill with the railroad tracks atop.  It was a sledding hill in the winter.  Some kids would toboggan down the other side, but there were trees at the bottom, so many of us didn’t see that as a smart thing to do.  We transformed our wings into rafts when we put them in the water and rowed about on them, using sticks for motoring.  When we had exhausted “all the things you can do with an airplane wing in the water,” we hauled them to the shore.  I managed to step on a broken bottle and badly cut my foot.  Blood everywhere!  Three heads together – three boys heads together – had to come up with a strategy to get me home.  Our brilliant idea was to leave one of the wings there and use the other as a stretcher.  A new twist on the mutation - one airplane wing going down the road, with two sets of legs propelling it!     Head first, Scandinavian Style:  Idle hands are the devil’s playground?  Well, boys have no intention of having idle hands.  They build things.  And of course, when they see any amount of standing water, they build diving platforms!  And then they dive into the water.  I proceeded to hit my head on the bottom.  Hard.  (One might wonder why my hands didn’t go in ahead of my head.)   I probably had a concussion, or maybe I died.  Maybe all of the years that followed have been a dream.  After all, before that, my life was calm, well-ordered, exemplary.  Did I conjure up my time in flight school?  In Vietnam?  Do I really have a wife and four daughters … nah!  Who would make up a life with the ya-yas! 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Say not, 'I have found the truth,' but rather, 'I have found a truth.'  Kahlil Gibran   That would be a good thing for them to cut on my tombstone:  Wherever she went, including here, it was against her better judgment.  Dorothy Parker   In our civilization, and under our republican form of government, intelligence is so highly honored that it is rewarded by exemption from the cares of office.  Ambrose Bierce, The Devil's Dictionary   “I have thought about it, and I agree with myself!”   Billy Bob Thornton in “Homegrown”  I can win an argument on any topic, against any opponent. People know this, and steer clear of me at parties. Often, as a sign of their great respect, they don't even invite me.  Dave Barry  All married couples should learn the art of battle as they should learn the art of making love. Good battle is objective and honest - never vicious or cruel. Good battle is healthy and constructive, and brings to a marriage the principle of equal partnership.  Ann Landers (1918 - 2002)  (which can be summed up in Kevin Bacon’s secret to a successful marriage… “Keep the fights clean and the sex dirty!”    Character cannot be developed in ease and quiet. Only through experience of trial and suffering can the soul be strengthened, ambition inspired, and success achieved.  Helen Keller  Life is either a daring adventure or nothing. Security does not exist in nature, nor do the children of men as a whole experience it. Avoiding danger is no safer in the long run than exposure.  Helen Keller  A banker is a fellow who lends you his umbrella when the sun is shining, but wants it back the minute it begins to rain.  Mark Twain  A lie can travel halfway around the world while the truth is putting on its shoes.  Mark Twain   A man cannot be comfortable without his own approval.  Mark Twain    Always acknowledge a fault. This will throw those in authority off their guard and give you an opportunity to commit more. Mark Twain  Courage is resistance to fear - not absence of fear.  Mark Twain   It doesn't make a difference what temperature a room is, it's always room temperature.  Steven Wright   Take rest; a field that has rested gives a bountiful crop.  Ovid  Be sure that it is not you that is mortal, but only your body. For that man whom your outward form reveals is not yourself; the spirit is the true self, not that physical figure which and be pointed out by your finger.  Cicero  Be kind, for everyone you meet is fighting a hard battle.  Plato  No human thing is of serious importance.  Plato  How vain it is to sit down to write when you have not stood up to live.  Henry David Thoreau 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I caught the tail end of the baby boomer generation.  Of late, I’ve noticed the way that patriotism is spinning in the minds of those around me who have been on the same ride.  We were still young when the Vietnam war ended.  Not quite old enough to really feel the philosophical effects of the war, apart from the angry messages flying on both sides.  Any war brings the opportunity for an addled view.  On one hand we had people saying that freedom comes at the price of bloodshed, as it always had.  On the other hand, we had people telling us that the prize was not freedom; we were laying down our lives for the benefit of ideals that belonged to the greedy buggers who were holding all the cards… and not one of those cards had the faces of the American people on them.  Well that was a long time ago.  We’ve had a few years to mull things over.  We’ve heard the stories of conspiracy and abuse of power from then and now.  We’ve heard the songs of the prophets.  We may have even considered the possibility that some of the “all you need is love” people were not really full of conviction, but a lung-expanding smoke that made it apathy rather than love for their fellow man that drove them.  “Yeah man, we all agree… war is hell… now pass me another joint.”  But I have a feeling that heads are clearing.  While still holding a view of the great battles that made for great heroes, we are beginning to realize that the things we fought for then, are not the same things we fight for now.  It’s no longer a mystery and no longer something we can pretend is just a matter of opinion.  We now know that the only thing we’re fighting for is the face of a man.  A man who is not content to live in a world that sees him as a blithering idiot.  He is a man determined to do what it takes to show proof before the eyes of all the nations that he is a powerful… blithering idiot.
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well... I'm here to say... I saw this movie last night... yes, it's a movie... an indie film... always a risk... must be a character created by a humorous youngster (or two)... high school story of the popular versus the... well... let's just say... less-than-gifted... I found the humor to be uncreative and idiotic... attendance was less than fifty, and the majority were under 25... I can only assume that they knew some of the cast, as the entire  audience found the film to be uproariously funny! I must have been the only one who wasn't laughing... not even a chuckle... and if I had been alone, I would have walked out... Now... I can count on one finger the number of films that I wanted to walk out on... Swordfish... that's it... and I've seen a LOT of movies... this one was full of Idaho humor... which I can only sum up as "small minded" and Utah humor isn't far behind... now in all fairness, I enjoyed the actors, individually... and I would have liked the movie, if it were my kids, or my nieces and nephews, or anyone I cared about or knew in it... it was much like watching a video that your young ones put together, so you get a kick out of it... but since they were none that I knew, it just turned out to be a waste of time... or possibly... like watching a slide show of someone else's family!  (remember those days?  pleeeeeeeeeeeeez... not the slide show! :)   
      
</post>


</Blog>