<Blog>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Life's a bitch. The bitch is a bitch. The asshole is a bitch  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sitting on my ass at home cuz im down with a fever/cough/flu. SATs is around the corner and here i am falling ill. Yeah, it IS those chocolate binges.  So yesterday i saw Sunken again. And so did my best friend. She is from a different school from me and Sunken but she saw him at the place where we usually wait for our buses to arrive. Apparently, Sunken was also taking the bus, with his friends, who almost ALWAYS crash at his place after school (doesnt his grandparents get annoyed or something? I remembered when MY grandparents were still alive, and my girls crashed in, we made pretty hell of a noise. Boys should be no less). My best friend said he checked himself out in the glass where he can see his reflection. Yeah, he had changed his hairstyle. Suki said it's better. My best friend said it doesnt suit him. Well, i think it is bullshit. Actually, i dont care. Hairstyles dont make a difference. At least not when it comes to Sunken. My best friend hates him. She says he is a jerk. She says she feels my pain. I told her that she shouldnt feel that way because i've gotten over the hurt-trauma. Everytime news concerning Sunken pops up, it hurts but it hurts too often that i'm definately numb by then. He is THAT good-looking and he knows it. Judging from his hair (which takes a lot of time in front of the mirror to make-do), he's a lil on the vain side. Lots of girls loves Sunken. Like, my best friend told me that when Sunken boarded the bus, some of his female acquaintances went all giggly. I use to think that Sunken is the one for me because he is all nice and kind, well, guess not. Perception change. I dont hate him. I dont think badly of him. I guess he's just one of my outdated infatuation.  I wish Shorty likes me. He is from my school, about a level higher than me i think. He is more to the mild and meek side. He seldom hang around with his friends after school. Your typical good boy, which is why i am made for him and him me. I dream that if i were his girlfriend, i'll be the best. I'll be perfect cuz he is Worth it. TOo bad, Shorty doesnt give in to the infatuation crap. He is better off in his own world.  Im watching the way i eat. Not starvation because it accumulates fats. I'll go light on meals  Till the next time i blog, bye. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       An official reject, a no-life, low-life. What's with her trying to get a high-profile? She shouldnt have talked to him in the first place. Uzzy never talks to girls, even if he knew them. You gotta be pretty and outgoing, i guess, or he'll just ignore the shyte outta u.      Saw Gorgeous this morning and he's gorgeous. I am not even kidding! This is God's wonderful creation. He has this angular face, almond eyes, sharp features, smooth complexion and a hot body. Gorgeous is drop-dead gorgeous. Unlike Sunken, who is sunken man. I think he is anorexic. He seems sad and whacked out of place. He has a girlfriend who is as bony as him. League? Maybe they understood each other, i'll never know. Sunken is relatively tall. He is skinny and his bones jut from under his skin. He seem sickly to me but i analyse that he plays football often. He has cheek bones so sharp it could cut glass. His face has no fat layers at all and he has large, puppy eyes. My liking towards Sunken have long fade, partly because his bony-girl is in his life.      It's time to get bony. I'll starve myself to death. Let starvation be a friend. Starve off problems. Food is a hassle. I dont care. Skinny is the answer. Lately, i've come to a wakening. People judge me on my looks. I aint pretty nor thin. The opposite is who i am. How do i deal with this when school's over? Independance? Failure? Fragility? Everything new and everything sick. I dont care if i land in the hospital. It hurts that fat lives in me. I am able to rid it. I must. FOod is failure.      A close friend of mine is slim but she thinks she is fat and she goes as far as eating one meal per day. It gets me green with envy that she lost like nearly 15 ounds this year. Very much, she is my competition. I guess i do believe that i need 'it' when im done with high school.    im fat im fat im fat im fat im fat im fat im fat!!!!!!!!! guess wat? im farking pregnant babe! shyte!    Tats it. He doesnt like me at all. he doesnt look at me. He doesnt achknowledge my presence. He is ignorant of my infatuation towards him. It's time to stop this massive disturbance that caused me. I'm hybernating.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>