<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well i have a Guild War later~.... 10.00pm 07/31/2004... SO Cool~! But it is a friendly war... nothing much....  It is between   Guardian   VS     Eternal Star..    wooooo hoooo~!! best~!  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm a sad guy..~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO HHHHHHHHOOOOOOOOOOOO  Yea yea.... got my license~!! heheheh~.... hrmm 6 lesson... 2 weekkk.... wahahh~ not bad ar...~ yea yea.. now only have to wait for few day to wait my instructor to give me my license~ woo hoo... hahhahhhahhh........  Aaarriiigggaatoooo ^_^~ 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ...i am quitting mRO.      after thinking things over and weighing the good against the bad, i have finally decided that spending rm38 each month is just a waste of money, and that playing/botting endlessly to gain lv's in mRO is extremely pointless and completely devoid of reward and most importantly...FUN.       seeing that most players, including me, are literally forced to bot to gain exp lv's as well as money because of the absurdly high exp rates i believe it is quite a waste of time, as botting is completely devoid of experiencing the game as players just have to let the bot run to gain lv's. sure, the first 50-60 lv's are easy enough to earn. try leveling at lv70+. even at full bot(24-48 hours) the most you'll be able to gain would be max 2-3 levels. all is right for now. what about level 80+ above? you do the math. my point is, while most players are on desktops computers & ADSL connections which enable them to bot for hours at end, it is completely devoid of experiencing the game as a whole. the experience tables for RO, i assure you, are 2-3 times higher then any other online game out there. sure, you could reach lv99 after maybe 3-4 months, but the whole point of a MMORPG(Massively Multiplayer Online Role Playing Game) is to socialize, make friends and of course, have fun. which brings me to my next point.      in mRO, i am sad to say, the games text translation is so bad that it seems that all the game text was translated, at best, by a Form 3 student. and i happen to know some f3 students with better vocabulary then the whole mRO GM team put together. most of the game players are so terrible at social skills that the whole point of socializing online gets degraded to meaningless conversations which roughly boils down to "I have a better character than you. Better items too. And i have a game GF who I've never seen b4 in real life but who cares, I am l33t ur not. Haha". don't believe me? Try heading to the PvP rooms at any given time of the day &amp; you'll see my point.       if that's not enough, hacks & full botters abound! mRO players please take no offence as i do not refer to anyone in particular. just that the mRO GM team should make an effort to stop these hackers and botters. i realize i am a botter too, but why do i bot? read paragraph 2. in iRO(international RO) GM's and sub-GM's actually walk around in-game to catch botters, cheaters and abusers who totally spoil the overall gaming experience. go ahead and check out the iRO site and see for yourself.       screw this. i'm heading for those private servers where killing 10 fabres gets you to lv50+ no problem. i'm heading there for the rewarding virtual items. i'm heading there to play for free instead of paying rm38 to bot. i'm heading there where, even if unofficial, GM's ban &amp; suspend botters. i'm heading there to meet in-game girls who are well informed, and who do not come off as Ah Lians at first glance. i'm heading there where most of my enlightened friends are already having guild wars at a regular basis(suck on this mRO playas!) and where not everyone is a complete jerk off. i'm heading there to have FUN.       i can't believe it took me a year and 4 months to realise this. oh well. trial and error i guess.       *  while most of this blog consists mainly of my complaints, take note however, that most of this blog is FACT. if you've played it long enough, you'll believe me. oh, and for those guilds who keep "sapu-ing" the PvP rooms, i hope someone teaches them a lesson in ruining the whole PvP experience. those bastards.                ~fin~   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WTF~!!!!  Time past so fast.... Haiyoyoyooyoyo.... Tomorrow TEST~!!! sumore the subject is ADD MATH and BM... Argggg..... gonna fail...... stupid test... try imagine this world without test.... WOOOOOHOOOOO bagus~  Aaarriigggaaatoooo >:( 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wahahhaha...  Just come back from my 2nd driving lesson~..... "It's a beautiful day~!" Im so happy.....~!! Well today i learn Side parking... 3way turn... and Jalan A B C..... wahahahhaha..... everything is easy except Jalan A B C.... very hard to memorize the road.... well... Pending is a damn big area with alot of round about..... i think if the instructor put me in the middle of the road... i think i well get lost.... wahahaha... malu nier..... anyway... it will be easy if i drive more in tat area.....  Now waiting for my 3 rd lesson.. tat is next monday 2pm.... kekekkekek can't wait.... BEST~!  Arigato.... :D 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hermmm~  Today.... everything was just so fine..... the sky are clear.... the bird and singing... friend are laughing..... Until the end of Recess time..... Everything when wrong.... >. Let's say my fren name is 1, 2, 3, 4..... 1 besong 2 3 and 4 2 besong 1 3 and 4 3 besong 1 2 and 4 4 besong 1 2 and 3  This is like perang segiempat~ All i can say is they "sio meh" over stupid stuff~>...... If 1 2 3 and 4 are reading this blog.... hope tat u guys think carefully wad have u guys done.... We all are old friends... so why wanna "sio meh"...... >.  Arigato........ >. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      :X  Tuition Tuition just finish~!! me  and my friend go eat At "FOOD GARDEN"... after eating we dicided to go watana play for a while..... but we play until damn late..... wahahahha.... swtswtswt.. i mean it is School day...... we still play until so late..... >.  Sorry dear....... 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Woo hooo~!!  Tuesday~!! My favourite day!~ WAhhahahahah whole day sleep and plaY~! whoooo hooooO~!! bagus!! Hrmm..... ntg intresting today.... hrmm~! bye go sleep~! brb to update~!  Arigato~ ^_^ 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What phone should i buy~!?????  Hrmmm any suggestion~ give comment~!!!  Arigato~ ^_^"" 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello~!!  This is the site where you can count your stat for ur Ragnarok Charater~!   urlLink http://www.stud.ntnu.no/~magnusrk/calc/   Well enjoy it~!! I hope this will help you~!! Please send me info or website for Ragnarok stuff~ Or just ask any questioN~! Kkekkeke :)  Arigato~ ^_^ 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yippy~!!  Just came home my my driving lesson~ Kekekeke.... gonna get my   P    soon~... drive drive drive drive drive~!! muahahahhahha~! best~    Check out this web site  urlLink http://www.orgish.com  super cool sites~!  Arigato... ^_^ 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ermm... i just got back from Unimas.... Go there play Football.... I discuss a few stuff wif my friend and i got sumthing very very very good..... For all the ragnarok players u may find it intresting... this is the item and the price~! $$$$$$  Skill Spam - 400mil (Zeny) Item Duplicator 650mil (Zeny)  You can also pay it in RM (Ringgit Malaysia) Skill Spam - RM 600 Item Duplicator - RM 800  For those who are intrested..... Leave your Name, Handphone(if no Hp leave House), Ic and your house Address Or u can email me.. (kikile2000@yahoo.com)  We will discuss this in a private place....  Price will go up and not down.... And no Bargain~!! Price will go up every week.... so get it as soon as possible...  Arigato...... ^_^ 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Russell~!!  Thank you for your supporting.... Well help me update everytime k?? Kekekekekeke.... For anyone out there plz give comment and ask question~! me and my teammate tat is Russell maybe able to answer it.~!! so plzz keep support~!! WOOOO hOOOO~!!  Arigato.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just woke up~ i open my blogspot, then i see   SOMEONE      say bad thing about me... Well what should i do..???~!!!  Go find him...? I can't Go talk to him...? I can't Go bash him...? Even Worst... I'm still trying to figure out wad he wan.... Me now... is like keeping a red hot burning coal in my heart..... Everything he say makes me think alot.... What should i do... Why you always think that you are better and perfect~!!?....  I'm not going to do this kind of thing bocoz *I LOVE U* 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       does anyone know a place where i can get my ps2 which is pretty old repaired? it seems to be experiencing lens problems. i need to get it repaired ASAP so that i can play the upcoming big name games. it doesn't read discs and when FMV's play, they tend to skip and so does the music. anyone, pls pls pls heeelllppppp~~      if anyone has any info AT ALL, pls contact me at  urlLink dr3am3r@mailhaven.com . thanx!  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      testing...1...2...3  hey, it works. amazing. my 2nd blog which i'm posting on, which is quite cool since everyone seems to be getting blogging fever nowadays~kudos to blogspot for providing us lonely people with a free domain in which we can post our inner most thought. ~^^~  oh, it seems like you can use this site to keep updated about what's going on in Ragnarok Online's mRO server, Iris2. nich will keep u updated, since he's the uber "i'm-almost-lv99-hunter".    i hate the Star guilds and Guardian's soooooooo much. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We are the champion~!!! WAhhahah yeah~! last nite war turn out to be so fun~! Guardian rock~!!! woo hoo`~!! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>