<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahhh so here is number 1 maybe i will lose interest in the after awhile, but who cares, got nothing to do besides my art and english speech. ARG  Life at school is same old same old, besides the fact that i have strengthened my relationships with my freinds, which is good. i currently have 2 offers from people to go to their country, thailand or malaysia.  i want to go to taiwan though, too see my old mate there tim lin, and my friend 'tiffany ko; who i met on the internet like what... 2 years ago? damn that is ages, i can sorta picture the pop-up box (toast as the leet guys call it) on msn came up on tims laptop during prep which read "tiffany & co" i think thats what the sign in name is. funny how your brain remebers funny things like that.  it is currently term 3 at school (there are 4 terms in a  year and term 4 finishes late november/early december) this is the what you could call the eye before the storm (the storm being exams of course)  in term 4. i think those will be the most important exams of my life, even thought they dont count as much as 6 + 7th form. this is beacause it will show if i will be able to go to university ect.  i dont think that i am that dumb, but i have no modavation for school, i dont really give a shit right now, dont know why, i know if i fail exams i will be screwed for life lol.  recently been downloading more songs that usual, here are some songs that i am really feeling at the moment 2pac - i aint mad atcha kayne west - jesus walks the eagles - hotel california (like this song so much, even decided to download live version) 2pac - thugz masion alica keys - if i aint got you alica keys - when you really love somone  i have always liked rap and hip-hop, not too sure why,  it has recently exploded in nz recently and we have seen birth to the misfits (fools love) and scribe (currently blowing up is aus)  'oh lisa you came and you gave to me you came and you said to me' simon lim - good mate wether he was talking about my lisa or his i have no idea. lisa li is the one i know lol. she added me on msn awhile ago,(i used to have a crush on her way back) and then we became freinds (not like good freinds or anything). at first she seemed pretty boring. but, our relationship has just increased in last few weeks substancially. and i have realised what a diverese and interesting person she is. a real hard worker and it shows in her marks (these marks are really REALLY good). but, this seems like she has ALOT of pressure from her parents to do well(she calls it having asian parents), i can say that my parents want me to get good marks as well, but they dont seem to be getting any right now lol.  well i would love to write more, but i am going to watch some of the game (springboks vs. wallabies) it is part of of the 'tri-nations', an international tornament which has  nz, aust, and south africa in it.  my first post. Chris White 
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      testing again to see if simon is correct  
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      testing from firstclass  
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      testing testing  ... 
    
</post>


</Blog>