<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          Homeworks for the weekend (probably the most in my life) are as follows:     -Chemistry Workbook on Macromolecules X1    -Chemistry TYS November 2002                X1    -A Maths Vector Worksheet 2                       X1    -A Maths Vector Worksheet 3                       X1    -A Maths SCGS Paper 2                                  X1    -O Level November 2002 Paper 2                X1    -Chapter 21 Bio Notes                                     X1    - English Comprehension Exercise                X1    -Chinese Summary Exercise                          X1     Doh!     So I've completed about 5 out of 9 now. Gonna rush through the rest tomorrow. 
      
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          So now I have a blog. My blog. In fact, I was so influenced by the peoples that I've got my blog. Adaptability. Ok..cut the craps.         My basic background. I was born in Serangoon. That's my hometown for 15 years and counting. Basically, I've many things to kao bei in life, but that's just life. So the blog's for all my kao beis. I fell in love with sulphur - 32 in Sec 2 after smelling the pungent solid and Biology's got the better out of me in the same year too.      Speaking of kao beis, since this is my first post, I shall talk  more .  Ok today's Founder's Day. School ends at 11. Everybody's happy. Hendrik kept pestering me to go Orchard and watch I, Robot with him. But yet, for the umpteenth time, I had to reject the poor fellow to do my never - ending Maths homework. So he went alone, I think and I went home.      Before going home, I had to board the bus. (Obviously! Do you think I can fly?)   The 100  and  135 buses came at the same  time  and I popped into the latter with Yu Siang and Zhen Liang. (Hau poped into 100)  In the midst of the scramble to get on the vehicle, I scanned my e-z at the speed of lightning and was ready to pop my ass into one of the comfy seats at the back (if any), when I was stopped by that bus - inspector.      What did he do? He called me to  scan  again. Loudly. Obviously, that startled the whole bus as if I was the hitch - hiker on that trip.      Ok. I thought he was trying to piss me off. Do I look like that gangster face? Nah. And obviously he had seen me scan the e-z. If not, what's your job anyway,  inspector ?   In addition, I've got fourty plus in my e-z and that's equivalent to 20 plus scans. On the verge of retaliating, I gained my self - control.      And I scanned that e-z with the blue machine again. "Entry OK" it flashed.  Ok. That old hag said "Ok", headed back and found Yu Siang and Kek staring at me as if I'd just landed from a spaceship. Oh my god. I've lost all my face on the bus. Thanks to that old hag.      Too bad I didn't kope his name, or I would've posted to the ST Forum.  GOOD JOB,  SBS Transit. You've hired an old hag as a newbie whose got the  pa jiao  eyes ( blind) to watch over your keepings . Oh man, the company really needs room for improvement. A lot of room.      Yawn. And speaking of the old hag, an excerpt from the SS textbook claims : Senior citizens will be a pool of people with valuable skills, knowledge, work experience and talents. Maybe I should think otherwise. SCs are burdens to society. An excellent example would be Mr. Newbie Inspector From SBS whose pa jiao eyes gave me an adventure on the bus.      Anyway, gonna add more people to the list. Stay tuned. 
      
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      All right folks. The weather report's here again, extracted from the ST World section.  JAPAN: TYPHOON TRIGGERS MUDSLIDES, KILLS 9.  At least  9 people  were killed by a typhoon that swept through western Japan this week. Typhoon Megi packed  winds of 126km/h  early yesterday afternoon.  S.KOREA : AIRPORTS DOWN, HOMES DESTROYED.  Typhoon Megi swept across the South-western tip of S.Korea, emergency officials said yesterday. More than  1200 homes were flooded or destroyed  and about 2400 were left homeless.  7 airports shut down  and 41 domestic flights were cancelled.  FRANCE: 9 DIE AS STORM CLOSE PARIS PARKS.  About a quarter of metropolitian French administration district were affected by the bad weather and some  1000 people were evacuated  from a campsite.  SCOTLAND: URGENT AIRLIFT AFTER LANDSLIDES.  More than 80 people have been lifted to safety after landslides caused by  violent rain  trapped cars on a road in Scotland.  Just days before,  flash floods devastated  a tourist village in South-western England.   *****
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Guess what? I got 40 /50 for that Bio level test. And I beat the whole of A class. So, I can simply tell everyone in that class to sod off and  balek kampong  (go back home). This is really sweet revenge for me here...all thanks to Ms Fong.  Today started off with her kaobei-ing us about the level test marks. She said we cannot compare with the RGS, RI, TCHS people...that's why she talked so much for the past year.  Nevermind, Ms Fong...there's me, your adrent supporter. I am going to beat every single one of them. That's a promise, coz nothing is impossible. 
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Since the Chemistry piss-off debut, its back in action.  Okay. Today Jonathan popped over to Guan Kwee's seat and that's a good thing for me, because, I've got extra space. To avoid the water crisis, I purposely sat two seats away from the sink (its located at the center). Everything got fine and went along as usual, with me beaming at my new profound space.  Then, somewhere in the first period, Guan Kwee popped over to our sink to wash something. At the same time, David was also at the sink. They chit-chatted but I didn't care what they were talking about.  Suddenly, a jet of water shot out from the little hose, across the first seat, over the two solution cups, past the burette, and finally to poor me. And it hit my face.  Anybody looking at me would have recommended Woodbridge for me, as I gave that "really-pissed-off-face". Heck? You guys can wash your stuffs until water can shoot out from the sink? Facinating.  Really…I recommend confiscating all the sinks. I will live happily ever after.  Then there’s the Physics one, where Nico aka K got shot by Mr Chia for whistling in his class. What the? Whistle also cannot? And somewhat, almost everybody had finished the practical at that moment.  The funny thing was that Nico kept giving the cheeky face even though he knew he was being scolded. Nevermind…he  always  does.  
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      She's still stuck up in her 1950s colonial rule. She really sucks.  Here's what happened. The new sofa made its way into the house today. You think everybody's happy? No. By the way, there were 3 sofas (2 armchairs). However, they didn't arrive together as that sofa company had something called sub-contractors.  Oh hell. That colonial stuck-up didn't know what's a sub-contractor and started complaining and blaming everyone (except herself, for not knowing what's a sub-contractor). Furthermore, she said that the new sofa smelt awful. What the hell? Can't you recognise the smell of new leather?  Oh my GOD.  I told her to shut up, for fear that the whole house may collapse. And you know what she said?  She told me not to sit on that $300 newbie. What the  hell ? I mean, you didn't even contribute a single cent to that thing (the dad used his money) and you claim it yours? By the way, who the hell wants to sit on  your  sofa? To worsen the situation, she classified me as "mad" and "mental". (for telling her to stop kao-being?)  Next time...next time, if I have the chance to work at Gleneagles Hospital, I'll buy a gold plated one that's worth 5 times more. And I'll forbade you to sit on my sofa. How's that?  Next time...next time, if I have the chance to work at Gleneagles Hospital, I'll bring you for a mental checkup F.O.C. (free of charge)  And that again, you SUCK.   
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Lucky PM Goh didn't have his handover on this date. Nineteen hours after the swearing-in of the new PM, I would like to say its just a new chapter for the Republic and another major milestone for the newbie Lee.  Appearing in today's ST under the Asia section are two articles, which have caught me off-guard. Enjoy.  IN JAPAN : RECORD HEATWAVE SCORCHES TOKYO.  The mercury reading in Tokyo' s financial district hit 30 deg C for the 38th day in a row, breaking a record set in 1995, an agency spokesman said.  On July 20th, the temperature in central Tokyo hit  39.5 deg C , the  highest since 1923.     IN CHINA: 22 KILLED AS TYPHOON HITS ZHEJIANG.  "This is reckoned to be the  strongest typhoon since 1997  ," said Mr Pan Jinsong, vice-director of the Zhejiang Meteorological Observatory.   ******
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whoosh. The oral's OVER. And today's theme was leadership and teamwork. Guess what? I've got an Indian teacher as the examiner. Just my luck.  Okay. So D Goh really listened to Ragu and brought all his shower stuff for today's aural : Towel, shampoo...everything. I must admit that I'm really impressed by his attitude towards the aural examination. Keep it up man!  And then there's the aural. The passage was okay, and I made only one mistake. Then, at the very last sentence, we have the following:    "...maths was just getting difficult." 
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I, candidate number 2341 0064, has identified myself with the Ministry of Education and the University of Cambridge Local Examinations Syndicate (UCLES), that I shall be sitting for the General Certificate of Education for English Language 1127 Aural Examination on 12/8/2004 at 2.14p.m., on par with my team of commandoes, team F077.  I, candidate number 2341 0064, shall have a good time with the aural examiners and hope that everyone else has a good and fun time with the aural examiners.   
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The Day After Tomorrow tornado pics will stand in my blog.  Enjoy! 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is my second post for the day, before I  chiong  for Prelim 2. In fact, I have already started  chionging  for P2. Before the prelims start, here's what I'm gonna do, or what I have decided to do.  There's no need for the time-table at all, I have decided, since I've not made use of any time-tables for the past few years. They really suck. The moment you plan sometime for something, an unexpected event knocks on your door and viola! Your whole schedule is disrupted.  Doh! So I'm gonna stick to my own way of studying : Equal time for each subject.  Secondly, I'm gonna post weekly during the prelim period .i.e. on Saturdays and/or Sundays. So its useless coming back checking for new entries everyday.  I've also decided to score 9-10 points for P2. No, I ain't aiming for a six-pointer to go RJ. Just get into a decent JC is enough. By the way, though its a little bit early, here's what I'm gonna do after the O's:  -Either get into NJ or TJ or follow the majority of where my class's peoples are going. I've decided  not  to follow the  sluts and gays  of my ex-class (and undoubtly, the PRCs), so if they get into NJ, I'll enter TJ. In fact, I think most of them are going to patronise RJ. So, I guess, for the next year and forever, I will not have them spoiling my life again.  Here's who I will follow: Chung Teck, Nico, Jeremy, ET, Hen and some new friends I've made over the past few months. And plz peoples...I'm not meaning that I'm setting you a standard or what...so don't mistaken me.  So, I can forget about the majority of the sluts and gays of my ex-class, some of whom I decline to name. But somehow, there's some people whom I hope, can get into the same JC as me.  Next year, in the first three months, get two decent CCAs. I simply do not want to repeat the mistake made four years ago. Imagine please: A person whose trying to score 9-10 points for P2 in the CPC (Pugi Club), a club for those hooligans and soccer fantics. Oh my god.  If that's not worse enough, I can't bring myself up to tell others about my CCA even until now.  Here's some tips to choose a CCA:  1) Don't go for the newbies (that's what I did), they have no achievements, nothing. 2) Go for the ones with giant memberships. Which means, a lot of people in that CCA.  My favourites are the Biology Club and CO. So next year, I'm gonna tell myself not to ruin my uni administration due to a lousy CCA.  Here's all. Back to my revision. By the way, does anybody know how to put a pic on the blog?   
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sound. That's what I am gonna talk today. No, no, no, it's not your normal Physics lesson. I know it's a bit lame...but read on for what I'll have to say.  Track 1: At Cineleisure  Two days before, I was at Cine(Refer to my previous post). There is really something I cannot understand at all. Whenever Will Smith woke up in his underwear, there's the  oohs  and  arhhs  by the girls. To be precise, the whole theatre was about eighty percent girls and twenty percent boys that day. Whenever Will takes a shower in his undies, the  oohs  and  arhhs  are inevitable. When that guy whose involved in the riots against the robots appear, there they go again.  Can somebody enlighten me on what's going on?  Track 2:On the adjacent block  Yesterday, some lion dance troupe came at the wrong season at about ten to eleven in the morning. Of course there will be the  xing li  (greetings) for all the shophouses. The problem was that, many were not open yet. In fact, the  noise  they made really got me pissed off.  I was about to shout across and tell them to shut up when I thought : Hey...can they hear me over the  noise  they're making themselves?  On second thoughts, I retreated back to my own bedroom.  Track 3:My blog  Yeah. I'm thinking of inserting some sound here. The Day After Tomorrow's soundtrack is choice No.1. Stay tuned. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      At Cineleisure, laws are meant to be broken. That's right. I went watching ''I, Robot'' with some folks today. And there were four folks altogether. Wow...its damn rare to have four people watching a movie with you.  So school ended at around nine today, without any National Celebrations. Instead, a class quiz was held and that got me fired up. One of the subtopics in the quiz was "Short and Sweet" and the participant was to guess what the various three-letter abbreviations meant (their  adverse  meanings, I mean).  Examples go like this:   -HDB - Housing Development Board a.k.a. Highly Dangerous Building -UOB - United Overseas Bank a.k.a. U Owe Bank -ERP - Electronic Road Pricing system a.k.a. Everyday Rob People -OUB - Overseas Union Bank a.k.a. Owe Until Bankrupt   This got the class laughing their heads off.  Then, me, Chung Teck, Hendrik, Da En and Qi Tang went over to Cineleisure, Orchard to catch the robot movie. That Qi Tang, who could not miss his soccer or whatsoever game, promised us he'd arrive before skimping off with his gang.  Oh boy. When we arrived at Orchard, there wasn't much people around (it was still morning). Some guy from our pack suggested buying the tix early to avoid the possibility of getting last minute seats (was it me? I really don't know) . Thus, we headed over to Cineleisure to book our entry into the theatre.  When we got into that building, I was mesmerised by its infrastructure. Never before had I gone in a place, whose primary purpose was to accomodate movie seekers. Normally, I would pop down to GV Plaza to satisfy my movie needs. But this building  is  really magnificant.  One thing I must mention : That guy behind the counter was really nice. He allocated us a five-seat position right smack in the center, where you can get the best view. Hendrik fished out a fifty dollar note and got all our tix at one go.  With about one and a half hours at our disposal, we went to Taka to get a bite.  It was about twelve when we got back to Cine. By this time, flocks of people, mostly students, were pouring into the building every second. Upon reaching the fifth floor ( where you get your tix) we were stunned by the hundreds of students present. This made Cine an instant "United Nations" from different schools.  By now, Qi Tang hadn't came yet. So Da En setted a time limit for him : 12.30 PM. If his presence is not felt before 12.30 PM, off we go into the theatre without the tall guy. But somehow, he was really punctual and turned up seven minutes before 12.30.  Time really flew and the next thing I know, we were inside watching the robot movie.  It was totally hilarious and action packed(Trust me). Along the way, I learned new phrases to deny Hau. For example, Will Smith got this out:  Arhh choo  (sneezed) I'm allergic to bullshit.  Haha. Really funny. But the plot was a little confusing. That's all. At about two, we dismissed ourselves and got back to home sweet home. Well, that's probably the last movie I'm gonna catch before the prelims and I still have the two E maths papers. Damn. 
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         Oh yesterday I did not blog. I was too sad to do so. 'Cause I lost to the K class. 4 Kevin to be precise, in the science quiz. Today's even worse.  "Wei Xiang, have you finished your observations?" she asked.  "Yesh," I said. Then, she took my petri dish containing the poor leaf soaked in iodine solution away.  Then, she picked up Royston's dish which had, really, a pathetic amount of iodine solution added, as compared to mine. She said to the whole class, "Now everybody listen up. What Royston did was correct...and you should not soak your leaf until like that," holding my dish up.  Oh my god. For the first time ever, Ms Fong made me the bad specimen and Royston was the white sheep in today's Bio practical. Wow. Da En and Pek had done the same as me. But yet, Ms Fong  had  to make me the specimen.  And the funniest and strangest thing is that, I  don't  feel bad at all, for the fact that she made me the so called "black sheep", cause that's all part of learning. In fact, I was laughing myself up at my seat when she publicised my  wonderful  specimen.  Second thing. My mother bought me a new pair of nike shoes. I said I don't want them ( and I didn 't ask for them) and wow, she was like...on the verge of going mad. Thus, she kaobei me for the rest of the whole day. Even as I am sitting here posting, she's still kaobei-ing me at the back, while watching the TV at the   same   time. Geez.        Third thing. I've learnt not to post personal stuff and info on my blog through some websites. People can take advantage of your possessions, say money and properties ( if you tell them you won 4D). So, I've deleted some previous articles.  Lastly, I'm going to watch a movie (I, Robot maybe?) with Hendrik and Chung Teck tomorrow before the Big Bang starts (study lar!), and I'm gonna have the  erhu  as my companion for providing soothing music to the ears.  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I ain't going to be a Bio or Chem teacher for the rest of my life. Even if so, this would be my last resort.  Well, the reason's very simple. Look at Ms Jazilar. She's pissed off by Jonathan, Darrell and Hau( that misbegotten son of a motherless whoremonger) ...so pissed off that she's gonna go mad anytime soon.  Then today there's the surprise fingernail check by Mr Lim BH (our form teacher aka maths pro). Lucky I passed it man, all thanks to the  erhu  ( I can't play it with long nails). And look at Mr Lim also. Long hours spent in the making of his notes. I can't say mine are more superior than his. Look, he's writing them in both pen and marker and printing a different set for us. Geez... he's really zai.  Right after recess we have Mr Chia scolding Hau ( " You LIAR!" ) and some teacher screaming his lungs out at some student downstairs on the adjacent block. Rumour has it that its the Canteen Boy again. This stimulated the two Kohs aka potassium hydroxide (KOH), namely the DM ( Mr Denis Koh) and Ms Koh Siang Cheng, to be part of the dispute.  Haiz. These people are going to suffer from high blood pressure some day, especially the rumoured Canteen Boy.  Absent-minded Royston revealed my identity to LJS ( the Chinese affiliation) that I'm the Bio level highest for Prelim 1.  I wish he hadn't done that.  I know the characteristics of the PRCs after one year in 3A, and ever since then, I've became very cautious while speaking to them. Well, I guess it's a matter of time before LJS pesters me for my notes.   
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Some points to take note of in Science practicals. Here goes:  Point 1) Look peoples... How many times have I told you not to sprinkle those little water drops onto my face, uniform and most outrageously, my question paper? This is getting more and more irritating and I simply cannot stand this nonsense anymore.   So what' s the big deal, you may ask? The water's going to evaporate anyway, no harm.   Ok. Let me tell you what's so harmful.   Chemistry practical. Anybody who tries to wash his/her boiling tube, burette, pipette, flask or any of his/her shit is likely to wet his/her hands. In the attempt to dry his/her hands, will neither prefer drying them onto his/her clean and neat uniform nor use the torn and dirty cloth soaked with sodium hydroxide to dry off his/her hands.   Instead, what does this chap do? This chap will simply flick off the water droplets containing some of the soluble shit, such as managate (VII) ions or sodium ions ( ionic compounds dissociate in water, for those who don't know) onto another poor innocent chap whose quietly doing his work ( that's me!!)    Am I right? I am sure every fellow does that, or you can try proving me wrong. I'm not trying to discriminate anyone, but just revealing the feelings of the poor innocent chap.  Ok. so this innocent chap is gonna suffer as a result of the shower of hard water onto his possessions. And most importantly, the soaked question paper. Excuse me, pilot ink dyes are soluble in water and the end result is a striking chromatogram on the question paper. ( when you are not even told to do one)    The worst thing that had happened to me was getting the droplets containing soaked onion juice into my eye after they were flicked off by my partner in Bio practical. Or when some crazy fellow, in the attempt to copy your answer, goes way overboard and snatches the entire paper with the filthy wet hands, thus creating a full - mark chromatogram.  Oh well... Water really sucks.  Point 2) Asking questions when I'm doing my expts. Please peoples, I know you finished your practicals fast and want to check the answers. But can't you just wait patiently for me?   One example I must mention is Darrell Ong. Asking a quesion while I am titrating caused me to press the burette clip so hard that a whole mass of liquid spurted out, causing me to miss the end - point.  ...  Really. Can I do my practicals with no water? (haha...)   Ok. The prelim 2 timetable's given out today. Biology and Maths together. Geez.  
      
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dot dot dot... I hate this chapter. Chapter 21. And only this chapter in the whole book. For those who do not know what I am talking, refer to Mr Lam Peng Kwan's Biology text. Most of the terminologies used are really sickening to me.  That's why I've censored most of the terminologies and substituted abbreviations or shortforms instead. That is also the reason why I am taking such a long time to write the notes, particularly for this chapter. Besides, this is the first time ever I'm not including any pictures in my notes.     Another reason for why I am taking such a long time is simply because Ms Fong talk too  much . Really. For a simple subtopic such as describing an insect pollinated flower, I have 3 chunks of paragraphs staring at me. Nevertheless, I've adapted to such situations.  By right, the situation is gonna be more worse in Genetics. She says she's gonna spend 4 weeks on it and you can imagine how much she's gonna talk ... and how thick my notes are going to be.  Excuse me, I'm not saying that she's talkative or what, but that's just her nature. In fact, I think she's the best teacher in the school. Why? Simply because you cannot find any Bio teacher like her in Singapore, who teaches the heart cycle graph, compensation point etc. at Oridinary Level.  Ok. I still got four out of nine homeworks to complete today. Maybe the Bio notes are going to steal the whole day out. Jeez. Sometimes I wished I  could  have dropped Bio in the first place. Before I forget, its Desmond Goh's birthday today ( King of August) and 8 days down to National Day. 
      
</post>


</Blog>