<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       This will be my another online diary. I don think i will let people know about this because i want to write some of my feelings in this diary. Well tt's it for today. Update later! ^_-  
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i really am confused now. i thought today would be a gd day but it wasnt. when i saw that na n jesslyn r going to b roommate for the perth trip, my heart totally sank. i really feel like crying n shouting out loud. what does that mean? i donno... issit bcoz she thinks i'm not going or what? i thought we'll b roommate not she n jesslyn? this really make me having 2nd thought about going to perth especially when lyn will b sharing the room with shumin. it's really not my charachter to go over n say 'hey can i share with u all?'... but i'm going to miss the chance juz bcoz of this??? also she acted like it's normal n ok for her n ask me if i'm going or not n said she's sharing the room with jesslyn.... i donno... what can i do?? complain n grumble?? angry with them??? they planned to have the 3 of us together but it doesnt seem so coz they didnt say anything abt the sharing of room thing. guessed i'm too 'zi zuo duo qing le'... donno y i suddenly don wan to go to the chalet too... though i did say abt frenz don really have to stick together but this kind of things i thought is obvious! mayb not going le ba...  tml chi results will b out... will i really get an A1? or things might not turn out it shld be?? in abt 15hrs later we will know the ans...  heart really is broken....  NewS's latest single akaku moyuru taiyo is released today. hope will topped the chart again! ganbatte!!  A.J.. r we fated to know each other??  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm back! Nothing much about today. I just want to write about the incident happened in school juz now. I'm sleeping quite soundly in class after school n suddenly na came n wake me up. she asked me to help her to carry the phy bks down. Though deep in my heart i was abit relunctant as why was she calling me as i was sleeping at that time. She could ask other ppl to help her instead. But i still woke up anyway n asked her to wait 1st coz i wanted to go to the toilet 1st. When i came back i saw her walk out of the class carrying all the bks by herself. I thought she was angry even though after that she said she didnt. i guessed somehow when i woke up that time my face don looked very gd then she was not very happy abt it though she said she was tired. Afterall it's history so let it be then. well, i have some thoughts when this happened. i want to be a fren that will really help ppl when they need me, whole-heartedly. not help them but grumble here n there. i tried to change, persuade myself but it doesnt seem to be very successful. but then i'll still try my best. treat this as a little lesson to learn. so what if na said she can manage herself?? being her fren n knowing that she was sick at that time, i should help her to carry when she walked out no matter she angry or not. haiz... 'main zi wen ti'... it's gd to say things more openly when no one will look at this entry. that's the end of today's entry. mata ne!!! Love A.J
      
</post>


</Blog>