<Blog>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         2dae i go cut mua hair....actualli not cut....is trim. Not obvious aniwae........juz trim the fringe and hair shorter a little bit niah........    
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          haiz....these 4 daes damn sian lehz. Besides wacthin tv, playin com, nth to do liao. Sat tat dae went out wif mom andbought more assessments leh! Haiz, no choice mah. Common tests nex wk....mus settle down and cannot plae liao! Then bought tiz chinese book called "the rose", the chinese called "qiang wei zhi lian", the S.H.E show lor. Beri nice leh the bk. Aniwae, i dun tink i will hav time to cum update mua blog nex few daes liao coz i will be beri busy liao and hav to prepare for the common tests liao.........=)   
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        2dae celebrate national dae.....woah....beri tired. For the class notice board, unexpectedly my class got 3rd siah! Cant believe it....coz i feel tat our notice board like beri plain......but still heng heng we get 3rd. We shared the snacks inside...got lollipop,sweets, chips and more. Shiok siah. Eat alot oso. Got tiz bottle souvenier...i took blue leh..but regret leh...shld hav taken black instead. Haiz. Da song competition damn sian lor....only the upper sec one veri gd...especially 3e1. Way to go! But da whole dae realli enjoy lor..plae in class then go out see ppl sing...somemore can run around and plae. Haha. Then in class plae songs veri loud oso...woah cant tahan siah! Tat Abel sick somemore hav to perform....poor thing siah. But sick hor...he still hav energy plae leh! Go throw the spices at me somemore pretend nothing happen. Think i stupid! Haha. I went to throw back at him.. But the whole dae he lyk veri quiet and pale. Ppl all go take the snakcs to eat, onli he sit there...poor ting.2mrw still got CO, sian~.....           [ PSSST! Got new target liao......upper sec de! hehe! =p ]    
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          now in sch computer lab.......got tiz entrepreneurial ship tingy and the lesson is lyk *yawn*.....so open com and plae. But then hor that mrs leo i tink come in and scold us siah...make us close all com.......but i open again.......heck lah. 2dae beri suay lor....ask huiping then u noe liao. So suay. 2mrw national dae celebration........haiz........goodie...dismiss earlier. But got home econ....go cook that spaghetti..haiz...   
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         2dae oso dunnoe for wat reason hor, i juz broke down and cried at home lor.  I juz finished my napfa, which was veri late, then reach home my bro stil usin bathrm, i hav a heachache and cant bathe....somemore coz of somethin......(secret)....haiz......juz cry lor. But after cryin feel alot, and i thought alot of things.....learning to let go..............              my napfa sux lor.......but still ok lah.....i manage it well at least beta than primary sch tat time.                     ++[learning to let go..................feeling great and beat.....]++    
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I juz enhanced mua site with guestbk, feedbacks and more. Music nex time then i add in. Coz gotta log off le. Pls sign in my guestbk and give me some feedbacks can? Thnks!  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         haiz........juz changed mua blog template....so sian lor...fixin the web...hen tiring leh. Worse still hor, 2mrw i got NAPFA test leh! I hate it more than i hate exams ah! Wat standing broad jump all tat crap de....and i hate tat shuttle run lor. It sux man. Smmore until so late. Hate PE. Went bugis juz now. Veri shiok siah......bought alot of things. Bought a new disc oso. hAiZ. But 2mrw go bac sch jiu sian ald. Aniwae, my teacher sae on fri we celebrate national dae then can walk ard the sch to see the events goin on. Lyk "carnival" lyk tat. But sian lor ms tan on duty then will sure catch attire. She sux one lah....owaes lyk to suan ppl. She used to be a rebellious kid herself aniwae. ( dun ask me how i noe k? shhhhh) She dunnoe catch me how mani times ald. "Your socks are too low" "ur skirt is too short" "your shirt shld be tucked in" aiya........i heck lah. Owaes make me write 300 lines oso. Lyk as if i care. Aniwae denisa they all go decorate the board 2dae. Dun noe how it is goin. Hope to see it 2mrw.              [ 4gEtTiN HiM DaE 1- nEw tArGeT DaE 1]       [hApPy]    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         SuNdAe owaes beri de sian one lor....luckily mon no sch...so i can do mua homework 2mrw. Hate to do homework on sundaes....and sundaes sux cause the nex dae u hav to report to hell(sch) and see thse xia lan teachers. Haiz. Mua bro todae go cut his hair and dye his hair...mus cost him a bomb. And mua mum made him pay himself. Hehehe. But i realli wonder wat to do 2mrw lor. Mayb my frens goin back to sch to help out wif the board. oh yeah. Mayb goin back to primary sch as well. But i tink i heck lah. My primary sch teacheres sux aniwae. Haha.    
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Haiz...another normal dae....earli in the morin got sch practise pipa...senior sae muz go early to practise then abt 3 or 4 (i cant remember) the senior will test us lor...veri sian siah...i realli cant tahan le. Then as usual go for CO, break time i went up to my classroom to see how my frens were goin decorating mua class notice board for national dae. As usual, less work was done as they were all playin! Haha! So envy them siah...no cca on sat one...then we lyk plae and fool around lor....haha. Mua class veri fun de......hope nex yr still same class as them...coz i noe i will realli miss some of them if we are separated. Then after CO, i went bac to classrm again till ard 4 them leave the class. Bt i was not hapi....coz i couldnt do wat i wanted to do...(secret...shhhh) Kenneth, abel, chengkang and teck chuan finish cca then come up oso lor. That stupid abel and kenneth somemore go plae wif mua pipa...somemore hold it lyk as if it is a guitar! HAHA. But tats wat they are......foolish but cute....hope that da noticeboard will be done in time. Oh-oh....haven do mua gy project.......studies SUX!          ~wHy dId u bEliEvE HeR AnD NoT me? Do yOu sTiLl lOvE ME? iTs aLl mY FaUlT....iT HuRtS Me tO See.....ShLd i wAiT FoR U? i mIgHt PrEtEnD To b sTrOnG....BuT I DuN NoE HoW LoNg i cAn gO On........I ReAlLi cAnT TaKe iT...~   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>