<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      At Last!!! My blog is created!!!! 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry that this was delayed, but here it is.  Last week i was holidaying in Wales, land of sheep and rain. Twas a pleasent week, i have many photos to show but, alas, my lack of a digital camera has left me with no choice but to use my scanner, which decided to be an arse and refuse to do so. I will give you the opportunity to view my photos as soon as i catch my scanner and give it a damn good thrashing.  Anyways, here is the lowdown of my week, minus photos ¬_¬.  Sunday: I spent the better part of this day travelling from home to Wales, mostly on the M4, with my mother at thge wheel, naturally. So naturally, no photos of this part of the day. I doubt photos of roadkill or roadside shrubbery etc. would appeal to anyone. Anyways, it was evening when we arrived at our destination, a farm outside of the town of Cwmduad (pronounced, 'Coom- dee- ad'), where my fathers cousin, named Terry, trains sheepdogs and, quite obviously, keeps sheep( and the odd cow as well). He has many dogs there, and pictures of them form the bulk of the accumulated photos we snapped. There were 7 Border Collies (sheepdogs) and 4 Alaskan Malamutes (big sled dogs) I will give their names in age order:  Collies: Rebel(♂), Taff(♀), Pen(♀), Cap(♂), Harley(♂) and Bonnie(♀) Malamutes: Timba(♀), Kali(♀), Chief(♂) and Meeka(♀)  The Collies are medium sized dogs, and are all extremely friendly to all humans they encounter. The Malamutes however, are big dogs (Chief on his hind legs almost matches me in height) and can be quite vicious as they took bits out of each other and occasionally growled threateningly at their kennel mates, in particular 2 young labradors who were being looked after for a while. The Malamutes drove Terry to his wits end with their antics.  Monday: Nothing much happened here. We paid a trip to the nearest town, which is called Carmarthen. It is pretty much the quintessential british town, so, i shall say no more on monday.  Tuesday: As a birthday treat for my my youngest brother (Micro Baz to my friends, Alex to others), we went to Pembrey Park, which had a very pleasent stretch of beach. We spent the day there, where my brothers and myself engaged in various excavation acts on the sandy coast. We then proceeded to go into the water, and not even the veritable minefield of shells could stop us...until one pierced Alex's foot. Myself and my father went to the nearby shop, which sold diver shoes which we used to protect our feet against future shell attacks. We also purchased a surfboard for added fun. Whilst queuing to buy these items, an amusing sight greeted my eyes. A man with pink hair, face piercings, a huge moustache and, most funny of all, pastry cutters IN his ear lobes. I tried hard not to laugh, because he was at least 7ft tall and large in build and thus he could quite easily have given me the beating of my life if i laughed at him. At night my family, terry , the dogs and myself gathered around a fire we had set up. This little experience was taught me that rural wales makes a good place to know if you're being spied on, since on a clear night like this one with no streetlights etc, it is possible to see satellites moving in orbit. The Americans and their GPS can't hide from me!!!!  Wednesday: This was a funny day. First, our dear friend Chief got holes in his muzzle, courtesy of Kali, one week before he would be in the Crufts dog show. Whilst Terry took him to the vet, my family and myself went to another beach in Cwmtydu( pronounced ' Coom-tid-ee'). There we awaited Terrys arrival because he was planning to show us a hidden bay over the other side of the cliff by the Cwmtydu beach. While we waited, a large family of Orthodox Jews appeared in their battered, yellow minibus and literally took over the beach. They did some pretty silly things, included leaving a baby in its pram behind a parked car and propping deck chairs behind a reversing car :S. After our little trip to the hidden bay, the weather, in typical welsh fashion, turned dismal and it started to rain. While the Jewish family packed away their little camp, my brother (little baz) tried rather loudly to engage me in a conversation about bacon, knowing full well that Jewish people can't eat the stuff. In spite of the rain, we bought a 3 man inflatable boat, complete with oars and a free doughnut from a local shop. Eventually the rain drove us back to base in Cwmduad.  Thursday: Thursday saw us travelling to a nearby National Park, where a stately home called Newton House and a castle ruin reside. The house was rather interesting but i won't go into detail (it'll take too long). Deer were spotted (oh deer) around the grounds, despite the gentle rain. The castle required quite a trek up to it, but the view from the top of the ruins was well worth the walk. Going down, i saw that the the thin wooden beams, wet from the rain, were excellent for grinding on, Sonic style.  Friday: Twas my last day in wales. Firstly, we travelled to LLandowey (pronounced 'clan-dov-ree') to see if there was a dog show on. Unfortunately, it wasn't on until terry decided he wouldn't enter :S. so, to pass the time, my dad aided in the changing of a burst tyre for the unfortunate family who had one. In the evening, i travelled back home with my Father. As we crossed the Severn bridge, we saw a massive dark cloud hanging over england, which was still with us about 100 miles later when we arrived home.  All in all, twas a fun experience. I will post my photos shortly, but for now, farewell. 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Twas a good day today. My friends Jon, Dave. J, Dave. C and Richard paid me a visit. We started the day with a seemingly civilised game of Monopoly (Baz's rules applied). Things really kicked off when Dave. C established territories on the purple sector (park lane and mayfair). I would have done that myself but i had spent most of my time languishing in jail. From that point onward, the Anti-Dave alliance was formed, in an attempt to break his grip. Alas, it was all in vain. Dave.J fell to 'tother Daves schemes and a vital member of the alliance was lost. During this time, Richard (the evil capitalist pig that he is :)) was establishing his 'corner of death' (he was building up the orange and red sectors). My complete dominance over the blue area could not save me from his evil plots. I too fell. By the time Richard was seen as a true threat to all on the board, it was too late. Dave was annihilated. It was only Jon and Richard. Brave Jon put up a considerable fight, but ultimately, he too fell. Richard is now the uncontested ruler of my monopoly board :(.  'No matter' i says to myself. I introduced Richard to the CnC Generals, and he was hypnotised long enough for me to pack away the board and hide it ^^. The excitement of Monopoly now gone, we all turn our heads to a thoroughly exhilerating pastime of all our crew... beating the odd smelling and much loathed Paul Leonard at games he claims he 'pwns' all on. The foolish Paul attempted to break our extremely potent Gattling defenses with,of all things, technicals (pick-up trucks with lame-arse machine guns on top). They were ripped apart. As we closed in on him, he disconnected saying he was 'kicked out of the game' (yea right...).  After Richard finished ridiculing paul with my headphone/microphone set (a device he is enthralled by), we got to work on my Gamecube. Smash bros. was first on the menu. Dave., the techno throwback of the crew (56k, Playstation etc.) and thus not knowing the names of some the characters involved, announced that his character would be Seamus.(You know! Seamus Aran, hero of Leprechaun Prime etc.¬_¬) He meant Samus, but that didn't stop Jon losing himself in the world of laughter, bringing myself and Dave.J with him. Dave.C then decided to use Browser (the Tortoise/Dragon crossbreed who fights with Mario the Administrator ¬_¬). This was actually Bowser, and once again, we were laughing.  Eventually the fight was underway. Dave.J was Capt. Falcon, Jon was Ganondorf, Dave.C was Roy and i was Donkey Kony. By luck i picked up a Super Mushroom and, consequently, D.K grew in size. At this, i couldn't help but say, 'Now he's Horse Kong.' (Cos a horse is bigger than a donkey, is it not?) Laughter once again ensued, ensuring that Smash bros.     remains a group favourite.  Other games were played. They were: F-Zero, Mario Kart and Clone Wars. All were fun and all kept us inside, which was good, since it was rather wet and stormy out.  All in all, Baz has had a good tuesday 3rd of August 2004, and hopes that similar arrangements will be just as good. 
    
</post>


</Blog>