<Blog>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm an idiot. I have heard about the bandwith issue on so many websites before and it never even crossed my mind to think about it. I've signed up for Keenspace or Keenspot whatever you want to call it out of hopes that maybe it will still work for my site. I'm really not sure if I'm still gonna be able to work with geocities and if I can't I'm gonna have to learn a whole lot more if I plan on ever getting this working. I'm alright trying to figure out that angle at this moment though so we'll just see what happens. Damn this was so much simpiler a few days ago. I'm gonna look through all of my options though. I may have to settle for only having my comic strip seen on one of them Drunk Duck things. Good luck getting much notice off of that. Hobbies really should not be this stressful 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      At this point I'm trying to get sponsored on keenspace because GEOCITIES SUCKS!!!!!!!!!!!If too many people come on in an hour it blacks out. This sites goals are not gonna come to if the site blacks out whenever you go though the damn ARCHIVES! So right now if u see a fucking overdata thing on one of my websites I want you to make your hand a fist shake it in the air and scream "DAMN YOUS GEOCITIES" 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One of the great things about the bloggers is the ability it gives you to bitch. I mean I can bitch on my website but I feel I have to keep my bitching short and sweet on there. To start out I HATE THESE OLD STRIPS! Theres a few decent ones in there but its not until the second storyline where it gets good. Don't worry though...That will be in less that 2 weeks. So it wont be torture for too long. Although it does take alittle longer than that for the addition of Rish. Rish made a huge improvement to the comic strip. That doesn't mean shes my favorite character though. Chuck is by far the best of the three of them. Steve also alittle later into the comic strip really starts to rock a whole lot more. I love Rish but out of the three main characters shes dragging in last. But thats why she has boobs. Big boobs. Ladies love holding thier big boobs so Rish is more than happy with coming in third. There are also a few other interesting reacurring characters that you'll meet later on in the strip as the storylines become better and more complex (not lacking on the funny complex though). I'll have more to talk about once I rip out a few more of these strips. Later 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There is a reason for me starting this thing. I'm not so much interested in people getting a look inside my psycie (you try spelling that right), or taking a live look into my feelings and that kind of junk. I am posting this becuz I want  urlLink Sticky Fingers  and  urlLink Bloody Fingers  to be successful. I'm hoping that with this I can talk to the few fans of the site though thier comments because I don't really think that the guestbooks on the site alone are going to be that big of a help for that. Eventually I plan to get a forum on the website. That will be whenever I figure out how to make my own one. If any of you happen to have any idea on that send me an e-mail. I'd appreciate it a lot. I think thats all for this update. Later people 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         this is what i sent in for the Loserz geust strip. I hope that he picks it.  Turns out it shrinks when u put it on here. TO make it legible click  urlLink here   *update* Yeah the weeks up and this strip wasn't picked....Oh well.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If I weren't lazy I'd have the sites up and running right now. And once everythings running it'll be a piece of cake to update. Its just getting started thats the problem. I need to get myself motivated. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A lot of you have noticed that I am the worlds greatest genius. You also may have thought to yourself wouldn't it be great to have me for President of the WOLRD! Well now is your time.  From this day forth I am running for world president. If I am elected I will shower the world with my geniusness. I promise many many changes  Change 1: I promise to put to toghether a group of scientists onto the most important issues like Microwavable Lettuce. NO LONGER WILL YOUR LETTUCE TASTE LIKE CRAP WHEN ITS HEATED!!!! YOUR LETTUCE WILL NOW GET THE HARDCORENESS OF HOT THAT YOU DESERVE!  Change 2: Many of you have heard me state this idea before but I think it must be done. All women must wear a shirt with a picture of themselves on the back of it. I am SICK OF CHECKING OUT THE GARGOYLE WITH THE HOT ASS! IT MUST STOP!!!!!!!  Change 3: I will rid the world of pants! Why must everyones ass sweat so much over such a stupid law. In Europe nudity isn't as big of a problem. WHY HAVE ME MADE IT SUCH AN ISSUE HERE WHEN WE GOT HOTTER CHICKS IN AMERICA!!!!!!! DOWN WITH PANTS....You know what....DOWN WITH ALL CLOTHS!!....unless its cold....good idea Zorro..  Change 4: Tools song "The Grudge" will become the worlds anthem... BEAT THAT PLUTO!  Change 5: Pop culture will include midgets in with whats in and hot along with the already tall skinny whore movement...You can't take down the Tall skinny whore movement but you can throw short hot whores in there  Change 6: People will recriate in the bathroom and no longer in the kitchen... people make stuff in the bathroom a lot more than they do in the kitchen...  Change 7: Training dogs not to run into an owners crotch will be included in dog school...We desperatly need that one.  Change 8: Nobody will have weapons of mass distruction...All our wars will be fought in Nerf and occasionally squirt guns and water ballons if its hot.  Change 9: Insurance companies will no longer be able to be buttholes. Guys and girls will get equal treatment in thier payments. Ladies may mature faster but I garentee you there are a lot more of them driving and talking on thier cell phones than guys. By the way thats not sexist ....thats the truth...  Change 10: People listening to Evanscence or ICP in my prescence will be charged with assault and will receive brutal force from Clowns....kind of ironic eh?  ALL OF THAT AND MORE IS INSTORE FOR YOU WHEN YOU VOTE FOR ME YOUR GENIUS THE PRESIDENT OF THE WORLD!!!!!!!! Thank you 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had left a post on here ealier saying that I would probably have the site running in about a week....Yeah it wont be that easy. I actually have to redo the 21 strips that I have currently colored so that I can get them to fit the new design I have in mind for the site because of the diffrent program I have to use to make the design. I'm onto using the program Adobe Go Live. Which is actually an a lot better program than the geocities site builder but its harder to use. So as for when this site will be up and running again I have no clue. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So far the guy has picked 2 guest strips for his site and none of them have been mine. That would be fine with me if the two strips WERE NOT CRAP!!!!! Look at  urlLink his site  and take a look at today and yesterdays strip and tell me they're better than mine....dammit I relize I should be humble and alittle less pissed since theres still 3 days this week that hes doing guest strips...BUT I WORKED 4 HOURS ON THIS!!!!! Thats more time than I put into my own strips. SO COME ON!.....Jeez I sound like a butthole....whatever 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok I think I understand how to use Keenspace. Give me about a week before I make any more comic strips. The ones that are up already are gonna be going too. The geocities site will be gone very shortly. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Alright today I got my password for keenspace. Hopefully I'll be able to figure this thing out and have a comic strip site that actually runs decently. Thats all I want. If theres any more news needed for this I'll post it on here. Later 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm not quite at a good point where any kind of advertising is gonna help anyone out but I figured why not give it a try anyways. The writer of a terrific comic strip  urlLink Planet Earth and Other Tourist Traps  made a post on his site to try to tell at least one person about his site. I feel like I owe it to him since his strip is probably one of my greatest influnces. Not so much in the content but in the way that I write the strip. Before I saw his strip I thought that I had to pretty much stick with a strip that had almost no plot lines and was primarily just pointless jokes. I found his comic strip on accident actually. I had thought that back then I had the most original idea of putting a comic strip on the internet when I found his. It has great characters great plot and a whole lot better art talent. This being the first webcomic that I have ever read it holds a signicant amount of meaning to me. It remains one of the top 3 comic strips that I have ever read. So if your bored and want to do something with your time go check out  urlLink Planet Earth and Other Tourist Traps . Its very good and very original. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went through another  urlLink update  today and I am definatly calming down a whole lot about the complications I've been having on the site. So thats good. I'm glad to finnaly post some things on here that make me come off as alittle less of an angry guy. Cause normally I'm happy. I pretty much never get depressed or any of that stuff. I actually fine myself very funny. Thats one of the reasons why I started cartoons in the first place. I'm hoping that other people find me funny too. I don't care if you laughing at me or with me as long as your laughing (and my pants arn't down when ur doing it). Thats all for this update later.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well I'm really seeing a decent future to the site. A large part of this is because of the people I chat with online. One of the people I talk to (sage) is already making herself comptfortable in the forum. Shes even hunting for visitors for the site. I also have a lot of ppl (by that i mean 2) people already working up some votes for me on Buzz. Everysingle vote does count and it continually gets the site closer to the reconigition point. What would make me happier than anything is to get a decent amount of people that enjoy reading the strip. I know I'm not there yet and probably wont be for awhile. But it will happen. Sticky Fingers has the potential to go absolutly anywhere. The support of my friends and even my family is what really leads to my confidence in the characters of this strip. Even though I'm going nowhere on it at the moment I have a huge graditude towards all of you. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think I'm in a better mood than i was yesterday. I've got things figured out like I said in the last post so  urlLink Sticky Fingers  is still gonna be coming. Also a big reason for me being in a better mood is that I did nothing to try and fix my site today. I know its out of my hands for the moment so I'm just gonna let it go. I am still updating though because I'm hoping that when it slides back into my hands I wont have to start over. I'm an optimist an optimism can addmitally make you stupid at times, but who cares. Everybodies stupid. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've come to the conclusion that this whole situation is very doable. The only thing that I need to work on is my patience. Hopefully soon I'll get the Keenspace password and I can start using this thing for alittle less bitching and alittle more optimism. I think if I try to lay off the sites as much as possible I might manage to keep myself from going homicidal on people and thats a good thing. If Keenspace works primarily with HTML I figured out a way to make that work. So there is absoutly no problem there. I might have to buy another domain name but I've seen those they're often less than $10 to buy. It wont be a problem. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>