<Blog>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Actually, I can't be bothered going in. It's 10.00 now. My parents actually haven't said anything about it either which is a first. Maybe they haven't seen me? Oh no, I'm transparent. You know who are good? Kalmah. You know who else are good? Norther. And Children of Bodom. And Soilwork. And In Flames. I suggest you check out ALL of them bands whatever music you are into, it's so insatiable. Maybe I should go now. I am so bored, and tired... and I have a LOT of homework to do. Grrr... 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 8.30am and I should be waiting for my bus but I really can't be bothered today. It is only a half day anyway. Maybe I will go in at 8.50.&nbsp;I dunno what else to write. Oh yeah, on Monday me and some mates went to Liverpool with college&nbsp;and we just went to this bar and had beer, so no complaints really. I'm just happy with the way my life is going for once. Adiós.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      That party was cool while it lasted! I had lots and lots of beer and got very very drunk. Two people were sick which ended up in everyone having to go home quite early which was a bit GAY. I was planning to go back to&nbsp;another party at first but&nbsp;Charlie's mum decided to be a biatch and make me go home. But oh well. It was all actually quite funny. I am just really confused now... I don't remember coming home, getting into my house, or anything for that matter. I faintly remember being on the phone to Chelley, then waking up about an hour ago.&nbsp;The PC was still on and I had millions of messages from people thinking I was ignoring them. I love not being able to remember what happened. I just hope nothing too bad happened when I saw my parents! 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Velcra rule. Went to Liverpool yesterday to watch them with Breed 77.&nbsp;It was really cool! They invited us backstage for the whole day because it was such a shitty venue! Anyways, today I'm fucking bored.&nbsp;I&nbsp;got a&nbsp;Soulfly digipak earlier and I love it! I met Chris in town today and drank lots of wine with a bunch of people I didn't know (save Daniel).&nbsp;There was a&nbsp;sweet girl there called Jo and Chris seems to be totally in love with her... and he rarely loves anyone.&nbsp;I got a letter saying my school's having a reunion after like... half a year. But it will be good to see some old mates I ain't seen in a while.&nbsp;I will post again when I can be bothered.  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My name's Matt, I'm 16, I live in Manchester, UK. I&nbsp;have long&nbsp;dark-red (dyed)&nbsp;hair and blue eyes, I am about 5'10/5'11 and 10st in weight. I LOVE Skittles. They own you bitch. Music is VERY important to me. I love messing about on my guitar (not that I am any good). If you want any more info go to  urlLink www.faceparty.com/slow_chemical  - t'is a mini-site full of my details!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy. I am a happy chappy indeed. Mandy (a.k.a. 'unnamed girl')&nbsp;and I planned going to the cinema on Boxing Day seen as it was shut on Christmas Eve, but the buses were being bitches and not running, so I couldn't get into town! So Mandy came round and stayed! It was so nice! I asked her out that night and she said, 'Yes please'! Aww! So I just wanna state that I AM OFFICIALLY WITH AMANDA-LAILA EID! Then yesterday we spent the whole day in town. I bought a few CD's, a ticket for CHIMAIRA, and we went to the cinema (see, we got there in the end!). We also went to Pizza Hut and had the most retarded waitress ever. She was so dull. She brought us the wrong pizza at first. She had cuts all over her face and a huge forehead. WHY was she working there? She spoke funny too. Like she had a wall of slime over her mouth. Anyway... Mandy stayed again last night! We both dyed our hair... I did mine dark-red again and she did hers pink! I am so happy I am with her. She had to go this morning damn it... shall see her soon hopefully though. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well last night was indeed fun. Me and the unnamed&nbsp;girl mentioned in the entry before this one decided to go to the cinema to see L.O.T.R. again, except all the cinema's were closed! So we were walking around town looking for an open cinema but we didn't find any. So we ended up buying two&nbsp;10 packs of Fosters and going back to my house. I got just a bit drunk but we had a really nice night! I miss her now. I never thought she would show any kind of interest... shows what I know. Anyway, today is Christmas day! Hangovers on Christmas day suck. My little brother woke me up at about 8.00am. To be honest I wasn't expecting too much. I got some nice stuff really. A really cool digital camera (which I was gonna buy with Christmas money anyway!), about £130 (upto now!), loads of art equipment, some gift vouchers, a wallet and some other random useful things! Not bad really! Just finished Christmas lunch and I can't breathe due to stuffedness. I'm gonna sign off now. Merry Christmas! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it's 6.12am, Christmas Eve. Hardly excited about it this year really. Nothing much has happened to me in the last few days. I went to the cinema yesterday (well, the 22nd) with a girl I met from the net called Lauren, and a few friends. We saw the new Lord of the Rings movie, it wasn't so bad, heh. The graphics were amazing, but I have to say, it was a bit too long at 3 hours and 20 minutes! Lauren and I spent the day sniffing these funky ass&nbsp;tissues, so obviously an amazing day was had. Oh and just a few hours ago, a girl I like told me she liked me! Won't mention any names just yet though. I'll just say she has been mentioned in this diary before... 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I haven't wrote in here for a while. I apologise to anyone that might actually enjoy reading this. The reason being nothing interesting has happened to me at all this week. Oh - there is one thing. I got given a new name this week by Jo -&nbsp;'Moomin Maffoo'... hahaha.&nbsp;I broke up from college 'til early January, so that's a good thing as it is just adding to my stress levels.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Once again I saw another amazing band and got very drunk yesterday! This time, the band being the one and fucking only MY RUIN! The day went pretty quick though. I met Laura first in town and we went to Music Zone 'cause she is in love with someone who works there basically. Then we met up with Ruth and Sean and some other random people. I left them and went into the pub and&nbsp;met up with&nbsp;some more friends. A girl called Jo who is a friend of an ex (Debbie), another random girl called Jo who I always see at gigs, and Jo's friend Hannah. I also saw a girl from my college who I said hi to, so I have met a few people from my college this past weekend...! Then we queued up and Chris soon arrived with his many bottles of alcohol (well Malibu and Red Square really) so we finished them off with the help of everyone around me... then we went in. John Loughlin of Raging Speedhorn/Murder 1 was in the toilet and told me I had an amazing t-shirt on (which I did)! Murder 1 were playing first, and they were hella-heavy! Throughout the first two bands I just walked around seeing if anyone I knew was there. I went to the front and met Jo and a Jessicka look-a-like, and got me a free beer out of them! Then My Ruin come on, and wow. They played for a good hour or so in the shittest venue I have ever seen. After the show we went round the back and met a few members, including Tairrie B! Then we were fucked as to how we were getting home, we decided a train was best. So we went to the train station, missed the only train in hours (again) so I didn't get home until 5.00am! Also got stopped and searched by the police at the airport just for wearing a hood... all worth it though... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Me and Buffon went to Rockworld last night. Think I can honestly say an amazing time was had.&nbsp;I had quite a lot of alcohol in my system by the end of the night. We bumped into a few people from my college who I had never spoken to before which was pretty cool. I remember getting off with one of them too. God I regret it.&nbsp;Then I bumped into my ex Lauren. She was with one of her friends called Mandy. I have met her&nbsp;before...&nbsp;in April or May of 2003.&nbsp;I think she's really nice! I love that she was so sweet and listened to me and took an interest. I don't think she believed me though because of all the crap Lauren has told her about me. I suppose the fact I was a bit drunk didn't help either. The annoying thing is I really meant it too. I will live. I shall post next time something remotely interesting happens to me.   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      WOW! I went to see Machine Head last night, it was so amazing. They must of played for at least 2 hours! Their encore must of lasted about half an hour. I actually think this gig topped Chimaira, and I didn't think that would ever be possible. But it did. They made an excellent entrance to what I'd expect of a band like Cradle of Filth to make. Breed 77 and SikTh played too. Breed 77 were phenomenal... they are a really good band! SikTh were really fucking weird... didn't like them too much to be honest. Machine Head blew them both away. I waited until 2am to meet them... I was so fucking tired. But meeting Robb Flynn was something I won't forget. He was so friendly and just an all round safe guy. Something really gay happened to me at the train station... as I was getting on the train Chris stood on my heel and my shoe fucking flew off and went in between the gap and under the train! Anyway, I'm tired and hungry. I'm gonna go see what food I have lying around this shit-hole, then get me some well-earned ZZZ's.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Not much to write about today. College seriously stressed me out though. All this writing she has got me doing is driving me insane... it isn't why I chose art!&nbsp; If I wanted to fucking write endlessly I would of chose English. Ahh well. The girl (Aimee) from the gallery called me a good few times today. Seems cool though I suppose. Also, Laura gave me a ringydizzle which was quite fun... we had a good old 'chit-chat' about the party!&nbsp;Oh yeah, and so did Lisa. Nothing major happened today. Except I got told I have to move out. But that's all. Everyday kind of stuff really. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Good evening. Today was actually a&nbsp;very eventful day! College took us to the Lowry Gallery in Trafford. It's quite a cool building, it's very trippy. On our lunch break we went on a stroll around the shopping centre and I bumped into the woman who plays Shelley's mum in Coronation Street, so that was pretty cool. Then we went on more random strolls and did more doodles and stuff, and I noticed this girl kept grinning at me everytime I looked back at her. I thought something was up with her at first!&nbsp;She came over to me a while later, apologising incase she scared me,&nbsp;asking me my name and stuff, telling me the reason she was grinning is because she thought I 'looked cute'... yeah right! She seemed quite sweet really. She was only 14 though, but she looked about 20! Anyway, we exchanged numbers because she doesn't have many friends around here yet, so I thought I'd help her out.&nbsp;After that, we&nbsp;went over to the War Museum and went in a pretty scary elevator that went up at least a mile, and had thin caging to walk on when you reached the top, so you could see right underneath you... pretty scary! Then after the gallery I went into town to meet some friends (Laura and Charlie), and it was so funny! I thought it would be quite&nbsp;awkward seen as I got off with them both only last week but things went smoothly! They doused me in tattoo's with permanent marker, but it's all good. I got free Skittles and free chips out of them though. So I win... 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aw my God, what a night. I have been in bed practically all day (it's 5pm now). Went to the Tavern on Wednesday at lunch time with Gav, Adam, Sean and Donna. That was pretty cool 'cause we were in there for hours and I had quite a few! So I was a little drunk when I got home.&nbsp;I went to Jilly's again last night and got a bit overly drunk there too... not good. But I had a lot of fun last night! We left at about 1.30 and realised we (Mandy and I) had an hour and a half to kill, so um... yeah. Wow. Probably the most fun I have had in an hour and a half. Then we walked into the town centre to catch a bus. On the way, I decided to run up a car and jump off the back and I kinda smashed my heel up. It's agony to walk! So we got into the centre at about 3.00 and I was hobbling around and everyone thought I was a homeless bum or something. But I started laughing at some guy for giving some cigarettes to a girl in a short skirt for some reason... don't ask. The bus journey seemed to last 5 minutes. Then&nbsp;we had to walk home on the slippy ice which was so fucked! But&nbsp;we fell straight asleep when I got home! So it was a nice night apart from smashing my heel up. And now I'm sat here unable to walk, but I have Dr. Pepper, so it's ok.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things are going so damn well with Mandy it's unbelievable! We see each other practically every day, even on days where it seems impossible. I went round on Wednesday and ended up staying! So that night was really nice even though most of it was spent watching the TV and erm... other stuff. I went home on Thursday morning and ended up coming back that night! I wasn't meant to stay but I went to wait for a bus and ended up waiting about 2 hours in the freezing cold and rain for nothing. But Mandy (being the amazing and&nbsp;beautiful&nbsp;girlfriend she is!) bought us chips and gravy (mmmmmm) but even though they made me feel sick they were nicccceeee! So we had no choice to go back to Mandy's. I did offer to walk home so many times but Mandy wouldn't let me! Mandy's mum wasn't happy... I hid in the kitchen while they were arguing in the front room! So she got her ass grounded! Great! (Sarcasm).&nbsp;I suppose it's my fault though. So I won't see her for ages now. Yesterday though, I went to meet her outside of college so I could see her for at least a little while and that was really nice I think. We had Happy Meals! No wait... she did. Like I'd eat a Happy Meal?!... lalala. And we spent ages watching people stand in a dead bird on the road, t'was so funny! Anyway, I am tired still, my sisters crappy dance music woke me up and I have no plans for today... maybe I will go into town and see some friends I haven't seen in a while. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Friday was so good! I got a bit overly wrecked though... apparently. We got there at like 8pm, had lots of beer then had a little 'jamming' session and it went alright seeing as we were all a bit mashed! We did some Lostprophets, Misfits, Korn, One Minute Silence and some other random crap. Then we had a 'waterfall' bong and I cleared all 3 of my turns, go me. That was the point where things started getting weird. I don't really remember too much after this. Apparently, Amanda took me to bed 'cause I was in a pretty bad state and I told her I'd go look for her phone because she had lost it. She come down a while later to find me asleep, and she woke me up. She asked me to go look for it so I stumbled into the living room and&nbsp;walked back out claiming I had searched the living room. Then she asked me her number and I said I don't know it. Then a few minutes later I said I did, and typed 103 into a phone and said "I don't know how this thing works!"... so I was pretty bad. Then we had a massive hug in the kitchen and I fell asleep on her shoulder, and woke up asking what the tap was doing in the sink... yeah. All of this (by the way) is stuff I have been told, I don't remember any of it. Stuff I do remember... not a lot. I remember making mini-pancakes with syrup and standing in doggy piss! I have been pretty ill the last few days too, I think it was a dodgy burger I ate on Saturday...  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's the early hours of Friday 16th January 2004. Not much to report. I honestly think I am an insomniac. I have the weirdest sleeping patterns ever. Spent the afternoon with Amanda today... was a really nice night. She's so lovely. We finally formed a band on&nbsp;Tuesday. Well, we got some people together who want to start a band and we are actually gonna be taking it VERY seriously this time. First practice is tomorrow night. Already thinking of band names. Funny one was 'Wasted Energy' and a picture of a stoned battery to go with it. Still not decided on a fixed sound either.&nbsp;Collectively, we&nbsp;wanna make music in the style of Sepultura, Incubus, Misfits, Chimaira&nbsp;and Superjoint. What a sound that will be... each band is completely different. Gonna be a wicked party tonight at my mate Gavins house. Gonna be lots of chronic and alcohol. So I guess I should go try and sleep so I ain't too tired, as&nbsp;I wanna go get my hair braided in the morning. But I can't sleep damn it! Hmm, I'm gonna go do some writing. For now, in a bit.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hola. Life is good.&nbsp;Four weeks today until Chimaira! Not been upto much recently. Just spent loads of time with Amanda! First week of college was alright. Went to the pub with some friends on Wednesday. Puked on the bus home because I didn't eat that day. Went to Jilly's on Thursday night with Mandy, Adam and his new girlfriend Kelli. That&nbsp;was fun/confusing (at times) because she was tripping on LSD. Mandy come back to mine and stayed until&nbsp;yesterday morning. Seeing as she had the house to herself&nbsp;last night I thought I should take advantage of it so I went round when she finished work and stayed over. T'was ace! I love spending time with her. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, it seems like I haven't wrote in here for ages. Well I have been really busy with Mandy lately! She spent 5 days here (Monday - Friday) and we spent all of Saturday together... and I ended up staying there. Come home this morning drowsy as fuck... I wanna sleep.&nbsp;One of Mandy's mates&nbsp;(Lauren) is being such a&nbsp;cunt right now. She thinks that just because I cheated on one of my ex's with her (she was FULLY AWARE I had a girlfriend) that I am going to do it to Mandy, who happens to be one of Lauren's friends.&nbsp;This is how sad she is... she actually spent time making about 10&nbsp;new profiles on Faceparty just to rate me bad things (because Faceparty ratings mean everything obviously). So if anyone I can call a friend is reading this, ignore her. She is a sour little whore that gets used and abused by every male in Manchester. She doesn't understand how close I am to Mandy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello all, I'm Amanda aka Mandy aka PROUD OWNER OF MATTHEW :D. Well I came round to Matts last night and we made....pizza. Then today we spent the whole day lazin about just chilling and cuddling (we spend a lot of time cuddling coz i love it) and now I'm waitin for a super late bus so i can stay at the love of my life's house for just a little bit longer. I really love him, it's bizarre coz I've been hurt in the past and am usually a bit cautious about relationships but this time I've totally fallen and couldn't be happier. If you don't know Matthew then let me tell you this, he's so amazing in every way, he's so sweet and doesn't even know it, and really loving and a big ol softy at heart, and he has the most amazing bright blue eyes and a smile that brightens up his face and makes him look even more beautiful,&nbsp;plus he makes me so happy&nbsp;and the best thing is HE'S ALL MINE! Woo for me!! I'm missing Matt now (he's sitting over there with my guitar) so I'm off to cuddle :D Love you loads Matthew, Amanda 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday evening. Bored out of my skull. Mandy stayed over a total of 4 times this week. And every second of it was amazing. We went to the cinema on Friday night to watch School of Rock. I highly reccomend it, it's so hilarious!&nbsp;I spent a lot of time in town yesterday with Gavin and his new girlfriend (who by the way is one of the most annoying girls I have ever met!). I bumped into a lot of people. Simon, Scott, Zoe and Nuala from high school and&nbsp;my cousin David (who I haven't seen for years)&nbsp;and his mates. I had 2 Big Mac meals from McDonalds as they are a bit lovely! Come back home and Mandy made me such a nice curry! Very stuffed that night. I spent most of today sleeping and then practicing acoustic non-stop. I learned (this weekend)&nbsp;Master of Puppets (the breakdown) and the intro to Behind Blue Eyes so I am quite proud of myself. Anyway, I'm bored and don't know what else to write so I think I shall go. xx 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had our first non-drunk official band practice today (without drummer), went seriously well. We realised I am a lot better on bass than guitar which is odd because I have hardly ever played one. I just have a really good ear for music and I know what notes fit with chords and riffs. So, yes. Looking for a bass now. xx 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy shit. Where do I begin? It was amazing. I went to Chris' to see if he wanted to come and he did, so we went into town, I met my girlfriend&nbsp;and got to the Academy at about 6.30 and went inside to meet Chimaira! Unfortunately Mark and Chris weren't there but I still got to hang out with the rest of them for a while! I took a few pictures and got my stuff signed. Then I went into the concert hall and watched them play. Incredible. They played for 70 minutes. Some old, some new and an amazing 10 minute drum solo. I come out with some injuries which is an obvious sign I had a good time. I hope they come back soon. Mandy come back home with me to stay. We didn't get back until pretty late! I was so tired when we got home and I have really fucked my leg up worse than it already is. Anyway, I'm tired still, so goodbye... xx
     

    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The day I have been waiting for for so long has finally arrived! Today I go and witness a headlinging show by CHIMAIRA! Last time around they were amazing even though they were only on stage for about half an hour. Today I am hoping for at least another hour on top. I can't even wait any longer, it's driving me mad! I got their collectors double disc edition on Friday and it's really quite amazing! Has some cool tracks and the live tracks are awesome. I'm on the meet and greet list for the show tonight which is so fucking fantastic, THANK YOU SAMI! That means I get to go backstage and hang out with Chimaira a few hours before they go on stage! WOW! I'm so hyped about this show. It's gonna be incredible! I'll post all about it&nbsp;tomorrow!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heylo, quite a busy past few days! College still sucks, I'm thinking about dropping out but I have made it this far so I dunno. It's so stressful. Wednesday sucked this week. We went to Yates aboout 5 minutes from Piccadilly but it was fucking crap. I had no money and Adam and Sean were being stingy! Slept most of that day. Went to Jilly's with Buffon on Thursday night, it was pretty cool! Had quite a few drinks. It's so good on Thursdays because it's soooooo cheap! I bumped into a girl I hadn't seen since&nbsp;the first time I went to Jilly's which was odd, she has changed so much! My gum started bleeding too 'cause Adam headbutted my lip-ring which then lodged itself inbetween two of my teeth. Luckily they didn't break! Adam sliced his finger open too picking up broken bottles (I dunno why?)... ok. We danced all night, amazing time was had. Got in at about 4.00am and fell straight asleep. I saw Mandy yesterday! She came over at about midday! I was so good to see her, I missed her so much! She stayed over and it was really nice. She went home this morning though, at 7.30! Too early for me! Anyway, I am knackered so I'm gonna go get me some sleeps. Bye bye...  xx   
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just had a pretty weird dream and I thought I'd write it here before I forgot it. It was a snowy morning and I came out of my door to go to college when I knocked on an old womans door asking her if she wanted to walk me to the bus stop (I have no idea why!). But she did. There were about 12 kids in the drive and as I walked past one I threw a snowball in his face and ran away with the old woman flying behind me! Then I was shouting something like, "You're number 0!" at him. When we got to the bus stop (after lots of slipping on the ice) a massive weird black bus pulled up and out stepped my beautiful girlfriend Amanda! I threw the old chick away (somehow) and ran over to her and asked her what she was doing home and she told me she'd caught the bus from France to come and see me! Wooo! Then... I took her back home and we hid in the kitchen where her friends were calling her and she was like, "Oh I'm still in bed, don't disturb me!". Then I took her into college and she sat next to me. Some guy with long ass hair come into my class with a camera and said to her, "There you are love, we've been looking for you!", took a picture of her and left. Ok. I asked her who he was and she said her other boyfriend, and she just couldn't refuse him 'cause he was 'so sweet'... so kinda confusing. Then someone phoned me (in my dream) as my mum woke me and I was talking to the phone person even when I had woke up. Mad dream! I am really missing Mandy right now. It's unbearable. I have to admit I've cried about 3 times. I only get to speak to her for about 5 minutes a day... it just isn't enough. I should be heading off to college now. UGH. I don't mind it... just hate being up this early for no good reason! It's 8.55am! Have a nice day, whoever reads this...  xx   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Feeling a little down today. Mandy's gone to Paris and I am already missing her so much, it's unreal. I actually feel physically sick at the thought of knowing I'm not gonna see her for the next few days. It's kind of odd too because with past girlfriends I would be really angry at the thought of her being in another country sharing a room with a friend who happens to be a guy but I can honestly say I trust Mandy and know I have nothing to worry about. People are probably wondering why I am saying stuff like this after quite a short time? Well, I've never had feelings so intense for anyone so soon before. And I know what I feel. I can't wait until Friday morning because I get to see her again. I'm probably gonna spend most of this week sleeping or keeping myself busy so I don't upset myself too much. Wow... I have an emotional side... 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I had such an odd dream last night. First I was on a bus with someone I didn't know talking about the bus stop I was getting off at. Then I got off and walked into a bathroom, and when I walked out again I found myself in a bull-ring with a bunch of other people, and there was a metal fence all the way around us. After a while several women came out and started singing. After they were done Max Cavalera came charging out screaming really loudly and people were chasing him, causing him to skip parts of his lyrics. Then I saw someone in the crowd who I hate from high school and I bit him. It caused my tooth to snap in two and one half was hanging from my gum. I shown my cousin (I dunno why he was there), and he pulled it out and we were laughing. Then I woke up. I really wanna know what it meant.
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today marks the 3rd month of my relationship with Mandy! I'm so glad we made it this far. Maybe this proves to most of the people who don't agree with us that this is serious. Nothing out of the ordinairy has happened as of late. Went to the cinema a few days ago to see Starsky and Hutch or whatever it's called... it's pretty good. I got an insect bite on my leg and it is so sore. I think it's infected too! Well Mandy's on her way over so I'm gonna go wait for her in my room. xx
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Howdy. My birthday was great! I got me lots of nice clothes and some ace DC shoes! Heard my mum got me some Sketchers in New York... oops. Also got me some cd's... Exodus and Probot. Mandy got me a really nice ring, I love it! Jilly's was so good, lots of my best friends shown up (Adam, Chris, Donna and Gav) and I kicked all they asses at pool! Chris got me some Skittles... obviously the best present ever! On a more negative note... I broke up with Mandy today... for about 2 hours. It was so scary. I have been taking her for granted and it isn't good. It has to change, so it will. I realised today that if it doesn't I will totally lose her and the thought alone scares me. Well, she's asleep in MY bed right now so I better go keep her warm... xx
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy. Had a big, nasty argument with Mandy today =( but we sorted it out! It kinda brought us closer together! In my opinion anyway. I stayed at hers at last night, was nice. My birthday tomorrow! I can't wait to go get some new shoes and clothes! I might get a tattoo too! Woooooo! xx 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hola. Well that was scary. The shop Mandy works in just got raided and she had 2 guys with knives and baseball bats&nbsp;holding her up against a wall, the little bastards. But... she's safe thank GOD!&nbsp;=) Yup, things are still going really well with Mandy. I am loving it! I see her practically every day and on the days I don't we speak on the phone. We have the odd argument but never anything too serious. She stayed last Tuesday and brought&nbsp;over a big-ass bottle of Budweiser&nbsp;and it was a bit of a nice mixture. Then on Wednesday I spent the day drinking in Piccadilly with my friend Gav. I think I drink more and more every week! Thursday night I went to Jilly's again and got completely fucked - probably the worst I have been. EVER. I ended up starting on a car because I was angry about something... unaware there were 2 beefy black dudes in it. They got out and started punching me in the head. Ouchy. But oh well, no permanent injuries. I cried a lot that night too over the most retarded stuff, which is why I am limiting my spending money in Jilly's to just £6.00-8.00. That way I know I won't drink too much. Then on Friday we went to my friend Adam's 'gathering' - didn't drink too much there... around 8 bottles of alcopops. There was a really nice bonfire in the back too and some very nice words were said between Mandy and myself. Then I stayed over at Mandy's&nbsp;on Saturday night - ya see I can't get enough of her, even after almost 3 months! Wooooo! T'is my mums 50th tomorrow! My dad has a trip to New York arranged for her, that he has been planning for over a year. I know she will enjoy it. Still haven't got a clue what to get her - shall think about that when she gets home. Speaking of birthday's, it's mine on the 19th! WOOOOOO! Love you Mandy =) xx 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haven't wrote in here for a while. Nothing really to write actually. Just been having a really nice time with Mandy over the weeks, it's insane! Several badly failed attempts of breaking us up have been made by a bunch of people with WAYYYYY too much time on their hands who&nbsp;should just begin to get over it. Oh, Adam (Banister)... you forgot to keep the part about you threatening to slit your wrists over Mandy and the part about me keeping my business out of what you and Mandy talk about when you happily read the conversation between two people that have nothing to do with any of you anyway. If any of you wanna read the WHOLE conversation and not the edited last half of it, ask Mandy for it =)  PS -&nbsp;Next time any of&nbsp;you wanna threaten / insult me, do it to my face instead of behind a keyboard, it's pretty cowardly. xx 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well yesterday marked the day that Mandy and I have been together for 4 months! She come round to stay and we had a really nice night apart from one even - I got a death threat via phone. So yeah. I've been nervous, paranoid and shaky since. Mandy's on her way over again (YAY!) so I am gonna go.
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just a little message to say I'M LOVING THE AMAZING SUNNY WEATHER LATELY! Finally, Manchester gets a bit of sun!
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was so cool! Gav asked me if I wanted to go drinking in town and seen as it was super sunny, I did. I got on the bus and my mate Becky was on there. We were talking about night clubs and college and other crap. She got off and went to Urbis and I went to meet Gav at Burger King. We started walking to Urbis and there we stopped to listen to this guy stood near HMV playin' reggae... he was so cool. I bumped into Jenny and Ellin and spoke to them about their photo shoot with the weird perve guy! Then we carried on walkin' and there was this tribal drumming band who were amazing. They should so combine their skills! Then we got to Urbis and started drinking and skating (attempted skating anyway). There were loads of security dudes walking about so we decided to get McDonalds cups and pour the beer into them (clever)! But we still got caught. Some dumbass made us throw them away! Then some people walked past shouting 'slow chemical' at me. Aw wow, I'm famous! Then Mandy called (wooooo!) and I bumped into my cousin Dave again. Things got pretty boring from here. We just walked about, setting newspapers on fire, got some food and went to the bus stop. I saw my friend Sarah and her boyfriend there and they told me they were attacked with a Coca-Cola can! Bit gutted! They went to see Passion Of The Christ and it made her cry apparently! Then my bus come and I got on and some weirdo guy started talking to me about magic. I think he really WAS insane. He told me he taught David Blaine everything he knows  'and more'. Rrrrrriiiiiggghhhhhhtttt! Anyway, for some reason my back is hurting so I'm gonna go now.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Went to Liverpool today with Gav, Sean and Turek. It was pretty good but really tiring. We saw a really mad exhibition called 'Uncanny'. It was really freaky and sick. Spent half the day walking aimlessly around town. I am really sleepy today. I fell asleep on the bus ride home and banged my head on the silver railing above the seats. Mandy's coming to stay tomorrow! She's coming really early, so we're gonna have a day in doing nothing. Things are really weird lately. Lots of pointless arguments keep arising and getting really bad. We clash so much. But still, I refuse to give up. I don't care if that's wrong or whatever! We had a great day yesterday. We spent the afternoon in town and went to see The Butterfly Effect... what a good film! Apparently, I spoiled the night because I didn't say hi to her mum when I come into her house and Mandy fell out with me for it. But it's resolved now.
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hello. Had a long, complicated talk with Mandy last night. She seems to be getting tired of the relationship, but she insists she isn't and that she cares and loves me. I believe her, but I think she's having doubts. First day back at college today. It was pretty fun but nothing special. No one from college was on my bus this morning so I got the impression it was Sunday or something. Then when I got to my classroom there was nobody in there and it had gone 9.05. But then... everyone turned up, so that was alright. The 2 old buildings are officially closed now, and the 2 canteens in the new college are open, so that means we don't have to walk for 5 minutes every day just to get some food. There was this cool, huge, bouncy thing (I dunno what the hell it was exactly) outside my class today and it was slightly fun jumping on it many-a-time! I also spent 20 minutes riding around the college in a wheelchair type thing and it was super fast and I was doing drivebys! Adam wasn't in today.  He claims to be on holiday, but I saw him in HMV not so long ago... so we have decided not to tell him we are going to Liverpool on Thursday! The lil' rascal.
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ello. Last few days have been great! Mandy stayed for 3 nights in a row and it was so nice (apart from the odd fall-out). We just spent the whole time lying around, doing nothing (which, by the way, is better than doing anything else)! I feel I really have to better myself though. There are a lot of things I do wrong. It is mainly due to stubborness and jealousy on my behalf (which is really silly, but in a way it does show I care). I am not letting this relationship go, so I will better myself to make it continue. xx
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hello all. Had quite a busy weekend. My family went to London early in the morning yesterday, so I had the house to myself all day (well until about 5.00pm when Mandy come over). We went to some Indian place for a meal yesterday. First we went to some pub to meet her workmates and then we went to the restaurant. It wasn't that good in my opinion. The food was nice but it just took way too long to get it. The beer was great though! After the meal (which finished at about 12.00am) we made our way into town and stayed there, doing nothing, for a few hours. It was kinda nice most of the time. We sat by some heaters until 3.00am. Jesus Christ... the ammount of guys who walked past and said, "Alright ladies?"! It was ridicoulous. I'm THIS close to cutting my hair off! Mandy went home this morning. I got the bus with her into Sale to make sure she was safe. HER MUM GETS HOME TODAY! Hooorahhh! No more staying at her dads house! God I hate him. Guess what he said the other day when on the phone to Mandy? He goes, "If I ever meet this guy you're hanging around with, I'll kick his face in, I swear!". Nice. Mandy told him all about me though, but she said he wasn't that surprised. But I really don't wanna meet him. He will stand on my face a bit. Well it's Easter today and I like chocolate, so in a bitsiziziziz. xx
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well I spent the day with Mandy at my house yesterday. We had a really nice day and I loved every single second. It seems like it has become a new relationship or something. I keep learning from mistakes I have made (which is a good thing), therefore, making the relationship really stronger (in my opinion anyway). Not one disagreement or argument arose yesterday. First we went around town in pound shops where Mandy bought piles of crap. We also visited a sex shop where Mandy also bought some stuff. And then we got a bus to my house... and had lots of fun. When it was time for her to go home, I got the bus into town with her to make sure she was safe (because Manchester is spooky at night!). Going out with her tomorrow to some place for a meal. It will be fun and scary, because it's with her workmates, and I don't know any of them really. Anyway. I found out I'm boring, yay! xx
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I hate this. Why does Mandy have to spend a whole week with her dad?! She's old enough to stay home alone now. I think the increase in diary entries prove I am lonely (they are DAILY!). I really miss her. I wish I could spend more time with her. Anyway, she had her University interview today! I hope she got in! She'll be so upset if she doesn't. I can't wait until next week. Mandy told me she wants to stay here for a few days to make up for the lack of seeing her this week, so that's gonna be amazing! Wow, my dad just said he likes Sublime. Aw yeah. Anyway, if you're reading this Mandy, I love you! xx
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well. Yesterday was really nice! Spent the entire day with Mandy in town. First we went to Urbis and saw a graphics exhibition... that was pretty cool. Spent about 2 hours in there. Then we had to go clothes shopping for Mandy because she wanted a dress, but she got quite a few bits. Then we went to the cinema to see Gothika. It was really spooky... I really liked it! One of the best films I have seen in a long time. Then we went to this place called Nando's and had a really big meal but I couldn't finish it because I was still stuffed from the Chinese a few days earlier. Then when I was walking Mandy to the bus stop I bumped into some of my friends (Chris and Damien) and decided to join them at Ritz. I waited until Mandy got on her bus then walked to the Palace Theatre to meet some of Damien's friends. They didn't show up but they called him and told us to meet him in this bar called Overdraught. Wow - that place is amazing. I really like it. It's like a bar but with good, loud music and sofa's. We stayed and had a drink in there before walking up to the Ritz. Chris and I got in but one of the girls got rejected, so of course, we all had to leave too. We walked up some super long road for ages to some club that was SHUT. So then we had to walk all the way back. We found this underground club and went in there for about half an hour. 2 of Damien's friends left and went to Ritz and Damien and this other girl went on to 5th Avenue so Chris and I decided to go on to Ritz too. First impressions... I hate it. It looks cool, but it's just like one huge, sweaty room. Didn't have much fun. Spent most of the night sitting near the toilets shouting 'EYYYYYYYYYYY!' to everyone who walked past. I was really missing Mandy too. She was in my head ALL night. God I love her. So anyway, we left at about 1.30am and walked to a kebab place and had some food. Then we got a train to the airport and got a taxi home. All of this took around 3 fucking hours. I got home at about 4.00am. I briefly spoke to an upset, angry Mandy on the net before going to bed. So I went to bed and woke up around an hour ago. It's Mandy's 18th today! Hopefully I will get to see her but it sounds like she's too busy. Anyway, I better go. I'm getting hungry now. xx
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well that was scary too! Mandy and I have been texting all day and she stopped at 9.00pm, but I didn't think anything of it. Then at around 11.30pm I noticed she still hadn't messaged me for a long time and I started to get worried. I text her a few times telling her to let me know if she was ok or something... but no reply. I grabbed some money and ran to a phonebox. On my way I got a message saying she is ok and her battery had run out. That explains it! I was on my way anyway so I carried on running and called her and told her I loved her. I think a lot of people don't believe the way I feel about Mandy is real because I have good things to say about my past relationships... they just usually end badly (my luck) but because I have good things to say about them they think things I say now aren't really meant... if you know what I mean. I know what I mean. And I know what I feel is real. I love you Mandy. xx
</post>

<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ELLO! Not wrote in here for a few days so I thought I should. Been spending lots of time with Mandy still, it's great! Spent the day in town with her yesterday which was nice. We went to an art gallery... was pretty interesting. Then we had to meet one of her friends to go to the cinema and I went into a silly, paranoid, possessive mood (that's me...). I realise now it was overly pathetic. But today was the nicest day ever! Mandy's family and myself all went for an all-you-can-eat Chinese meal and I am still really stuffed! The food was so gorgeous and Mandy looked beautiful as always. She's staying at her dads (he's mega strict) for a whole week now. I'll be seeing her on Tuesday though because I'm taking her out for a meal for her 18th! That will be nice. xx  
</post>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Last few days have been confusing. I met Mandy and her friend 'Cox' on Saturday in town. He's a really cool guy! We walked around town shopping and then went to the cinema to see that film with Jim Carrey and Kate Winslet... I forget the name. It was confusing and I didn't really understand it. Went to Mandy's after the film and just lay there cuddling and stuff and it was lovely! Then Mandy came to mine on the Sunday and the whole day was so nice until the last hour or so. I got angry. God, I have a problem. Mandy pointed out that most of my friends are female and I didn't understand why she got upset about it. I should of thought about it from her point of view. Anyway, I got angry and shouted, and when she tried to leave I hung on to her. I followed her to the bus stop and pleaded forgiveness but she got on the bus. I cried all the way home and cried on my bed whilst reading various things she had written for me. Cheesy? I told one of my best friends, Adam, about it and he invited me over to get drunk and talk about it. I wrote a really long letter to Mandy and grabbed some money. I went round to Adams and had a pretty good time drinking and eating snackages. I left at 10.20 and went to catch the bus to Mandy's. When I arrived I gave her the note and went for a walk. I remember getting myself lost but I found my way back. We talked for ages and it seemed that Mandy really did want it to end. So we went back to her house and I cried myself to sleep. I woke up at 5.30am and got kicked out. Had to walk about 2 miles in the freezing cold in hope that the bus driver would let me on with only a £20 note. He did, wooo! Chris called me and said he was near my house so I met him and we walked around for a while. I got home at about 7.00am, lit some candles and cried myself to sleep again. Woke up this morning at around 11am and immediately started texting Mandy. I went to see her at 3.oopm to try and sort things out. After a few hours, things weren't looking good. I tried so hard to convince her she was the only thing I wanted and I would do anything to prove that to her. We decided that I am to go on an anger management course thingy to try and sort it. I want to cure this so much. In the end, we kinda got back together, on a trial type thingy. But I am so happy and these last few days have really shown me how much she means to me and how much I would hate myself if I let this all go. I love you Mandy =)
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Should be sleeping right now, but I can't, so I decided to write in this. Yesterday marked the 5th month of my relationship with Mandy! I met her in town and we just hung around there most of the day. We went to see 'The Day After Tomorrow' and wow, what a film. It's really amazing and kinda makes you think a lot. Then I started feeling weird and seriously thought I was gonna throw up, but I had a burger then everything was fine. Then we went to Jilly's for a while. I actually danced, with very little alcohol in my veins, and... I enjoyed it! Whoa. A first. Everyone from college (who actually never go to college) were all surprised at my hair and someone called me pretty! I saw the usual people I see on a Thursday (Ash, Jenny and Ellin) and I met Ash's boyfriend (unsure of his name, but he was really cool and so easy to get on with) and her friend Jenny who spoke to me about college and Download and various other crap when everyone ran off on me! Also, saw my friend Sarah and her boyfriend Andre. She was the first person I spoke to in Jilly's, ever! Mandy and I had another pathetic fall-out over trust and paranoia, but all got resolved in the end. The bus ride home was so fun (in more ways than one...)! Some really funny guys got on and they were making me laugh so much, but then when some other guy got on the bus who looked all gothic and stuff, they weren't so funny. For no good reason one of them started on him and was really punching him so hard. So pointless. A girl who works in 5th Ave. got on and sat with us for protection apparently. She's never heard of Slayer!!! Pffffttt! It's so weird how in society there are some people who are really nice and some who are complete cocks! Oh well. It's Friday morning right now and I am kinda bored stiff. So, bye bye.
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You know what I love? When you wake up in the morning super tired, and you think you have to get up, but you look at the clock and it's like... 5am or something. That happened to me today! Anyway, today was really funny. I stuck loads of hot glue to Gav and he rubbed sandpaper in my face... yay! Mandy's poorly today so I'm gonna look after her later on! I don't really know what else to say. 
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, hello! I'm in the happiest mood ever! Last night Chris and I went to Jilly's and got insanely drunk! We played some pool and spent a lot of time shouting at people and other random crap. It was a good night and I had a good time... laughed a lot! This morning I had a raging headache but went straight to Mandy's and spent the day with her. It was such an amazing day. Sunny and clear, we decided to go for a walk through this really nice countryside(ish) place. Really enjoyed that. And now I am sat at home listening to Hanson! Hahaha! But this song is having some kind of effect on me! It's so uplifting and the musical harmonies are incredible! A lot of people are gonna be shocked at this! Ah well. I am kinda getting used to my hair now and I really like it. I am glad I cut it. It was hard to do but I have no regrets. There are some pictures at  urlLink www.faceparty.com/slow_chemical  =)
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I really have no fucking idea what is going on in my life anymore. I love Mandy and I love being with her. I cry like a baby at the thought of not being with her. I like to think we can make it through anything (as we have done so far), but now that's kinda changed. Don't get me wrong, I do want Mandy...  I want nothing else. But I am just working on hope rather than belief this time around. I would hate myself forever if I let what we have just fall apart. I can't give up on us.
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today I cut my 40cm+ hair off. That is all.
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well it's Wednesday night and I am fairly bored so I thought I'd write on here. I have to say (and I don't give a fuck who rips me for this) the new Slipknot album is pretty amazing (except the really queer acoustic songs which just AREN'T Slipknot). 'Three Nil' is the best song so far. Anyway, today I got really hyped up and ready to cut my hair. I was gonna do it. The only reason I didn't is because Mandy stayed late at college and it is her hairdresser that was supposed to be doing it. And now I have gone into the mood where I couldn't bear to cut it (I go through weird hair moods)! But oh well. I shall wait until next time around. I am thinking that tomorrow, after college, I may go to the hairdressers and get my hair (which is now almost 50cm long) cut off. I am gonna look so weird(er). I just can't be bothered looking after it anymore. If it is only 3/4/5 inches long I could just get up in the morning and not do a thing to it when I go out. Ah, that sounds like bliss. I'll write about what happens tomorrow. I am so bored right now. I fell asleep in the damn bath before. It's fucking scary waking up in a cold bath. I haven't even had a proper meal all day either because my mum made something I didn't like. It had tons of vegetable crap in. But oh well. That gives me an excuse to get some chips mateeeeee. Ah fuck this.
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well last night was fucked. Mandy and I went to Jilly's because it was meant to be a NWOAHM club-night or something, but I saw little evidence. We played pool and as usual I kicked ass. Aw yeah. Anyway, on the way home some stupid twat punched me in the side of my face and now it is so sore. I can hardly hear properly. Everything's echoey and metallic.
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Had a pretty cool week. Went back to the Lowry with college on Wednesday or Thursday... I don't quite remember. It was pretty cool I suppose. Went to Rockworld with Mandy on Thursday night but I regret that. We had a silly argument and ended up temporarily breaking up. It was so upsetting. We left Rockworld without a single penny. Therefore we were trapped. Luckily I saw Jenny walk past so I lent some money to get back into Rockworld. Mandy and I were talking about why we should break up and then I kissed her for about 10 minutes and it was SO nice and perfect! We ended up realising that we didn't wanna lose each other *cheeeeeeeessssssseeeee!* and got back together! Yeahhhh mateeee! Then I had to find Ashleigh and lend some money off her for the bus. I lent lots off my friends from college on Thursday and I feel all guilty! But it shall be paid back! Yesterday was an amazing day too. I had my graphic design interview at college and I was really nervous... didn't think I'd get in. But the guy said my work was the best he had seen(!!!) and as long as I pass my art course I will DEFINATELY get in! Plus he said I will be at a massive advantage to everyone else because I have used most of the stuff they use on the course before! So, yeah! Next 2 years of my life are planned now! AND, Mandy got me the 1st Chimaira album, woooo! Also, Mandy and I got Download tickets! FUCK! Ok, er, sorry, but that is so exciting. I get to see Slayer, Metallica, Soulfly, Machine Head, Slipknot, Damageplan, Ill Nino, Soil, Hatebreed, Drowning Pool, Cradle of Filth, Korn and so many other bands... it's insane! Plus next month I am going to see Chimaira, Killswitch Engage, God Forbid, Shadows Fall, Exodus, Re-Aktor and Hatesphere at seperate shows! How amazing is June?! I think I am gonna die. Then we went to the pub and I got fairly drunk, woo! We were playing pool with some Iraq dudes and I won EVERY game I played! 'Cause I'm 'well mint' at pool! We went to the cinema after that with Mandy's friend Will and his girlfriend, and saw Van Helsing. I didn't really like it. The graphics were pretty dodgy and it wasn't really my thing. We went back to Mandy's and spent a few hours just lying there, watching TV. That was the highlight of the day for me. Well, I think I am needing me a shower right now. Gotta go to town and meet Gav 'cause he said something bad happened last night at the Incubus concert and he wants to talk about it... 
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today I dropped chocolate cake on the floor and drank some beer. That's all. I'm kinda feeling a little empty and vacant at the moment and my mind is blank, so I'm not gonna write about the last week.
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Thought I'd write some stuff in here as I haven't for a while. Turns out the 'death threat' was someone messing around in a phone box, so sorry to all the people who hate me! Mwuahahahahaaaa... anyway. Mandy got in my college! She's doing a 2 year course in jewellery and I'm doing a 2 year course in graphics. The thought of spending 2 years at the same college is amazing! Last few days have been nice. It feels like a completely new relationship because we both really are stopping the stupid arguing as it's overly childish and now it's great! We went bike-riding on Saturday on some hills 'n stuff near Mandy's house and I went and popped her mums boyfriends tire! Ah well. We've spent so much time together lately too. Every possible minute. Today it is May Day so I didn't have to go to college. We went to Styal and carved stuff into a stone wall. The nice weather is great too. If it carries on we're gonna have a BBQ on Friday! I got a new stereo yesterday, FINALLY. I have had my old one for about 4 years and the CD player on it doesn't work so I have had to use my DVD player! It sounds so good! I have 4 speakers on it too which adds to the sound quality. I put up all my old posters too on an angle and it makes my room really trippy! Anyway, it's 11pm, meaning Mandy is out of work now, meaning I am gonna go call her.
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Today was so damn cool. Met Mandy at my college and took down all of my exhibition crap. Then we all went to the cinema (well, Mandy, Sean, Turek and I). Hahahaha. No we didn't. We swapped the tickets for cash and just went to the pub and Burger King and played pool. Yemate. I played three games and won one. Also had my favourite crisps in the world. So yeah... was great! Mandy's behind me right now playing the Sims. I swear to God, she loves it. But it's so sweet. She's made a family called 'Hartley' and in it, there's Matt, Laila and a little kid (he was a mistake...). It's like she's playing God and she's been spending ages making the perfect villa type building for us, including a greenhouse. I wonder if any Gibbs' will start wandering around it like at Mandy's college?! My GOD, I hope so. Imagine seeing a simulated Gibbs? That'd rule a little. I discovered two great bands yesterday... one of which got reccomended to me months ago. They are As I Lay Dying and The Agony Scene. Pure hardcore. It's such a good genre! So yeah... Mandy's getting into computer games a lot lately. She keeps playing the Sims and Harry Potter! She's better than me actually. That's because I spend my time on more creative things such as sleeping and watching the TV. Well, I rarely watch the TV unless there's something I really like on it. And I don't like many programs. I like dumb-ass humour shows like Dirty Sanchez, Moronic, Ripleys and sometimes Jackass, but that's just getting old now. But I do spend a lot of time watching music channels. Because I am unemployed and I am a slob-ass =) - and now I'm gonna go snoggify Mandy's face mateeee!
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today, my family, Mandy and I went to a Titanic exhibit. It was pretty cool. We saw actual artifacts from the Titanic, and a huge piece of the ship. Most of the stuff that was brought up is still in really good condition like the ceramic pots and stamps. I am really tired right now, and I can't be bothered writing much in here so I don't think I will. 6 MONTHS TODAY MANDY!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mandy is great, you know? Yeah, she really is. She is my girlfriend and she is bloody great. She has a really cute name which is 'Laila' (her full name is Amanda-Laila Eid). Tomorrow (June 27th 2004) is the date that marks the 6th month of our relationship! That's half a year! And the time has just flown by! I suppose that's what time does when you have fun. I don't know what is it that has stopped me from becoming bored like I have done with my past relationships! There's something really insatiable about my Mandy-Laila! She's just so fun to be around. When she isn't here, I feel odd... like something is missing.  Yeah, I take her for granted sometimes (well a lot of the time...), but who doesn't take someone they love for granted? Or is that a stupid question that only refers to me? But, the thought of not being with her brings me to tears. I think I have cried more these 6 months than I have in the rest of my life. I don't know why on earth she is with me... she can do so much better. I am way too paranoid and way too aggressive. One thing I seriously regret happened about 2 weeks ago. I was really tired (and stressy) and Mandy and I were just going to bed, and for no reason AT ALL I started being really mean to her. I turned the light off, got into bed and hugged her. Then I started to cry. I just couldn't believe I could be like that with her. I have got such a short temper! And I know that 99.9% of the people to read this will agree. But, believe me or not, it has calmed down so much since I met her. Never before have I wanted to change for a person. I want to be what she needs and I seriously intend to be, because I love her, and when we are together, I get lost in time and nothing else matters. 
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This week has been an extremely tiring week for me. On Monday, I spent the morning painting some big wooden boards for my college's end-of-year exhibition. So that was kinda NOT fun. I left at dinner and went to Mandy's college to help her with some of her work. I was there from about 1.00 until about 6.30! Anyway, it was kinda nice. I found myself being extremely patient all day which is something kinda new to me. That night, after we went to Mandy's, we went to see San Francisco thrashers, EXODUS! We got there half way through the first support bands set, Re-Aktor. I thought they were really damn good. Next band up were Hatesphere. They were your average fast guitar, fast drums, screaming band. I am getting bored of the unoriginal metal scene. But next up were Exodus! They played an amazing set despite being on a tiny stage and the fact they only played to about 150 people! I was just stood at the side with Mandy all night, holding her close, looking after her. After the show I met every member of Exodus and got my ticket signed by them! The next day I had to go to college and put up 'the best of' my work from the course for the exhibition. I'm kinda proud of it. That night I went to see the one and only FEAR FACTORY! Supports came from i-(def)-i and Johnny Truant. Both weren't bad. But Fear Factory were amazing. They played tons of songs, along with my favourite tracks, 'Replica', 'Cyberwaste' and 'Edgecrusher'. So yeah, that was cool too. I was stood at the back and some mean looking drunk-as-hell headbanger kept swearing at me! I had a day off college on Wednesday so I spent it at Mandy's college. On Thursday I had to go in for the morning to sort some work out. And then I felt sick so I came home, and Mandy come to my house and ended up staying because she missed the last bus home because of some stupid diversion going on at the moment. So I took her to the bus stop this morning and got me some job applications while I was out. And then I got home, and wrote all of this above!
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       And now, an update on Mandy! Been having some nice times with her lately, just lying on her bed doing nothing. I dunno why but with her that becomes fun. Also, we are almost 6 months in. That's half a year! Impressive. With every single other girl, I became bored after 3 or 4 months but with Mandy, I still get excited when I know I'm gonna see her and still love just spending time with her. I know I don't always show it and most of the time I am a moody bastard, but this is the truth =)
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok, just an short update. I remembered some stuff about Thursday night! It's all stupid facts but, oh well. Gav also told me some stuff. Apparently, the following happened:
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well that was confusing. I went to Jilly's with Gav and the night was really cool. We arm-wrestled and put lit cigarettes at the side so the loser's hand got burned. And yes, to my shame, I lost. I gots a big yellow blister on there now, hahahaha! Anyway, I must of been pretty drunk because I woke up in the airport on my own. How the fuck did I get there? I woke up in a chair but I really can't remember getting there. I remember everything upto arriving at the bus stop. And then there's a few hours of nothing in my mind. And then I woke up at the airport. Maybe I took the wrong bus or something. I need some fucking answers. 
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Went to see Chimaira for the third time last night! Also playing were Shadows Fall, God Forbid and Killswitch Engage! It was a really cool show. But I still think the show in February was a lot better. Anyway I can't really be bothered with this, just wanted to write about the concert before I forgot.
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well what an amazing 4 days! Very tiring though. And I have sunburn! We left really early on Friday morning and got there for about 2pm. We just drunk all day and met up with my friends. The atmosphere was really good most of the time. I saw so many of my favourite bands... about 15 or something. In total I saw Arch Enemy, Breed 77, Cradle of Filth, DamagePlan, Dillinger Escape Plan, Ill Nino, Linkin Park, Machine Head, Metallica, Monster Magnet, Opeth, Slayer, Slipknot, Soulfly, Sum 41 and The Distillers. How many good bands is that?! Arch Enemy were incredible, it was pretty damn violent though. Some guy jumped about 20 foot into the crowd, but nobody caught him! Shame. Breed 77 were good as always. Cradle of Filth's stage presence was amazing. They had these women on stage doing some weird tricks/dancing on a rope! Quite amazing. DamagePlan... oh my GOD. Incredible. Quite possibly my favourite performance. They played 'Walk' by Pantera at the end of the set. I was secretly hoping they would play a Pantera song all along. Dillinger weren't bad... very good opener. Ill Nino... nothing new. Seen them guys twice before and the show at Download was just the same except the sound equiptment was really bad. Linkin Park were actually really good too. Chester looks pretty evil in real life. They played very well and really interacted with the crowd... I enjoyed it. I didn't see much of Machine Head... I saw them play 'Imperium' and I left. I have seen them before so I didn't really miss anything new. Metallica were excellent. They played their whole set with Joey Jordison of Slipknot and Dave Lombardo of Slayer because something happened to Lars. I am actually glad. How many people can say they watched Metallica play a set with members of Slipknot and Slayer?! It made it so much more memorable! Sadly, they didn't play 'Master of Puppets', 'One' or 'Welcome Home' (some of my favourite tracks) because their set got cut short because they had to decide on a drummer from Machine Head, Slayer, Life of Agony, Hatebreed and Slipknot. They took their time choosing! Monster Magnet were... weird. Completely not my thing in the slightest. Opeth were pretty good. Not heard much about them but a lot of people say they're good. They have good contrast of heavy and mellow with a blend of folk. Slayer were really good, they sliced through their set flawlessly! Kerry King is a demon, I swear to GOD! They had to play in a tent though, 'cause they turned up about 3 hours late. Slipknot were amazing... my favourite performance. They played a mixture of songs from 'Slipknot', 'Iowa' and the new album, 'Vol 3: The Subliminal Verses'. They are so insane... constantly running around the stage and headbanging. Incredible. Soulfly were really good too but I was really tired and in pain due to over-the-top sunburn. They played 'Roots... Bloody Roots' which was incredible! So energetic. Sum 41 were actually very good too. I'm one of the only people who think their riffs are really good. They played Metallica's 'Master of Puppets' and a R.A.T.M. song. I watched The Distillers from really far back and watched them purely out of boredom - nothing else. The whole weekend was just a constant flow of alcohol and live performances. Amazing. I actually forgot a duvet and a pillow so I had to sleep on a crappy little mat thing clothed! Mandy got a duvet the next day but it was so crap. It was really thin and really fluffy. I woke up covered in fluff. But every night Chris and I went on 'treasure hunts' and found so much alcohol! On Friday night I found about 5 cans of lager! On Saturday night I found only 2 and found none on the Sunday night but made up for it on the Monday morning. I woke up at about 8.00am and went for a walk and found 12 cans of Carlsberg, and next to that, an UNOPENED 24-can crate of lager! So I kind of took it home. How amazing is that? I come home with more beer than I went with! And I drank all of the cans I took! That's pretty damn impressive. We also found some fold up chairs, a throw-away BBQ, some Mini Cheddars and some other random crap. I got home at about 11.30pm that day. I had to spend 7 hours at a bus station and I was so knackered. I actually fell asleep on a bench! Anyway, I am done babbling about Download now. I had an amazing weekend! Roll on next year!
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Howdy. What's new? Well, Mandy and I went to her 'place in Sale' yesterday. I planned to go alone 'cause Mandy and I had a little fall-out but she decided to come along. We were both in a kind-of-stubborn quiet mood with each other for a while. But she just grabbed my hand and then everything was fine. It's such a nice place. I love it there. It makes me feel really small and makes me forget most of my problems. The only thing I don't like is the walk there because you have to pass a sewage place and it's well smelleh! Mandy was running around photographing stuff. I tried to act like I wasn't bothered but secretly, I found it incredibly cute. She went berry picking (for ages, might I add!). She got looooaaaadddds! Her mum made some kind of jelly with them. Then we went to Jilly's and it was nice, at first. Alcohol really boosts how strong my emotions are. I found myself just staring at Mandy and thinking how lucky I am to have her because I know she isn't happy with me a lot of the time, and I just find it amazing that she puts up with it. And while I was doing this, I started crying. I couldn't help it. I love her so much. I didn't tell Mandy why I was crying because she wouldn't have believed me - she would have said it was the alcohol talking or something. But from then on, I was in tears for practically the rest of the night. Once it started, I couldn't stop. Kinda silly now that I think back. After tearfully walking the streets, we got on a bus to my house. I felt really stupid and guilty for the way I had acted. But I think/hope she forgives me. I have been extra loving today because I want her to know how much she means to me. And I plan to be from now on. It isn't hard and it makes us both feel a lot better. But I can be extremely stubborn, as can Mandy. So that's why a lot of things don't get resolved for ages. Anyway, moving on. Mandy give me some really cool wireless headphone the other night. I only just got a cable I needed to work them today so I have had them on all day. It's great! I can listen to my music while I'm crapping! Yayyy! I just upload my 3000+ MP3's onto Winamp and put it on random. Niiiicceeee. My camera dock should be arriving tomorrow. That means I can use my camera more often because I won't have to keep buying batteries (the dock charges the batteries). I wanna go back to the place Mandy and I went to yesterday because I saw some things I'd love to snap. So, if my dock arrives, they will be uploaded onto my Flickr account ( urlLink www.flickr.com/photos/slow_chemical ) by Sunday night. I also added a forum onto my website ( urlLink www.blindedbyfear.esmartguy.com ) so I'd appreciate it if some of you guys could take a few minutes to register and post in the forum. It is generally a dumb-ass chat room type thingy. Check it out =) That's all I have to write about this evening. Night.
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Last night was so cool. Buffon came round at about 1am to talk to me about relationship problems. He brough some beer and some really gorgeous alcopop thingy. Mmm. And snacks. We consumed them and went for a walk around my town. Then we raced around my road on his bike. We had to turn right from my drive, past the shops, into Austell Road and then turn right back into my drive. I done it in 1.38 and he done it in 1.48. Then we saw a milk-float. Then I went to bed. Then I woke up and did some art-work. Then I wrote this. Then I clicked submit.
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Testing, testing... 1, 2, 3... hey. Made a few changes on my site. I changed the layout completely on the main page, and I also added a bunch of images. That's all for now. I'm gonna add a page tomorrow about Mandy's alter-ego, 'Monster Mandy'. Should be pretty fun. I've been playing pool on Yahoo! quite a lot lately. I don't really have much else to do with my time other than play guitar. Which reminds me - I learned some new songs. I learned a few Tenacious D songs and some Shadows Fall stuff. I am really into Shadows Fall lately. They sound like they are really heavily influenced by Pink Floyd. They have some really beautiful acoustic tracks. Kind of a big contrast when you compare them to their 'known-for' stuff! Well I better go. In a bitsiz.
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well hello. Last few days have been pretty crap 'cause Mandy hasn't been here. But I am going round in the morning, so it should be nice! I spent all of yesterday and today building a website -  urlLink www.blindedbyfear.esmartguy.com . It's my first proper site and I'm pretty proud of it, even though it's nothing special. I also took some more photo's of random crap around and about my house to put on my Flickr account. I think my photography is going pretty smoothly too. I'm no expert, but I'm happy with it. Anyway, I dunno what else I can write, so go check out my site and leave a comment =)
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well howdy. Mandy stayed again a few nights this week. It was so nice! I just download music by tons of bands on Earache, like Decapitated, Morbid Angel, blablabla, whatever. Most of it is too heavy for my liking! I also made an image hosting site at  urlLink www.flickr.com  - check it out at  urlLink www.flickr.com/photos/slow_chemical  =)
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Had the worst ever dream last night =( I dreamt that Mandy had died! It was so horrible.
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well today was really nice =) Mandy came round at about 10.00am and woke my lazy ass up! We wrote me a CV out and printed about 20 copies. It was pretty blank because I couldn't think of good qualities about me! Then we went to town and gave them out everywhere. I'm really determined to get a job now, I really need some pences in my bank account. I've managed to save £80 up to now for an upcoming festival but a job really would help out. I tried Music Zone, H&M, Littlewoods, Schuh and some other places but I can't really remember them. I am just waiting for some replies now =) and they better start coming! I'm just thinking of something to write to waste 20 minutes, 'cause that's when Mandy finishes work and I can call her. I've missed her a lot today because we had a really nice, argument-free day and I didn't want it to end. But she's coming over tomorrow night so it's gonna be good. 72 hours of Mandyness =D aww yeahhhh mattteeeeeee! Well, I am thinking it's babble time! I am really into the following bands right now - The Agony Scene, Sworn Enemy (they're a bit like a not-as-hardcore Hatebreed in my opinion), As I Lay Dying, Cannae, Bleeding Through... and some other bands that fail to come to mind. Why didn't I discover this genre sooner? It's got everything I like in music - fast, powerful riffs with plenty of pinch harmonics and palm muting, speedy drums and screaming vocals that put plenty of others to shame. That's exactly what The Agony Scene, Cannae and As I Lay Dying sound like. Sworn Enemy aren't as fast, and there riffs are a lot more simple, but it still sounds damn good. Bleeding Through are pretty similar to Cannae but they are a lot darker. What's the time? 10.48. Dammit! All of that only took me 8 minutes. Hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm. Huhuhuhuhuh! I wanna job. Well no, I want money. I might mug Bill Gates and steal his wallet, huhuhuhuhuh. I got a goofy laugh apparently. NICE! Oh fuck this, I really cannot be bothered!
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Wait, I need a pee! Ok, hey. Not much to write about really. But it's Sunday night and I normally write in here on a Sunday night. I'm gonna apologise now for any poor grammer on here, but I'm on my dads computer and his keyboard is funny, and I'm also still feeling slightly odd. I downloaded a really cool program that you type into, and then the computer says what you typed! But you get tons of voices like robots and hyper women, and you also get Spanish. Went for a meal on Saturday and it truly was king sized. I had me some nice baby-back ribs. Huge! And chips and salad. And a massive desert, consisting of ice cream, caramel, strawberries, cream and marshmallows. Quite nice but sickening at the same time. I went to Mandy's today too. It was nice, as usual. I like spending time with her. EDIT - PS. It's kind of ironic that I apologise for any grammar mistakes, and the only mistake I make in the whole thing is the mispelling of 'grammar'!
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Howdy =) This week has been fairly nice. Mandy stayed a few nights again. She come over after having a huge fallout with her mum. She brought loads of food so we had feasts. We went to town on the Wednesday and Mandy decided to buy me some hair dye out of the blue, so yeah, I dyed my hair other night, hoping it would turn out the usual colour it does (which is a nice shade of red) but it actually came out purple this time, but sometimes it looks black. I don't really like it. We also saw Shrek 2. It's so damn funny. I won't write about any of it incase you haven't seen it yet, but I do reccomend it =) Also, Mandy got some new shoes. Again. What is with Mandy and shoes? If she sees shoes that are under £20, she'll have them. She has about 5 pairs that all look so similar. But I must admit, the design on the bottom of Wednesday's pair was funkeh. Makes her happy so I won't complain anymore! Hmmm, I got a really bad headache earlier. I've been having a lot of them lately. I dunno why but I ain't liking them! Oh yeah, my birdy died today =( after 26 months of being owned by me! Ah well. I don't think I'll get another, because they're loud bastards and they shit all over your room. But... I dunno, I might. If I get a super young one, I could teach it to talk! Who knows? Well it's 4.20am right now and I've spent the night doing lots of downloading. Sad, I know. But me likes music! My mum just come in and she is hammered. She's been at her bosses place... hmmmm...
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Last night was kinda weird. I felt rotten all day, so I decided to have a really hot bath (with bubbles - they are so relaxing) at about midnight. Well I think I must of fell asleep because the next thing I knew, it was 2.00am and the water was really cold. I got out and I felt so weird. I couldn't think straight at all. I felt too weird to dry myself, so I got into bed soaking. Then I woke up at about 5am and it was really bright outside. I couldn't hear a thing either. Since then, I woke up every 20 minutes in some kind of panic. It's really strange, I don't know what's happening to me. I have a really sore throat but I don't think that has anything to do with it. I also keep getting hot and cold flushes. When I move around, it feels like my brain is rattling around in my head. It's quite painful.
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       That eye infection has come and gone. It was a horrible experience. The last week was so nice! Mandy come over on Tuesday and stayed here until Friday night! The whole time was just really natural and felt right. You know how you are in the first few days of a relationship with someone you really like? Well, things are like that after 6 months. I still feel the same way. I'm not bored at all! But she's got a new job in a pub and that'd kinda annoyed me. I just don't fancy the idea of her being around a load of drunk guys on a Saturday night... but oh well. I had a pretty funny conversation with her earlier. I was like, 'Yeah, I'd still love you even if you had no arms and legs and you was just a stump with a head', and I was going on about all the fun things I could do, like throw her onto a bouncy castle with a load of kids jumpin' on it - she'd be fucked! Hahaha. Sorry. God I'm an idiot. Been listening to some new stuff this week - Cannae, Dillinger Escape Plan, Bleeding Through, Sworn Enemy, From Autumn To Ashes, Atreyu, As I Lay Dying... and some others. I'm hungry.
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       God, the doctors are such pricks! I have been ringing all day, trying to make an appointment because my eye is really sore, and all day they have been saying they are all booked up. I called at 6.00pm (that's what time the chemist shuts) and they said they have room for me. Well how helpful. I went in and he started poking my eye, saying he 'wanted to get some gunk out of swollen bit'! PRICK! As if it doesn't take the piss enough that I have to go through a whole night of agony before I can pick up my prescription! Ah sorry. I can only see out of one eye right now. The vision in my right eye is completely blurry. All day I have just wanted to fall asleep in Mandy's arms.
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Oh my Goddddd, my eye! I got a fly in my right eye the other day and ever since then my eyelid has been swelling and swelling. It's so huge right now and it's so uncomfortable. I can't stand it. Hopefully I'll be at the doctors this afternoon. My dad knows a guy who works in a graphics studio and he gave him a call earlier and asked if they have any vacancies (for me), so yeah... I could be getting a job there, so fingers crossed. Anyway, I'm gonna go sleep.
</post>

<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Got to see Mandy today! Woke up at about 1.00 and realised I had another day of doing nothing ahead of me, just like every Saturday. I had some breakfast and started browsing the net. I text Mandy, saying I wanted to see her and stuff, and she rang me and asked if I wanted to go over when she finished work. Obviously, I did. She was working until 4.00 so I got the bus to there and waited for her to come out. Then we got the bus to her house. There was no one in so we got to slob on her sofa which was pretty nice. We had some food and watched the TV for a while. I looked in her fridge and thought I saw coleslaw, so I made the noise you make when you see something you love, only to realise it wasn't coleslaw. Then I saw something else and made the same noise, and again... it wasn't coleslaw. Damn my eyes. But then I did find some coleslaw! Yemateeee go me mate! I had to leave because she had to go to her dads. GOD I HATE HIM. Anyway, as we were waiting for my bus, I threw her shoe into someone's garden 'cause she threw my hat into a tree! I found that quite funny but she didn't, and because my bus arrived, we had to leave each other on a bad note. I hope she isn't too mad at me still. Anyway, I better go. I dunno why, because there's nothing to do. But still...
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm really bored right now so I thought I'd write in here. I haven't done much today apart from browsing various 'humour' sites. I've just been sitting around missing Mandy. I don't miss anyone else in the slightest (well, maybe my family). It sounds selfish and possessive but I just want to be around her all the time. I love seeing her arrive and I hate seeing her leave. I'm so glad I have found her! I just know she deserves better and I want her to be blissfully happy...
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Arghhh, I'm running out of entry names! Anyway, I have to write about last night while I'm semi-refreshed. Well, it was fucking ace! It was like a reunion because so many of my friends came! There was Scott, Buffon, Daniel and his girlfriend, John, Amy, Chris and his girlfriend, Gav, Kyle, Becky, and not forgetting my angel, Mandy! There were the usual faces too... Jenny, Ellin and Ashley. It was so damn cool. After the whole thing, Mandy came back to my house and we went to sleep. Aw, she looks so lovely when she's peaceful. I love just holding her and knowing she's right there, 'cause sometimes I'll think 'aw I really want a hug so bad' and then I'll realise she's right there! It's great! Last night, I actually bought my own drinks and my own food for once. Kinda shocking? Anyway, I just took her to the bus stop 'cause she's going to college to finish some work, and then, she's gonna come see moi! I know you're gonna read this when you get to college Mandy, so, I love you lots and I'm thinking about you 24/7. Hope you're okay! Scott was overly generous and bought everyone a pint and later on in the night bought some of us shots of vodka, which made me vomit all over the floor! Yemateeee. He's a cool guy though. Haven't seen him since high school and he hasn't really changed, which I'm glad of. Buffon dissappeared in the middle of the night (as usual). I dunno where he went but I remember getting a message off of him saying he was outside and he was gonna wait at the door... which confused me. Ah well. Daniel is still exactly the same as last time, except now a little more respectful towards people which is pretty good. He's still really funny and charasmatic. Can't really say much about John as I've only met him a few times but he's very funny but something about him intimidates me. Can't really say anything about Amy either because she's one of them people you don't really get to talk to because they know practically everybody. Chris... well I'm glad he was there, he always makes me laugh. But I think alcohol alters his sexuality as everytime Mandy introduced me to somebody, he would be hugging me, feeling me up... etc. Not so nice. Kicked his ass at pool by default! Well, he potted the black and the white so I won and played Daniel, and lost. Shame mate. We went into the girls toilets with Mandy and her friends and it was pretty cool. Their toilets are so much nicer, they have blue glowy light things, and we don't! Some girl told me I looked like 'a girl who looks like a dyke who looks like a guy'. I actually took it as a compliment. Chris' girlfriend Nicola still seemed the shy little thing she is. Had a little chat with her about my vodka incident and she tried offering me hers... I think I put her off, hahaha. She helped me steal some really cool skeleton glasses though. Gav was being the usual loud-ass, drunk-ass 'anarchist' that he is with his 'sex grooves' and screaming on the dance floor, especially when they played Sex Pistols. He stood on some fat shits foot and she's like, 'Ouchhh my foot, watch it shithead!' and I said, 'How the fuck can you miss that fat-ass foot?' Ughhh it was so rank! He's kinda predictable. He chatted some women up on the way home and he actually got their numbers, somehow. Kyle is an old friend, from when I was with Donna. Donna used to live in Bristol and she had a friend there called Claire, who was with Kyle. Kyle wanted to go and visit her but not alone so he invited me. Ahh that was a cool weekend too. It was cool bumping into him though... don't talk to him much these days. Becky is also a kind of old (ish) friend. Chris met her a few years ago on a bus and he introduced me to her at a concert last year. Ever since then I regularly bump into her and have a chat or whatever. Well last night, it was her birthday so she was pretty happy which was pretty good! Jenny's hair is different everytime I see it. This time it was her actual hair (no extensions) AND it was all one colour! Didn't get to talk to her 'cause she got dragged away... ah well. Ellin was very talkative last night. She told me all about God Forbid on their recent UK tour (she was lucky enough to join them). Apparently she gets majorly insulted on the Chimaira message board so I think I'm gonna go there and say a few words myself against them. Ashley... she actually annoyed me last night. She is completely overly loud when she gets drunk, to the point of complete irritation. But ah well, she looked happy and she was smiling, so I'm not too bothered. If only I took a damn camera...
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm feeling kinda low today. I dunno why. It's been ever since my dad had a go at me last night for shouting at my little brother. I don't really think it's that that is causing me to feel like this, I just think it triggered something. Even my friends from college noticed I wasn't myself today and they are some of the most unobservant people I know. Ah well. Hopefully it's just a phase. Mandy's coming over later in some new 'gear'. She's gonna look so lovely. I can't wait to just hold her. I've been missing her a lot today. I've been thinking about this relationship and how we are with each other. Most of the time it's really nice but when it's bad, it's really bad. But I love her and nothing will change that =)
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should be used to the fact that Mandy doesn't contact me at all when she's out. It's kind of selfish. She knows I have no way of contacting her except through SMS, which I send free from a website! And still, she doesn't even bother to reply... 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from the meal. Argh, never been so full. I had the same thing I had last time I went there, plus a full English breakfast and some ice cream. I hate being that full, it's horrible!  There was a fire in the avenue next to ours near where Chris' grandad lives... and I thought it  was  Chris' grandad... but luckily it wasn't. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Where to start. Lalala. Mandy come over last night and we went to Rockworld with my friend Chris. It was so cool. I love when Chris comes out too 'cause he makes me laugh so much. We played lots of pool and I discovered that I love malibu and coke! Mmmmmm yes! The bus ride home sucked 'cause it broke down for about half an hour and we were just sat there freezing our asses off. We got home really late... about an hour later than usual or something. But anyway.  After making Mandy some breakfast, I decided that I don't have the patience to look after tropical fish, so I bought 12 goldfish! They look soooo damn amazing, love 'em! Anyway I'm gonna go 'cause I'm going out for ma din-din's today! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right now I feel really meaningless... vacant... empty. And I don't really know why. It has just overcome me tonight out of nowhere. People use these things to get their feelings down but I don't know what the hell to write about. So I'll write about the last 24 hours.  Mandy came over last night and we had a nice night. Today we just lay in bed all day doing nothing. There was another amazing storm again today. There has been loads lately for some reason, but I'm not complaining. I took a few pictures but I'm not really impressed with them. I need to set another date to venture off somewhere again with my camera, because my garden and my house are getting boring...  I must admit, the arguing has stopped with Mandy and I... but how long for? I think that's what I find scary... not knowing if it will go back to how it used to. But I only really have two choices...  1. End it and be miserable... 2. Stay with her and hope things won't turn bad but be scared in the meantime...  I got a text message earlier and grabbed my phone from Mandy's hand to read it. Seems stupid I know, but I just wanted to read it. I should've thought. It gave her suspicions. Well anyway, I told Mandy I have strong doubts about us still and that maybe being with her isn't such a good idea, but I soon changed my mind. We spent the whole time at the bus-stop hugging, but for some reason I felt kinda uncomfortable.  I don't know what's wrong with me. It isn't anything that Mandy has done... it's me. I wish I could read the signals my brain is trying to send me. Hopefully this is just a phase and it will be gone by tomorrow morning.  Sorry if this post seems retarded and stuff but I really don't care right now. Mandy just hung up on me without realising I was upset (immediately thinking I was angry - but I suppose my own human nature has brought that on)... 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh, I ate way too many cornflakes. I filled a fat-ass cake bowl full of corn flakes and icey cold milk (mmmm) and I didn't even get halfway through. Things are always harder than they seem with me. I still want to eat them but I fear they will start pouring from my nose.  So today, I 'started' to redecorate my room. I've done next to nothing. I grabbed some tile grout and started filling in all of the massive holes in my wall. I plan to put up some plan white wallpaper and to paint it whatever colour I choose. I also wanna do something with my floor... either varnish the floorboards underneath my carpet or try to find a new one which I actually like (as the one I have now is appauling)... 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy. Me again. The bathroom is nearly finished (incase I didn't say before, it's being completely restyled right now). All of the tiles have been put up, and my dad is halfway through putting up the new ceiling. Still a lot to do though, I'll help in any way possible.  I think I have a new favourite band in Fear Factory, but I'm not sure. They have a lot more music out than Chimaira so it gives me a little more to explore, but a lot of Fear Factory's stuff sounds the same... but it's such an amazing sound. I'm just scared that I'll grow bored of it, because I now own 5 of their albums.  Anyways - went to Mandy's yesterday. As soon as I got there we both fell asleep and we were just lay there for about 4 hours listening to the same song over and over. Was nice =) and time really flew. Before we knew it Mandy had to go to work. So I went to the bus stop and she went into work. As I was waiting for my bus she sent me a nice text message so I started walking back to her work. I stayed there with her for her 5 hour shift, but halfway through I went to her house to shower. I had lots'a beer and watched the 'Top Rock Goddesses' on Scuzz when her brother come home. I felt like such a tit and left.  I stayed over at Mandy's that night. I hate it when there's no one but her brother in because we have to be really quiet all night. You can't even say anything (which was kinda unfortunate because I spoke a lot in my sleep last night)...  Anyway, she come here for a while today to read these entries and set up her own Flickr account. I'm happy we're back together but I still have really strong doubts. I don't know how long it will take before I am how I was. But I'm prepeared to wait... 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't slept in such a long time. Right now, I haven't slept in exactly 59 hours, besides a short 2 hour nap. I stayed up all last night and my friend Adam (aka Buffon) came over at about 2.00am. We kept ourselves amused by playing low-budget online games and watching videos of skateboarding bails. Time soon passed and we finally got to 4.30am. We left for Styal Country Park with camera in hand. I took tons of pictures and I'm really proud of them all. View them at  urlLink www.flickr.com/photos/slow_chemical . It was a bit of a hard thing to do to stay awake all night just to make sure you leave the house on time.  I was exhausted by the time we left, which was at about 9.00am. I still am! And all day it has felt like we are 5 hours ahead of time. We got home at around 10.00am and barely had time to have a bit of a rest because I had to go out again. Adam and I had been invited to go to Laser Quest! It's so cool. Incase you don't know what it is, it's like a real-life Unreal Tournament, but with lasers. Everyone gets a target-pack attached to them and a laser gun. The aim is to run around the terrain, avoiding shots from other players, and to shoot as many people as you can. We had two twenty minute sessions. The first time I didn't have a clue what was going on, and I barely shot anyone because I didn't know we weren't playing in teams! So I only come 15th out of 18 players that time. But I learned from my mistake the second time around, shifting my score output to 3rd! Buffon and I worked together a lot in kicking mucho asso. It was so cool, I really enjoyed it!  Then I went to meet Mandy in town. I didn't know if this was a good idea or not at first. Things seemed really weird between us. But in the end, I ended up giving in to her and giving it one more final chance. And I do mean it when I say final chance. It's not that I don't want it, because I do. It's just that I'm still unsure if it will work. But it's down to Mandy to prove if it will or not. Anyway... she was being extremely loving! And I was being extremely dopey because I was, and am, knackered. I am still half-expecting that things will change back to how they used to be, and it's scary. But still, it's amazing now like it always should be, so I'm gonna enjoy it while I can.  Whilst in town, I went into Music Zone to buy a Fear Factory CD. I had to choose out of 2 CD's, so I asked Mandy her opinion. And what an opinion. She ended up offering to pay for the CD I didn't choose which was really nice of her! But she's a sneaky one. I was queing behind her to pay for the other CD, when she grabbed it from my hand and payed for that one too! So she payed for both of the CD's I wanted! I told her not to, constantly! But she wouldn't listen. How nice of her! So with the money I was planning to use on a CD, I wanted to buy Mandy something with instead, but still she refused. So I bought a DVD instead - Donnie Darko. I have heard lots of good things about this movie so I will watch it sometime soon.  Anyway. I am exhausted. I can guarentee I will be asleep within one minutes time. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I just tried to pierce the cartilage in my right ear. OUCH. I got it through my ear but it's simply not worth that much pain. I'll get it done professionally. So instead, I repierced my lip! Looks pretty cool even if I do say so myself.  Right now, I am waiting until around 5.00am (which gives me 4 hours and 40 minutes) because I'm going out to a huge nature park type place called Styal with Buffon. The reason for it? I wanna take some really amazing photographs. They have so much cool stuff there, like waterfalls and really cool scenery. So I can't wait to get going, even though it's a 40 minute walk or something.  You'll have to excuse me if there are any grammar mistakes in here, I only got 2 hours sleep last night and it looks like I won't get any tonight. Which gives me an idea. Starting Monday, I am not going to sleep for a whole week, and I'm gonna write a report on it every night in here to see what kinda stuff happens to my mind. I remember when I went 3 days without sleep and I started hallucinating. So yeah, 7 days will be pretty freaky. Anyway, I'm gonna go and think of something to do for the next 5 hours... 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So my camera dock arrived yesterday. I charged my camera up and went out at 6.00am to take some pictures. I think there was a fault or something though because most of my images turned out blurry and the batteries kept draining really fast (which is unusual). So I got home and tried charging it but it wouldn't. So I went to sleep and when I woke up and installed an upgrade into the camera. Now everything seems to be working just fine. None of them turn out blurry anymore. So tomorrow morning at 4.00am I am going to a massive park with rivers and waterfalls and everything, so I should have some fairly exciting shots this time tomorrow. Hopefully the weather will be nice... 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a post to say I have relocated my website. The new site is located here  www.freewebs.com/the_vicious_cycle  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So. Some guy just gave me some advice about a very similar situation he had with his ex. He said they broke up in the end and he kept a pointless grudge against her. He told me that he regrets doing that now because he realised he was only happy when he was around her. So that's my argument to get back with Amanda once again. But there are so many reasons to not get back with her... 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       AAAAARRRRGGGGGHHHHHHH!!!  WHY does she do this?! She called me up last night and started telling me that she can make it work and that she really wants it to. She told me she was going to try her hardest not to let it go wrong. But the thing is... I don't know if I want to anymore. This always happens. We break up and I begin to get used to the idea. And then she calls me up saying she has changed her mind. And I usually go running back, no matter how she treats me.  So I am spotting a pattern here. I need to ask myself... will it go back to how it does every single time we try to make it work? Well it has every other time. Why shouldn't it now? Talk about a 'vicious cycle'! But anyway...  Mandy is trying her hardest to change my mind. She called me up in tears, telling me that she has thrown away 'the best thing in her life', and she wouldn't let me hang up. I really do just wish we can both be happy. But I know I won't if I get with her and I know she won't if we stay apart. So I guess this comes down to who's happiness is most important to me.  Right now, I can honestly say that I am used to the idea of not being with Mandy. It hurts, a lot, but I'm used to it. And I'm actually starting to look forward. I just hope that one day she will be happy again.  I often wish that Mandy never met me because I have done nothing for her at all (except bring her down time after time). She really does deserve someone so much better... someone who can make her happy.  There is still chance for us. But not yet. I want time on my own. To think about it. And to be sure that Mandy will be a little more grown-up about the trust and the stubborness. And I don't want her to wait for me either, just incase I don't want to be with her in the future. Then I will feel really guilty.  I won't feel any emotions that I shouldn't feel for doing what I need to do, such as guilt or regret. So this is what is happening. I am spending some time on my own (maybe a month or two) to think about what I need in life as a teenager. If after this time I realise that I do need her, then I will give it a chance. But like I said, I don't want her to wait for me... just in case...  I still love you Mandy and I'm sorry for the way things turned out. Hopefully you will get to read this... 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I ain't never coming home.   I'll just wander my own road.   I can't meet you here tomorrow.   Say goodbye. Don't follow.   Misery so hollow.      Hey you, you're livin' life full throttle.   Hey you, pass me down that bottle.   Hey you, you can't shake me around now.   I get so lost and don't know how.   It hurts to care. I'm going down.      Forgot my woman, lost my friends.   Things I've done and where I've been.   Sleep in sweat - the mirror's cold.   See my face - it's growin' old.   Scared to death - no reason why.   Do whatever to get me by.   Think about the things I said.   Read the page - it's cold and dead.      Take me home...  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Fucking HELL!  I have had enough of this. Why does Mandy  ALWAYS  get with me and then end it straight after?! Well - here's what happened. I called her up and asked where she was going tomorrow with one of her friends (who I happen to despise). Apparently, this is 'starting an argument'. All I did was ask where she was going. I mean... yeah, I have a hard time trying to handle the fact that she is gonna be spending the day with a guy who is a complete twat to his girlfriends (this guy happens to like Amanda), but what guy wouldn't be the same about his girlfriend? It's just human nature to be a bit paranoid and cautious. Well anyway - this raised a whole conversation about trust and how she doesn't trust me and how she never can. I don't see how. I'm not the one meeting girls and going to the cinema with them,  alone!  She claimed that I don't trust her for not knowing what would happen with them both tomorrow. I am right to have slight doubts. It just seems weird that she plans to meet this guy when we break up.  Anyway, I just wish she thought about all of this before asking me back in the nicest way ever last night. It seems she repeatedly puts me through hell. But it isn't as bad as it was last time. I went through all the pain I could possibly bare the last time she did this to me. I'm not gonna moap around this time or chase after her. It's over.   For good.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mandy and I are officially back together! Last night was such a surprise. I went over at about midnight and she was stood there in a really nice long black dress and there were candles all over the place. They led up the stairs and into her bedroom. In there she had glasses of wine* awaiting us and rose petals* scattered around her room. It was a really nice atmosphere. And then she asked to get back together. I was a bit unsure and cautious at first but then I realised it would be too hard to say no.  * when I say wine, I mean Smirnoff Ice! * the fact that the rose petals were fake didn't matter to me!  Anyways, today I went on a sunbed. It wasn't great but wasn't bad. The whole experience was very greasy. I went on for just 6 minutes but by the end I was dripping in sweat and had a tingling sensation all over my body. Overall, I don't think it made much difference but I'm thinking about making it a regular thing... 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       There's a darkening sky before me. There's no time to prepare.   Salvage va last horizon. But no regrets from me.      Maybe I'll be back some other day to live again, just who can say?   In what shape or form that I might be, just another chance for me.      A hurried time - no disgrace. Instead of racing to conclusion   and wishing all my life away. No one can stop me now.      Time is up - it couldn't last, but there's more things I'd like to do.   I'm coming back to try again. Someday, maybe I'll wait 'til then.       Iron Maiden - No More Lies    God I love them lyrics. They seem really relevant, too. 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy. Things are still weird with Mandy and I. We still see each other daily but the arguing is starting to come back, even though I have tried not to let it. It's so confusing. But anyway, we went for a meal on Sunday and it was really nice. I had some chicken-bacon-cheese thing! Yemate!  I have also finally set up my tank. It looks really nice but half of the equiptment doesn't work. So I'm gonna have to get replacements.  I had a job interview. It was only my second ever and it was really nerve-wracking. But luckily the woman who interviewed me was really kind, and she kept writing down answers to questions I didn't know! Hopefully I'll have a job by weekend... 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm really confused. It's been two or three days since Mandy and I split, but since then, she has been nicer to me than ever. We have just been in really nice moods with each other 24/7 (for a change). The stubborness that was constantly there has dissapeared and when we get to the typical point where we are on the verge of falling out, we don't. It just seems to fade.  I really want to be with her still and I really do want to be able to say I can make it work. But I have tried in the past and it didn't get me very far. I just don't know why all the petty arguments stop as soon as we split. Mandy and I are still madly in love and it's too hard to just let go of this, even if it does make us both unhappy a lot of the time, because the times we have that aren't bad are fucking amazing. And I'm still not giving up on this. She's still my angel.   Always will be.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh yeah, I saw Sarah-Louise from Corrie yesterday! She looks so much older in person! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy. Things have been a lot better today. Mandy and I know that we love each other like crazy, so we're going to stay in touch and still be loving towards each other and then one day, when the time is right... we will give it another go. She has been so lovely the past 24 hours and I'm not really sure why. She calls me all the time, saying that she misses me... it's really nice. Maybe it was a mistake breaking up with her. We will see.  I got my aquarium stuff the other day. I'm gonna tidy my room up tomorrow and then I'm gonna set the tank up. Hopefully, it will be running smoothly by Sunday, and I can go to the aquarium and get some tropical fish!  I just got back from a meal. It was my friends birthday, Laura. She invited me and some more of her friends along. It was kinda nice, but to be honest, Mandy was in my heart all night. I couldn't think of anything else. Plus, Laura was really down most of the night. I think it was her dad that caused it. He really is a twat. He had a go at me for speaking on the phone. He told me to go outside! What a knob-cheeeeeese. But yeah, it was a nice night really and there was another thunder storm! How cool! Better go... 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well. It's me again. I don't really feel much better to be honest. I've cried a good few times. I keep trying to convince myself that it's for the best but everytime I do, tears come out of nowhere. Right now, it feels like 10 family members have died. And there's nothing I can do about it. And there's nothing I can do without her. But I do know we are going to be good friends. She told me she wants that. And I want it too. I think I need her company just to remain slightly sane. She also told me there is a chance for us in the future. That really does give me a bit of hope. Anyway...  I just went to my half-sisters uncles aquarium (how confusing?!). It's cool there. I decided to rebuild my own fish tank, so I cleaned a massive bag of gravel this morning. It took so long. I'm gonna set it all up properly tomorrow. I'm too tired right now and I have way too much on my mind. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well that's it. It's over. I feel nothing right now but I know that when I get into my bed tonight I will start crying like a baby. I seriously don't know how I am going to be able to handle living over the next few months. I don't really see much point to be honest. I've never loved anyone so much. I'm never going to stop loving her either.  If you ever change your mind, I will be here Mandy. I will drop everything and come running. All you have to do is ask. I promise.  Last night was the best night in my life. I felt so special. I will never forget it.  Anyway - like I said, I don't feel anything right now because I haven't yet accepted it.   FUCK YOU ALL.  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This diary is pretty cool. A lot better than the old site I was on. This one looks a lot more modern. But I had to copy every single post over (about 80) and put imaginary times on them. So like, don't look at the times because they're probably way off. So yeah. The other day I decided to create a range of characters for a series of cartoons, comics etc. They're called the 'Mr. and Mrs. Something-Or-Other Pants'. Yeah, the idea does partly come from Mr. Men and Sponge-Bob Square-Pants, but mine's gonna be better. Some of the characters I have thought of so far include 'Mr. Kewly Pants', 'Mrs. Nerdy Pants', 'Mr. Horny Pants', 'Mrs. Dykey Pants' and 'Mr. Happy Pants'. I thought of so many more but I left the list at Mandys house. So this is going to rule. I'm going to actually take time to design them all, and they're all gonna have a unique pair of pants (that's the trademark)! So I'll post more info on them when I have it.  Mandy and I are having kinda... rough times lately. Mainly down to me being insensitive about her feelings. I don't deserve her in any way at all, so God knows why I still have her. But from now on I'm going to be a lot more sensitive and a lot less argumentative, less stubborn and just generally less moody. I can't lose her. I couldn't handle it. I dunno what else to type about really. So g'bye.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Howdy. Well today was an average day. Went round to Mandy's early in the morning and she was doing what she does best - slobbing! We went round to 'her place' again. I really do love it there. I went off exploring in a load of 6 foot weeds and took lots of pictures of various things, like flowers, bees, insects, trees, etc, while Mandy did some sketching. Then I did a little sketch of a really cool tree. I got home and took some more pictures in my back garden. All photos have been uploaded onto  urlLink www.flickr.com/photos/slow_chemical . Check them out please, and post comments! I'm going round to Mandy's in ther morning, EARLY. I plan on getting a bus at about 7am, if I can even get up that early! 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey there. This is my first official post on Blogspot. I just completed transfering every single one of the posts before this from another online journal site. And it was very tiring. So I'm gonna go now. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>