<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          ...me.      Hehehe...and welcome to t  he official beginning of my quarter-life crisis.       Thanks SOOOOO much all you gorgeous friends out there who throughout the day emailed, called, sms-ed, msn-ed, personally delivered their best wishes, from all corners of the globe as far as HK, Shanghai, Singapore, London, Melbourne, NY, Malaysia and of course Sydney. You guys made this wet and dreary birthday the sweetest experience and every single call/message/email/hug made me feel like the world's most special girl.       For those of you in Sydney, woohoo let's rock and roll this Friday night!! I have explicit instructions to put my party shoes on and get roaring drunk, so will one of you kindly promise to cart me home in one piece after the damage is done?      If anyone called me under an anonymous number today and got cut off - apologies &amp; kudos.      Biggest hugs  *mwah mwah*  xxoo          do re me: " Non, Je ne regrette rien" - Edith Piaf    
      
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          1 corona + 1 singapore sling + 1 glass of cabernet sauvignon + 4 shots of B52 + 1 shot of wet pussy        = NOT ENOUGH TO GET ME DRUNK.       Not even tipsy. Boo. I'll have to try harder next Friday night.      Boo #2 is having 5'2'' males grope my hips and try to get me to dance with them when I'm shaking it with my chickey babes on the dance floor. Yo shortie, yes you - get your hands OFF me and go away. Stay away. No chance even in your next life time.      But my spanking new Balenciaga lariat motorcycle bag has finally arrived *swoon* from ebay after all the hoohaa with customs and couriers - woohoo! All kinds of excited. Just in time for my birthday too, which is super as the purchase was my birthday present to myself (that almost broke the bank, but who's asking?).       The other happy purchase of the week is a satin oyster-coloured bomber jacket with hot pink trimming a la Mooks. I am SUCH a retail sap.      As an aside - nothing beats a Harry's hotdog with mustard and tomato sauce at 4am after grooving.       Nice job last night NastyInc &amp; sir3n.           do re me: " In Da Club" - Mary J. Blige, featuring P. Diddy, 50 cent, Beyonce.        
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          After my mandatory fortnightly pilgrimage at Borders &amp; Kinokuniya, I am no longer suffering from acute withdrawal symptoms. Eye candy for the month of August are as follows:       "Norwegian Wood" - Haruki Murakami       O. M. G.       Where the  frick  have I been for the last decade?? I have been such a HUGE fan of the Chinese translation of the japanese author 'Choon Sheung Chuen Shu', otherwise known as Haruki Murakami that it never even slightly  occurred  to me an English translation might also exists. Duh me. I was hooked reading just two-thirds of a paragraph whilst shifting from foot to foot in my stupid heels at Borders. Always thought that the Chinese translation was a bit stilted (double duh me), thank you there is a God.       " Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil" - John Berendt         Terrifically entertaining book of murder, mayhem and suspense. I LOVE the haunting cover photograph of the Savannah cemetery statue holding the scales in either hand. Bird Girl must be the creepiest cover girl of all time. Jack Leigh rocks.       " The Lady and the Unicorn" - Tracy Chevalier         The male and female leads are so sleazy it's delightful. Funky mixture of art, sexual tension and fifteenth-century power struggles. Can't wait to move onto 'Girl with the Pearl Earring" next.       " National Geographic" - August Edition       Did you know that the flamboyant Caribbean reef squid has over 35 patterns of 'skins' in their wardrobe, which they can change at whim depending on whether they're in the mood to mate or pick a fight, including the aggressive zebra print which translates to 'back the fxck off!!' to other male competitors? How handy. It can also split patterns, showing the female their 'come-hither' coppery side whilst flashing a warning 'silvery' opposite side to fend off rivals? Very convenient, and perhaps the next step in evolution.        " How to be a Domestic Goddess" - Nigella Lawson         I WILL learn to perfect the passionfruit, mascarpone and meringue trifle. I WILL.      Or maybe the gin and tonic jelly. Ha.         do re me: "Breathe Again" - Toni Braxton     
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            This is too interesting not to share:     urlLink  http://www.njagyouth.org/colortest.swf     Takes less than 30 seconds...try it and see just how 'in control' of your mind you are.      do re me: "Dance me to the end of love" - Leonard Cohen    
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Ooooohhh one of my favourite topics -   What is uber sexy?         Let's list:      (before anyone goes berserk I better disclaim the following blog as a purely personal tirade)      * Tall (5'11'' plus thank you) guys with strong shoulders in a white shirt, rolled up at the sleeves, open at the throat, paired with scruffy well-worn jeans that look like they survived two oil-changes and a university degree span of rave parties. With spiky hair and a wicked grin. And dying old school sneakers. And a body temperature 5 degrees above average. *enthusiastic grin* Pfffwoar!      * The creamy, milk-pale skin on the back of a girl's neck.      * That precious first-kiss moment right when your lips are an inch apart from those of the guy/girl you've been pounding the pavement for... when the air trembles, time turns syrupy sweet and your heart is thumping so hard you almost have a cardiac arrest except for the fact that you just plain refuse to die through sheer willpower before the kiss is consummated.      awwwww.....      * Orlando Bloom snowboarding down that castle wall (LOTR1) whilst firing arrows with deadly aim like a house on fire. Kills me everytime.      * C.O.N.F.I.D.E.N.C.E. Not the type that comes from owning a 360 Modena or what hangs between your legs, but in-built, natural born confidence in both men and women that leaves no place for jealousy, insecurity or self-consciousness. Confidence in who you are, what you do, who you're with, what you believe and what you represent. That 'others be damned' attitude rocks on. Go go go.      * French and mandarin. Those syllables just  rollllllll  off the tongue and caress the skin like a gentle lover's hand.        "Me reveiller a cote de toi, c'est le plus beau de tous les reves"       *sigh*      * Dancing to R&B music - the groove, the swaying hips, the pumping music, the bodies pressed together...the slow, knowing smile of your dancing partner.      * Kirsten Dunst &amp; Jake Gyllenhaal - this is probably going to sound weird but does anyone else find them strangely sexy? I haven't even seen Superman II, but Kirsten Dunst's special brand of kooky cool dress sense, cherubic apple cheeks and wispy blond hair paired with Gyllenhaal's scruffiness and solid frame really works together. Too bad they split. Pooey.      * Rumpled bed sheets on a rainy day.      * Sparkley stiletto shoes with delicate straps and a dangerous heel on well-manicured feet and well-toned bare legs.      * Traditional tiramisu. Eaten with fingers.       * That deeply concentrated look on a guy's (preferably your's) face and the faint furrow between the brows when they're 100% focused on their job, be it staring a computer, DJ-ing, or shooting a gun. All the chicks I know dig this one.      * Humour - enjoying it, spreading it, using it. It's the lubricant of life that keeps the wheels turning despite not-so-minor glitches and troughs. The ability to laugh at one's self, to shrug off setbacks and refusal to bend to God's cruel jokes. Why do you think the clowns always get the girls?      * Floaty, chiffon print sundresses in summer that twirl at the knees with ribbon straps at the shoulders. Worn commando.      * Someone singing an acoustic guitar solo, just for you.      * A huge mass of fragrant soft white flowers gathered haphazardly in a bunch and tied with a bow.      * Good posture. It's simple really - stand up straight, chin up, shoulders back, proud torso. As a shrimp I can tell you that simply by standing tall one can add inches to their height, not to mention send off waves of confidence, style and assertiveness.      * Good manners. Also simple really - please and thank you are imperative, smiling is free, waiting in queue, ladies first, get your butt off the train seat NOW for the World War II veteran. Oh, and if you're a guy here's a free tip for you - practise the habit of opening car doors for your girl until it's second nature.      * The chase.      * Audrey Hepburn...she just resonated class, talent and style through every fiber of her being. Single-handedly showed Hollywood and the rest of the world that sexiness doesn't have to come in the package of a royal surname, or a DD bra size or dresses slit up to the hipbone. Revolutionary in her day. Her gamine chic and wide eyed grin charmed the world up until and long past the day she died. Even when she grew sick and her skin was no longer taunt, she used her name to tirelessly work for Unicef and children in poverty. My heroine forever and the epitome of uber sexy.      ***********************      Stay tuned for the next blog on what's NOT uber sexy...promise I won't name names.        
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I have always wondered how some people manage to live their lives day by day with absolutely no opinion about anything.  Understandably not everyone understands the ins and outs of the current situation in Iraq, or the degree of logging in Brazil or the government's budget for the current fiscal year, but hell and damnation...if I'm asking you a simple question like 'what would you like to eat for lunch?', it shouldn't be so damn hard to get an answer.  Is it seriously possible to breeze through life with zero care factor for anything and everything? To have no opinion whatsoever on abortion, types of red wine, sporting team, brand of jeans, classical movies or the fish of the day? It must be because otherwise there wouldn't be so many dead souls out there shrugging their shoulders whenever somebody asks their opinion on something.  To me that screams mediocrity at full volume in technicolour.  Indifference is something I have little talent in tolerating. Opposing opinions are interesting, even if the inevitable result is a screeching match at the top of the lungs by the relevant parties and involves perishable objects being winged across the room. Preferable any day to a bland 'don't care' lame response.  What makes me see red around the edges of my vision and blow smoke through my nostrils are girls who DO have an opinion but who PRETEND not to have one in order to defer to their equally lame partners. When I see this I have to fight the urge to yank the pathetic offender by the end of her hair and hiss "listen sista, keep it up and you'll get dumped faster than you can say 'doormat'"!  Why oh why? Your poor mother didn't suffer through hours of labour and 9 months of looking like a bloated cow so you could pretend to be stupid.  And why are there people in this world who are so indifferent about their work that they will leave on the dot 5pm even if they haven't given you the work they promised you from a week ago, knowing full well that you have a deadline today and desperately need their work to meet it? Why don't you just give me your pay and I'll do your frigging job for you?  The really sad thing is, care factor zero people are so terrifyingly D.U.L.L. Do they put themselves to sleep just by being themselves?  ???     
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       They say there is a first time for everything.      So here is my first blog post. Shall I start by firstly introducing myself?      I am 100% Chinese, born in Hong Kong and bloody proud of it. It doesn't embarrass me to admit when I saw news footage of the half a million ppl protesting in the 1 July demonstration in Hong Kong this year I started to drip severely. And I didn't even cry as much when my 2 year relationship fell down the gutter.      But let's not go there...      I'm a teeny 5'2'', slim but not skinny, have long black hair and a signature dimple in my right cheek. More often than not my perpetual grin comes with a cheeky comment or two, so thanks to all my big guy friends who have on numerous occasions bailed me out and allowed me to hide behind them.   Being shrimp sized does has its benefits. Ppl tend to judge based on size, so by the time they realise their miscalculation it's too late and I've already chewed them up for breakfast.      Ha.      I work like a dog in an investment bank that is renowned for being a millionaire making machine. Unfortunately being so low in the corporate ladder it looks like I'm the exception to the rule. Boohoo...my dreams of becoming a cafe owner and barista look ever so far away. BUT NEVER STOP TRYING. Starbucks will eat my dust one day.      Talking about dogs, the one and only love of my life is a maltese terrier that weighs less than 2 kgs but has the ability to make me laugh, cry, release any worries, fall asleep and connect with other dog lovers. He also turned 18 this year.      I have a severe obsession over high heels, especially the strappy sexy ones. My shoe collection is notorious enough to wrangle me the 'Imelda Marcos' award last year from work. Considering that I don't do drugs, don't smoke any substance of any sort, don't speed (err...hmm...), don't mess with other ppl's boyfriends I figure one vice is allowed (excluding the ebay obsession and the addiction to prawn crackers and the messy bedroom and the chronic inability to get out of bed on time).       I am going through the quarter-life crisis at the moment. At a crossroad where I'm beginning more and more to realise what I want and becoming less and less willing to accept anything less than that. Perhaps that's why the relationship fell apart, why I want to take time off to travel, why I'm spending more time with my family and why my circle of friends is getting smaller yet more tightly knit as the 'whatevers' get weeded out.    I LOVE music, and have vastly indiscriminate and different preferences to suit different moods. R&B for grooving, spunky pop for early morning, jazz for drinking wine with friends at home. The ipod is on the wishlist for this year's birthday present *hint hint*.      Pet peeves:     Ugly clumpy shoes    Movies that try too hard to be 'arty'    Nineteen year olds who try to hit on me at clubs    People who wait for the lift right in front of it and block me from coming out    S...l....o.......w.... people at work who give me white hairs    Driving and not being able to drink    Sunday drivers    Split ends    Feminine guys who are skinnier than me    Trains that do not arrive when they are supposed to    People who are late     I am unashamedly, absolutely, positively the epitome of girliness. I would never want to be a guy, although I love their company and almost everything about them too. Being a girl is the greatest thing. Not just having flowers delivered to your house and french manicures, but the fact that it's so damn easy to get what you want most of the time. You only have to try, but maybe that goes for both genders.    I don't mind being alone and have never been one of those girls that cannot function without a boyfriend.  My detriment seems to be that when I meet a guy I really really like, for some bizarre and insanely stupid reason I try to be much tougher than I really am.  Which of course makes them slot me into the 'buddy' category and flushes my chances down the toilet *head bang bang*.  I've only just recently realised this fact, and have vowed to curb this self-defense mechanism going forward.    I also love all things bad for you except for a few.  I love coke (the soft drink), full cream caramel lattes, krispy creme, skimpy outfits in winter, convertibles in the rain, staying up late, over-spending, over-working, downloading music illegally, skipping gym class for cocktails and of course - bad boys.     God bless bank holiday. I think this pretty weather we've been having calls for late lunch at clovelly beach.       
      
</post>


</Blog>