<Blog>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm waiting here for Lindsay to come up in visit me for the week.  I haven't seen her in a couple weeks ever since I've started my job up here and she stayed back in Cincinnati.  It will be fun to have her around for the week since I've missed her so much and she makes me very happy when we are together.  Well I guess I should say she makes me happy all the time, even when we are not together.  My parents are coming up at the end of the week to help me set up my new house.  My dad and I are going to put new shingles on my roof and my mom, with the help of Lindsay are going to work in the house and doing some landscaping.  It is going to be a hard 4 days of work that is for sure.  My house is going to look a lot different when we are all done.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Man it's hot out there...I just got back in from cutting the grass. But who cares. So I was watching CNN/FNC/Meet the Press this morning and I think I've come to a obvious conclusion...unless you have very slanted to the left, you do not trust and or really like Democrats (with the exception of Obama, and how doesn't love him right now). I mean Kerry/Edwards supporters really stand up for him but it seems like if you are at all in the middle you are always questioning what they are doing and the real reason they are doing. They can never make a speech and actually believe in these opinions...always have ulterior motives.  I guess this is were Bush does so good.  He always gets people to believe what he says.  I mean he wants a war with Iraq and misleads the nation into a war (faulty intel or not) and still a majority of the nation trusts him.  How does this happen and if Kerry sees the real merits of the war after the start, even though he voted for it, and he is labeled a flip flopper.  Doesn't make a lot of sense.  I guess when you are fighting for a poorer class it is harder to get people to believe you, when the same people have been lied to for the last four years.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey anybody who is reading this...probably just me.  I just wnated to start a page where I could randomly put my thoughts on what is going on in my life and the world in general.  You will probably see a lot of reaction to what I see on TV, since my laptop is right in front of my TV.  You will definitly see reaction to Mr. Bill O'Reilly (INDEPENDENT??) and Sean Hannity (Fair and Balanced??).  Well....Let the fun begin!   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>