<Blog>


<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For those who haven't heard of exoSyphen, which has rececntly been developing these simulation hacking games, which I find very enjoyable. Here is what exoSyphen say about themselves...  "               exoSyphen Studios was founded in 2003 and focuses mainly on game                development.                We also develop software and games for mobile platforms and other                portable platforms and software components for 3rd party companies.exoSyphen                Studios is open for business relationships.                We are currently offering licenses of the game engines used in our                major game titles, for commercial game development.                The prices are very affordable, and if you want to develop your                own game, using our already existing and tested code, please contact                us.If you wish to resell our games and products, we are offering                a highly attractive opportunity.                You can either receive a 30% commision on every products you sell,                or you can pre-purchase a large bundle of products at prices starting                from as low as 20% of our retail price"  You can visit their site at http://www.exosyphen.com  This product ranges from a free price of you own the recent series, or up to $9.95 if its your first. It seems promising, the requierments are low, so all PPC's should be able to handle it, and it seems as promising as the first game. Here is how they describe the game...  "               The world of hacker games is no longer reserved for the PC platform.                A completely new and innovative game has just landed on the PocketPC                platform. Experience the unique feeling of beeing a hacker on the                move, int this hacking simulation game.                Stay updated with new information about vulnerable targets, and                be the first to hack in, cash in the money, trash the host and run                away. Just watch out for the tracer so you won't be traced and continue                your job safely.                A complex and intuitive interface, based on excellent graphics,                will be your virtual center of operations. You can pause your mission                any time, and if you exit, your assets are safely saved and you                can continue anytime."  They also have a PC version of the PPC version, though Im not sure who will want it, unles they are a diehard fan. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, as ALL of you know, Doom 3 has been released, and many people are writing up their reviews. So, why dont I do one?  First off, Doom 3 is obviously the game with best graphics. I belive using the brand new unreal engine, it is a superbly beats all other games in the graphics aspect. Be it be in lighting, animation, physics, or just the actual atmosphere of the game, Doom 3 is a revelation. However, going to the gameply aspect, it does not shine. The single player is very unsupported, with just you blasting your enemies back to Hell. Not to mention you will be reading emails!? Whats with reading emails, when all hell broke loose on the ship. And how come its you that must defeat the aliens, and that everyone else died, or was taken over? Multiplayer is even weaker. It supports up to 4 players. Thats right, and just the regular deathmatch style gaming, you recieve major lag. So unless the Doom 3 makers fix it, or these moders start moding, multiplayer will rarely be touched.  All in all, I did not like this game. By a technical standpoint it was oustanding! But gameplay really dissapointed me. If your looking for the best FPS game of the year, or month, then look elsewhere. If you looking for a graphicaly great game, or just something to blast away time with, then you might want to try out Doom 3. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, they have done it again with six new ones, all using the new Windows Mobile 2003 Second Edition. They range from the low leveled budget user rz, to the entertainer and buisness user. Currently however, I am debating towards the Sharp Zaurus line. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, for those who are going down to San Antonio sometime here is my review on the Staybridge Suite, near the AirPort. I give it 3 stars, it was nice to have 2 rooms, 2 beds, 2 tv's, and a kitchen. The reason though for taking away 2 stars, was that, it was near Traffic, so it was hard to leave. Also, the comunity wasn't all spectacular. And while the hotel was nice, it did show some age. So, for a low price hotel for a prolonged stay, that should suffice your needs. 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know Terranet and all those other websites where you put in your address and you get to view your house? But its in black, or its blue, and its not in high-resolution? Well, try EarthViewer, it is a little pricy, but you can always use the 7 day trial, and then use Kazza or Limwire to get a serial, etc. All you do is load it up, and persa I would enter my address and zip code, and it took me to an area of Mckinney showing my house, and surrondings. I got pretty darn close, and for a 2 or 3 minute wait, it got High-Rez. However, I noticed it is about 2 or 3 years outdated, and I am not sure on how they handle their updates, but overall a great program. You can swirve, swivel, zoom in and out, its great. And you can view Poland, Russia, every place on Earth, just not in High Res.  Maybe some of you watch these family drama shows, but I just started watching, "The Days." It is actually great, its about a family, where the mom is pregnant, the dad is in a mid-life crisis (seems like in next episode hes getting better), their daughter is pregnant, their gothic &amp; dark son writes, and their little smart boy becomes evil after visiting some kids house he beat up. :p Im not really good at these sums up, so check it out on Sunday's at 9pm for me. (Im in Texas) And for those who watch "Life as we live it" It looked great, but I missed the premiere.. should I wait for reruns... or? 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I got W.Bloggar, which is in my P.O.V, a great way to manage your Web Log, its so much easier and faster, and you dont even have to be on the damn web. For more info, or the actual program (ITS FREE!) visit www.wbloggar.com
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes! Got my first damn blog, and it seems to be working great. :p Ill be posting some cool tech shit from now and then. If I get around to it, I might get me another site about my Warlock group. 
    
</post>


</Blog>