<Blog>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Here's what you've been waiting for, striplings.    A little while ago, as I got home (home being Alex's right now) a guy in his car honked at me and gave me a suggestive gesture. I didn't catch his liscence plate number, but I didn't really think of it. I thought he might be a friend of Alex's, or Emili's (Alex's girlfriend), but they didn't know him.   Now, here comes the rant! Whats with old guys just automatically assuming hat its alright to make obscene and sexually suggestive gestures at me?! Do I look like a girl?   *yes*   But thats's completely aside from the actual point! People should have a little more decency than that! Especially adults, seeing as how they're running the entire goddamn country!! A lot of guys out there seem to like young, rather girlish boys, especially old and creepy ones.   Right after my gramma died, before I went to stay with Conrad (an old pal of my mom) I stayed at a guys house who was named Manny, and he said that he'd let me stay if I helped him out a bit. I agreed, because he owned a shop, and being the niave kid that I am, I assumed he meant help out in the shop. The next day, he takes my wallet from me and says come back after school. I really needed the wallet, or else I would have gone straight to Con's. I came back after school, and he's there, waiting, with my wallet in his hand. Not to go into much detail, let's just say he "decided to have some fun with me". No, he didn't get far, my boss (named Michael) came by, and scared him away. I managed to grab my wallet (thank god) and I took off.   Is there a growing number of pedophiles or what? Maybe its just that more are getting caught.    Phew. That rant went nowhere.    Спасибо за чтение,   Johnny   (It's "thanks for reading", btw)   
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I   wrote this abot the same time last year:    "Bisexuality means you go either way, right? So how come, if I have  two times  the normal chance of getting a boy/girlfriend, I'm still desperatly alone? Am I that much of a loser? That's just fabulous!"         I used to write a lot of short, unsent letters to Lance, who was my best friend and is now my boyfriend. I started a little after my mom passed away, and most of them were short and obnoxious like:    "Happy New Year! Is it 'year' or 'years'?"    I'm in a good mood today, though this is probably a matter of opinion. I got my face and ribs bashed up quite a bit a little while ago, and recently got out of the hospital. I have this huge, ugly bruise on one side of my pretty face. I keep losing my smokes.    --Johnny      
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I work for my teacher/friend's boyfriend, who owns a baby store. I basically cut down boxes and price things in the basement. It's driving me insane, this maternal concern for children who wander down the stairs! I feel like an ass, with my "Do I Look Like A Fucking People's Person?" t-shirt, going, "Oh no! Be careful, you don't want to fall and upset your mommy!"  Johnny  
    
</post>


</Blog>