<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So today is my 40th birthday. I have the day off. Have a list of things I should be doing but instead prefer to surf the net. In surfing the net, I found my full name, Olga Patricia, come up on a google search. The link is above.    urlLink ">Link    It turns out my name is also the name of a cargo ship that also was used for off-shore radio with the UK. How interesting. My father was in the Navy for most of his life and also a merchant marine. I wonder if he knew about this ship. He is dead now, so I will never know. You would think that he would have told me...or not...considering his lack of communication skills. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is my 40th birthday and I am not spending it with my twin or mother.  What a change this is.  Last year was so bad...lots of name-calling and crying...mom suffering heart pain...I told myself I would not be a part of any celebrations come next year...and now next year is today!.   I get kind of lonely but I have a sweet husband and adorable dogs and a kitty with a most interesting personality...so I am not alone.  I have a job that pays very well for someone with no college degree..just lots of charisma and determination to get what she needs.  I own my place with the help of DH..the location ...close to the beach.   We are in the ghetto part of town...but that means we can blast music loud too and smoke the smoke without any dirty looks.   I'd like to do a little shopping, color my hair, pack for our road trip tomorrow, walk the dogs, etc.   Here's a poem I wrote a few years ago, it's called "Color My Gray"  I color my grays Thank God for each new day Challenge myself in small ways Love my friends with all my heart even those who one day will part. Take a look inside you can see the tears I've cried. Change is in the air Life is a dance on a dare I am never alone in my place I call home.   wrote this on 7-2-01 when my friend Kate was moving back to her home in Australia.  I miss you Kate!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So rotten sometimes..and then it turns around and is so great.  I don't know if I am coming or going most of the time.  There are many things i would like to change.  Turning 40 is a scarey thing.  First of all I would like to find another job but the idea of being 40 and looking for new work seems tough.  I should not let my age get in the way with my pursuit of happiness.   Life will always be a challenge and I have done pretty good so far...(in my humble opinion).   I was so depressed most of the day today.  I did not get the house cleaned up like I wanted to.  Instead I moped on the couch and watched Lifetime movies all day.  I love that channel.  I could write stories for that channel for the rest of my life.  I have a rough draft of a story I wrote at work...of all places - God that place is so damn dull.   It is about a woman who becomes a multi-millionaire with a dog product.  She is a dog lover and loves children too.  It is a story about a homeless shelter, a farm and dogs, and people who care and people who do not care....but mostly about people who care and how they all come together.  Right now it is 13 chapters long.  It is the reason I signed up for the creative writing class at the community college.   I really need to keep myself in mind...my goals..my life.   Instead i get all wound up over my mother and my twin sister.  I hate it when they get stuck in my head for the better part of a perfectly good Saturday.  I guess cuz it is close to my birthday...my 40th too..that I was so down and out.  I always get down and out around my birthday.   I have issues with my family.   Verbal abuse is rampant.  So glad I have enough sense to learn how not to yell and argue.  I used to do that all the time with past boyfriends...drove them all away.  And I also never accepted being verbally abused...OH No.  It was mostly the other way around.  When I was in my early 30's I learned how yelling and aruging gets me absolutely no where.  Got me all by myself is what it did.   Ha!! but now I am married to a sweet wonderful man who helps me learn and grow and vice versa.  Yes...Life is wonderful, beautiful, painfull, confusing...and always challenging.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Learning how not to react to people who push my buttons is a difficult thing for me to do.  But, I think I  need to learn how to do this better.  My husband helps in this area and most of the time he doesn't even know he's helping me.  He definitely knows how not to react...in fact sometimes I wonder what does make him react.   Hmmm...Anyways, he is good for me in a million different ways.   Ah Fridays...means I have another two whole days off.  Today I daydreamed pretty much all day what it would be like if I did not have to work.   It was great fun...imagining, daydreaming.    my creative writing class starts next week.  our road trip starts the next day.  I won't be able to write in here.  maybe i will write down on a piece of paper what happens...and take lots of pictures.  I really hope when I come back from vacation things at work will improve...I will have something to do...more paper to push..cuz right now things are incredibly slow and I dislike incredibly slow.   Watched the Whole 9 Yards last night and the Whole 10 Yards right now.  They are comedy gangster movies with Bruce Willis, the actress who played opposite Madona in that 80's movie, and Chandler in Friends.  Funny movies.  I walked outside for awhile today at work.  I love the weather in San Fran.  and here in Half Moon Bay.  I saw my mom after work today.  She is so wierd.  God, it is such a good thing I do not have children.  Sometimes I wonder why I even exist.  Oh Well.  Life is very good for me as long as don't talk to my mother or my sister very often.  I know they think I am "this and that"...but frankly I don't care what they think.  Funny, that is what my dad used to tell me all the time..."I don't care what you think".  It really hurt my feelings.       Now I behave like my father...pretty damn scarey if you ask me...yes...very good thing I don't have kids.  They would be a neurotic mess just like me and my dog OP.  Stick with the dogs and learning how not to react to people who push my buttons.   I am going to have a great weekend.  I am going to get my place orderly.  Pack for the trip.  Put together all the stuff I have written.  I think I lost some stuff I wrote due to too much illegal downloading....Dear Husband loves to download surround sound music DVD's.  Must be surround sound though and usually we just get the music..not the video portion of the DVD..takes too long cuz it comes in bit and pieces...blah..blah..blah.  I bought a bunch of double CD jewel cases from Central Comp...went there at my lunch this week.  What a Man's Store that is...YUCK.    So many things I want to learn...like how to write stories and poems...how to make my own web page.  I want to put a bunch of pictures and stuff.. it takes time.  I wished I did not have to work so much.  Maybe someday.    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spent this past weekend with my mother.  It was her 72nd birthday on Friday.  I called in sick at work and took Belle to an orthopedic surgeon.  She has a cruciate ligament tear...about $3,600.00 to fix. Quite a lot of money.  Of course, Marie, my sister, heard all about it.  I didn't really want to talk about it.  She does not care about pets.  Her two cats are neglected and I would barely call them pets as one is always hiding and the other is so old and scraggly looking.  They never seem to have fresh water and their food?... Well I will just stop here about Marie takes care of her pets. My mother was upset because her evil husband does not want any more pets and their three brats do.  I said it was probablly a good thing because the pet they get will only suffer.   Marie, my twin, wants to spend our 40th birthday together but I am not that interested.  She has been married to a verbal abuser for at least 15 years.   She has changed and is not the nice wonderful sister I had before she went to college.   I don't trust her anymore.  After all the years of being told   I   am not to be included in anything family things they do...I honestly feel that Marie is now thinking like her husband Bob.  The past two years in particular have left me feeling like she hates me too.  Last year on my mother's birthday of all days, we had a BIG fight.  She was in my face telling me that I was crying because she does not have a nice husband like I do and that I feel sorry for her.  She told me to keep crying...what a bitch.  I will never forget that.  Oh and all the past birthdays when I thought we would get together...I was single back then (i've only been married for a year and half) and Marie just plain...flat out...had no interest to do something together.  I remember one year when Bob, my sister's husband, threw a surprise birthday party for her at the baseball parking lot of course and I was not invited.  I asked her the next day what she did for her birthday and she told me all about the party Bob threw for her.  She did not like it as she HATES baseball.  But her husband loves it and he is quite selfish so he thought it was a wonderful idea and I did not get invited.  Now this year for our 40th she wants to do something together.  YUCK.  I would rather pretend I do not have a twin sister as I have in the past and celebrate all by myself.  I do not have a problem with being by myself.  My dad, may he rest in peace, always made fun of me for not having more friends.  My sister criticizes me in her underhanded way.  I have made peace with myself in not having friends.  I have a wonderful husband who is my soulmate and a couple of adoring pets that I love with all my heart...that is all I need in this world.  I lived by myself for years and years...since I was about 18 to about 28.  There were some years that I lived with a boyfriend but they were not true and I split up.  I don't mind taking the risk of being lonely versus staying with a guy who does not truly love me....no thanks.  I would rather be by myself.  So now Marie is all gunho on getting together.  Corey my husband suggested I don't answer the phone.  I think that is what I will do.  I don't know about Belle either.  She is our 3rd dog.  We have three dogs and one cat all together.  Corey came with two dogs and I came with one dog and a little runt of a cat.  We bought a townhouse where the association allows two pets wtih no weight limits.  We looked high and low for an association that would allow this.  Most associations allow only one 30lb and less pet.  We knew we had to buy something cuz no one would ever rent to us with four pets and if they did the house would be run down and in a poor neighborhood.  Well we found this townhouse in a poor neighborhood but it is so cool.  I love this place.  But the thing about Belle is that after her surgery it will be very important to keep her quite and calm for at least 3 weeks and for a total of 3 months.  Belle lives with my mom, who is a widow and adores Belle but my mom is not very good with responsibility.  See, my dad was a verbal abuser too and he controlled everything.  My mother never drove, never paid the bills, never did anything that involved responsibility.  All my mother did was cook dinner (and it was never very good) and shop for clothes...not even groceries.  My dad always bought the groceries.  So anyways, I don't know if my mom can really think ahead and make sure Belle does not bark and get excited when someone comes to the door or if she can handle taking her out on  a short leash in the front yard to go potty.  My mom's brain is like mush...all she does is watch Mexican soap operas and go to lunch with her friends from the Women's Club or church.  I wish we did own a house with a yard so we could keep all three dogs together but we don't make enough money to do that.  I think eventually we will sell this townhouse and get a house-house...but will all three dogs be still alive?  Chief is 11 and OP is 8 and Belle is 7...Rex kitty is 9.   Chief will probably live another 5 years or so..then we'll have Belle come live with us.  That is how long my mother will probably live.  She is always talking about dying in the next year...  Corey got a big big raise...YEAH!!..  He now makes what he used to make when we bought this place.  He lost his job right after we got back from our honeymoon.  We had bought this place a year prior.  Things have been very tight for a year.  But now, we'll be getting more money in.  What a relief.   well better be off to work today.  must walk the dogs before I go and my coffee is ready.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I made it through another Tuesday. I don't like Tuesday.  Monday is OK b/c I'm back from two days off and feeling rather refreshed.  New week.  But Tuesday...there is nothing good about Tuesday.  It is still the beginning of the week.  I wore blue jeans today.  I think I will continue to dress down on Tuesdays just to make myself feel better about it being Tuesday.  
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      New month today. I turn 40 this month. Very wierd to know I am actually going to be 40 in a few weeks. I don't want to turn 40. I want to stay young. Yes, young and innocent. I liked it much better like that. Life is truly fun when you are young and innocent.  Yeah, I'm almost 40 and I am happy where I am. I wished I was doing more. At least making this blog is something I've been wanting to do for awhile. We'll see how this one works out. Will it be easy? I don't know.  i probably should be cleaning house, grocery shopping, or exercising or walking the doggoes.  Instead I sit here and type my thoughts out on this new blog.  I have been writing to myself for quite some time now.  I like it.  It helps me feel better about myself.   Opilies is my nickname for OP, my sweet dog/bitch.  She is an 8-year-old mixed breed.  Probably Ridgeback and Rottie....very red in color with no ridge.  She is the greatest and quite a handful.  My first dog besides the ones we had at our parents' house.  OP is a great watchdog.  Now that she is older she loves to bark at stuff outside while she is lounging on her big fat comfie in the bedroom.  What a princess she is.  In fact OP stands for Obnoxious Princess.  I call her Opilies.  My husband's cousins all have names like Jennilies and Annilies....so I call my dog Opilies and now call this blog Opilies too.  My secret name.   So gray outside today.  I live by the beach and I love it.  I love the beach and being outside. So does OP.  We have another dog Chief.  He is my husband's dog.  He is an 11-year-old black lab.   Well enough about my dogs.  I could go on and on.  I would like to post some pictures soon.  I really would like to make my own website someday.  I have some poems I'd like to post too.  We'll see how it all goes.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>