<Blog>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What's on my mind...ten thousand things. I've been watching the first season of Alias on dvd that I borrowed from Janice, and I've realized two things: One...keeping secrets is one of the hardest things to do on the face of this earth. Well, at least it is for me. How are you supposed to really know someone when everything is so hush-hush secretive? I don't think anyone can know someone until they've lived with them for half a life-time. Two...if you lead a double life, you are so screwed. Why? B/c being two different people means you're keeping secrets! (refer to "One" above) I know all of us have different personalities...one for each of the people-groups you socialize with regularly. This also hinders people from seeing you... So ergo, my conclusion...which is actually a question. What if you don't know you? Then my points above have no meaning b/c it doesn't matter if you keep secrets to hide the person you are but you don't know who you are! And...leading a double life is pointless when you retire from all the masks and come home to find no home...you've never had a home b/c you've been too busy pretending to be other homes! AHH! Does this make any sense? I don't think I know me. And I KNOW that I don't know you. It's sad that I'm just beginning to realize this. And I know I've done really really stupid things in the past, but I think this is the smartest thing I've done ever. We all keep our secrets. But we can't base relationships on them. We can't build a home upon a secret. I am afraid that there will never be enough time or enough effort put into any relationship I make to actually understand a person or to know a person. What if I married a guy that I'd been dating for 5 years, but only found that we were headed toward divorce b/c he was a completely different man than who I thought he was? I think people change after they get married. Before you marry, all you're really trying to do is get the other person to marry you...and then, once you're married, it's like you don't have to be the person you were before you got married b/c now...you're already married. And I also wish that people could be honest in their relationships with other people. All those secrets you keep at the back of your head are just sitting there...waiting for you to tell them. They'll never go away, and they'll never be dealt with unless they come out. The hardest  thing  about opening up is the fear that the other person will hate you for keeping them away. Also...I've realized if I'm this concerned with all the secrets I've kept, what about the secrets other people have kept? I am worried.   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I never really realized how much effort and energy can go into being angry. And what really bugs me is that I don't really even know why I should be so angry. I mean, I know what I'm angry at and I know why I'm angry, but I can't express those feelings for some reason. And I am completely exhausted.       I'm going bowling tonight. I hope I try to have a good time. Christine's spending the night again. We'll listen to Jay some more.       Also, being so angry and exhausted I think is making me go crazy. I've been thinking of doing some stuff that I might probably want to take back later.   
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm so tired, it's not funny.       I hung out with Caroline today and had dinner with her family. Grilled shrimp, potatoes, and corn on the cob. Really good. But we started a 500 piece puzzle, and I got a headache. Haha. When I got home, my headache worsened, so I took excedrin, and it helped a little. I got home a little after 10, and my parents weren't home! After an hour, I got kind of worried, so I called, but they were at the Yeh's house partying it up. Haha.       I have no idea why I feel so stressed out. Planning an evening of bowling or any other event for ATPC should not stress me out this much. I know this stress is coming from my personal problems. Aiyoh. I shouldn't be upset about this, but I feel...like argh. It's so frustrating. When I have problems with people, I don't think I communicate it well to them. It's...really frustrating. I guess I expect people to understand it when I'm upset and why I'm upset. I need to vent.       I feel a little better...  
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm alive! WEEEEE.  
    
</post>


</Blog>