<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      finished my first homemade ride today! Need for Speed: Underground... u can really taste the garden-grown goodness. i hope the southern public has a need for speed - 'cuz i got a need for their money! i'm actually impressed by the $50 video editing software i bought for the gig - it gives the illusion of professional quality... ha! after getting down and dirty, this ride really only took about 3 or 4 hours to edit. most of the "work" involved hours of racing through the streets of ____ City over and over again to capture the most   Action-Packed!   footage i could collect. In the end, i'm fairly pleased - with it being my first ride - and will be able to build upon my experience and software upgrades to pop out some unique masterpieces of video game adaptation. Now to spend the next week programming the bitch... 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    holy shit! road dog is summa the bestest beer i can remember tasting in a while! thank you dr. thompson.&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Internal view of my sim showing a screenshot of my "Need for Speed: Underground" ride adaptation.  urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My Simalata&nbsp; urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i took sum pics of my baby today. she's big and purple. i'll let anyone ride her sweet ass... but they gotsta pay ME first! 'cuz... (drop tha beat) I don't know what you heard about me, But a bitch can't get a dollar out of me, No Cadillac, no perms, you can't see, That I'm a motherfucking P-I-M-P!  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i would kill my pc at work if it didnt make me so much money. 8am-12pm today. has anyone seen a current comm32.ocx file? ...'cuz i really need one. thanx. i swapped mpeg cards 4x today. 4. at least windows xp works... for now. thank u bill. i hope it proves to be worth the 200motherfukkinclams i shelled out for a solitary computer upgrade license. u really are the man. no, really... 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today's the day. lookout world, saucer simulation technologies will soon bring individual realities into question... you think that's  air  you're breathing? ha! i am   the   lawnmower man! a goddamned magician! i put a roller coaster in a box suckas! muhahahahaha!  yes, ladies and germs, robert scott myers (a.k.a. saucercrab, saucer, the sauce himself, whiskeycan, chemicalAli, and your momma's sugar daddy) has finally found his calling. blindly fortunate as he may be, he has none the less worked his ass off over the past year - alone, away from friends and family - to buy the ultimate entertainment system; a 12 passenger, 3,900lb-capacity motion theater with a 6'3" viewable s-video input display and surround-sound stereo capability. eat it world. eat it up.  more to come...  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      fuck fuck shit shit shitty shitty fuck fuck. ha.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>