<Blog>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just wanted to let you know, i love you guys. when i heard page break down during the 8-15-04 Wading, i began to cry. when trey broke down during his post-glide speech, i began again. but when trey says, "lets blow off some phucking steam!" and they tear into a massive Split Open and Melt, bringing the smile back to my phace as mike harmonizes in his dulcet tones. and now, i can honestly say, that i am better and pheel the best i've ever phelt and i owe to a couple of special people, besides Phish, you know who you are. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so the band that has changed my life, changed my entire perception of the world, is gone from my world as quickly as they arrived, with one final, emotional concert last night in Coventry, Vermont. many of my good phriends, including a phriend i've known almost my entire life, was in attendance, and some local helena kids i met this summer. and now it's all over, they played their last song, The Curtain With, a song i was listening to yesterday, a song from a show, another beautiful show, 12-14-95, where the segue gods came out in force and drilled the listener with some insane sounds. page crying during Wading, trey unable to speak, a Split Open and Melt jam to blow the steam off. an insane setlist, an insane end to the most gifted rock band from the last twenty years. in my opinion, the second greatest american rock band behind the grateful dead, the torchbearers for the jam industry. will we never hear another mike's > Hydrogen > Weekapaug, another flawless 2001 > Down with Diseas, and no more Fluffhead's, with Fluff's Travel's included or not. Will we never see page tinkle the ivories on his baby grand, or Joe C or Greasy Fizeek or Henrietta, or whatever Fish's name is that night, pick up his vacuum and play something, Somewhere Over the Rainbow, or Terrapin. Will we never see another Trey face, another Mike head bob, another I Didn't Know? Remember how they sang to us? will this be the end, will this be the last we will see of Phish. Simple answer, no. because when human beings are kind to one another, when human beings share mutual love for one another, when human congregate at special places for strange reasons, phish's legacy will grow, and flourish. and maybe, when the time is right, they will return to us, from their mother ship, and lead us to another place, although i can't imagine a place better than the place they've led me.  Has music ever made you cry? Has a guitar solo ever made you feel like you were being lifeted up onto your feet and carried above all things? Has the voice of a familiar singer never let you down? Has the pounding bass line ever made you slap your wheel so hard that it hurt your hand? Has the sound of the piano meant more to you on the day your grandfather died than your own father's eulogy? Has Jon Fishman's face ever made your day?  if so, you've experienced the power, the strength, and the stability that is Phish  the rock, the foundation, the core, the essence, the School  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Set 1 The Divided Sky, Suzy Greenberg -> Down With Disease -> Prince Caspian -> Scent of a Mule -> Tears of a Clown* -> Scent of a Mule, Mexican Cousin Set 2 Run Like an Antelope -> 2001 -> Golgi Apparatus, Waves -> Tweezer -> Hold Yourself High ->Terrapin** Hold Yourself High*** -> Timber Ho! -> Sample In a Jar Encore Bouncing Around the Room, Tweezer Reprise Notes *With special guest picked from the audience on vocals.**Fishman on vocals and vacuum.***Trey and Fishman drumming  One of the last sets in Phishtory, and what a way to go out! Divided Sky Opener, the first real Golgi in who knows how long. Just puts a tear to my eye, THAT part in Down with Disease, the Divided Sky solo that always takes me up to the ceiling of wherever i am, and of course, a Fishman vacuum solo that begs the question will we ever hear another one? and to a syd barrett song? come on, this setlist is almost unbeatable. reaffirms my love, my respect and my languor for this band.  Great night tonight, peter, stuart, daniel, gary, nick, cason, alec, and i, really fun, bummed that i couldn't spend more time, but am headed to the Sphinx tomorrow with my bro, 9,342 feet of sweetness and a view worthy of Zeus   
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Set 1  Chalkdust Torture, Bathtub Gin -> Runaway Jim, Walls of the Cave, Loving Cup  Set 2  All Of These Dreams, Limb By Limb, Lifeboy, Crowd Control, Seven Below ->*Stash -> NICU, Bug, Contact**, Character Zero  Encore  David Bowie Notes *Trey thanks his guitar tech, Brian Brown, on stage at the end of Seven Below. **With "Little Drummer Boy" ending  In my opinion, the most highly anticipated phish show before coventry's last set, all the rest cannot be more important than this. bob weir and phil lesh in the audience, jerry's anniversary, hampton! HAMPTON! a set unworthy of all the history phish has filled that place with over the years, from their incredible '98 run there to their triumphant return in '03, it oozes history, not just for phish, but for the grateful dead as well. this was the site of the return of the warlocks show in october 89. there set lists for a two-night stand:  Hampton Coliseum, Hampton, VA, 10/8-9 1989  10/8   Set 1:  Foolish Heart, Walkin' Blues, Candyman, Me and My Uncle, Big River, Stagger Lee, Queen Jane, Approximately, Bird Song, The Promised Land  Set 2  :Help on the Way > Slipknot! > Franklin's Tower, Victim or the Crime > Eyes of the World > Drums > Space > I Need a Miracle > The Wheel > Gimme Some Lovin' > Morning Dew Encore: And We Bid You Good Night  10/9    Set 1 : Feel Like a Stranger, Built to Last, Little Red Rooster, Ramble on Rose, We Can Run, Jack-A-Roe, Stuck in Mobile with the Memphis Blues Again, Row Jimmy, The Music Never Stopped  Set 2:  Playing in the Band > Uncle John's Band > Playing in the Band Reprise > Dark Star > Drums > Space > Death Don't Have No Mercy > Dear Mr. Fantasy > Hey Jude Reprise > Throwing Stones > Good Lovin' Encore: Attics of My Life  The Grateful Dead pulled out all the stops, with Brett Mydland laying down some fierce sounds from the boards, bob and jerry's thrashing guitar licks resonated, and phil's, and mickey and bill's bass line was grandiose. You see, this is why i'm disappointed. Phish is done in a week. One last week for them to pull out all of the stops, and they give us a 5 song first set! i'm not complaining about the song selection, but in the second set, a crowd control! come on! i'm just a little disappointed that they chose to end their illustrious hampton career with a second set closing Character Zero, but from what i've heard, the Bowie encore was sick, possibly the best Bowie encore of all time, first one since 11-16-97 and only the fifth one ever. but again, no nod to the old man, no onstage antics, no phil or bob, seems a little of a bummer when you expected the world.  theres a lesson in that: when you expect the world, you will be unpleasently disappointed  don't disappoint people. and remember that no matter what time of day it is, YOU CAN STILL WRITE COMMENTS ABOUT MY POSTS!  coooool breeze 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "You know when that girl broke your heart, and told you “we need time apart.” Then you spent a miserable year trying to get her back, and when you finally convince her to give it another shot, after two weeks you realize she was right all along. But you have a good couple months of drunken, sloppy sex anyway before you both eventually decide to just break it off for good? That was the hiatus." From Glide magazine 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And remember as you saw that man, wearing his thirtieth anniversary tour shirt, you wearing your Jerry Althea shirt in that cozy La Honda street. It was the morning of August 9th, 1995, and you’d just heard, and apparently so had he, and you walked out of your house, and sat on the grass for a bit, crying. Yet something beckoned you upwards. So you stood up, and you saw a shirt design you’d recognize from anywhere in the world, a shirt design you’d seen millions of times. He is crying, too. You don’t know what to make of it all. You are both so stunned. You can’t fathom no fall tour, no Jerry, no Jerry, no fall tour. It hasn’t even begun to sink in yet. It’s only eleven-fourteen. Yet, you feel you’ve endured ten years of pain, ten years of grief, when you received that phone call from your friend from tour, Stella Blue, that the old man was gone. He’s gone, you thought, like a steam locomotive rolling down the track. Your first instinct whenever you hear a Dead song is to smile, but today, it isn’t the same, and it’s all over for you. You get up, look on your floor, and you see the shirt you once decided you’d wear when this day came, but you never really expected this day would come. They would always be around. Then you begin to categorize every single show you ever missed; great ones like 5-14-74, 5-5-77, 5-7-77, aw shit, the entire May east coast tour of 1977, and that final show at Soldier Field, where Stella Blue said that the Box of Rain they played had some special meaning, especially when Bobby belted out "A box of rain will ease the pain, and your love will see me through." So you see Jerry’s face, smiling through it, and above him, it says "There’s Thing’s You Can Replace" and below him, it says, "And Other’s You Cannot" and you categorize how many show’s you’ve seen when they played Althea, all the while feeling this immense tightening in your throat, and an immense bout of sobs threatening to begin. So you let it go, and it all comes out, every last bit of energy you had is bent on sobbing for Jerry. Your vision is skewed now, and you cannot understand why this is happening, why there isn’t going to be a fall tour, why there isn’t going to be anymore Terrapin Station’s with Jerry hanging on the word lad-y, and why oh why will there never be another veggie burrito, with cucumbers, carrots, tomato’s, all the vegetable goodness, all gone, every last thing, your purpose on life for the past twenty-five years, your source of income, joy, pride, your family, your grateful family, your kind family, all of it over with the one call from Stella Blue. So you have to leave your house, and you do, but you don’t get as far as the grass, where you begin to sob again, then you see him, with THAT shirt on, the shirt which will always tie you to anyone who wears one. You see each other, you look into each other’s sobbing eyes, and you embrace, for five minutes you embrace, laughing, sobbing, laughing, sniffling, it’s all wet, it’s all uncomfortable, but it’s all fine, you don’t care, you don’t care anymore. Yet when you leave each other, you keep walking, down the cozy streets, where V-Dub’s with the Roses and the Skeletons, or the Steal Your Face logo haunt you. Some of them must know, but other’s don’t. And as you see those who do know, you embrace them as well, and down on the turnaround, by the beach, a dozen of us get into a circle, sway back and forth, find the groove that he gave us, and remember watching him smile, smile, smile, and remember that there is nothing left to do but smile, smile, smile, and you do, and as we smile with each other, through red eyes and tear-streaked cheeks, you understand that everything will be all right, because you are a family, a grateful family. So that is that, you think, but the pain doesn’t go away, it’s always there whenever he sings, or his guitar reverberates where you, or you remember him smiling at you, and you smiling back, and you feel the hair on the back of your neck begin to stand on end. And you realize because you were there for Jerry, and he was there for you, that you two are cosmically bound, with some indelible ray of light, no matter how infinitesimally inane you feel at times, Jerry is inside you, looking out for you. No Jesus, no Buddha, no Mohammed, no Vishnu, no matter, because you’ve had Jerry, and that’s all you need, thank you very much, all you need for joy, for brotherhood, for friendship, for everything was included in Jerry, the old man. Thanks for everything. b J Ward   i wrote that, also in may, for a creative writing showcase at my school to convey the strong feelings i was having for a man i'd never met, a man who to me was still a mystery, a man simply named jerry, a man who died 9 years ago today. whenever you watch him perform, his shaggy hair dropping down to his all too familiar black shirt, his right middle finger non-existent, his voice so soulful, believing in every word he ever sang. every note was special. but to gaze out into the audience, to see people transfixed by this man, is truly special. grown men cry when he plays guitar, people with no other will to live other than seeing the Grateful Dead perform shower themselves in his watery tones, his sublime skill only matched by his supporting cast, no matter who's on keys; preferably pigpen, but keith and brent sure had their day. no matter if its just bill, but preferably its both bill and mickey. there will never be another jerry, no matter what. nobody can capture what he captured. he is the epitome of the visceral spirit of the human being. he truly is one of the most important human beings to ever live. his music is timeless, his smile is flawless and his legacy golden.  so this is robert hunters eulogy for jerry, a very amazing and immensely powerful piece to read  Jerry, my friend, you've done it again, even in your silence the familar pressure comes to bear, demanding I pull words from the air with only this morning and part of the afternoon to compose an ode worthy of one so particular about every turn of phrase, demanding it hit home in a thousand ways before making it his own, and this I can't do alone.  Now that the singer is gone, where shall I go for the song? Without your melody and taste to lead an attitude of grace a lyric is an orphan thing, a hive with neither honey's taste nor power to truly sting. What choice have I but to dare and call your muse who thought to restout of the thin blue air, that out of the field of shared time, a line or two might chance to shine ;  As ever when we called, in hope if not in words,the muse descends. How should she desert us now? Scars of battle on her brow, bedraggled feathers on her wings, and yet she sings, she sings! May she bear thee to thy rest,the ancient bower of flowers beyond the solitude of days, the tyranny of hours;  the wreath of shining laurel lie upon your shaggy head, bestowing power to play the lyre to legions of the dead. If some part of that music is heard in deepest dream, or on some breeze of Summe ra snatch of golden theme, we'll know you live inside us with love that never parts our good old Jack O'Diamonds become the King of Hearts.  I feel your silent laughter at sentiments so bold that dare to step across the line to tell what must be told, so I'll just say I love you which I never said before and let it go at that old friend,the rest you may ignore.-Robert Hunter  So beautiful, so true, one man's best friend gone. puts a tear to my eye, i'm not ashamed. when you are touched by something, you have got to show it. today, i challenge everyone reading this to be kind to someone they otherwise wouldn't be kind to, to show someone how truly they special they are to you, to thank them for being there. i'd like to thank jerry right now, thank him for all he taught me, without ever speaking to me, thank him for all the memories of riding in a car, listening to his music. jerry truly is an ethereal gift, a special person set on this earth to bring happiness. he truly is missed. have a nice sleep, jerry, i can wait to meet you but i can't wait you meet you  with love  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      no worries, he's back 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My brother, and his two good friends, who i've known for almost all of my life, were supposed to be home from climbing the great northern mountain north of flathead lake yesterday evening, it's now 24 hours later with no word, i'm in desperate needs of some good vibes to be sent my way, it's kind of starting to freak me out, because the weather wasn't the best, a sudden thunder shower on saturday afternoon could've done some shit to them, and my brother is wildly idealistic, climbing a mountain in the class 5 range in shitty weather, them being less than expert hikers, i just hope they are ok, anybody reading this, i'm in need of some good vibes. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So you appear on the corner of Reality and Dreaming, with no particular direction in mind, except heading from this place abandon, leaving all your ties on the ground, all your soul-crushing elements on the grass, the trite, deer-shitted grass where the color scheme is all wrong. It looks monumental; the grass. Something distinguishable there, indistinguishable here. Contradictory patterns, of course, resembling an evoking memory from far off in the cosmos. Where the light of your eyes shines but once, and is lost forever. Forever seems too vast, and the present to unimportant, and all the while your thoughts run down from your ears like a trickle of some leaky faucet in a dank basement. Dripping, dripping, dripping. Then Collecting on the floor below your head. Drip, drip, drip. The puddle contains many things, many irrational things, many undesirable things, like the insides of a milk carton or an orange peel from the days of yore, the days before yore, the days when the rain was warm, the snow was cold, the wind was blowing south, and there was never a threat of either on a sunny day, when the sun’s rays were peaking, and the smell of those fine huckleberries beckons you back, far into the recesses of time, back when 5 was your age, not your raison d’etre. But, oh well, that is life now, with it’s wide plateaus, steep valleys, thatched-roof houses, and cozy fireplaces. Smelling like some pipe. Some pipe, some pipe, some glorious, glorious wide-brimmed basin filled with the jovial root of earth, twisted bracken like a gnarled tree up on a brazen, wind-racked hill, sloping silently upwards to meet the mass of the sky that lies just above it. In that sky lies the hopes of it all, the infinitesimal boundaries of sanctity and unity, and brotherhood, and peace, and justice. Wherever you go, wherever you are, you are bound, intrinsically, to that essential part of the sky, the sky so beautiful, so savagely undetermined that it must be from somewhere else, some long, and beautiful world, where people are always dreaming and shining, the sun is always high and warm, the breeze is always cool, the water is always cold, the women are always beautiful, the music is always kind, the smell is always home, the life you lead is never normal, and the life you want to lead is always possible, and never will you retreat from your position on thing’s of this earth, such as the color of the trees and the feelings of a wind on your face. And as you stare atop a peak, looking west towards the towering peaks of sustenance and beauty, you remember that Life is Beautiful, and beauty abounds, and you remember that Life is Good, and that Everything WILL Be All Right, and you descend back into the heartless world below you. Where there is no soul, no majesty, just an emptiness and the rumble of cars, trucks, and buses, and a train whistle blowing. Wherever you feel the most complete isn’t around you, and there is never going to be another feeling like it. From the far off distant hills you feel that cool breeze, feel that beautiful woman, smell that air, taste that cool, crisp water, and hear that beautiful music. Aaah, what its like to be home.  I wrote this once, in May, because i was the happiest i've ever been then, and i wished to express my happiness in some way. i owe it all to the life sport, grateful dead and phish music, and this really special girl i'll just call katie.  It's alright, 'cause I love you. And that's not gonna change. Run me round, make me hurt again and again. But I'll still write you love songs Written in the letters of your name. And brave the storm to come, For it surely looks like rain. I only want to hold you. I don't want to tie you down. Or fence you in the lines I might have drawn. It's just that I've gotten used to Havin' you around. My landscape would be empty If you were gone.   Looks Like Rain written by Robert Hunter Expressing my feelings like no other man can 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's August 7th, it's sunny, it's not too hot out and i'm back in helena after a couple days excursion in the wilderness of Glacier National Park. the song of the day is 5-6-77 Sugaree, possibly the best Sugaree of all time, definitely the most underrated song in that 4 day binge of excess that we deadheads call May '77 with such joy and pleasure as adults refer to their children. may '77, with its powerful second set at the boston garden (5-7-77) and possibly the greatest show of all time in 5-8-77 has leant more in the way of quality tapes and shows than any one stand of shows in dead history.  nice to be back home, with a computer. looks like i didn't miss much. not a whole lot of news these past couple of days; bush still in the white house, we're still in iraq, southend united still in division three. Phish still broken up, Jerry still gone. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      now i will engage if one of the most free-feeling forms of unconventional writing, the stream of conciousness, devleloped by james joyce, then reinvented by herman hesse. what i'm doing is actually not a stream of conciousness, but i'll do one of those some other time, right now, i have shit to say.  high school has been the greatest time of my life, and i certainly owe it to all of the people i surround myself with. but i'd like to say this, to those of my friends who feel like i ditched you, it's not the case. simply, i've just found some happiness right now, some interesting feeling that i've been digging on for most of this year, feelings of unsettled necessity for something more, complacency, and the longing for a more real experience. high school isn't about the arguments or the fights, it's about having fun, experiencing everything, digging it all. and that's simply what i've been doing: digging it all. like sal and dean dug san francisco on that end-of-continent night.  And now to religion. Religion is tricky, you see, because every religion is vowing for the "my dick is bigger than your dick, you are infidels" mantra. it just isn't the case. if there is a god, why would he create an exclusive religion that isn't possible for all faiths to follow. most faiths are reflective on their regions. you don't see a lot of muslims in the northern regions of the world, islam just isn't conducive to anywhere else. region affects religion as well as religion affects region. to those of you who think you belong to the superior religion, i'm sorry, but there isn't one. there is a massive disparity between those who believe and those who don't. those who believe feel that they are happier individuals, which in all likelihood, they are not. those agnostics, myself included, are viewed to be sad, mordant people, which we aren't. i'm one of the happier people i know, happier than all of my faith-filled friends. so what does that have to say about your logic? if there was a god, i think he wouldn't care what religion you belonged to as long as you cared for each other, as long as there was love in the world, he wouldn't give a shit if you were christian or hindu or janist or what. as long as you treated yourself and others well, you'd be accepted. god would want all of his children to come into his arms once more, and sit by his side. everyone is welcome.  and now about jesus. and i know this will offend people. but christianity is a massive cult, with more people. in fact, the reason christians were slaughtered in the early years of the church was simply because they were thought to be cult followers. what the christian religion tries to do, and this is the major similarity between christianity and islam, is divide people against non-christians. christianity, although preaches tolerance, love and freedom, is seldom practice by its followers, even it's most devoted followers in the case of the sex abuse scandals of the catholic church. few people actually understand who jesus was. if jesus was here on earth, he would be the hippy kid you'd make fun of at lunch, with his nappy hair, his sandals and his fashion sense. i believe that jesus existed, i believe he was killed, but i don't believe jesus "died for our sins" whatever the hell that means. i believe he was just a peaceful man with a message. i believe he was arrogant, of course, for he wanted a church to be built after him. he was basically a man with a good message who wanted it to be remembered. and it has been remembered. it's a good message, but son of god, sorry, that's too far-fetched for even me to believe. and i hope nobody takes offense to this, because no disrespect is intended for JC.   that about does it for monday night, phish's IT documentary was on TV, very, very cool. reaffirmed what i knew all along that the Breakup was slightly planned. unfortunately, they didn't tell me when i had the chance to hit up three Vegas shows this spring. aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah, boy. man. god. shit.   thanks to all of you who empathize.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i watched you got served last night, and well, i do believe i've been served by the makers of this film. you got served is quite possibly the greatest piece of cinematic genius ever put to film, capturing an alluring part of america much like henry james captured victorian life in A Portrait of a Lady. it's sensual, it's free-flowing, it portrays the very essence of human nature, it's frailities, it's triumph's, and it's love. never before and never again has a movie thus summed up the era we are living in. you got served transforms the conventional thought put on us by ourselves, develops a rich, harlequined pattern, likened to lace and gold, and takes our minds to a place, far, far away from here, away from the sadness, away from the pain, away from our comfort zone, if only for two and fifteen glorious hours. no matter where you are from or what you are doing, no matter if you are the lowliest peasent or the most decorated king, this movie speaks volumes about the transcendent nature of the human spirit, and our ability to overcome obstacles of not just time and place, but eons of adversity. this movie truly is a gift, an ethereal gift, something to be kept in a time capsule in fort knox and preserved as a testament to the greatest this country has to offer.    My Favorite Scene from you got served again, the sequel to You Got Served   David:  I think we got served!  Elgin:  No way, dawg, no way did we get served!  David:  Can someone please check if we got served or not, come on!  Elgin:  Yo, i don't think you understand. this thing we're in is bigger than us, bigger than any serving their crew can dish out. They are the new crew, and if we get served by them, god-damn it, we'll never show our face around here anymore!  David:  El, it's not always about who got served and who didn't get served. i mean, there's a war going on for pete's sake, and what are we doing? just dancing? how's dancing going to bring the deficit down? how's dancing going to make the economy stronger? how's serving wade's crew going to affect global warming? how are we going to get out of iraq? can john kerry establish an international coalition? how do we deal with the situation in iran? by dancing, and serving people? no, i think not, my brother. we get wise, we read the newspaper and watch cnn, nigga, we are going to stand up and say, hey man, this world has had enough of it! i'm sick of serving people, i'm sick of it all! i want an end to this. and then, my brother, the world can be a much safer place and you won't have to serve people. you can serve them with love, serve them with kindness, and brotherhood. Go out, El, and serve the world!  Elgin:  Aight   end scene   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's a great day, it's not very hot out.   a conversation i had once:  me: have you ever wondered what the hell is going to happen to yourself in ten years? wade: yeah, then i get really scared me: why's that? wade: because i'm 24, and i don't have a job me: so...? wade: are you fucking serious? me: yeah, i mean (voice trailing off) wade: well, i'm 24, right? me: right wade: and i'm unemployed, meaning i have no source of income me: oh, i see what you're saying wade: no, i don't think you do me: oh, i do wade: what i'm saying is that i'm broke right now, and i have no job, meaning, and no matter what way you slice it, i'm fucked! me: dude, you could just pull a kerouac and go wander all over the country wade: kerouac was a pussy me: how so? wade: he just wasn't very manly. he sipped wine me: wine's good, what's wrong with wine wade: it's all a little girly to me me: jesus wade, you are an accepting kid wade: the world hasn't accepted me, so i don't accept the world me: you sounded really goth just then wade: thank you me: you aren't welcome wade: damn me: i know, it hurts, doesn't it wade: what are you going to be doing in ten years? me: probably trying to understand why my life sucks wade: that's a shitty attitude me: oh wade, i know, i fucked myself over wade: how so? me: i'm not rich wade: good point, pass me the lagoon passes wade the lagoon bong me: wade, want to come hit the road with me, just you and i, us versus the rest of the country, billowing out across the prairie, meeting different people everynight, sleeping in another place every night. digging everything as we go. we'll start here, then go dig missoula for a while, then spokane for a time, then the cascade villages, think about, you and i up the cascades, DESOLATION PEAK, like Japhy and Sal! wouldn't that be wonderful? and then go up to seattle, hang out there for a while, then up to BC, then down Interstate 5 along the coast for days, oregon and stuff, then california, san francisco, we'll dig san francisco like dean and sal did that end of continent night!!! man, we just got to do that! then we'll go down to mexico, all the way down, to guatemala and everywhere in south america, we'll dig it all up wade, it would be the greatest adventure on the history of the planet! we'd be legends, they'd talk about us in the same breath as Jack and Neal, man, could you dig that? wouldn't that be fun?? wade: no (silence for the next 15 minutes as i get unexcited about this trip) finally me: fucking wade wade: what?  wade is a kid i met a couple weeks ago standing outside matt g's house. i went over to drop something off at the g's house and he was standing outside of it. he asked if i wanted to go to a party, and having nothing to do that night, i said sure, why not. and i did, and it was really fun. i met a lot of new people. and i owe it all to the phish tour shirt i was wearing.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A year ago today, Phish played in Limestone, Maine in front of 70,000 people. The IT festival was a moment i will remember most, although i wasn't there, simply because i felt so close to the band at that moment. all summer, leading up to my first show (7-12-03 Taste, Mexican Cousin, Stash, NICU, Heavy Things, Mock Song, Army of One, Maze. Piper, Two Versions of Me, Tweezer > Dogs Stole Things, Water in the Sky, Ghost, David Bowie. Frankenstein, Tweezer Reprise) i had this amazing closeness with the band, something indescribable. They meant more to me than anything i had come across; more than my family, more than my friends, more than writing or reading. Every happy thought i had ever experienced or ever wanted to experience culminated into 4 very special individuals. At the concert, i experienced more than i ever thought possible, things i've never told anyone happened there; the ten or so seconds when trey and i stared at each other, him digging off my energy. that beautiful, and i mean the most beautiful girl in the world, dancing a few feet in front of me and to my left, her hair flowing, smelling like some ethereal dreamlike olfactory scent, kicking my nose straight into my balls. i even saw my friend benj burke, the man who introduced me to phish.  But alas, it's all over, all of it. no more phish after august 15th. what will we all do?  "there are things you can replace, and others you cannot" you can't replace phish, you can't replace the memories and the feelings. you can only hold on to them, forever.  why is it that we never appreciate the truly important things until they are gone?  why is there no fall tour, no festival outside reno in the nevada desert, no more shakedowns, no more calls for set openers, no more BLISS or LIZARDS signs, no more Forbin narrarations, no more trey banter, no more chairman of the boards, no more greasy fizeek, no more vacuum solos, no more NYE shows, no more harry hood glowstick wars, no more of the infinitesimal things that make this community the best community on earth to belong to. i've entered it far too late, and really don't have much to say for it. i wish everyone of you who reads this will someday experience what phish has meant to me, because it truly is the most amazing experience in the world, far better than a blowjob, far better than saving a penalty, far better than even chilling at home with your friends. phish music is life music. they dedicate it all to you. you've got to feel something when You Enjoy Myself or Divided Sky comes on. if you don't, i'm sure you just haven't experienced life yet. no matter how many bands i will see, no more how many cd's i'll buy, nothing will ever compare to the time spent listening to phish, blazed or not, with friends or by yourself, driving or sitting on top of Red Mountain, they are always going to mean an immense amount to me. and i dare you to find anything that can improve your life as much as phish's music. for whenever the going is shit, the road you are leading is a little tilted and skewed, you can rely on phish to make your life great, by just listening to them play music. i owe an immense debt of gratitude to phish, for they honestly have changed my life. i can't comprehend life without them. on days when it was hard to get up, what got me up was knowing i'd be able to listen to them, to throw in 12-31-95 Reba, or the 11-19-92 Divided Sky, or some classic shows like 12-13-97, 8-9-98, or 12-14-95, and be saved. i've been saved by four goofy looking guys from vermont, who play the music they love because they love the music they play. it truly is time for the last rewind, this has all been wonderful, but now they're on their way, just when it's time you think to leave it all behind, you've got to find a way to but there's nothing i can say to make it stop. thanks phish, thanks ernest, thanks fish, thanks gordo, thanks mac, it's been a wonderful experience, thanks for the music.  and now i'm on my way. do yourself a favor: open your mind and listen to some phish. you'll never forgive yourself if you don't.  signing off
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello and my name is brendan ward, i live in helena, montana, i'm 16 and 354/365th days. i used to have a website hosted by blogger, but it was quite inappropriate and quite defaming to certain people i.e eminem and ally meyer, so i decided to lay off of that whole thing.  But this website will take ship once more, it'll basically be a daily journal of my life as i see it, with hopefully a lot of good stuff, and hopefully a lot of fun as well.  A little about me:  Favorite food: steak and baked potatoes Favorite movie: Lock Stock and Two Smoking Barrels and The Grateful Dead live at Winterland Arena 1978 Favorite song: Terrapin Station by the Grateful Dead Favorite move: right jab to the throat with a tire iron Favorite sports icon: Heinrik Larsson Favorite Football Match of all time: Celtic 6 Rangers 2- Martin O'Neills first Old Firm match Favorite Book: On the Road- Jack Kerouac Favorite Fashion item: my adidas one-piece jumpsuit or my man camel toe shorts Favorite line from a movie: "and one more thing...it's been emotional" big chris from lock stock and two smoking barrels, a film everyone should see at least 3 times in their life Favorite human being of all time: che guevara, james joyce, and jerry Least Favorite Human being: G W Favorite curse: for fuck's sake or fucking shit Favorite word: brendan Favorite voice: katie f.'s Longest period of time without sleeping: 65 hours with horrendous hallucinations Longest period of time without showering: 5 weeks in 2003, just because i wanted to smell like shit Longest time without eating food: 4 and a half days. just wasn't hungry. then i ate a lot and got hunger pains Most famous claim to fame: met abe from the road rules something odd about yourself: i have a third nipple and i sleep naked, no matter what time of year it is Another interesting thing: my intelligence peaked in the third grade One more interesting thing: i'm the only kid i know to get suspended from elementary school. i told this fatty new girl that hanson sucked.  favorite drink: fierce melon gatorade or lemonade    i just watched You Got Served tonight and have been unable to listen to rap music or watch coreographed dancing on t.v.  this website will express my innermost thoughts, have lyrics i find inspirational and will be a good stress reliever. peace,  brendan 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>