<Blog>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Democrats have even made Wal-Mart an issue in the presidential race. Sen John Kerry has called the company that provides paychecks to 1.4 million americans, "disgraceful" and "Unconscionable."  Wal-Mart stores "destroy communities" and "drive me crazy", said kerry's wife, Teresa Heinz Kerry.  This was told to a group in Minnestora, the home of Target Corp.  She failed to mention to her audience that she had bought more than $1 million in Wal-Mart stock.  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Make you perfect in every good work to do his will, working in you that which is helplessness in his sight, through Jesus Christ; to whom be glory for ever and ever. Amen. Heb 13:21    MILITARY AND WAR................................   Information that never reaches the front page of the newspapers : 1)The UK has signed a deal witht he United States to purchase 64 Block IV Tomahawk Cruise Missiles at a cost of $1,937,500 each which totals $124 million dollars. Now, I think President Bush knows what he is doing. With this money he can help in many areas of America and abroad.  2)Saudi Royal Family lambasts Michael Moore's movie, "9/11" This is from an article in todays Telegraph newspaper. Saudi Royal family lambasts Michael Moore for twisting the truth in his 9/11 film. The Royal family has launched a bitter attack on the American Film-maker over his claims that the Bush administration secretly smuggled a number of high ranking Saudi nationals out of the US in the immediate aftermath of the Sept. 11 attacks. The Royal family states that Moore failed to carry out adequate research into his controversial claims that the Saudis were involved with Osama Bin Laden. Michael Moore made a request prior to making his movie, to visit Saudi Arabia and this request was granted to him, but he never came, said Prince Turks. Michael Moore missed an important opportunity to find out key facts. Instead he made a movie of lies to hurt our country and other countries.  3)Marines publicy dissed Vietnam War "hero" Kerry: This article was in the New York Post. A group of Marines publicy dissed the Vietnam War hero in the middle of a crowded restaurant. Kerry approached four Marines and asked them questions. The Marines were polite but curt while chatting with Kerry. They turned downright nasty after Kerry thanked them "for their service" and left. "He imposed on us and I disagree with him coming over here shaking our hands." one marine said, adding, I'm 100% against him." A sergeant with 10 years of service said, "I speak for all of us. We think we are doing the right thing in Iraq" before saying he is to be deployed there in a few weeks and is "eager" to go and serve. Kerry talks against war and the troops over in Iraq and then tries to be nice to them when confronted by military, this shows his true colors---two sided!!!!   OUT OF THE MOUTHS' OF BABES:  In the first book of the bible, Guinessis, God got tired of creating the world, so he took the Sabbath off.  Adam and Eve were created from an apple tree. Noah's wife was called Joan of Ark. Noah built an ark, which the animals come on to in pears.  Lot's wife was a pillar of salt by day, but a ball of fire by night.  The Jews were a proud people and throughout history they had trouble with the unsympathetic Genitals.     
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "May the Lord bring you into an ever deeper understanding of the love of God and the endurance that comes from Christ." 2 Thes. 3:5    WHAT IS AN AMERICAN.....   You probably missed it in the rush of news recently, but there was actually a report that someone in Pakistan had published in a newspaper an offer of a reward to anyone who killed an American, any American.  So an Australian dentist wrote the following to let everyone know what an American is, so they would know when they found one.  An American is English, or French, or Italian, Irish, German, Spanish, Polish, Russia, or Greek. An American may also be Canadian, Mexican, African, Indian, Chinese, Japanese, Korean, Australian, Iranian, Asian, or Arab, or Pakistani, or Afghan. An American may also be Cherokee, Osage, Blackfoot, Navaho, Apache, Seminole, or one of many other tribes known as Native Americans.  An American is Christian, or he could be Jewish, or Buddhist, or Muslim. In fact, there are more Muslims in America than in Afghanistan. The only difference is that in America they are free to worship as each of them chooses. An American is also free to believe in no religion. For that he will answer only to God, not to the government, or to armed thugs claiming to speak for the government and for God.  An American is from the most prosperous land in the history of the world. The root of that prosperity can be found in the Declaration of Independence, which recognizes the God given right of each person the pursuit of happiness.  An American is generous. Americans have helped out just about every other nation in the world in their time of need. When Afghanistan was overrun by Soviet army 20 years ago, Americans came with arms and supplies to enable the people to win back their country. As of the morning of September 11, Americans had given more than any other nation to the poor in Afghanistan.  Americans welcome the best, the best products, the best books, the best music, the best food, the best athletes. But they also welcome the least.  The national symbol of America, The Statute of Liberty, welcomes your tired and your poor, the wretched refuse of your teeming shores, the homeless, tempest tossed. These in fact are the people who built America. Some of them were working in the Twin Towers the morning of September 11, 2001 earning a better life for their families. I've been told that the World Trade Center victims were from at least 30 other countries, cultures, and first languages, including those that aided and abetted the terrorists.  So you can try to kill an American if you must. Hitler did. So did General Tojo, and Stalin, and Mao Tse-Tung, and every blood-thirsty tyrant in the history of the modern world. But, in doing so you would just be killing yourself. Because Americans are not a particular people from a particular place.  They are the embodiment of the human spirit of freedom.  Everyone who holds to that spirit, everywhere, is an American.    IMPORTANT......IMPORTANT........IMPORTANT..............   November 2 will be here before you know it. Know the correct information, study the Presidential Candidates, Pray for God's guidance on who would be a good leader for our country.  Remember, those of you with children, we need a President who puts God first, who puts family values first, who cares about our children's education and their religious beliefs. A President who respects marriage as being between a man and a woman.  Who holds daily Bible studies at the White House and allows other members of the staff to do the same, a President who prays daily for America's safety and for guidance in making decisions.  
      
</post>


</Blog>