<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, I was the lucky winner of a root canal.  I have previously had root canals, however, this was a particularly nasty one.  It was also my first "service" by this new, very "gameshow host" dentist.  Another first was the nitrus oxide that they gave me to keep me from jumping out of the chair.  By the way, if you ever need to go to the dentist for anything more than a cleaning, check up, etc, you should MOST DEFINITELY ask for this!!!  I could go on and on, but just take my word for it.  IT ROCKS!!!  Anyway, the root canal was so "invasive" that they had to give me a NARCOTIC to ease the pain... well, so much for that... I have 2 children.  Narcotics are just not an option.  Last night, since my DH was home, I took one... it was quite potent.  I was dizzy, sleepy, and generally pain free. Today, however, being on mommy duty and all, I have a strict regimine of ONLY Ibuprofen (placebo basically).   I'm wishing for the nitrus!!! Aamena 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really honestly might be losing my mind. Aneesa is still awake *SCREAMING* in her bed since 2 hours ago, and Zaeyd, well, he's sleepy, thinking he's hungry...  THE BOY JUST ATE  almost 4 oz.   My head is about to split open.   I'm starting to wonder if I can handle a full courseload.  Maybe I need to hire some help??  Hmmm... now there's an idea...NOT do everything myself... how novel. In any case, I need to do something fast, or I'm going to just lose it.  I was watching Oprah the other day and it was about mom's who turn to drugs and alcohol (sometimes manufaturing methamphetamines in their kitchens) just to be able to get through the day.  I was dumbstruck... but not for the reason you might be thinking... I was   NOT   thinking " Wow, what a horrible mother... how could she do that to her poor children.  I would NEVER do such a thing.. ."   Nope, not even close... I think I actually thought " Wow, you can make meth in your kitchen??  Maybe I should google that one... OH, I couldn't do that, that whole Islam being against intoxicants and all.. . DAMN!!"   The point is, once you have kids, you learn to judge others a lot less... at least that's what I learned.  Alhamdulillah.  I hope I don't have many more lessons to learn... Aamena 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           No offense to all those on the George W. bangwagon!!! ______________________________________________________________     There's a teacher in a small Texas town. She asks her class how many of them are Bush fans. Not really knowing what a Bush fan is, but wanting to be liked by the teacher, all the kids raise their hands except one boy--Johnny.       The teacher asks Johnny why he has decided to be different.    Johnny says, " I'm not a Bush fan ."    The teacher says, " Why aren't you a Bush fan ?"    Johnny says, " I'm a John F. Kerry fan ."    The teacher asks why he's a Kerry fan.    The boy says, " Well, my mom's a Kerry fan, and my Dad's a Kerry fan, so I'm a Kerry fan!"        The teacher is kind of angry, because  this is Texas , so she says, " What if your Mom were a moron, and your dad were an idiot.&nbsp; What would that make you?"        Johnny says, " That would make me a Bush fan ."   ______________________________________________________________     Out of the mouths of babes...     Aamena    
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
               from    www.muslimsforkerry.com       BUILDING BRIDGES TO THE MUSLIM AMERICAN COMMUNITY       John Kerry and John Edwards recognize the many contributions that Muslim Americans have made to our nation and will work to protect and defend the civil rights and civil liberties of all Americans, including Muslim Americans. They support rigorous enforcement of our nations civil rights laws so that all Americans, including Muslims, can live, work, learn, worship, and gather without fear or discrimination.     A Kerry-Edwards administration will not tolerate the targeting of Muslim Americans for threats, violence or discrimination based on their religion.      E ND THE  E RA OF  J OHN  A SHCROFT :     The Ashcroft Justice Department has unfairly targeted Muslim and Arab Americans and has selectively enforced the immigration laws against these communities. John Kerry and John Edwards will uphold constitutional rights and protections, and civil rights laws. They will also strengthen terrorism laws that work, including sharing information with local law enforcement. And they will e nsure that American citizens held as detainees receive access to counsel, an opportunity for judicial review and at least minimal constitutional safeguards.      A MEND THE  USA PATRIOT A CT :    While John Kerry and John Edwards support the majority of the PATRIOT Act, they, along with a growing number of both Democrats and Republicans, believe that certain provisions should be modified. They support efforts, such as the bipartisan-sponsored Security and Freedom Ensured (SAFE) Act, to amend the PATRIOT Act to set reasonable limits on access to library, medical, and other records containing the sensitive, personal details of the lives of law-abiding Americans and on the conduct of so-called sneak and peek searches.      E ND  R ACIAL  P ROFILING :    As a former prosecutor, John Kerry knows that racial profiling is nothing more than ineffective law enforcement and must be prohibited. He and John Edwards support the End Racial Profiling Act, which would ban racial profiling and require federal, state, and local law enforcement to take steps to end and prevent racial profiling.      S TRENGTHEN  H ATE  C RIME  L AWS :    John Kerry and John Edwards support strong enforcement and equal justice for all victims of hate violence. Both support expansion of our nations hate crimes law and Kerry has consistently voted for the Local Law Enforcement Enhancement Act, also known as the hate crimes bill.      P ROMOTING  M UTUAL  C ULTURAL  U NDERSTANDING :    Kerry and Edwards will support the establishment of study centers within American universities, expand development of American corners in educational and cultural institutions in Muslim countries, and launch a significant translation project. They will work with the private sector and international institutions to  help civil society groups and governments aid democracy, public participation, free expression, transparency and efficient economic management.       P ROTECT  W ORKPLACE  R ELIGIOUS  F REEDOM :     John Kerry has led the fight for the Workplace Religious Freedom Act which will ensure that no American is forced to choose between the job they need and the faith that sustains them .                       Aamena     Know that the life of this world is only play and amusement, pomp and mutual boasting among you, and rivalry in respect of wealth and children, it is like vegetation after rain, the growth is pleasing to the tiller; afterwards it dries up and turns yellow; then it becomes straw...&nbsp; Race one with another in hastening towards Forgiveness from your Lord and towards Paradise... (57: 20-21)   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;                        
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some would say it's too early, or that I'm jumping the gun here, but, I really can't help it.  I have been so FAT (read pregnant) for so long, that two weeks post partum seems like forever, and I NEED to do something about this ugly baby belly jiggle.... YUK.  Today alone I have spent so much time looking at clothes, magazines, etc.  In the end, I just come back to "until  you are at a healthy weight, all the clothes in the world won't matter."  Not to mention that I am probably going to Zambia over Christmas break to meet DH's family... that gives me what 4 months.... ONLY 4 MONTHS!!!!!! CRYKEE (sp) I have to get busy...  I was planning to do South Beach, but it costs money to join the online community... Weight Watchers is free (well the message boards anyway)... In any case, I have to lose weight and fast... I'm feeling toooooo flabby for my own good.  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm doing better this time than last time.  My daughter only technically breastfed for about 3 days, then I pumped and bottle fed... HEY SHE GOT BREAST MILK ALRIGHT!!!  Yeah, so I'm a tad sensative about it ;o).  Anyway, at least Zaeyd is still breastfeeding... the goal is 6 weeks and 1 day. (One day longer than Aneesa).  Let me be frank, for those of you without children... BREASTFEEDING SUCKS!!! It (at least for me) is not a bonding experience.  It is wonderful not to have to get up and make bottles, and it is the BEST nutrition for my baby, but FOR THE LOVE OF GOD, I would hardly call it a party.  In my "circle" complaining about such things would cause you to be completely ostrisized (sp?), and basically excommunicated...  The baby is crying yet again for some boobie, so I guess this one will have to be short.  PRAY FOR ME AND MY BOOBS!!!!!!!!!!  Until Next Time, Aamena 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In the wake of Farenheit 9/11, I find this news unfortunate. ____________________________________________________  from:  urlLink www.MotherJones.com/News/Outfront     .: No Child Unrecruited :.    Should the military be given the names of every high school student in America?  David Goodman  Sharon Shea-Keneally, principal of Mount Anthony Union High School in Bennington, Vermont, was shocked when she received a letter in May from military recruiters demanding a list of all her students, including names, addresses, and phone numbers. The school invites recruiters to participate in career days and job fairs, but like most school districts, it keeps student information strictly confidential. "We don't give out a list of names of our kids to anybody," says Shea-Keneally, "not to colleges, churches, employers -- nobody."  But when Shea-Keneally insisted on an explanation, she was in for an even bigger surprise: The recruiters cited the No Child Left Behind Act, President Bush's sweeping new education law passed earlier this year. There, buried deep within the law's 670 pages, is a provision  requiring public secondary schools to provide military recruiters not only with access to facilities, but also with contact information for every student -- or face a cutoff of all federal aid.   "I was very surprised the requirement was attached to an education law," says Shea-Keneally. "I did not see the link."  The military complained this year that up to 15 percent of the nation's high schools are "problem schools" for recruiters. In 1999, the Pentagon says, recruiters were denied access to schools on 19,228 occasions. Rep. David Vitter, a Republican from Louisiana who sponsored the new recruitment requirement, says such schools "demonstrated an anti-military attitude that I thought was offensive."  To many educators, however, requiring the release of personal information intrudes on the rights of students. "We feel it is a clear departure from the letter and the spirit of the current student privacy laws," says Bruce Hunter, chief lobbyist for the American Association of School Administrators. Until now, schools could share student information only with other educational institutions. "Now other people will want our lists," says Hunter. "It's a slippery slope. I don't want student directories sent to Verizon either, just because they claim that all kids need a cell phone to be safe."  The new law does give students the right to withhold their records. But school officials are given wide leeway in how to implement the law, and some are simply handing over student directories to recruiters without informing anyone -- leaving students without any say in the matter.  "I think the privacy implications of this law are profound," says Jill Wynns, president of the San Francisco Board of Education. "For the federal government to ignore or discount the concerns of the privacy rights of millions of high school students is not a good thing, and it's something we should be concerned about."  Educators point out that the armed services have exceeded their recruitment goals for the past two years in a row, even without access to every school. The new law, they say, undercuts the authority of some local school districts, including San Francisco and Portland, Oregon, that have barred recruiters from schools on the grounds that the military discriminates against gays and lesbians. Officials in both cities now say they will grant recruiters access to their schools and to student information -- but they also plan to inform students of their right to withhold their records.  Some students are already choosing that option. According to Principal Shea-Keneally, 200 students at her school -- one-sixth of the student body -- have asked that their records be withheld.  Recruiters are up-front about their plans to use school lists to aggressively pursue students through mailings, phone calls, and personal visits -- even if parents object. "The only thing that will get us to stop contacting the family is if they call their congressman," says Major Johannes Paraan, head U.S. Army recruiter for Vermont and northeastern New York. "Or maybe if the kid died, we'll take them off our list."  urlLink    
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know who wrote this, I got in e-mail... it's cute. __________________________________________    Southern Women 
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         from   urlLink  www.alashrafia.com       (emphasis and formatting added) 
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I guess, my purpose for starting to "blog" is to have a forum in which to express myself, rant, if you will, to publish certain articles, and basically just have a place to call my own. I hope that you will feel free to post replies, opinions, comments or questions.       I plan on covering such things as religion, marriage, real life, children, school, politics, etc. This should be fun, so lets get underway.      Today is my birthday. Happy birthday to me. While I don't believe that birthdays are a halaal celebration, I do believe that duaa's (prayers) are in order, since I am one year closer to the Akhirah (afterlife). I am now one quarter of a century old... (Old being the operative word there.) I just can't believe in the last 5 years, how many things have changed... whew.       Well, if there are any other "old" young people out there, I wouldn't mind hearing from you... maybe I wouldn't feel so bad!!! Married, 2 kids... geez. I mean, Alhamdulillah. ;o)      .: Aamena :.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>