<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, here I am sitting humming to a rough version of "Prince Charming". It's live and a tad dodgy. Just back from my first day of third year, it wasn't too bad. Not many of my friends are in my classes, but i don't have many friends in my year. Art shall be hillarious, knowing only one person in my class, you just gotta laugh. Got in my credit English and French class. Not sure about maths yet. Lets put the boring school stuff behind us.  Life is becoming to philosophical. Sometimes I wish I was waking up to my third birthday party, when life was easy and I was naive. Oh, to be naive. A wish that not many people share with me. Maybe I'm the only person in the world who sometimes just want to scream, cry and throw a tantrum when they don't get their own way. Sick of being told that I'm old enough to know, but too young to decide. Tired of being one of the girls who sit around and wait for prince charming, maybe i'll spend my whole life looking for him. Can I be princess charming? Can I save my guy? I don't want to be saved.  Thinking can't be good for me, but I do it, a lot more than the average person. Wish that my thoughts would just record themself in this blog instead of me having to recall everything.  Reminicing just makes me think of more things to write. See, even now when I was going to write about what was going through my mind today in french. I am able to write a good couple of unnecassry thoughts. Is this what makes a blog good? If so, please enter me in some kind of "Blog Award".  My mind is wondering again. Where was I? Oh yes! French.. well the fact that I happened to be participating in a french lesson is irrelevant, i'm basically setting the scene.  There I am, 2nd row from the front, rubbing my eyes. A large eyelash appears on my finger and i decide to make a wish. Usually it would be "Make so and so like me" etc etc. Today, is revoloutionary, I wished for an end to world hunger. You're probably thinking , so? It was an eyelash. This though was the first thing to cross my mind, but it lead to me thinking... when other people wish on an eyelash or say, their birthday candles...what do they wish for? A cute boy/girl to like them? To win the lottery? Most likely. What about say, world peace? An end to poverty? I doubt it. John Lennon once said "If everyone wanted world peace, as much as they wanted a new tv set, there'd be peace". These words were just a clever saying to me yesterday but today they meant something. How many times have you wanted something so bad that you'd stop at nothing to get it? If everyone wanted world peace, then we'd stop  at nothing to get it. We'd have it. This is just what John Lennon meant. Why are people so ignorant, why do people care more about what jeans they where and how their hair looks, in 30 years time that won't matter...what will is what you learned and how you used it. Okay, truthfully I stole that last part from a wall in my Religious Education classroom, but it's true. This blog basically goes out to very few people, it's more of a question into the void. Peace and Empathy, Love and huggles good night dear void. Rhona xxx  god is nowhere, god is nowhere, god is now here. 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heehee sing it for me! Well ,I hate to say "I told you so"....wait scrap that no ...i don't hate it. I  l0Ve it! I got dumped....ach well!Being me...A drama queen, i ran down to Amy's at 1am. It was worth it, we ate chocolate and stuff! Now, I'm fine. Glad the Emo Angel is back , to be honest. So I spent the last few days messing about. Last night my friends from school Emma and Becky stayed over, I had a grrrreat time. hehe like frosties. The only problem was i only got four  hours sleep *yawns*! Today was ace, I got two pairs of vans. They're awesome...I shall post some pictures, sooner or later. gotta go, love you and leave you! Peace and Empathy Love and Huggles -Rhona xxx 
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Deary me, who knew so much could happen in one night?! Not me, that's for sure. When I came home I phoned Paul cause he wasn't speaking to me on msn, we chatted which was nice. I asked if he wanted to do something tonight, but he said he was going to Stuart's which was fair enough. He was nice enough to ask Stuart if it was okay if I came. Then I made the mistake of asking "Do you even want me to come?" he said "I'm not bothered".... YOU DO NOT say that to me. It hurt a lot, but he obviously didn't realise. Quickly I told him I had to go, and him talking to me on msn just gave me the impression that I was getting dumpe.So what do I do when I'm upset? Put on some Dashboard, straighten hair and cry :( It does help.      Later on I called Paul, this is when I found out we couldn't go to Stuarts anymore. Would he have even called if I hadn't have called him? Doubtful. Oh, I forgot to say, the other night I asked if I was clingy and he said "It does get annoying, you kissing me all the time" *shocked* ,well you won't be getting any loving from me boy! Anyway, when I phoned him I think he realised I was upset. He was a tad nicer to me, and I realised that he was probably only kidding, it made me feel much better. Although I must admit, I think he's going to dump me! Maybe I'm paranoid! After the phonecall, Amy phoned! So I went down to her's for a bit, we prankied people, including Paul! It was good fun!:) Made me feel a little better ;) .Got home just after 11,keeping in mind I had work the next day (amn't I a clever cookie). Lying in my mum's bed, where I decided to sleep cause I felt like it! Just thought about the day, i'm awefully good at getting upset over nothing! From now on I've got to be less paranoid, that was my thought for yesterday....didn't really work though! Today's been dull, just there my best friend's dad came in. That's about as exciting as my day gets. If you're wondering, Amy's dad is an account...hence why he was here! He was laughing at me cause I'm on msn :) I better go, y'now...work to do *rolls eyes* Peace And Empathy Love and Huggles Rhona xxx 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night after work I called Paul to ask him what he was doing for the night, he was going over to Stuarts for dinner! I really love speaking to him on the phone, I've decided to stop being paranoid and just enjoy this relationship. 'Cause I see it lasting, and I want it too.    Yesterday evening Amy called me to say that all the girls were going up to Joanne's (Lyndsey, Alison and Amy)!So we both went up. It was a really good night, I suprisingly had a lot of fun. Don't think I realised how much I really missed hanging about with them:) Joanne was in Canada for three weeks so she's brought us back pressies, she got me a black paper book, spider pens and shoe laces. The shoe laces are totally awesome, they're black with red stars, I'm gonna wear them with whatever vans, dc's or duffs I choose for next year! During the night this guy called Darren in my year phoned Amy and Alison picked up, she made up this crap about her just finishing with a boyfriend and stuff, whislt I in the background said stuff like "don't tell darren "and "did you tell him that he finished with him for Darren" it was funny cause he totally bought it. When I went home him and his pal Craig called me up asking if what i said was true, i told them it was a wind up. They don't believe me! Oh well the laughs on him! Today works been pretty boring...I was supposed to be meeting Billy and Emma, but i think they'd just think 3's a crowd! So I left it, hope they ain't still there waiting for me....although it would be rather humorous. Listen to how amazing i'm being. Today I was looking at Pauls profile and it said "view my personal website" so i did! It was a face party thing! It said favourite person "Linsey", that's Paul's ex-long term girlfriend, but then I said to myself it's his EX girllfriend, repeating this over to myself a few times made me realise he doesn't have feelings for her, and I was alright when I found on his old profiles "long term relationship" ! :) I'm glad i with him, I'm totally chuffed to bits! He's amazing....ok...maybe i'm a little clingy! I haven't really made plans for tonight, I'll tell you what went down tomorrow! Peace and Empathy Love and Huggles -Rhona xxx 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, that night. Things started off odd at first, I was planning to see my friend Joanne who'd just arrived bac from Canada. Unfortunately she was tired and was going to just stay in. It wasn't too bad because I'd already had an invite from another friend (Nicole) to see i fi wanted to hang out at hers. Paul etc were going. So, I phoned Paul. When I phoned he was in the midset of shaving, I just ased the basics like "Will you walk me" etc. Then he said " Yeah, we'll walk you" and I was like "We?" he said "Yeah, Sarah's here" in the phone call i was just like okay and joingly said "thanks for phoning me" but in my head was..."Why the fuck didn't you call me! You actuallywere gonna go with sarah there." The other night I found out they had a thing for each other but he assured me that he only thought of her as a friend now, and anything else would just be wrong. Anyways, I met them up like 15minutes later! On walking up to Nicole's I realised that Paul was being kinda distant...or was I just being clingy? Either way, something was up. When we got to Nicole's things were cool,and everyone went up to the loft while Paul and I hung out in Nicoles room...well we made out and talked!:) not at the same time! That was the highlight of the night. Later on we went to Nicole's room; all of us this time. We just talked,played cards and doodled. At first things were cool, then Paul started like not wanting to hold my hand and stuff, maybe i'm just being a bunny boiler but hey, it was weird! Then I also noticed he kept staring at Sarah, I pulled Roslyn out the room and showed her, I know she was thinking the same thing. Right now, I'm just back from lunch! Went home for a bit and called Paul, we were fine on the phone and he told me his higher results (well some of them). Then just there I was talking to him on msn, things were y'know ok but he didn't do his usual ' Peace and Empathy, love and huggles -Rhona xxx 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't posted in a while, the reason being I've been kinda busy. The ongoings of the last few days haven't been to significant, if I think of anything I'll mention it. Last night , while I was awake (i think i'm an insomniac), I sat at the end of my mum's bed and just thought. Are we forever haunted to live the same days over and over again? Are we in somewhat of a black hole? Althought I hate the phrase "life is short", last night I believed it. It's hard to do something exciting everyday, but I want to. Maybe this is just me looking into stuff, or I shouldn't have probably listened to "sunscreen" by Baz Lurhman, earlier on in the week. Either way, I scared myself. For a few minutes I was so tempted to just leave my house, and take a train to Oban. To see Chris! At the time I felt I couldn't bare to spend 2 more minutes of routine. Ever think about those days that you can barely remember, the ones where there's nothing worth sharing? We have so many of them. So, i've decided...today after work, I'm going to do something spontanius and every day, from now on. This is a small step, but at least it's in the right direction!      There is one thing on my mind. The other night practically everyone in my house was drunk and/or high. So my mum said it was oay to have friends round for a while at midnight, so they just popped in. One of these people, was Paul. My current boyfriend.  During the night I was sitting on his knee, and my mum came in. She didn't seem bothered. Later on my brother (overprotective bastard) came in and ased everyone's age. Paul is 16, two years older than me. Later on my mum and brother pulled me out into the hall and said something along the lines of "Euan thinks your showing interest in the older boy", it was pretty harsh on Paul...and he heard it. I was really upset once they'd all left. :( My friend Roslyn was staying over so we done girly stuff (that neither of us are accustmed too) like nail painting! We chatted,ate chocolate,drank tea,watched 'Almost Famous'  and stayed up till 6am! Right now I'm at work, it's been somewhat of a skive, haven't had to do anything really. Had a subway sandwich for lunch , t'was awesome! I shall post later on or tomorrow. Peace and Empathy Love and Huggles, Rhona xxx 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday... well I went out with my friends Emma and Roslyn. We went to the town centre and walked about, then over to the skate park. There was this hawt guy at the park, his name was Billy. He was really cool, up himself a bit and he said I talk to much!! I know, what the fuck is he on about!? At night I only went out for a bit, saw Paul, Sarah, Roslyn, Steven and Stuart, just briefly, I got annoyed cause I found out that Paul used to "like" Sarah, I think he realised I was mad...maybe cause I locked him out his house and forced him to walk me home :)  I went home and went on msn, I managed to convince a guy from Canada that I met on BenFolds.org to call me, it was fun. I'm totally playing him cause he's a prick. Then I went to my Dad's house and stayed there. My parents have been divorced, well at least seperated since I was about four, it doesn't bother me. My mum said the only thing I was concerned about was wether or not i would be allowed to take the rabbit to my dad's house ( i was, score) . Anyways, I stayed there. Called Chris and we were talking for ages :) aw, I love the guy. We watched tv together basically, it was fun! Then I felt I should call Paul. So I did, yeah it was cool, but I was too tired to be bothered. So i fell asleep. I'll post about today later on tonight. Peace and Empathy Love and Huggles, Rhona xxx 
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today,was well interesting to say the least.Woke up to my mobile phone ringing, it was my dad. He asked me if i was working today, I had no idea that i was supposed to be. He said we'd discussed it, well we had, but a good few weeks ago. Right now my brother and dad have had a major fall-out. Basically my dad's being a prick. Anyway, he got kinda angry at me. I went back to sleep. Woke up later and got me some brekky, then when i was on msn, my best friend Amy told me she broke up with her boyfriend, well being the best friend i could be. I ran to the co and got some chocolate and sprite:) The best thing to get over a break up. We decided to go into glasgow, for some impulse shopping...and a bite to eat! I had a really good day. I haven't been hangin about with Amy recently. Although this probably sounds very immature, she is kinda neglecting me, I'm not saying that the fact we're drifting apart is her fault. Just I feel that her and my other friend Lyndsey have got so pally. So i've been hangin about with some different people, and they're totally awesome. Sarah, Nicole, Roz and myself are just becoming so close. You know that feeling where you can pretty much share anything with someone, I have that with all of them. They listen too :) ...this emo angel is sounding too happy. Okay, Lyndsey just said that tonight her, Amy and Kirsteen went jogging round the loch. After I spent the whole fucking day with her, she doesn't even mention it to me. I even phoned her to invited her to the cinema , and her mum said she was out jogging, :( I feel really used. This blog is becoming somewhat of a bitching parlour. Where I express...how much I hate everyone. Okay, let me change the tone. People I love... Chris! Where to start.... well Benfolds.org, that's where I met Chris, we clicked (having lots in common including music and the fact we live in scotland). Chris lives in Oban, and i've met him once. We had "something" going on at one point, but it got called off (by chris) ;) but i'll love him forever, we're soul mates! Paul is my current boyfriend, he's really sweet. God knows why he went for me, he's too good for me. Tonight all the gang went to the cinema ('The Gang' being Paul, Stuart, Nicole and Sarah) we saw 'King Arthur', I didn't watch much of it, too busy talking to stuart about films, music, and being vegetarian. We have a lot in common, except our music taste is different. Today was pretty awesome. For the rest of the night I'm basically gonna listen to music and mess about. Have an nice night. Peace and Empathy, Love and Huggles, Rhona xxx
    
</post>


</Blog>