<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I've had the most unfortunate luck of being on a football team. Why you ask? Well I now have practice from 12-3 and then 4:10-6:30. I know, that's something that you would expect, dedecation asides, I really like doing nothing. It's good for me though, because I get to stay in shape.  I have been ignoring my blogging duties. I'm ashamed because I have thought about it and it has been in the back of my mind. I have thought over and over again "You need to update your blog.". Puke. I am too lazy, and I was enjoying my vacation time.  I'm going to be a junior in high school, the big One-One. A year before my senior year, which is the year most colleges look at most intensly. Sucks for me because I don't intend to spend all my time on school this year. I want to experience a lot of stuff. I like always being able to talk to jess right now. She's there, I'm here, and we're happy(at least I am). It's going to suck, because we both have school then practice, and anything outside of it(community service, school functions) and I won't be able to see her as much but it's okay. It's not like she leaves me anyways.  Corny or not, I feel that no matter where in time I might be, she'll be there. She always will I hope, and I promise to always be there for her.  This fills me with great joy, to know that she too can feel the same way as I do and not have to wonder about whether this is true. Everyone would assume that I might be too young to love. Isn't that a complete contradiction? It's like saying you don't know what your emotions are. I know I love her, because I can feel it. I know this because when I'm around her there is a certain feeling of euphoria that I feel. I feel comfortable, I feel true. I can speak what I want, with her understanding me. It's a feeling of warmth, it's like the sun. It's immense power blinds a person who looks too much, just like my love for her, which might possibly be strong enough to kill. I feel good expressing this, I love my Jess...  -Cheers, Rod  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've changed my mind so much I can't even trust it. My mind has changed me so much I can't even trust myself.  Well I woke up with some really nice and really bad messages on my away thingy. I see that the extra mile i've gone to show Dan that you can't ignore me seems to be working. The away messages, signing up to myspace and inviting everyone to by my friend...but i'm bored of it. He thinks i'm a bad friend I suppose. So i'll leave it at that.  Football season offically starts this sunday. Pre-season...wee...then after that I start practice with pads! Yay! I've waited to long with pent up anger, now I get to unleash it all. Fucking sweet. I'm so excited. Who cares if we win, I'm just going to fuck some people up.  I'm really happy, or at least these couple of days I have been. I can't wait to get back to school and see some people...most which I don't want to see, but some I can't wait to see.   This post sucks.   -Cheers,   Rod   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not that i'm saying your wrong(which you are) but Punk came before all that in 1970's. Grunge is okay, as long as it's done right(Nirvana, Alice In Chains). You're just to biased. Music is music, take it for what it's worth. But, most of your music was right, alternative is sucking, pop punk and what not is shit right now(althought there is a lot of great punk, you're just too naive to know it) and rock is taking a turn for the worst, just like Hip-Hop did. You ask what's worse? How about Rock/Rap? Linkin Park already pissed on musical history by actually selling CD's enough to make it platinum. Then we're insulted by them released a "re-mix c.d.". Wait a minute, back in the day shti like this got you shot. The beatles never released their remixed hits. You'll see frank, metal is becoming the next fad. After emo and punk are out done by stores like Hot Topic and magazines like YM by exposing these genres as the "Fad of the year." you'll then see that Metal will be the next sound for the next revolution. Believe it or not, more and more people are buying into the "Shadows fall guitar solo" crap. Our generation of musicians are all lost trying to find the next "Big seller." and small underground bands (such as punk and metal which sells have never been a big point, they've always chosen indie publishers to produce c.d.'s). If you ask me the reason Emo and Punk are so big right now it's because the real meat of the industry is lacking. Smaller bands like The Adicts for example, play in small venus and actually have a closer interaction with their fans then, let's say'; KoRn does playing a 10,000 people arena. You gotta realize though, there's more than just liking music because it's "Not mainstream." This is a long ass comment by the way.-------------------------- Excerpt from my conversation on Myspace...:(  -cheers, Rod 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've never been an art and crafts kind of guy. I can draw, well, I kick ass at drawing. But besides that, i've never, ever been able to shape something out of nothing. So when I sat around with Andrew contemplating the mysteries of space, love, and the grass while he weaved; I never gave second thought to even attempt to creat anything.  *Begin Flashback* Insert wavey blurriness  I sat their and wondered in amazement at how he could manipulate the threads to his liking and produce beautiful pieces of jewlery worthy of being sold for "vintage" at Abercrombie & Fitch. I didn't give thought of trying, I know I suck at building things. When he offered me my inital response was, of course, no. After he explained to me how simple it was I tried it. After 4 "necklaces"(calling them necklaces is a shame, they where really ugly) I produced something that resembled what he had been doing tediously. He looked at me and said  "I hear it's a little easier if you're making it with  someone  in mind."  Maybe it was the practice, but I don't think that. I pulled two threads and held them up...and thought about how perfect one of these would look on Jess. I held the threads and thought to myself of how I should even begin this to not mess it up. I took one of Andrew's necklaces and decided to sort of copy his, minus the really intricate weaving he had on his. After about  3-4  hours I had labeled my project complete. Held it up to the light and was proud of what I had produced. I had taken about 300 times more than I had with the previous ones, but it showed...  *End flashback*  I took Jess out to Ice cream today which resulted in great fun. I'll admit I felt a little sick the whole day, which didn't turn out to be the greatest mood. Yet I enjoyed my time with her.  I love her tons . We stopped at a Baskin 31 Flavors for some ice cream(I stayed traditonal-chocolate- while she got all new-age and got Chocolate Chip Mint or something, it was greenish-blueish) which we then brought back into the car to let it drip on the seats. We then went to pick up her great friend Liz who ended up not knowing what her favorite song was off the Group Sex CD. We drove around until we decided to see what Memo was up too...we ran into him on the street and I raced whoever was driving for him(hit 95 on a 35MPH zone). We dropped liz off and then it was just me and Jess again.  I really wanted to take her to this park, with a giant moon sitting right in the center of the park. It's really nice, but maybe next time...I was going to give her, my little something on the moon too, but I gave it to her in the car.  I told her to turn around for fear of her thinking it was ugly before it was around her neck, and I gently placed it on her and quickly begin a serious of random babblings and blushing(my shy instinct kicking in). I really wanted her to have it though, because I had worked so hard on the weaving...and I wanted her to have it so whenever she ever felt down she could just hold it, kiss it, rub it, etc. etc. and it would remind her that there's someone always thinking of her. Wanting to hold her and keep her forever...so I gave it to her and she loved it. I don't mind if she never wears it, I just want her to have it so she knows  I love her a lot ... well that's enough, it's late, i'm about to fal asleep...hahaha.    I love you Jess!         -Cheers   Rod     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I keep thinking a lot during the night. Tons of stuff go through my mind...but i've been thinking about space a lot. I think it's probably the coolest subject ever.  I know this is a bit off subject...sorry if anyone is offended-wait a minute, no i'm not. I'm more of an evolutionist than a creationist.  Anyways...Evolution is freaking coool. I kept thinking about it and then I get puzzled about a little incident...let me explain.  Primates where an evolution of reptiles. Well, to some sort of reptile(not sure which one). So let's say that we came after reptiles, that was 170 thousand years ago I believe(I could be wrong, i forget =[ ). Reptiles have been here almost since the plants and fungi co-evolved to develop the first land organism.(after insects came the amphibian) the reptile was then brought to existence and has since lived on earth. Soon, evolution brought fourth the Primate from a small shrew-rat like animal. I'm not sure how along the primate came afterwards, we'll say 170 and the reptile 200 thousand... why do we have a bigger brain and more intelligence?     I think about that a lot.  Good times.  -Cheers,   Rod    
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        *Update: Just kidding, I meant everything in my original post. After trying to be his friend, he tells this girl that he doesn't want anything to do with me...so Fuck you!*     I don't usually do a dobule post...or conclude my last post from like 5 days ago.   But I need to address again...another issue, of the same sort. , I don't really want to put up with him, I really want to brush him off and call it a day. I want to say  "Fuck it.",  I want someone else to put up with it. Yet I can't, because no matter what I say, he's my friend.   He was a great friend too.     Maybe we're both changing and spreading off to other directions for diffrent reasons. I can't help but think about last summer, and what we might have been doing right now. We spent hours fisihing all night, days talking about extra phenemenal shit, and how hot it was in Mike's room.  I write my blogs with every intention to make it sound the way I feel, naturally, my last post about my friend was super-charged with pure hatred. It was injected with hate. Of course, I was pissed. But regardless of what he does in the back of my head i'm thinking the same thing, over and over and over again. This guy used to be my friend.   This guy used to be my good friend.     Things change, ideals are changed and people move on. Tonight was diffrent, I annoyed him, he told me to shut the fuck up. And then he told me "See you in hell.". Emotions erupted and words spewed, things rather left inside then let out. Point being, I might have said everything in spite, I meant some of it, just like he did. I'm not upset of what I said, I'm not upset at what he said. I'm upset at the fact this might actually be the end.  This is the end.  I won't feel like this is my fault but I understand it was a group effort of mixed feelings. If this is over Jessica then I can't really do anything to help him. I'm too head over heels to stop now. I'm pretty sure like he said earlier, "I'm not here to tell you how it's going to end. I'm here to tell you how it's going to begin."(The Matrix I believe.) maybe this isn't the ending. But the beginning of something more. This time we won't be so full of ourselves, this time we won't assume too much. Maybe 12 years from now we'll look back at this and laugh. Maybe we won't.  If this is over Jessica i'm saddened to know so. Couldn't he possibly show a little more excitment(it's hard, but i've done it) that we actually got along so great?  Everything will eventually all fall into place.  -Cheers,   Rod   
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Friday, Friday, Friday.    Time to wind down, cool down and take it a little slower. I love weekends, regardless of what, when, where, and with who. I don't know what I'm doing today, althought I didn't cancel the date was moved to Monday because her parents where sort of pissed.  I love her  though, so waiting a little more only builds more anticipation.  I am looking to go out tonight, believe it or not. I want to go watch a movie, I haven't gone to the movies in a while and there are too many movies that are out that sound good and I haven't seen. So I did some thinking, I asked some people, and no one wanted to do anything really(or had plans in place). So I just started randomly choosing people. Hanging out with Nick is the best and all, but I don't think I can take it again. He's way too emo for me.  I sent a Text to my friend luis and in the regular Luis fashion, no response. I sometimes question his motives.  I'm having an alright day. Kind of bummed because my beautiful Jess isn't going to be with me today, but it's alright. We'll be together on monday, and that's only 3 days away.  I'll post up later on tonight when I'm pissed off or in a diffrent mood then happy.   I love you jess.   -Cheers,   Rod   
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I have a knack for upsetting the balance of things. I may be too sarcastic for some people to handle I suppose.  When I ask to barrow a car at  3PM  I expect the car at or around 3PM. So when I called my sister to find out where the car was at  4:15PM , and she yells at me, I'm sort of confused here. I never told her I wanted the car at 3. I asked her to let me barrow it, and she said...  "Sure, I'll bring it over at  3 ."  I assumed there was no strings attatched, and that she literally meant 3PM. So when she said she would bring it over in an hour(it was 4:15 now), my only response was   Why?   It's a feasible argument if you ask me. The car which was allegedly supposed to be at my house at 3 never shows up, and I ask to barrow a car sometime before 5 and she tells me yes, and then I get yelled at for wondering why I'm getting the car 2 hours after the original time?  I'm sorry did I  miss  something?  It seems that my family has a knack for blowing shit out of propertions. When my mom got home I told her how I didn't get the car; thus, no shirts where bought(that was the original intention). She said "Fine, take mine." Remember now, she said it, not me(very important later on.). So I call my sister to tell her that she no longer needs to come over and let me barrow the car because I now had my moms car. She says to me "Okay.". I run upstairs to get my glasses and I walk down the stairs and sit down to tie my shoes. The conversation over heard bothered me a lot.  " Well he bugged me for the car ." My mom replied hastily "Yeah, I don't want him driving either, but he came to me with a sad puppy face and bothered me for the car."-She spoke in a pissed off voice.  Once again, did I  miss  something here ?  I don't remember asking.  She hung up, and I sat there thinking about why she would do that. I wondered to myself why she would lie about that. What kind of advantage was gained, what sort of idea flew through her mind.  She walked right in front of me. I sat there, staring at her.  "So are you going to go?" She told me with a  smile.   Woah, crazy lady. Weren't you just griping about me driving about 2 minutes ago? I didn't budge, I didn't flinch I didn't say anything. With my most monotonous voice I asked her  " Why did you tell her I was bothering you to take the car ."  Why would you lie was what I meant. Her only answer was a sort of summery of what I did.  "Well you said you where going to buy some clothes and now she wasn't here."  " But I never bugged you about it ." I replied, this time, quit angry.  She didn't say anything. She didn't smile, she didn't nod, she didn't say sorry, she just stared at me and turned her head. My sister then says she wants to talk to me. Which, I don't understand, when I got home she didn't say anything. Dumbfounded I was confused, awaiting a wretched confrontation, I had my best defense ready. My tounge was going to be my gun, the cobra ready to attack. It was loaded and coiled, ready to spring to defend myself. I layed down in the living room with her watching TV, trying to force the argument, to only prove her wrong. I tried and tried and tried, but I got nothing. I got absolutely nothing. The empty feeling of having a pent up rage and never expressing it was stuck in my head, and bothering me. I still sit here and wonder what she meant....what they meant.  "... I don't want him driving ..." Could she mean that my trip is off for tomorrow?  Why is it always before it's something I'm so excitied to do. Why is it always when I have something to do...I love you jess, I'll do my best to not cancel on you tomorrow.  -Cheers, (wish me luck)   Rod       *update* Mom must have been PMSing. Asked her again about tomorrow, didn't even argue.  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel sometimes I'm driving on a road shaped like a figure 8.  I know there isn't, I know there is always another way. Yet it seems I can never find that route.  For a couple years now I keep telling myself that I have to change the way I am. Nothing such as character, mind you(my character is grrrreat!).  The smaller details taht improve the way you look, or the way others see you. During the course of the regular school year, or any other day when nothing is planned, I will take about 10 minutes to get ready. I don't really suppose I care, since I'm never really trying to impress anyone at school. I figure that if I actually took some time, say an  extra 10 minutes -everything would be a little diffrent. Everything would be a little nicer. I wouldn't have to sit in 1st period mindlessly wondering why I chose the shirt I did for that day. It was a good idea last night, but that was last night.  Ths is not the only point that I'm trying to express, that's the smaller part of it. I'm a very motivated guy when it comes to, well, being motivated. Yet for those 6-7(can't rememebr) hours in school I feels so sluggish. I'll only do the bare minimum to get the grade that I need to make a 3.5 or so. I know I can achieve more, I know I can do a lot more when it comes to me. The question still remains of course...  Why don't you do something about it?  I would like to say I have attempted it, but I can't. It's a cycle, I have to fall in this cycle to function properly. Anything else would only produce effort on a lower scale, since I would be forcing it upon myself. When I force things onto myself I only manage to make them worse. I work at a pace, and it's understandable possibly to others, but I have this problem. I have this little problem, many of you have heard it before, we like to call it being  lazy . It drags me down A lot.  Let's take this summer for example.  I needed to get my permit and my drivers traning. I held it all off, I didn't care, "Why should I" I kept telling myself. There's no real big gain in my life with it.   Then I met Jessica.   I know, the next sentence is going to be cliche but I really mean it when I say it. I've never felt like this about anyone before. People have nibbled and bit me at it. Yet i've never been like this. Agh! I seem to have gone off track again.  When I met her I thought she was cool, you know, regular stuff. Then it hit me, like a bag of bricks right in the face. I wanted to show her everything, take her everywhere. I wanted to show her things I wanted to do with someone I thought was  special to me.   Gears started turning and I started to get my act together. I got my drivers training, and my permit in one week. I feel that I really need some sort of motivation in order to move, to do things, to re-act.  Anyways, my car is here. I need to go pick some people up and go get some clothes because everyone wen to knotts without me.  -Cheers, Rod 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's never the same experience here in Orange County.  I'm currently in summer school, I have two days left before i'm left to be free. Yet there are four schools in my one school, for summer school(sounds complicated). The schools here are Costa Mesa High School, Newport-Harbor, Corona Del Mar, and Estancia. It's a big culture shock to walk onto campus and find such a diverse network of schools and students.  You basically have your rich kids, and everyone else.  The Estancia Parking lot during the regular year is not too packed, there's always room for more cars. During summer school you're lucky if you can find a parking spot. There are so many Mercedes, so many BMW, so many nice cars, of course, daddy bought them. Yet it makes you think-how care free this kids are. They have everything they could ever want, Hell, i'm struggling to find a 98 Mitsubishi Eclipse that I can afford. In some ways I envy their financial status, I envy how they could possibly have enough to even afford a car for me if they chose to purchase me one. Then I look again, and i'm glad I am who I am, with what money I may have. Many of them are habitual drug users, many of them are alcoholics, I guess having money is license to disregard care for yourself.  During the line for lunch(I love watermelon) I overheard another Corona Del Mar girl talk about how she got pulled over speeding down PCH with a trunk full of alcohol. Now, you have to remember she is not only speeding, but endangering others, with a trunk full of alcohol she isn't even supposed to have. Her friend said  "Oh my god, really?" in a calm voice "Yeah! It was like so freakin' dumb!" she replied I wanted to ask, but before I even turned around to face them, her friend asked my question... "What did your parents do?" "Nothing really, just to not do it again, the cop just told me to go home."   What the hell is this shit?   If it was me, I would have had my car impounded, i would have been fined, ticketed, and had my license revoked. When I heard this I was so pissed. How the hell is that even fair? Because she drove a BMW she can't get a fucking ticket? Stupid fucking rich kids, they'll all get what they deserve.  moving away from this for right now, or ever, 2 more days to have to put up with this crap.  I'm still trying to figure out what to do with my life. I'm not too certain on what to spend my life doing, grade wise, i'm elgible to any college really. Well, a pretty ok college with a 3.6 overall GPA and tons of extre curricular activies...questions is...  Do I really want to go to college?  No.   Do I really want to go to the Airforce?   No.    I'm sort of lost, because I don't want 4 more years of schooling, but I don't want to work labor and the only other place I can get a decent career, at least to me, is the Military.  Besides, my family has some sort of history in there anyway. I'v had family in the military since World War 2. I won't be a grunt though, i'll be an engineer, or something. As of right now all I have to look forward too is getting my car so I can take my little somebody everywhere.  -Cheers,   Rod   
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so it seemed to me.  When you decide to call someone a friend(let alone a best-friend) it is(i think)because there is a trust, there is a bond. There is something there for both parties to contribute from. What you ask? Maybe a little advice, a shoulder to lean on...anything really. Maybe you have a hot date and you're red shoes don't go with the outfit you chose; so you call up you're friend and ask him to let you barrow his black shoes.  I've never really had many friends. I have had plenty of acquaintances before, but never really friends. At the moment my friends are in the single digits(they always have been), of maybe 5 at the most, I don't feel like counting.  When you call someone your bestfriend you say this because you aknowledge the bond and trust and what not. You acknowledge that your friendship is a step above, it's a house built on solid ground, not on an emergency landslide cliff. You both nod your head, and say "Yes, I trust this man.".  Sometimes you can be wrong.  Sometimes you can call someone you're best-friend, accidents happen.  I have never been one to talk behind someones back. I have never felt it a good way to release any type of stress that or tensions they have put on me. Yet I had a friend(best if you will) once, who did that to me. Who used words such as "He, him, that guy" to describe me so that I wouldn't know.   I'm not stupid .  I decided to rant about this, because it has been bothering me for quiet the time now. Being unable to fully express what I mean on my other blog didn't help either. So let me sum up what I mean,  Fuck you . In simplest way, I just want to walk up to him, and stick my middle finger in the middle of his face. About 1 year, and all it's been is good time after good-time. To trash it like this and now. Our friendship was built on the beach, and then a 40 ft. tsunami blew it to the center of california. In a matter of days it shambled, mainly because he just assumed too much. Yet i said today, about awhile ago, that because he asked nicely, or because he was going to  bitch  about it, he wouldn't control me with constant nuisance and chilidish sub-messages. Hopefully you run into another person who'll stick by you, because as far as I can see, we're done. Posting on my blog about what you think I feel for someone, when you can't even express yourself is something of an unorthodox approach.  Too bad pal, we where destined to be great. Hell, I would have took a bullet for you.  -Cheers,   Rod  
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm moving away from xanga. Good-bye xanga.  It sucked anyways.  It was ugly, it was sloppy, it was everything I didn't want. I really want a journal. The old one will still be up, but I won't update ever again.  I'm happy that i'm with Jess now. Even if it ends another friendship, it's not my fault, I can't help but feel attracted to sweet people. Yet if this is how it's going to end, then let it be, because I will NOT give up something this great because someone else feels like they're going to cry.   Cry me a river.      I don't care.   I'm going to try to actually do what I set off to do with my orginal Blog. Which ended up being garbage compared to what I felt really. Yes I tried to think about making my posts private, but why should I censor myself to please other people? I don't, and I won't. So this xanga might be a little harsh, so if feelings get hurt-live with it.  Am I sorry about it? Will I be sorry about it?   No.   This wasn't forced upon you, i never force fed you the link. So you came on your own accord and if it upset you then i'd suggest you leave. Good god am I dick.  -Cheers,   Rod  
    
</post>


</Blog>