<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I found this cool website with lots of free stuff for websites. It is Gifs Animations Clipart Software Hosting. It includes java scripts which I'm implimenting in my website. I started yesterday adding java script to the photograph pages. When you click on a photograph to view the larger size, on the pages with the java script, a pop-up will give the larger picture. With this design, you won't leave the photograph page which will be convienent to those with dial-up, and also will help control bandwith on my server. It will take awhile because I plan to convert all of my photographs to that format. I'm starting in order on the list on the main page. I won't keep updates as to when I finish java scripts on each page because its not new information. Its just something behind the scenes that makes navigation in my website more simpler.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well I got around to going to the public library today to look up information on the Hotel Denison and the 'old' Denison High School. I found enough information to write a small report on both buildings. I posted the Hotel Denison information today, but I'll post the high school information another day.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I started adding photo descriptions to the galleries. I'm going in order with the buildings list on the main page.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      July 23    August 4 - Same view    The facade on JcPenny building at Sher-Den Mall has been torn off. The only recognizable part of the old mall is the powerplant on the back side. According to the news article at the first of the year, they would take about 6 months to demolish the old mall, which is about right. August will be 5 months. Once the land is clear and I take final photographs, I think I will keep the Sher-Den Mall up for awhile as a memorial, however I will go through my photo collection and reorganize the site.
     

    
</post>


<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys!  I just signed up with this new blogger, and i'm so excited!  Okay okay, I know, simple minds simple pleasures, right?  LOL well this is where I will just let out my most inner soul.   I will improve the blogger as time goes by, adding info and pictures and learing how to operate it.  For now, my narrowmindedness won't allow me to do anything more than jost post.  =D  Ta ta for now!  ~Jimmy 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes I just hate emotions.  They can be a real bitch!  And since depression is heriditary, I have more of a battle.  This is my third time writing this bloq.  The first time, my browser did the stupid Illegal Operation on me, and I had to rewrite it, then my entire computer shut down on me, so I gave up and went to bed.  That was about 11am this morning.  Emotions is like prision.  There are times when you're locked away in confusion, depression, sadness and grief.  Then there's days you're set free in happiness and joy.  Those of you that's familiar with Star Trek the Next Generation, sometimes I'm jealous of Commander Data, being able to just remove an emotion chip.  And on the Golden Girls, Sophia seems to have emotion, but most of the time she's a bitch.  She's my favorite character.  But with me, its like a roller coaster.  Up and down, all around.  I know people aren't perfect, but why do they do things the way they do?  When I'm not completely alert, just waking up, tired from lack of sleep, are bad times to discuss anything important or serious and certain friends of mine know that, but yet they insist on discussing things they know will make me angry.  It is like they set me up.    And I just love how your friends tell you "You don't like me" or "You dont love me" or "You hate me."  It is almost as if they have some direct tie to your heart and brain telling you how you think and when you tell them they scream that it isn't the truth.  These are people that you've know for years that know you.  And why is it your friendship may last for a few years, then suddenly the small things that you don't do make your friend more angry than the good things that you do for them when in the past it didn't make a difference?  It is as if they are bored with the friendship and want someone different.   And its funny, that, certain friends expect you to perform a certain way, and if you don't, it makes them mad, and they stay angry at you until you conform to what they think is right or not.   Then again, maybe its me.   Maybe I need to be a bitch verbally, like Sophia, and those that don't like it can just leave, and those that it don't bother will end up being close to my heart.   I still feel the same now as I did before I went to bed to sleep this morning.  I don't know what emotion to display?  Should I cry or be angry or what?  I know what emotion I'm not in the mood.  I'm definatly not feeling joy right now.  I feel I lost one of the best friends I've had.  This friend I met while I was still living with my mom, and gave me encouragement when I was kicked out, and through loosing my job at McDonald's, and through having to move, and loosing my job at Cigna.  I need a hug.  Just a hug from anyone, a friend, family, someone... even a stranger if they tell me everything will be okay   :`(  
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ug!  It's after 3am and I'm sitting here working on my personal website, figuring out this blog program, and watching Star Trek Voyager.  I took a Benadryl to help me sleep.  Before, I had taken two tablets, and it completely knocked me out for about 12 hours.  A friend of mine suggested that I cut one in half and take it, which I did.  However I'm not feeling anything so I'm thinking about taking the second half, and seeing what one table will do for me.   Miss Kitty is playing with something in my closet.  She's really cute and adorable.  She's my baby.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
            Well its almost 6am, and this is me. I guess I should get some sleep! lol Its wee hours in the morning! Compared to yesterday, I feel alot better. My friend and I discussed things and tempers were just lost, but after I woke up and had time to get my mind together (and of course being depressed all day) then I was more able to talk about important stuff without getting pissed.  I just got through drawing some graphics using windows paint. I really need to get a graphics program, but that will have to wait until I find a job, because good graphic software costs around $200.  I will be working more on my personal site. I'm anxcious about getting it finished, along with my old building site. I have been working on my website for a long time, changing the design several times. I think I'm pretty much going to leave it as is. I'm really satisified with the layout. Now I will just add more stuff (translation: junk) lol.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
          If this is how the 21st century urinal appears, then I think I'll just go outside and use a tree!  I slept late again today :( Oh well. I'm considering going back to McDonald's, although it is not a final decision. It will be a last option.  I'm sitting here watching Willy Wonka &amp; The Chocolate Factory. I've never seen this movie before, and now I know why lol. Anyway, just wasting time until I have to leave in about 10 mins to go to my aunt Eva's house. We're going to meet once a week and have dinner together.  I'm going to try to update this blog on a daily basis, unless if I'm out of town, but I don't see that happening for another couple of months. My friend Canaan from Longview has a birthday coming up at the end of September, which I'm thinking about going back to Longview to visit him then.   
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      True Friendship is like diamonds. Rare but precious. Today a best friend of mine, Iyan, whom I hold our relationship close to my heart, met 3 years and six months ago. It really does not seem that long, but so much has happened in my life during that time. I was still living with my mom when we met, so he's like the last friend I have that I had when I was still living at home.  I have had good friends, but it seems they get married, or move, and they just completely forget about the friends they have. And when you do hear from them, it is in form of mass email from stuff they "share" with all of their friends.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think sleep is a waste of time. I didn't sleep at all last night, I stayed busy cleaning house. This morning early, I had to call maintenance to come up to fix my leaky faucet in my bath tub. Finally about 11am, I went to sleep. I woke up about 1:30, so I only got about 2 1/2 hours sleep in about 36 hours. I've been staying up all night and sleeping all day. Its hard to find a job that way, so I'm trying to get my sleep in order. By 6pm today, I realized I hadn't eaten in 24 hours, so I had to eat. I did some grocery shopping and visited my aunt Eva.  I also went with Henry, a friend of mine, to a resturant and we went to a store to see if I could find some stuff cheep to sell on e-bay for a profit.  I have an idea to make additional money for profit on ebay, so I hope it will go well.  I got home about 9 and went to bed at 9:30pm. I woke up at about midnight after a dream, which I had a hard time to go back to sleep so I thought I would post in my bloq for today. I'm tired and sleepy but the way I feel I know I wont go to sleep :((   
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
          A few days has gone by since I submitted an entry to my journal. I thought I would try to update it daily, but I get side tracked and forget to submit an entry.  I got a side job working as a mystery shopper. Of course I cannot put any details here as to my assignments, but it is interesting. Actually I would love to study to be a health inspector for the health department. When I use to work at McDonald's, we had some health inspectors that were really great, and some that were just down right bitches. After my experience with McDonald's you can guess what kind of health inspector I would be lol!!!  I'm sitting here watching Star Trek the Next Generation. I haven't seen this series in so long. Let's see, what else can I ramble on about. Ah, we might get rain. I probably jinxed it saying that. It appears to be getting cloudy outside. I love rain.  I was suppose to meet my friend, Iyan online, but he's sick. He's having stomach problems. I've chatted with Sumit, a friend from California. I haven't heard from Henry, my local friend. Must made plans without me :((((( Oh Well, I know when I'm loved! Just kidding!  *yawn* okay if you're still reading this then you deserve  a cheer! 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
           I had to get up early today. I got a job assignment as a mystery shopper but had to go to Durant, Oklahoma. Henry and I went up, and afterward we took some picutres of an old hotel in downtown. I got back home and my new drivers liscence was in the mail. My picture actually came out better than I expected.  I entered the information from the business visit afterward I layed down and took a nap. I got up and put some spiced chicken in the oven to bake and I had a spinich salad.  It rained about 7am along with thunder and lightning.  We have had an unusually wet summer, not to mention cooler than normal.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
           I'm listening to Get Real soundtrack.  The movie is about a gay high school student dealing with coming out of the closet.  Very good.    I just finished making my bed, and straightning up some stuff.  It seems that's all I do these days lol.  I make a mess, I clean.  My front room is cluttered, but that's with junk I'm trying to sort and organize.  But my bedroom and sitting area I'm trying to keep clean.  It is kind of cloudy outside, I hope we get some rain, which I doubt.  But I can't complain.  We have been dipping into the low 60s at night time, which is very unusual for August.  At least for Texas.  I've posted my first essay on my personal site.  I'm going back and forth between my Urban Exploration site and my personal site.  I get bored with one, I just start working on the other.  Please pray for a friend of mine.  His name is Iyan.  He's been sick alot this year, and I'm concerned about his health.  Right now he's sick at his stomach.  I'm really worried about him.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have made a decision, which I know I will receive criticism, but, can't make everyone happy, right?  I have done this before, and backed out, and who can say that won't happen again?    The last few years my life has been a wreck. Even though I may seem happy on the outside, down deep I feel a void, something missing from my life.  I have really wonderful friends, which I hope they will not allow this decision to affect that.  I would like to make it known that it is my wishes and desire to return actively as one of Jehovah's Witnesses, effective September 1, 2004.  Looking back over my life, my happiest moments were as an active Jehovah's Witness. My memories, both good and bad, are within the faith.  Life is not perfect, people are not perfect.  People are going to make mistakes.   They always say, never quit your place of employment out of anger at someone.  Why can't the same thing apply to religion with and directed by imperfect people?  The past few weeks, I have not spoke this with anyone, but I always dream about my dad at least once a night.  And when I wake up, I always remember what comes to my mind when I saw him for the last time, laying in a casket.  I promised him I would see him in Paradise.  I would take what route I feel in my heart is the best way for me personally to make that happen.    Life is too short to be angry at anyone or anything.  Jesus Christ taught that we should love each other, show compassion, humility, and encourage one another.  One of the things that makes me feel like I'm floating on clouds from joy, is when an elderly person smiles from me encouraging them with Scriptural thoughts, and up on stage, giving talks, watching people that are honest heartly listening, and using that as an opportunity to encourage and put smiles on people in this smileless world.  This is my choice.  Nobody has "talked me into" this, and this journal entry is the first time I have made this publicly known.  If you know anything about Jehovah's Witnesses, you will know that I will have to make sacrafices, and stop doing things I have been doing since I became inactive four years ago.   I wish everyone the best, and I hope my friends respects my decision on this matter and not let it cause any divisions.  Regards, Jimmy  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>