<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       WOW HEY YALL!!    sorry i havent written in forever..i have just been SOOO busy with Holly here..then her leaving.then having school! omgsh Highschool is a nightmare!! just one week into it and  SOOOOO   much     homework    already..it is waaay unbeliveable, and i just hope things will tinker down from now on..ahhahah! and well i just dont know what to do!   well anyways... so Monday i actaually start 'swimming' in the pool for GHS, Monday, Wednesday, and Fridays i have to be at the stupid pool @ 6:30 am...and Tuesdays and Thursdays @ 7 am ((not much better)) and well i start up CGAT practice again on Monday too! How ridiculous..cause im just gunna have to go to swim practice, then school, then swim practice again!! AHH GEEZ! OH well...i guess thats what i get for swimming..though i dont have to go to GCAT practice everyday...YES!!    OH speakin of Swim.... our  first  Highschool  meet  is   October 19th   ((Kristin's bday!! YAY!! she'll be a wonderful 15 year old!! HA))  but yea.. its a  HOME  meet so if you want...you could  come and watch it .. i would like to tell you who were against..but im to lazy to go and look.. well swimming may not be that interesting to go and watch..but thats okay..lol but Coach said that the competeion got harder this year...SO UGH!   So tonight i am just staying home..and not going out anywhere..ick, but i have so much freakin HW its unbeliveable..and well im doing junk on Saturday & Sunday night, anyways...so i dont know when ill be able to do it..but well i could in the afternoons..lol DUH! but yea... um well i talked to    Callie    bout some junk today afterschool and it just made me  S O O O O O O O    happy   ! i love that girl! ((Callie im praying for you, about well..ya know)) She just takes such good care of me, and she really does care what is going on in my life!! lol AMEN TO THAT!! HAHH! well yes.. and umm nothing else to say right now...   Oh well today..was a fine day!! just so ya know..HA   i miss my youngins...Brad, Katelin, Travis, Taylor, Nathan, &amp; Kyle....ha!  i love all yall...yall are sweethearts...stay strong in the Lord, your God!!!!   well ill write more later... LOVE YALL ... XOXOXO Smooch   -    L    i  n  d   s  a   y    
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       yea..Hey Yall!! this week has been so fun!! Holly was in town visiting!! YAY!! and well shes leaving tommrow night..and like i dunno this week we went shopping, got our nails done, hung out, swam, went to six flags, went to Sam Moon...and tommrow were going to Burger's Lake with the Freshman, from my church!! fun stuff... yea well im bored as crap..and my parents just left to go to a concert..and well we're stuck at home! ick! but thats cool!! and omgsh   SCHOOL STARTS IN 3 DAYS!!   ick! im excited and stuff..but geez..ew school! and today i walked out my schedule..and it was insane!!! and i cant belive that i have to freakin swim every morning...HA! thats what i get for being a swimmer thou..lol!! well ill write more later..i guess...im gunna go do something else..   love yall!   -Lindsay  
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       1)Starting time: umm 1:54 pm      2)Name: Lindsay Larson      3)Nickname(s ):    4)School: Grapevine High School      5)Birthday: July 19, 1990!! Yes...sadly i just turned 14      6)Eyes: um, green or hazel or blue? idk ha!      7)Height: 5'4''      8) Siblings: haha...NO!      9)Ever been kissed: yea...      10) Ever cheated or been cheated on: um no..never cheated....cheated on? not sure      11) Ever missed school because it was raining:   not that i can remeber      1  2) Ever faked sick: of course! who hasnt?      13) Kept a secret from everyone: um...not from everyone? but from some people yea..lol    14) Had an imaginary friend: HECK YEA!      15) Wanted to hook up with a guy friend? um, yikes YEA!      16) Cried during a Flick: yea man, all the time..not that im proud thou!    17) Who is your "star" crush: ASHTON KUTCHER!!!! WOO!      18) Ever thought of animated characters as hot? uh...NO?      -----------------FAVORITE JUNK----------------   19) Drink: MiLK!      20.)food: hum...mac n cheese? i have no idea! ouo this salad that my ma makes!!      21.) restaurant: Catina Laredo & Thai Chili       22) Shampoo: Redken and anything by TIGI      23.) color: k...PINK! no doubt about that, sherlock!      24)Summer/Winter?: well BOTH, Summer cause well...its SUMMER, and Winter..cause of S N O W!!      25) favorite show: ...uhh??      26) Lace, Silk, Or Satin? SiLK...wait or lace..it depends...wait or Satin...HA!      27) Like anyone? hahah LOL   YES!!!!!!         28.) Who have you known the longest out of your friends? Holly, Emily, Kelly, &amp; Allison!! MY MINNESOTA GIRLS!! I LOVE THEM!      29) Who's the shyest: out of who?!      30) when is ur bday?: um...didnt i answer that like waaay up there?!      31) Who do you go to for advice: it really depends on what i need advice for!!      32) Who do you get along with? E V E R Y O N E!!!...you should know that..if you know me!       **IN THE COUPLE WEEKS HAVE YOU**      3) Cried: HA! yea...during Mission Trip...well everyone did!!      34) Been mean: um? no im a nice girl! HA!       35) listened to ur favourite band? OF COURSE!!       3  6.)Been sarcastic? lol...yea      37.) Been yelled at? um cant quite remeber..but prolly, by either my mom or Clay...HA! ((i love you Clay))      38) Talked to someone you have a crush on? no...i ignore him! psh yea i have!!      39) Kissed someone? hum...      4  0) Hugged someone? HAH! LIKE EVERYDAY!      41) Won an award? um no? unless wiat NO      42.) Wished upon a star? nope, but i saw some stars      43) Laughed until you've cried: hah YOU BET!! i laugh like all the time!      44) Played Truth or Dare: i dont think so...      45) Watched a sunrise/sunset: yeha      46) Went to the beach at night? well, accounting since we dont have beaches in Colleyville..but i went to the lake?!    47) Had too much homework? HA! NO SUMMER TIME!!      4  8) Eaten anything out of the ordinary? ew no..but i could have, at Laurie's church..for Fear Factor night..HOW GROSS!! ((squid in milk...or clam juice))      49) Are you lonely? hhah me? NO      50) Are you happy? OF COURSE!!      51.) Are you talking to someone online? psh yea      -----------DO YOU BELIEVE IN------------   52) God/Devil: well YES! i do! God..most definatley! and the Devil too..bc God's word speaks of the Devil!!      53) Love @ first sight: suuure, why not?? ((ouoo pig...lol Hayley))      54) The Closet Monster: no not at the moment..      55) singing in the shower: HA YEA! why not sing in the shower? its fun!      56) Heaven/hell: yep! you better belive it!! ALSO..you better belive in Hell..if you havent accepted Jesus Christ into your heart..hes the only way to get to Heaven!! NO DOUBT!      57)Superstitions: uh NO      58) Half empty or half full: Half full, most definately!!      59) Who named you? my Ma and Pops      60) Favorite quote: "Im rad, you're rad, lets hug!!"       61)What is the last thing u said online? i said: i have no clue, but thats what my mom said    62) When was the last time you showered? this morning, before church!      63) What is your computer desk made out of? umm wood?      64)What was the last thing u did before getting on the computer? went to church, then out to eat with the Miller's!!      65) Where do you want to go on ur honeymoon? um, not quite sure at the moment        66) Where do you want ur wedding? um either outside ((somewhere pretty)) or in a church!!    67) Hows the weather? nice!!!    68) What did you do last night? um well my ma had a dinner party..so well that      69) Things you find attractive about the opposite sex? christians, personallity, looks      70) How do you eat an oreo? i eat the cookies first..then the frosting!!        71) All time favorite show? umm idk?      72) Dream vehicle? well for my first car i want a Beetle Convertable or a Mazada 3!!!      73) How often do you go to the movies? at least once a week!!      74) Favorite music? Christian and Country!!!      75) How many kids do you want to have? um..im not quite sure      76) Something you just don't understand: people!!      77) Favorite animal? huh..idk i loove all animals...k except bugs and liek snakes...      78) Brand of clothing? well i like cute clothes, thats about it!! but i have mostly American Eagle!!      79) If you could change ur name what would it be? Lindsay...HA!    80) Favorite hobbies? um well my hobby is swimming...lol but its not my favorite..i really liek talking, and hanging out with my friends!!!      81) stupidest thing you've ever done? HAHAHA...    82) First son's name? duude, idk...im 14! but there are alot of really cute names..      83) Husband? AWH!! i dont want to offend anyone...lol      84) First daughter's name? um a cute name...idk yet!      85) Do you collect anything? haha NO    86) Dating anyone? ha! i wish....      87) On the phone or in person? person!!!    88) Lust or love? love..aw      89) If you could change something about yourself what would it be? um...huh      90) what time was intermission? wait what?    91) Who sent this to you? um..YOU? idk      92) What do you think of this person? k stop idk!    93) Favorite song? "Blessed be the Name of the Lord!!!" ((Callie, Alexis, and Clay..awh))    94) Anything you want to say to everyone? HI!      95) Time finished? 2:41, HOW SAD...but i did stop alot...lol  
      
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       HEY YALL!! how are yall? im pretty good...okay well lets see friiiiiday..well i did basically nothing! well i went to swim practice...((the last one until the 21st..SCORE)) and well then i went to the movies with Callie, George and Clay!!! we saw napolen Dynamite..it was soo soo dumb..but it was hilarious...if you havent seen it you ahve to stay after the credits..K?! good! and we saw lots of poeple that we knew..it was cool! but yea..so and today ((saturday)) i got up early and  i got   HOLLY   from the airport! YAY! i missed her so much! geez! well ha and then we went shopping @ Southlake Towncenter..it was coooool! and yea..wel then my mom had a dinner party..and were just hanging out watching tevee..and Corri is spazing out at me..lol but other tahn that..ha shes so funny i love her!! ((sorry you didnt go last night Cor)) and yea well so im really sad..cause well George isnt going to Grapevine anymore more! NOT COOL! but thats okay..ill see him lots! ha! awesome! well ill write later..love yall   -Lindsay      Philippians 1:3  
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       G R A P E V I N E....   1) Swim Team-- Bingenheimer 2) World Geography PAP-- Wilson 3) English 1 PAP-- Brem 4) Spanish 2-- Hodge 5) Swim Team--Bingenheimer 6) Biology PAP-- Steward-Ganz 7) Health-- Werts 8) Geometry PAP-- Patterson      yea..that would be my schedule..tell me if you have any classes with me!!!  
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       yea so i just got back from  Ben's house!  whew what joy! lol actually it was fun, it was a wendsday night thing for Highschool..it was super cool! ((whoa just reminded me of Billy Maddison..dont ask me how..lol)) and yea.. so not like a TON of people were there..but alot were...like Callie, George, Clay, Reagan, Elizabeth, Katie, Katey, Marshall, Ben, Ben, Tommy, Kristen, Britany, Whitany, Rob, Landon, Kat, and Kat lol i could go on..but i choose not to..lol cause ya know! well it was cool..and so tommrow i gots FISH CAMP!! hah niiice fun!! whew! im excited to see everyone!! ((YAY! soo George and Gail are both going to GHS this year...this is gunna be soo cool!)) but yea. and so right now i am listening to Marshalls, Bens and Kirks songs!! ha there hilarious..check them out..  urlLink http://www.purevolume.com/quantitynotquality  haha! Ah i love marshall, lol hes cool!! but yea...umm soo well im going with  HAYLEY JEAN KENNEDY  tommrow to Fish camp!! YES! i wont have to walk in alone.. haha!! lol and um yea..well ill write more later..   love yall   -Lindsay  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       hum, well  Tuesday  all i did was mozy around the house...until i had swim practice at 4 until 6, then uhh i came home.. took a shower and had dinner..ouo it was a good dinner!! but yea...and then i went to "TNC" ((thats what we decided to call it, i forgot whos idea it was..but its cool...lol)) and so yea i went to that and only like 15 people were there..but it was fun anyways, and yea! then i got home about 10:45ish and well then i got on the internet, and then i had my quiet time...and then i went to sleep! lol..so that was a really borrrrrring day! but other than that yea! Sooo Holly comes to visit me on Saturday, and shes here for a   WHOLE   week!! YAY!! ha she gets to live the "exciting" life of me! ha whew and yea so i just got back from babysitting and i made a whole 30$ in 4 hours..lol thats pretty good pay huh?! lol but yea now im just plain out bored..lol    ill write later...   love yall!   -Lindsay   
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       K well, i got back from swimming at about 6:10ish...and well then i talked on the internet for a few min. then i got in the shower...lol so now im out of the shower..and typing here, cause im bored!! and ya know what i hate CHLORINE..cause well i mean i took a shower..and i like used bodywash ((DUH)) and uhh i still smell like the pool, and 'Coconut Lime Verbena' ((k well thats my bodywash stuff..lol..From Bath &amp; Body Works..lol)) and yea so that bugs me..lol just a thought...and also so on my way to swim practice my Ma showed me the new clothes she got me!! AND THEY ARE SOOOOOO CUTE...i got one white skirt..and like 4 shirts that are like uber CUTE! ya!! and she got some shirts by the same brand ((SPY...its suposed to be a real good brand..lol)) and uhh yea so im gunna borrow hers sometime too!! lol)) but yea... so im trying on the shirts right now...lol! and yea im really bored..and im gunna have dinner soon ((it smells good...lol)) and uhh then YAY! WHAT I HAVE BEEN WAITING FOR ALL DAY..PRAYER/WORSHIP @ THE BOX!! YES!! ((at 8:30)) i looooooooove it!! and well Corri has professed her love for 'someone special' and shes kinda sad thou.. and yea...   call the cell, 706 8418   -Lindsay  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well okay..i dont know what made me think of Mission Trip.. except that, it was  MY MOST FAVORITE PART OF MY SUMMER , and the  BEST EXPEIERENCE OF MY LIFETIME!!  well then on that note, but yea my youth group ((DANG IT MY MOM JUST CALLED AND REMINDED ME THAT I HAVE SWIM @ 4 TODAY..lol)) k but my youth group went to NYC this year for our mission trip! ((July 17-July 21)) and it was just an amazing expierence we did so much in just a week..it touched each and everyone of our lives  in some way or another!! i really learned about the Power of Prayer..by just some of the stories that people told me during Mission Trip, and by my own expierence..i mean God will answer your prayers..and on that...         "More tears are shed over answered prayers than over unanswered prayers."                                           -Mother Teresa      just a thought...i found that in one of the books that i do my quite time with...lol! but uh yea Mission Trip..wow!! i have pictures of it if you want to see them, and like oh my goodness words cant describe it! and if you ever get the chance to go on a mission trip..TAKE THE CHANCE..its a life changing expierence! i loved it! and so many tears were shed in NYC that week just my my youth group and the sponsers..well im out of words to say..but only my heart can explain it...and just ask anyone that went on the mission trip..it was tottaly INCREDIBLE..lol      -Lindsay  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       OKAY WELL!     CORRI    IS BACK FROM UTAH!!!  YAY! YES! Well she got back last night, but oh wow i missed the bageezes out of her!! and well when she was gone, i took care of her dogs, T.D. and Hunter, and her Farett, Pinkee, and well they were good..but they still made me miss Cor!! but yea!   so Kristin and i hung out a couple of days when she was gone, but we still both missed her! lol and im just happy that she is home!!   yea...thats all folks!   -Lindsay      Cell, 706 8418! 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       well lets see,  Sunday  i went to church and hung out around the house mostly, but then around 6 i went out to eat at Gloria's, it was really good food, but not as good as Cantina Laredo ((ya know what im saying..yum)) and well then i went over to Ben's house... ((Ben Miller, that is)) for this thing, idk but some other parents were there ((from my church)) and like Rob, Wes, Landon, Grant, Ben, Elizabeth, Sean, Grant, and Grant were there too, but uhh yea it was cool..then most of us went over to The Box for a prayer & worship time with just the youth...((we've been doing this for a few weeks now...ever since we got back from Mission Trip..which was amazing by the way )) but yea, and a TON of people were there, not usual for this, but it was so amazing!!! And well after we were done Marshall was like okay can i see the Grapeviners, and so well since i am now a 'Freshman' at my church as of Sunday morning..lol i could go..lol...but well Marshall had a really cool idea about going up to the Highschool and having a prayer and worship thing the day before school starts..but then someone reminded him that we had our 'Back to School Bash' that day at night..so we couldnt do it then..and well so we moved it to Saturday, the 14th! which works perfect..lol!! ((YAY and also on that day, during the day, the Freshman are going to Burgers Lake..YES!! its gunna be awesome!!)) so yea..   GHS on Saturday Night @ 6 o'clock..outside, by the Flagpole..  BE THERE ANYONE CAN     GO!!!!    just for a time of worship and prayer for the school year it will be awesome!! but yea..    So  Monday  i went to Hurricane Harbor with the jr. high with my church, it was cool!! GOT TO HANG OUT WITH KAITLIN and TAYLOR...whhooop! hah! it was so much fun, and woo all the hott hott guys!! lol! but yea..when i got home from that Laurie IMed me and was like 'Tell me more about this prayer/worship thing at the highschool that your church started' and i was like tottally blown away, i was thinking WOW how could she hear about this already..i mean just the dozen of us that go to GHS at my church talked about it last night at about 10 o'clock, and already people know about it, and are wanting to go!! i was so blown away and soo excited!! and so i told her more about it...and then i found out that Stacy knew about it too..and i was liek gee this is soo cool! and well now im excited!! lol!! and YAY!! YAY YAY YAY!! ((haha that just reminded me of the Starbucks commericial...BEN! BEN BEN BEN! Ben's the man going to woooork...hha okay sorry..lol))    and  today  i am doing nothing but sit around the hosue..lol! my moms out shopping at Market today..no fair! ((but i just got off the phone with her and she said she got me a ton of new cute clothes!! YES! THANK YOU MOM!! lol)) and yea then i am just waiting until tonight so i can go to my youth's prayer/worship deal i love them!! ITS AMAZING HOW CLOSE WE ARE GETTING AS A YOUTH GROUP!!! i love it! and   YOU   should just try to go to one of these prayer/worship times that we have on Sundays and Tuesday nights @ 8:30...their so cool..and wow, a rival is comming..its GLORIOUS!! and yea.. thats pretty much it!        ALSO..dont forget about FISH CAMP, this THURSDAY from like 9-12... i think... but yea, hold on ill go check..lol! K YEA I WAS SOO RIGHT..wow! we get our schedules and junk there..so just go! lol  
</post>


</Blog>