<Blog>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I don't know what to think about this damn weather, but yesterday it was 93 and sunny, today it is 68 and cloudy!  No wonder people are sick and flooding the hospital!!   We have more people with pneumonia and just being sick than usual during this time of the year.  I wish this damn weather would figure itself out and let us have a season!!   
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Cardinals are the team to beat right now! The have been getting some big breaks and good pitching from a staff that wasn't supposed to be worth a damn! I am worried that their luck will run out once the post season arrives but until then I am rooting hard for the Redbirds!!!   Here at home, Logan is growing like a weed on miracle grow!! She is walking pretty much when and where ever she feels like going. Has been getting a new tooth every 10 days or so. I really am amazed at everything that is happening. I am soooo thankful that I have a beautiful healthy little girl that her mother and I can spoil and love!   That's all for today   D  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Just found out that the state of Missouri (where I hail from) has voted to ban gay marriage.  WTF is the big deal??  I don't care if any two people who love each other want to get married.  2 women or 2 men, let them.  In all honesty, with the number of divorces between hetero couples, I would almost guarantee that the divorce rate among gay couples would be much lower!  People need to wake up and realize that there is nothing wrong with two people, gay or not, getting married.   D  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am not happy today!  The damn Cardinals lost to the Expos!!!  In extra innings even.  The 'spos are horrible this year and supposedly the best team in baseball lost to them!    I am tired and have to work tonight at the hospital again.  Will probably get stuck with a bunch of confused people that I can't stand, not to mention the patients!     just a quick rant,   hope the Cards get their heads out of their asses tonight   D  
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am pretty new at all of this stuff, but wanted a place to just be able to rant if I feel like it.  So this seems like a good place to start.  I never thought that having a daughter would change a person, but boy does it!!  My girl is only 10 months old, but is my boss!!  and my wife's boss too!  She is as cute as a button and just about as good a baby as I have encountered, but damn, she is time consuming.  I don't think that is bad, just not really what I expected I guess. ok, more later, not sure really what is supposed to happen but will be back soon D 
    
</post>


</Blog>