<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Whay,  Back from a very fun and fan-fucking-tasticly dirty week at a Theatre course - Big up Beachump massive, more posting on that later. I just thought that Sam would like to very, very smugly inform you that yes, he will indeed be returning to Pate's yr 13....My mum drove me and Tom from Highnam to Cheltenham in the morning to get the results....     Psychology - A  (and get this - 100% i.e not  one mark dropped in the whole paper  of memory and child development! :D)  English Literature - A  (and a high one! 95% for the whole of  Wuthering Heights  and Harrison. SMUG.)  Biology - B  (in your berloomin face Mr. Dray/Mr you-cant-do-this-you're-rubbish-and-foolish.    Philosophy & Ethics - B  (cool, but dissapointing in the end cos I got 94% fucking percent for the whole philosophy paper (and there was me stressin bout it to Regan on his blog) and 80% for the whole Ethics paper, would you believe - so like high A. But then a D for c/w - I put my heart and soul into the c/w, it was on Materialism &amp; Dualism, Descartes etc, and my teacher, Mr Gardner only commented on my 7 (coutn em) drafts, never marked, and Mrs Sibley (ugh) refused to mark it, so it must have been totally wrongly done. Oh well).      Did anyone else find the results sheets totally confusing? I screamed at Mrs Smee at one point, trying to help me out but just shoving the "which subject are you dropping, then?" sheet right in my face in a totally Pate'sy way. Ooh, and no I shall not do retakes unless I'm fucking forced to, Pate's is sooooo annoying like that.       But yeah, AABB is a fab result, REVISION PAYS OFF KIDDIES!      Smiles. All the while.      Currently listening to: "Flashback" - The Beachump play - in my head.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Just so you know, Pate's kiddies, if I don't join you on September the 1st it's because I have, as I nightmare on about  every  night, failed my AS levels miserably, and Mrs Smeegal won't let me back in for Year 13. *ARGH!*.  So. I leave for a music and drama tutoring and performance residential camp thing tomorow afternoon on which I only know Jess, Chloe and Rich, and haven't even seen them, let alone anyone else at Beachump (the place it's held) for like 2 years. And I'll get there really late, after everyone's pitched their tents and met everyone else, becuase berloody Debenhams is making me work till 5:10, even though Tom is getting there at 3:45ish. :S So very tight for time.  What else have I done? Emily left earlier :( unless I go out to visit her in Malaysia, that's the last time we all meet for nearly 2 years! I have been frantically bidding for Less Than Jake cds on ebay. I met Naomi in town the other day, which was fun and rosy-tinted. BUT my nasty mother said I  had  to go to cheltenham f*cking library that afternoon to research course entry requirements for uni next year, otherwise she wouldn't put down the deposit for this week's camp :(. So I had to abandon Naomi after like an hour and a quarter and toddle off to the library. And THEN nasty mum phones going "Ooh! I say, (after rooting through my room no doubt, and not respecting privacy) I'm so pleased with all the prospectuses (which, as I tell anyone who'll listen, should actually be prospect i ) you've collected, I won't make you go to the library!" Grr. And then it was too late, so to cheer myself up I went and bought a wicked portable hifi to take to Beachump to play McFly all week in the tents (joke. Well, half joking. Mneh.)  So, results day is on thursday, 10:30 - are we excited, kiddies?!? And I'll be on camp in Gloucester! So me, Tom, and Nichola Bicknell, who is at Pate's and coincidentally at the same camp as us, will shimmy into school in the first acting session or sommat, and hopefully my mum'll drive us there and back. I hope the fact there's 3 of us instead of one will help our chances, cos I don't want to make it look as if it's a massive deal, which it isn't compared to the A-levels, but a) I didn't arrange postage to Beachump, and b) I WANNA SEE MY FRIENDS!  God, it'll be such a weird atmosphere. In fairness, it  is  quite a big deal. Like if I do better in English Lit than Psychology, I have to change my uni specialism because nowwhere I'm applying to study Psychology takes less than an A/B cos its so darn popular. And I  can't  even study it at Oxford, Manchester, Durham etc if I get a C in Biology probably, cos they're really keen on a science background.  God, that's another thing. After a shitty-pant-inducing interview with the Head about my application to Oxford (pretty much a bloomin mock interview, totally NOT "informal" or "discussion"), I probably won't get into Oxford anyway, seeing as I have to get st least AABB, which is very dubious ;) and I'm not really "Oxbridge material" as pretty much all my friends and family point out continuously. Lol, no, hopefully will be alright. I hope to God I do good, because - no joke - I worked really, really hard for these in revision, past papers etc!  Smiling nervously. But happy about drama course and McFly tent boppage!  Currently listening to: Lit - A place in the Sun. FANTASTIC ALBUM.    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Wow nip/Tuck is so so graphic! I always wondered what actual plastic surgery looked like...and now I know *gag-retch-puke-boak*. No really, it's actually darn cool.      I am in a sweating frenzy that only ebay bidding can lure me into. Seriously, I am fucking  addicted . Since my beloved polaroid camera came in the post early friday morning, I have been telling anyone and everyone who'll listen that yes, ebay really is "that easy!" Ahh, I do believe I sound like a phony advert. The only trouble with my fab £5.50 trendy, in vouge, retro camera is the film. £12 for 10 shots! Gulp - but mneh, the photos are fantastic, as you devoted readers will see when I figure how to publish the freaking things on the blog.      Today me and Naomi went into town. Ahh, swoon, holding hands like an old-married-couple in the manner of Julaaar and Dan rocks. Anyway we saw many people from school, and each time I swelled with pride at them seeing Naomi with me :D. But before this afternoon, everything was truly shit. Federico and Riccardo left today, and I won't see them for like, 15 months?! Or something, which isn't a big deal or owt, just a bummer :(. And Kate has got a  lot  of explaining to do, after all my careful planning to organise a  cheer-up-chook  night out. Grr am in a right ole' pissy with ya Kate, and no denying it.       grr. Weather. Yay! ebay! (have just found I am the highest bidder for "The Beach" soundtrack and "Divine Secrets of the YaYa Sisterhood" soundtrack! Does anyone else find ebay makes you buy totally random, often crap things?      Sam      Currently listening to: Less Than Jake - Anthem. Great album...  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        hmmm, testing a link....  urlLink   "http://obliviated.net/skin"   >Lisa's journal   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Ahh, sooo hot and sunny. Took a berloody long time to get here and all! And me, Tom, Federico and Riccardo had a class-A, thorns-in-bare-feet, shockingly cold hose, screaming in the face of water pistols,  WATER FIGHT!  I apologise if I sound overly enthusiastic, but it's been so long since I really did something like that, sliding on a sheet, hiding in the orchard with a hose, ahh, all of it. *reminiscent sigh*.       And what better way to spend a sunny morning than with ButtercupNaomi? Naomi, Juli, me and Tom lounged in the beer gardens from like 10 am (I know! early birds an all that) onwards till Naomi had to go to work, I think. I stopped jumping for joy then, because I started  missing her already *smitten* . So I sent a text saying "I miss you," etc. Personal things which I shall not repeat cos she'll blush like purple ;) if/when she reads this. But it's true, I really did miss her like 20 mins after she left (  So  gonna earn some brownie points for saying this!).  ahh, girlfriends are so much trouble, nein?! lol. Anyway, enough from infatuated Sam already.      And now I'm gonna have to love you and leave you, cos I'm going to see Shrek 2 with Federico and Riccardo. Already seen it once, but mneh, who can turn down a film like that?!      Smiling Sam  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       YAYAYAY.   I calculated, that, pathetically, I have spent £4.25 on voting for big brother contestants. Mostly to keep in Michelle, cos she's such a funny, dirty slapper, and trying my damndest to get rid of the *knob* that is Jason. ARGH, he's so, so nasty and old-mannish. God knows why he came second, betaing the average Shell, cool and funny Stuart and damn funny Dan. Tom reckons it's the scottish people voting. And it happened last year with Cameron (from somewhere in Scotland) who won. Anyway, Nadia's win ensured that at least some of my money wasn't lost, seeing as I voted for her like 6 times. And she got all spastic with emotion, which was sweet. So happy!   Ooh - and did no-one else notice Davina crying? methinks she is faking it, I don't know.      Nadia  won!       Sam      Currently listening to: Usher - Burn. Mneh, its on tv, and I can't be arsed to turn it off...  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Howdy kids,       Well . After a artery-clog inducingly stressful day, now nasty parents won't lemme go to the darn cinema, with my mates. And buttercup Naomi *smitten*. Lol, something I always used to say when reading my mate's blogs was that it's crazy the way names of  us  can be on the famoso internet! This inevitably entailed me saying to Zoe etc all. the. time. "Mention me! Say Sam said something about this or that!" Which is desperate, sad and star-seeking. Mneh, I cannae be arsed to be ashamed after the day I've had.      Federico and Riccardo, my darling but wearing Italian cousins, are obsessed with me and Tom's fashion, cos although Italy is wicked fashion, they have shit shops compared to Cheltenham, and I knew they would go spastic with joy at somewhere like Legends shorty, which would be great - if it wasn't a bleeding GIRLS ONLY shop now. But we located boys kids clothes in the boardy thingy legends. Nothing,  nothing  was right, which was dissapointing, seeing as I'd painted shopping here out as a orgasmic experience, esp. for skatey clothes. Mneh.      Then they don't have GAP near where they live, so we took them to it - and - like Legends - the sale shelves were *just* cleared, the shopfloor had basically nothing left, Federico and Riccardo didn't like anything I liked, Span (Cooper),   funny girl I know from school, wasn't there, cos she was in crete (altho Joe Luxton was working in Menswear, so we talked to him instead).       And nothing in freespirit, Cult actually  staggeringly  expensive, Burton boring, and so on and so forth, ad infinitum. But we bumped into Haz, who left Pate's last year when I wasn't there, but know through Sophie W, and Grace, Joe, Jenny H was in shortys, but looked to be in a pissy, so we avoided her ;).       AND I got a shit, chavvy haircut by a chav lady whose hair was so worrying that I felt physically sick to experience her hands touching my scalp, :(. Although it's partly my fault, for stepping into Tewkesbury the dump. Although we were looking around, and since spring it seems kinda on the up? But I still haven't forgiven chav lady for that cut. And I had to walk round Cheltenham, seeing everyone I know from school (see above) with hair sticking to my neck and my cousins imploding with frustration...      BUT. After a dire week of weather, weather is better - sunny even!      Smiles, with a half-full cup.      Currently listening to: Razorlight album. Starnge but good.  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Howdy,  berloody heck, I thought to myself when I read my first *ever* two posts, I am surely being zee king of ramblage?! (rambling). So I'll keep it quick now.  The post title is a piss-take of nasty Sue Nelson, who wrote in The Guardian yesterday about how street art is litter. Like wake up and smell the spray paint, Maureen! First, she doesn't make a distinction between normal, unthinking graffiti and thought-out, sourced-material street art, and second, she seems to promote the idea of sanitised blank walls in cities across the UK, which is a) unrealistic, b) creatively stifling, and c) darn boring. Grrr, non-apreciators do me 'ed in.  *Toilet break*. Eeew, eww,  ewww.  I just had a poo ;)    And then dropped the spare key, kept on the toilet cistern, into the loo when flushing it. Accidently. Key - retrieved but unclean. Me - scarred for life...   Smiles.  Soooo  Not smiling  Tsk, shall listen to some Keane to "soothe" me...mmm, piano solos.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Holla  Reading Brendan's blog (yes I know, I am a geeky blog 'trainspotter' stalker hybrid with a penchant for blogs of people in my school, lol! No seriously, I read  everyone's  - Zoe, regan, Joel, Bonnie, Katherine, Lisa, Todd, Brendan etc) I remembered that I've forgotten to put in my "currently listening to" line. Which is certainly a pertinent issue, seeing as I'm listening to....    McFly.   There. I said it, ok? And the thing that will have you all boaking is that  I'm Bopping my freakin SOCKS off to this tune!  I mean, seriously, who can turn down the cheerful welcome of "Obviously"? I implore you.  Anyways, I walked the walk of shame in the process of buying the album in Sainsbury's yesterday, part of the reason why I didn't mention in yesterdays post  (see fill-in post)  about our lil shopping ttrip, what with the shameful memory being too close in time to my traumatic experience an all. WELL, my darling sister back from Malaysia, because of my hilarity at the fact she hasn't eaten a sandwich for a year, becuase in Malaysia they don't really "do" bread  (see fill-in blog) ( werid, nein?)   , got me back big-style by exclaiming on my purchase  all the way to the checkout.  Ugh. Sigh, 'twas a very, VERY embarressing walk of shame, I must say. It felt like everyone was gonna turn round in the queue, nudging each other and pointing to my sinful, tweeny-bop purchase burning a hole in my hanging hand.  .. Oh well, it was a fair exchange for the sandwich laughing.  And to top it off, my good friend Barnett castigated me for buying the bleedin thing on msn last night! I'm sorry, ok? It was an instinct thing. sigh. Anyways seriously now thanks Barnett for being advicey and dudish, despite me not ever replying to it, on account of writing my blog ; )  Smiles (Smiling much, much more than my previous post, because despite the keys incident  (See evil thrives when good men do nothing post)  McFly have got me hopping with joy again. So THERE, nasty people. Lol.  Currently listening to: Yes, you've guessed it. McFly, Room on the third Floor. Or, more specifically, the modern classic - yes really - "Obviously".   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Well now, I'm all excited by having myself a blog, so I thought I'd bactrack across a few days. PS Look at my personal profile, cos it took so long to get the wordcount down, sorted out, seperated by commas to be accepted as like "favourite music" etc, you know how it is, that I totally burst a vessel in stress. So look at it.  PPS I've just realised my blog name, Nice Guys Finish Last, is double entrende! (that is a double meaning, of which the play on words or second meaning has sexual connotations, for those of you are tragically uniformed). whay. And lets face it, Sam has such amazing stamina he certainly finishes last, ;) actually a more obvious double entrende would just be Nice Guys Last Longest. Or Smiles Lasts Longest. meh. I digress...  So basically I thought I should put in a bit of background of this week, the biggest event of which was a family *argh irritating relatives* homecoming for my sister's return from Malaysia where she went to teach in a primary school from last August straight through till now. And from next week, if I don't stop off in Malaysia on my travels or whatever, we won't see her for a whole 2 years! Which is a bit weird.       So ANYWAY. She got back last week, and my Mum went spacco with worry that me and Tom (my twin) would take the piss, cos we always,  always  take the piss outta Em. Don't ask me why, she's lovely and the typical tolerant older sister. She even brought us back presents from Asia and Sri Lanka! And still we took the piss, primarily cos of how excited she got telling us anecdotes, and also cos we hoepd she'd have a Malay twang we could imitate. Alas, she does not : (. Anyways she reckons I've grown loads, :D so obvi I couldn't be nasty after her complimenting my height. Also, despite me and Toms' harsh banter to her, we actually really missed her. Argh! 2 posts in and already this blogging lark is leading me astray into communicating emotions, which I said I wouldn't do (at least in a way that gives away *anything* about me).    and she's bein a right ole jetsetter, which she never used to be. Where we might go to Cornwall for a weekend, she jets off on a dirt cheap little plane to a Thai island! It's very surreal, and cool, but I can never be happy for other people, dammit! I'm SO bloomin selfish :(  My gran, grandad, 4 cousins, older brother, and other older sister were also there. Joe (older brother) got thrills over his new car, a lushy-osa black fiat punto, a might chavvy. But still! And he just started his job as a fully qualified *doctor*. Soo, soooooooo worrying. "I hate sick or ill people" - his own admission! And party was fun, etc. Apart from my gran, not the most subtle of ppeople, calls me over and goes "Samuel, darling, your mother tells me you're studying  Paradise Lost  next year at school?" I said yeah, preparing to blag intelligence to her cos she is so.. exacting  about stuff like this. She just looks at me, and says "Well, I fear it will be completely lost on you". Yay! Thanks, gran!  Today me, my mum and my sister went to good ole Saino's to re-introduce Em to western foods. She got massively chuffed over sandwiches, which I found disproportionately hilarious. What was also funny is my mum getting all enthusiastic about cooking some fusion food, like Thai chicken or indonesian noodles, y'know the stuff, and my sister was just like "nooooooo, don't get me wrong, I love rice - but from next week onwards I'll be eating a rice or noodle meal Every. Single. Day, so whilst we're here can't we have western food? like... sandwiches ? "*sam cracks up nastily again*. In Kuala Lumper, its like 35 degrees all the time or sommat, so she spends the whole time here complaining about how cold, etc it is here. And poeple who know me, realsie just how much cold/rubbish weather in summer annoys me! So I got quite stressy about that... :S BAD SAM. lol.     Ooh and I went to the new "simply food" M&S store and dave WAS NOT THERE! I was so sure he would be, so was gutted cos I haven't caught up with him for ages. And if you're reading, Dave, I'll have you know that I looked all over M&amp;S in town on both wed AND thurs and couldn't find you there, wither. *smug face at having won a 1 sided argument*.    
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Word up kids, and welcome to Nice Guys Finish Last,  WELL I've made a blog which many people, naming no names *KATE* think is well up myself, but meh! I'm not bothered, becuase she doesnt realise just how obsessed I am with reading other people's blogs *blush of my patheticity (sp?)*  It started with Zoe's fantastic blog in Autumn, cos I well badly needed an outlet of bitchage about our nasty-but-as-a-whole-nice-drama-teacher, who directed our sixth form play, " The Three Lives Of Lucie Cabrol".  Do you realise just how darn fine it is to hear someone else getting bitter and twisted about The Mace? lol was funny reading.  Then I read Regan's, cos he was in the play to, although less was less Mace-bashing, : ( (Me and Lora, also in the play, hazarded the theory of a sordid lusty affair between Regan and the Mace, after her comment on "well, Zoe, if  my  director wanted me to act in an intimate way with other characters, I think I would agree to it!" because she wanted Regan to grab Zoe's, err, chest! And he looked well turned on at the idea of Mace's chest. Jesus, how I gabble! Anyway, it was only rumination, as the Mace is attached and Regan is normal. lol...  Then I started reading Joel's blog, which is good but infrequent, which was annoying when it was  only  me, I swear to God, reading blogs instead of revising conscientiously for my AS-levels. And to see so many un-updated blogs was mighty distressing, being an indicator of business and work.  When I can be arsed, I read Todd's and Lisa's blogs, which are both soooooo fucking professional! (I'm not so commited cos I don't know them so well) Its like my gard, amazing writing. Their proffessionalness is beaten only by the amazo Smiles. (Jokin, jokin!). And Bonnie's, which is good and damn funny, alhtough it makes me feel really down sometimes cos he sounds unhappy, and my well-hidden - rather unused *guilty face at my frequent heartlessness* - compassionate side sort-of makes me want to cheer him up.  So, after reading Katherine's blog, another fannytastic scroll (just so you realise guys, this shameless although genuine brownnosing is bloomin well gonna earn me links fomr you lot, k? lol) I thought "fuck it, I don't care if Kate thinks I'm too far up my own arse blah blah" and told myself to make a blog for the first 2 weeks of the holidays (whay HOLIDAYS!) and now I've got round to it I'll fill in on a few days history, althought I can't be arsed to backtrack to far, and bore my devoted readers...  So here it is. I don't want to bitch too much, or make people feel uncomfortable, or write anything *too* personal about myslef like you would a diary or owt, but at the same time I'm warning you guys that I don't hold my thoughts and opinions back to save feelings or emotions. That's rather cryptic, oh well, I'm basically saying "I mean what I say", hence the title of the blog, Nice Guys Finish Last. And remember - Smiles's sole aim is to entertain, kiddies!  Smilesey Sam   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>