<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The old workplace isn't as bad as I thought. The fear of about 40 people and having to talk pish to them was unfounded it was only 4 but it was me and 3 females so there was a lack of scope for converse, no much into bags and that. The ice-breaker thing as you would expect is utter pish you have to interview someone then read it out to the posse, I got this lassie who looks like the minger in girls aloud and she likes dmx ahaha. They're ok though my co-wrkers jsut hard to talk to, don't want to walk away or you'll look ignorant don't want to sit too close cos you know you won't talk and it will look like you're being nosey. Aye so when it came to interviewing the training guy he is going to strathy..... and the same favourite film, food, place as me. IN THERE. One of the lassies is a right spazzy though, we were talking about business partners then the guy says, so... Royal Bank of Scotland, Barclaybank etc what do you notice about these companies ? And this character goes "Ehhh I've never heard of them" Class. This place is seriously going o constrict my time, I think I will try to keep it going at uni cos the money is too good to turn down, and it would be hard to find anything any easier to get to anyway. just need strathy to give me some idea of times so I can decide for deininite, as big Ann says though if I do have to pack it in I could use the experience to get into Scottish Gas in Bothwell, easier job and nearer. Its a depressing thought though, it takes about an hour to get there. Its 4.5 miles away I clocked that on the run back but when you can't drive you have to go via Amsterdam and Timbuktoo so thats a big slice of you're day wasted. Need to learn to drive, would give me an extra 45 mins each day. Cos the now if I can make it from Uni it will be fuckin' hard, out the door around 7 in the morning up to Uni have to do well in there remember no just a matter of turning up then sprinting to work, sitting on a phone for 4 hours then back home for about 10ish try to study a bit probably then bed then same again, the friendships will be a thing of the past, people I really like I'll never ever be able to talk to, I would think I'll make some pals at uni but even then talk at uni sometimes between lectures and that and thats all, can't see me making too many pals at work where you get a 10 minute break and the rest of the time work work work. So, in conclusion my life is gonna' eat jizzum quite soon, I am starting driving lessons in 2 weeks, until I pass my test my life is gonna be shit and after that it will be just be plain pish. Makes you think how lucky you were just to be going to school. My laptop I was gonna buy could help a bit let me do something to do with uni when i'm wasting all this time travelling, if I can figure out how maybe a wee chit chat on msn so I can still talk to people every once in a while but apart from that I'm in for a rough 4 years, thats if i last the degree, I'll probably no be able to keep the job on, I am shattered and thats without uni. Ahhhh my fanbase of 0 will be ready to top themself now, it'll be ok eventually though just wait til 2008. Oh aye and see if I die, don't laugh, there was a life insurance form thing and you had to write down a few beneficiaries for if you die, and I put down a choice i would get slagged for but well I'd be dead so slag me if you want. £7800 they would get though, and big Ann aswell I really am worth more dead than alive ahahahah. 
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For anyone unfortunate enough to come across the pish of last night, I wrote something like the time is 2:12 but it is really much later, says it all doesn't it. Sometimes you think you know what you're doing then read that and you clearly don't. Student union will be murder I will turn into an alcoholic and I am buying a laptop next month so that will get nicked when im vulnerable or swapped for a Jack D or something. Girls Aloud doin' the freshers week sounds....class. The Libertines are number two, amazing for a band that good I listened to the chart for first time in ages there is some amount of pish floating around the now i must say especially what got to number one that babycakes mince, aw well I wonder if this will be The Libertines premature peak big Carl has already said he won't make another Libertines album without Pete, but Pete won't get back in 'til he is clean, but he says he won't so..... Theres now 5 merry men young; Cooney has joined aswell, me and Downey are lookin feeble, have to learn some new lingo Andy, at uni goin into second year. Cheesy, advanced english. Cooney, goin' to St Andrews, 8 1s 5 H As then 3 AH As. And me wae ma B in english and Downey with his C, looking bleak ! . Anyway work tomorrow theres a good chance I won't last the week I'm gonna hate it plus its always gonna be in my mind I'll have to give it up for uni anyway so even though I know i never would enjoy it anyway I will always be making sure I hate it just incase. I watched scarface again today that film is class, big Al Pacino knows where its at. This mincey B in english is coming into play cos I am aw over the place, got to text Jean and see what happened with his ill-fated shindig. Well I will write in this tomorrow for my ardent fan base of none and tell a sad soliloquoy of my tale of woe via cogent in Airdrie. Adios 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I cant even write straight the time accorind go you cheesy's comp is 2:12am but it is much later than it sounds. I will first set the scene Cheesy is playing "what a waster" to bonny i am writing this of course Downey is of course on the couch, Andy abandoned us at the adventure swingy Pauline and Lisa went awry at franklyn's along with Cooney fuck knows whatss goin on winners dont take drugs Souther comfort is quite good we got a wee ride on the chute notice how i can spell kinda mwaaaaaaaaaaaaa where danny oh at whitherspoons poking johann's bum anyway ut has been nice talking to you computer but i fear i must now go adios safe journey godspeed enjoy gutten tagge arividercie adios et al 
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will go down as the biggest disaster for many a moon, first Riley's u have to be member plus its full of characters known as cocks so then we done a bunk round to the safe haven of Franklyn's no such thing as a knockback from there correct ? NAW cos they decide to i.d everyone then Downey makes plans for a piss up back at his but then he is told otherwise by his lamb and the hat-trick of disasters is complete leaving me and young Michael with a search for alcohol and better company, unfortunately Andy was studying and by the time we got back everywhere was shut and it was looking like the 4th fuck up. It eneded up no too bad though better than it woulda been if it had been up to someone else, so it was " A couple a guys, couple a beers" and Blues Brothers and a dvd about Hugo Posh and the golden dildo. bahh 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spoke to young Jean Graham for the first time in ages, cos i lost his number the lines of communication were fucked then I eventually came up wae the bright idea of asking Comrade Downey for it, then i find out its his birthday, magic or wit ? He got a tatoo of big Ann's flaps, old habits die hard, takes me back to geog last year the hours he spent pokin' off a jotter and fuckin a table all in the name of Ann. Then i got an A, total pro and all that. Young Jean asked me to go to his gathering that young  urlLink Downey  and probably young  urlLink Michael  will be goin' to. The old Franklyn's trip is agreed for Saturday aswell so it might be an action packed weekend ye know full of twists, turns, suprises, a twist in the tail ? Some violence ? a sex scandal ? Or probably just a shitey anti-climax. I've got work on Monday it will be utter pish i keep thinking though I am losing my long lie but I'm no i start at 5 anyay it will be shite I am too shy for this kind of work especially the training thats basically so whats you're claim to fame ? In front of 50 people I will have to tell of the legendary time our wee pishy athletics club was on channel 3. Ahahaha. I spoke to young Jimmy "superstar" Strain for the first time in ages aswell he has left the legendary Airdrieonians Fc for the glamourous E.K Thistle. I was quite disappointed at gettin' into Strathy cos young Jimmy is goin' to Bell and he woulda been a much better person to be goin wae than fuckin poofy prick im landed wae now. Aww well, young Andy has also started his thing see 4 merry men now it's catchin' on. All this talk about Jean's b/day made me think wit I'm gonna do for mine, a party would be a shitey anti-climax and to quote big Jim from American Pie there would be "an abundance of weener" present, so probably goin' out somewhere wae 'a couple a guys, couple a beers' situation before it, but Cheesy works ahhh fuckin scotmid. So probably Franklyns at night while im stil 17 then after midnight anywhere cos I will be 18 we will finally be free cos Cheesy will be 18 aswell. Sorted. Cannae wait. But thats in the future, tomorrow is the key i need to think of something to get young Brian. adios 
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ABC..D And i got in. Fckin pr1ck Mcilvanney knew I would fck up craft. I got a C in chem and a B in english thanks to the glorious Jay Gatsby. And an A in geog (Dunno how). Good thing i've got the this or there would have been alot of trepidation about Uni cos ABCD is quite different to BBBB but I got in. It's quite weird because Downey ended up with 1 higher more than me and they knocked him back. Plus my personal statement was utter pish. Young Michael passed everything he got a C for advanced english which i must appluad the man for and getting an A in crash modies. i don't know what to think now Uni is cool cos well it's uni, going into Glasgow everyday real stuff and all that but.......... its further away and that means getting up earlier and I will probably have to give up that job before i even start it, plus Glasgow will get boring, and Uni will be alot harder than college woulda been, and architectural technology sounds well better than Arts n Social Sciences, that I'll be doing. But I am the first of my bretheren to go to uni so it is still a good badge of honour hahaha. So now young Michael is going to Glasgow to do English Literature, downey is going into clearing and will go to Cally probably, i am gonna do Arts n Social Sciences, apart from that I canny remember what alot of people are doin, Lisa n Pauline are also goin to the old Strathy, but so's a certain poofy fuckin wanker see another drawback. And Mr Mcallister that was doing everything the same as me had a bit of an appocalypse partly cos of me probably, i wrote that i put him off in geography and he failed it, no even one of these new fangled D's and I got an A so i extend my sympathies to him and Willhamima of course. See these pricks on tv, "Ooooh i got 4A's and a B I'm quite disappointed" pr1cks don't know how lucky they are. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Not long now, unless the postie does a bunk. Every other year i haven't really bothered that much about these, and i wasn't this year either really til my comrade came out with his dramatic monologue and it makes you realise I am up shit creak without the luxury of a paddle that young Michael has at his disposal. It's my own fault if I had been hardcore and no picked stuff based on Mr Brown and his crap jokes i would already be in Uni. But i need 4 B's and as Graeme Spieres said tonight, "I have quite a few hats and if that happens I'll eat them all" I think i was doin alrite in chemistry no done it for a year and that so i suppose i'd be aiming for a c might have failed it though the exam was quite hard if i remember right. But i got predicted at an a/b so at least Macca has faith. I've already failed geography once but thats more to do wae the fact its boring than hard. Last year I didny do anything just put comrade McAllister aff and talked pish I think i should get a c though. Craft we had a prick for, I'm no taking the blame, I had all the lingo in the book anthropometrics, aesthetical, hand-bastard i knew it all but half way through the year an invigilator came in and told us our projects aw wanked dugs and McIlvanney's answer is some guys will say, that wit a prick. I think i might have got a c though for the lingo alone, English wis a big bastard my task wasn't helped when i got sat beside Tashleigh amidst speaches about you might marry who you get sat beside in higher english. Scary. aye so I don't know thats where the great gatsby comes in. I don't know.... probably a c/fail cos my 2nd essay was pish and no finished. So in conclusion BCCC or CFFF. And also good luck to my comrades Downey who needs BBC I think, we have faith in the man and Cheesy who needs nothing but he's bricking it and also the likes of Lisa who is also in but is also bricking it. And may i also say i sincerely hope that poofy prick Mullarkey fails. And also good luck to lesser known comrades such as young Samantha-Jo and my ex compatriot known to you as dicky breath and people from her school who are okay. The rest can fail like me ahahaha. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ahahahahaha many giggles on this day. One of they wee inocious things that are funny as fuck to people of a certain jest hahaha I am still laughing the now. If you are a spazzy yourself tell you're comrade to stop reading or if you're mum, dad, auntie or uncle or something is also stop so me and young Michael decided to go into Glasgow to pass the time til tomorrow, then he regails me with a tale of how these people at a campsite were playing with a frisbie and they have a disabled person with them who they try to incorporate into the game, however as he is a mongo the frisbie strikes him right in the face ahahahahahahaha I know it's no funny but it is really, it's hard to explain but just the thought of it ahahahahahah away again. And even before that on my way to the rendezvous with young Michael I came across a mother with her daughter who was about 7 standing about then out of nowhere the wee lassie gets fucked right in the head, so she hits her mum back, then the maw screams "You're a wee bastard and naebody likes you" ahahahahahahahahaha it was a classic, So in summing up I am a saddistic wee cunt. I got Ash's singles collection thing and it's ok the rest of the visit was spent broosing fat people's arses and laughing at them ahahahaha i think someone has spiked ma cha anyway.... and on top of all that we saw a cult-hero of ours known as Brawley, ahahahaha. So none of this is funny except to again characters of a certain dis-position. Then when we returned i got my sleepin bag and i witnessed the aforementioned pentium 4000bc in action that really is 633Mhz to young Michael made me a copy of The Libertines first album. Its quite good so far. Really good infact but can't go too hardcore too soon, and i don't like how the NME lick their ring. I've got nothing to do now just sit and think of this young invalid meeting his fate of a frisbie right to the dish. ahahahahah away again. Exam results in about 15-35 hrs dependin on the shiteyness of the post-man, who have been known to mow people down over here so don't give them any shit. I will write about that later probably i just had to write about the spazzy the now 'cos big ANN is in a mood and is threatening to withdraw the comp later cos it's makin a funny sound. ahahhahaha spazzy frisbie head - wee lassie naebody likes - big fat ring ahahahahahaha. Ciao 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhhh see wit i didn't think of that my associate pointed out to me is if i get into Strathy i won't be able to make it to this job. So aww of the hype to get a job for nothin if i get good result in exam results so now im praying to go to shitty bell-end college ah fuck. Even then I'm gonna die, living in the middle of no-where is shit i will have to get up about 6:30 then go to college or uni then straight to work then get back in about 11. Then up early again on Saturday fuck that for 4 years i struggle to get outa bed before 12. This will be a big change everybody is used to fuckin about doin nothin or no much then we will aw get fucked at the same time into doing 6 things at once i will be workin 5 and a half solid days a week, I have to start driving lessons the now fuck spending my life on a train at least if I can stick this job it will mean lessons and a vechile will be on the way, meanin no more fuckin trains. Fuck this is depressing summer is too boring no enough stuff to do to fill up the time then aw of a sudden you've not got any time and i bet we all think of stuff we wish we had time to do. I feel sorry for young Michael he has to go away into Glasgow Uni extra half an hour there and back. Aw well Andy and Craig started uni this time last year and they can drive now so..... plus we'll be 18 so we can spread the wings further than Franklyns which is a tad pish.  Aye so who knows a good instructor then outa the 2 people that read this. Ciao 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "I am pleased to tell you your application has been succesful" they magic unexpected words ehhhh. But it was dodgy Mr Downey gave me a tinke at 1 to say emmm my interview got changed so i didny know where i was goin. Then it got changed back. Ohhhh dodgy company eh. Then they hadn't heard of me or him. Then they leave you for 40 mins to fill out a 5 min form then a peach of a script. You get the script like hello may i speak to mr/mrs smith but i didn't click you say mrs if its a woman obviously and i am calling this Claire character Mr Smith then makin a balls up of it soundin like a retard then the interview..... What did you think of your previous manager ? ehhh he was a bit of a gimp to be honest. ohhh or how would you feel about your shifts being suddenly changed ? Emmm i'd probably be quite angry cos i've not done anything have i ? Then they go we are talking about extraordinary events such as 9/11 you don't want to be seeling death insurance then do you. Fair enough. So then at the end have you got any questions ? Naw. then i thought i'd received the knockback... "Welll heres my tip for your next interview have questions prepared beforehand so you sound keen" Sounds like a knockback doesn't it but it wasnt this company are dodgy i will go in and kick some arse of course and be out in a week. Its dodgy might not even be able to do it cos it starts at 5 if i get into Strathy im fucked. Aw well and plus the ££ i was informed of on the phone was suddenly down 25% aw well. Mr downey had his second interview and they said they would phone him we have faith in this figure but when they asked why he wants to work there or something he came out wae cos the moneys good the guys a tit. And young Michael's interview is next Wednesday so there might still be a posse. Ciao 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      .... I didny tell anybody i'm no movin again. Big Ann mighta signed the deal but thats nothing so I am  no  movin to home farm again. And I've got a job interview on Thursday see if i get it and Downey doesn't, i think i might pish myself. Its a call centre in Airdrie thats a bit to go to work in a call centre but theres some people about here who work in Arnold Clark you would prob kill if you had to work wae them. No pointin any elbows but theres a poofy fuckin wanker you'd want tae fuckin strangle. See if your a fanny and typed in the big name haha ur a prick u just have to type in  urlLink darren1986.tk . And i don't care if i copied the wee shortcut thing, they copied it from someone else anyway. Aye and incase they read this they should make another site i know you aw go awww poofs haha and that but who cares it was a bit gay how they abused people for nothin and abused dead people but the site was a good laugh the songs and aw that so make it again just dont abuse dead people and that cos thats probably how it got deleted. Aw well thats quite enough pish see how you can write alot of pish about nothin its good int it i could work for the Daily spazzy. 
    
</post>


</Blog>