<Blog>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This is The first entry on my Blog and I wish to make it worthwhile. For the people who took the time to read this I hope you get something out of it and learn something. For the first time in my life I wish to have friends and loved ones close to me. Before this sudden change of heart, I was a good for nothing loser, with nothing else to lose because of my being a loner. I dressed like shit, went days without shaving and fixing up my hair, let my nails grow long because they made good self defense weapons, and I even through a period where I literally starved myself to lose weight, just because I thought I looked huge. So then came a lengthy relationship, I learned a lot from that one and I also lost a lot during that time. During the time I lost my 2 best friends. Dave who was my best friend since we were little, broke up with my other best friend Hilly. I still don't exactly know the reason for the break up and I'm sure neither does hilly. So Dave left to California , and Hilly has been wiped off the earth for all I know. During that period i was really pissed at Dave for what he did and I was worried about Hilly because she locked herself in her apartment and I dont know what she couldve been doing. So enough of that, i don't like going back to that. What I learned from that, was that even the strongest of friendships can fall apart and that things can never be perfect. So then a couple of months later I develop these problems in my life. This is the only thing I feel I shouldn't discuss with anyone because It could knock my solution process off balance and destroy my life. Quite a few times I have thought about Suicide--Did I do it? you ask...obviously not if i am here telling you about it-- But then you ask did I attempt it?.....Maybe yes, maybe no, only some people know the truth.-- What did i learn from this? Suicide is not the way, you can work out your own problems in a safe living way. Trust me, I have a lot going on in my life right now to know and I'm in the process of working things out. To be honest, I think that the majority of the world is Fake. You can never be too careful when it comes to knowing who is your friend and who isn't. But still, I realize   NOW   that you have to give people a chance and this is why I am trying to make new friends. I still think that most of Society is fake but what can you do? If you can't beat em' try and get along with them even if they are a bunch of preppy assholes. Keep your enemies close to you. But when you feel you are going nowhere with certain people, be it your best friend, you have to know when to let them go even if you hurt their feelings. It's for the best trust me, what you dont do, the other person will do it to you first. Everything in life has an opposite, I always say " You can't love without Hate and you can't hate without Love"....Ok now to the next topic...I already have a goal set for my future, Nothing will stop it from happening, even if I Die before I can do it, I will accompish it from my grave. If you want something, Strive for it and don't ever give up. It's hard to know who you can trust, this kinda goes back to Society being fake so I'm gonna drop this one, it ends up being the same way. This is a big topic for me, never and I mean never, never get your relations with people outside the family involved with your family. Your friends are another family of your own and your family is blood. At the teenage stage of life even from your 20's to mid 20's its a bad idea to get them mixed up. there is a big maturity factor involved with this. Just trust me on this, Family and friends are 2 different things. Just leave it at that, ok? Do what you want, when you want. If it feels right, do it. Don't rely heavely on other people's opinions, it will draw back and kick you directly in your asshole. I have more to say but i am really sick and tired about talking about the past so for now on, all of my entries will be about things that happened over the course of the day or day before. I will add fun things and not make this a boring blog. Later on I will tell you about my likes and dislikes, my hobbies, and what type of people I like and hate. I will take pics of fun things whenever possible and post them up. I will post links to cool things. And much more. See Ya!    
     

    
</post>


</Blog>