<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I just saw spider-man 2... I HAT EHAPPY ENDINGS right now.. mainly cause i get a bad feeling that im not gonna have one...Man i am tired..im tired of feeling and hurting.. and all this shit.. but I can see light... its just too far... i dont know if i can make it.. I will never lay down... i will not keel over... I WONT GIVE UP... i cant ive done too much to stop now      Its funny last night I got 2 offers for dates im such a looser.. i turned them both down... and these are girls that I have crushed on for like 4 months they both out of the blue are now showing interest in me... and i still cant back away.. my dreams for so long were answered and I stepped away... for her      I wish to dissapear completely....  how may I if you read this tell me  please  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I Feel Small... I feel Like im in a dream.. beacsue Real Life couldnt be like this... I Understand The Song mad world after last night... i had a dream....Sam was walking away from me I was sprintin Ive never ran so hard or fast in my life.. I felt like an olympian.. I couldnt catch her... i couldnt get her attention she was slipping away..... then the ground seperated there was a hude cliff between me and her I kept running I knew the one thing i wanted was her so I lept... And i Failed on the way down i looked up and sam blew a kiss at me. then a bullet wound appeared on my chest..... I was thinking on the way down I realized this is wonderful if i cant have her I will just die.. i then saw myself it was like i was watching myself fall i closed my eyes put a smile on and enjoyed what seemed to be like 4 minutes of falling it was beautiful.... a few seconds Troy appologized for everything he has ever done to me... and i died  I find It kinda funny, I find it kinda sad The Dreams in witch I'm dieing are the best Ive ever had  Good Bye -Rem 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My fucking God  Im gonna SWEAR SO much in this so be prepared..... Im fucking in PAIN... I ended prolly the best fucking relationship of my life so far today... cause im in love.... in love with a girl... THAT FUCKED A STONER LIKE 3 NIGHTS AGO.... I dont know what to think....I cant even be fucking angry im just hurt... i ran i ran for like 15 min It HURT it HURT SOOO FUCKING BAD I Can move my god damn LEGS.....IM honestly SICK TO MY FUCKING STOMACH.. i dont know what to feel or say or do... i dont know what the fuck is going on....I cryed today more then i think i ever have in my life....i guess my alter ego poped by today... ive never met him but i can hear him sometimes  he is a fucking asshole he's aslways fucking laughing at me...I HATE HIM!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! RRRAAAHHHH..... so yah she fucking ripped my heart out... but its still hers i cant not love her.... i think this is worse than when one of my ex's told me she fucked a drug dealer for drugs then got pregnant... hey what an interesting FUCKING PATTERN maybe i should become a drugy again i would get more PUSSY  FUCK           -Rem 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You Know.. it's truely amazing how much of an asshole rem can be soemtimes.. he is inconsiderate, and a jackass.... he is a moron.. he is hurt because a love of his is interested in another guy... its killing him... im not to sure if he can fucking sleep and you know she is amazing if she can do this to Rem... so something must be done...  in the next week a change will happen im sure what it will be but it hopefull wont kill the guy... well see yah later all          --Kalvin   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well  why do ppl feel the need to improve apon themselves?  I am NO prize but i am happy with me. and some ppl are amazing and it hurts my heart to see them not see it. I'de kill myslef if I could show the world its own beauty. i would bleed myself to show the heart of ppl. I would cry all the rivers full to know ppl can be happy.  i need ppl to see there beauty cause i am an empty vesle I hold nothing in me i am what surrounds me I am a canvas that fades i fade fast so i need to be around happiness or blackness falls on me and is hard to get out.  I wish i could be a white canvas  to show the world what purity is so they may feel the happiness that I would imbody i would gladdly give my life to show this to everyone or even ONE PERSON.  I am nothing waiting to be something  so incurage you all be something so I may be aswell  THANK YOU FOR READING THIS I LOVE ALL OF YOU 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to spill I am feeling my heavy heart everytime i get htis feeling it feels like my chest is getting thick and heavy with like concrete or something. I feel this way when I am feeling emotion that i dont know how to interpet i dont really know if its sadness or joy i feel now all i know is im feeling a lot of it. I can often feel the way the ppl around me feel I interpret what they are feeling and i in turn feel that way. that is the reason im the way i am. i focus on understanding what other feel and how others act sometimes i forget about me. But hey there are a lot of ppl who are more interesting than me. thats why I am a rounded person I take the cool parts of my friends and i become that, so i feel better about myself. I guess that makes me a huge phony but hey if you are gonna do something might as well be convicted.... or not whatever   i guess im done for now 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow  one thing you may realize while hanging out with rem is that he is very immoral he has almost no conscience its rediculous. I guess he makes up for it kinda he is nice to like evry one. But he has a serious problem unless he hurst some one he really cares about he wont give a shit. He has conned a lot of ppl out of money he is good at it he doesnt mind. But he hates it when ppl dislike for no reason he tries to make everyione happy see he is the con-man that wants to be everyone's best friend.  One thing he needs to work on is evaluating risk and having the balls to fallow through with the capable some situations are easily avoidable if you can think through the possibilities. Normally Rem is good at it but lately he has been lacking in this skill  "hey, Love does funny things to yah" says rem.  I dont even know why im writing this one Rem just wanted to sill his guts on some things so here I am writing for him. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, this is my first blog so you may wanna get to know the character well his name is Remington North he is 17 and he has had an interesting life so far.  When he was 3 he cracked his dad over the head with a frying pan When he was 5 he gave his 14 year old brother Ryan a black eye At the ripe age of 10 he was hospitalized for 2 months and almost died once and actually dies once. it was the most inriching feeling he had ever had waking the morning afetr even though he didn't know what had happened he just felt wonderful. At the age of 12 he left the country be himself for the first time on a plane to Cali to see his sister Stephanie, it was a wonderful experience. Age 14 he went to high scholl and fell in love for the first time. Unfortunatly she was a drug addict and got pregnant with her dealers baby then lost it cause of drugs... so we wont talk about her much. Age 15 he fell in love again and lost his virginity to a lovely girl who he still loves Trista she is one of his best girlfriends ever. he finds he loves anything sexual wether it be pleasuring a girl or being pleasured he quikly learns all he can about pleasuring a woman. Age 16 he meats one of the coolest guys ever Jay Vanderheart or "jesus" he is one of his best friends ever he teaches him indirectly how to live life and not be afraid when you dont need to be. At age 17 he falls in love twice but that is another chapter.   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>