<Blog>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Damn Boring,  Yesterdae National Dae Oso Like Nobody Day, haha! Who Cares. I Went to my Cousin Chalet Today, find Something Ro Cure my Boringness Lor, So Sianz. By TheWay I Before going There i Met Up With my Cousin First, at Pasir Ris Interchange and as Normal, He`s late again. After i met him up, we went to the chalet. His Frens havent Yet Come. But it Was Around 5pm, They should arrive minutes later.  Around 5.45pm,  My Cousins Male Frens Arrived Wth Charcols and Hotdogs and Burger Meat Patty. Hmmm, Party Time!! haha!. My Cousin Intoduce Them ro me, And We Get To know each other. They Were Friendly Chated With Me As if We`ve known Them for So LOng. Cool! Moments later My Other Cousins Arrived, Great! Atleast have Some Company.  Around 6.30pm,  Few Females Frens Of my Cousins Arrive, Around 4 of Them, hmm..i was not Paying attention to them at First Cause i was Busy Putting Up Fire For barbeque.When The Fire Was up. I took a break, Then, Chat with my Cousin. Suddenly, One Of The Girls introduce herself to me. 3 of Us chat together. Her name was "Francine",Hope i spell Her Name Correctly, She`s Chinese. Very Cute.haha!. Really Pretty. Now then i realise. I Think i have a Crush on Her.haha!Shh!!  Around 7.30pm,  BarbeQue!! yeah!! I Had No Mood To eat So i sat Down With all of MY cousins Aorund 3 of them together. While The host, My Another Cousin When to Entertained His Frens. Then I went inside the chalet After i took Few Hot dogs and Burgers Inside and i Watch TV.I was Watching "The Apprentice" . Then From No Where a Cute Voice So Familiar Came out "May i?" and its...*Francine!!!.i reply"Sure".She Was Holding Food too. She sat Down With me On top of The bed right Beside me. We Started To Chat as We eat. "Like Watching This Show?" She asked me. I said " yeah, Cool Show". haha. Around This Time i may look Normal But Deep inside My heart went Fast Beating, she so Cute. After We eat, We Clean up and Both i and Francine went for a walk, and we went to escape theme Park. had Our rollerCoaster ride together and play with her at the arcade. Cool! at Around 11pm, i Went home abd She too, I Went to Take a bus But She took a Different Bus!! ShiT! but So Stupd of me was that Yo! i forgotten to ask For her no.!! Dumb!. only Realised that after i got on to the bus.haha.Dumb!Guess to much Fun with her.. Still remember my last wave. After all, My cousin knows her so Whats The Rush.hehex!  
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        3 hunters went haunting and Was caught by canibals. They Were brought to see the Chief of the Canibals to determined their Fate.The Chief said " I`ll Give each of You a chance to live But Each of You must Do Something If Each of you Wan to live, Each Of you Must find a Different type of Fruit each and then bring the Fruit back here.Then I`ll tell u what to do next". So the hunters separated and went to find a fruit each. The 1st hunter managed to find a rambutan and brought it back to the Chief. He was to stuff the fruit into his nose and if he laugh, he will be executed imediately. The 1st hunter stuff the Rambutan up his nose but couldnt` managed to get a hold of himself as it was to silly and burst out laughing. He was executed and went to Heaven. He Saw the 2nd Hunter with berries. But the 2nd hunter was also executed and met the 1st hunter in heaven. The 1st hunter ask " i thought you had berries? why are u executed?". The 2nd hunter said, " I Stuff the berries in my nose, but i could'nt get a hold of myself and started laughing when i saw the 3rd hunter with a Jackfruit".    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       JASMINE SORIANO TRIAS   Age: 17  Hometown: Mililani, HI  Audition City: Hawaii  First Concert: NSYNC  Last Concert: Christina Aguilera  Official Idol Website Initial Interview:   Q. When did you first start to sing? A. Since I could talk.  Q. Do you have any formal singing training? A. Yes, I attend the Performing Artist Academy. I started when I was 8 years old and I stopped when I was 10. I went back when I was 14 years old.  Q. What other talents do you have? A. I play the piano, the ukulele, the guitar. I dance hip-hop and hula.  Q. If you don’t make it on AMERICAN IDOL, what will you do? A. I will continue to pursue a career in singing, or I will finish up my education and become a nurse.  Q. What are your personal goals in life? A. I want to have a recording contract with a big record company and live my dream of becoming a star. Or go to school and finish up my education to become a nurse.  Q. What album would your friends be surprised you own? A. A Filipino soap opera soundtrack.  Q. What is the first CD you ever bought? A. The NSYNC CD  Q. What is in your CD player right now? A. A mixed CD of different kinds of music.  Q. Who is your AMERICAN IDOL? A. I loved Kelly from the moment I heard her sing "Respect."  Q. What is your favorite type of music? A. I love all kinds of music. I listen to Hawaiian music, R&amp;B, hip-hop, alternative, contemporary.  Q. What is your favorite song to sing? A. I don’t have a favorite song. I love to sing power ballads and other styles of music.  Q. Favorite male pop artist? A. Justin Timberlake.  Q. Favorite female pop artist? A. Christina Aguilera.  Q. Favorite album of all time? A. A mixed CD of my top favorite songs.  Q. Who in the music world do you think your style is most like? A. I’d probably have to say Monica. She dressed sexy, but kept it conservative also.  Q. Most embarrassing moment? A. In 7th grade, I was drinking milk and my friend was telling me and my other friends a joke. When he said the punch line, I swallowed probably half and the rest squirted out of my nose and my mouth because I couldn’t hold in the laugh.  Q. If you couldn’t sing, which talent would you most like to have? A. Dancing.  Q. What has been your proudest moment in life so far? A. Making it this far in the competition.  Q. What is your definition of an AMERICAN IDOL? A.Someone that has the full package and has the charisma to make many people look up to them.  Q. Why do you want to be an AMERICAN IDOL? A. Because I think I have what it takes to make into the business. I’m a strong person and I want to share all my talents with the rest of world.  Q. Who is your favorite judge and why? A. I’d have to say Simon because even though his comments can be mean, they’re very true if you take it the right way. He doesn’t care what people think about him and I think that he’s the best judge.  Q. Who is your least favorite judge and why? A. My least favorite is Randy, because there’s only three words in his vocabulary: Dog, Man, and Dude.  Q. What advice do you have for other hopefuls? A. Sing your heart and don’t hold back. Don’t get intimidated by other great singers because you’re a great singer yourself, so just think that others may be intimidated by you. Confidence is key!  Q. What would people be surprised to learn about you? A. I can be very shy.  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>