<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       How is it that one can be soo pathetically bored and still be busy? I mean, cummon. I've been running around like a chicken with its head cut off, and I still find myself feeling bored and utterly fed up. I'm sick of it. I have no energy left to do anything that I should do, example: cleaning my room. Usually I don't mind, I even some what enjoy doing it... don't ask me why because I have no idea. Freak of nature in that respect I guess. Anywho... that's enough of a rant. Must be getting back to mind numbing boredom. See you there!      The word of the day is:  Wholesome!   
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Ok, these two games are the most addicting games EVER. I've got my whole family hooked on the chicken game, and just my sister and I on the little alien thingy one. Have fun!    Chicken game:    urlLink  http://www.ebaumsworld.com/fowlwords.html     Alien thingy game:   urlLink  http://www.ebaumsworld.com/tontie.html   
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Howdy all! Back in the world of electronics, dunno if that's a good or bad thing yet. I totally had a blast on the lake this past couple of days. Tanner and happier are always good things to come away with from vacations.    the word of the day is:  sleek!   
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So... I'm officially registered for my Fall college courses!!! I'm sooo excited. I'm buisy watching anime, Van Dread... It's pretty awsome, I like it so far. So.. yeah, catch more updates on here on Wednesday, a short vaca. is comming up tommorow! Buh bye!      word of the day is:  Blue Footed Booby   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok...Ok... these little short films are just too good to leave out!:    urlLink  http://atomfilms.shockwave.com/af/content/gangsta_rap_se       urlLink  http://atomfilms.shockwave.com/af/content/beastie_boys_check       urlLink  http://atomfilms.shockwave.com/af/content/tauntauns       urlLink  http://atomfilms.shockwave.com/af/content/atom_211       urlLink  http://atomfilms.shockwave.com/af/content/pink5          urlLink  http://atomfilms.shockwave.com/af/content/trinket_maker       urlLink  http://www.lowmorale.co.uk/creep/     I saved the best for last, I hope I become this cool when I'm all old and everything!:    urlLink  http://www.pixar.com/shorts/gg/theater/short_320.html    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm at a loss for new material to either rant about, poke fun at, or muse about, so as a result, I am now going to give you some links to totally awesome sites to visit.... ENJOY!      A site that is based on Japanese instructions/products translated into English, hence, Engrish:   urlLink  http://www.engrish.com/         Feeling particularly politically oriented, watch this short film that pokes fun at both parties:   urlLink  http://atomfilms.shockwave.com/af/content/this_land_af       Short little summaries of past monarchs who have some peculiar tendencies:   urlLink  http://www.xs4all.nl/~kvenjb/madmon.htm#maaikemeu         Just a random little music clip, quite funny:   urlLink  http://www.ebaumsworld.com/dubdub.html         Another random music clip plus animation:   urlLink  http://www.badgerbadgerbadger.com/       A complete list of phobias, are people really scared about these things?:   urlLink  http://www.phobialist.com/#A   -      I love the show Invader Zim, if you haven't seen it, you might not get it, but this is one of the webpages based around the crazy funny animation:   urlLink  http://www.roomwithamoose.com/       If you are completely at a loss about how to spend your summer here is a completely wierdsite involving the adoption of cartoon animals:   urlLink  http://www.adoptme.com/       Last but not least, here are two sites that you can display all that musical tallent of yours:   urlLink  http://www.typorganism.com/     urlLink  http://www.createbands.com/      go crazy!       ps, the word of the day is:  allergy   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I have this huge craving to get a new cd. I don't know why, I have plenty that I don't listen to. Anyway, I went online to see what music was out there by artists I liked already, and ones I had never heard of. I get to borders.com and type in The Killers, The Darkness, The Vines, The Shins, Modest Mouse, and a few others I had heard on the radio and liked. I listen to several clips from their albums, and guess what I hear. Most of it is useless filler crap. I like one song on these cd's of twelve songs each. What's wrong with music??? Am I wrong to want to have a cd that has at least three good songs out of twelve? No wonder people download songs legally and illegally in and effort to prevent the pollution of their brains with meaningless boyband wanna be songs.       the word of the day is:  disenchantment   
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok... short entry today... in true teenage fashion, my mood has displaced any inklings of a perky, happy freakin sunshiney mood left in me. Bu humbug.       The word of the day is:  curmudgeon         go look it up   
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well... Lemme see here. I am now officially off shopping. FOREVER! Not really, but I'd like to think so. I spent an entire four hours at a Fabric Depot in Gresham, a hellish experience. I also decided to make this expedition during the annual sale where everything is 40% off. Brilliant. For those of you who do not have the first hand experience of a fabric store of any kind, let alone during a sale, let me help you in your quest for better understanding. Picture acres and acres of fabric roles (80% of which are hideous patterns involving one or more of the various neon colors), little old ladies armed with shopping carts and pointy knitting needles, little screaming boys and a few brave or, more likely, sedated husbands trailing behind their determined wives. More like an obstacle course, it is your job to effectively maneuver yourself, and a cart around any one of these similarly encumbered individuals in an effort to scoop up a choice piece of fabric before someone else has the opportunity. I not only had to find fabric, but also a suitable pattern. In order to find a pattern, you have to find the picture of the outfit you desire in one of the many thick fashion books placed in strategic locations around the store, much like an Easter egg hunt involving large, older women viewing for the same books, looking for the best support hose patterns in Simplicity or Butterick. So, three and a half hours later, I'd managed to find book, the picture, and id number of the dress I wanted, the cloth, the buttons, zipper, ribbon, thread, and netting for the dress, and I had successfully made it past the register demons. Never again will I battle my way through a fabric store just to avoid paying 170$ for a prom dress. This was an adventure to remember.    The word of the day is:  Depot !  Hello Kiddies! Do you know what  Depot  means?   
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Heehee.... so, I've had my fill of city life for one year. I went to Portland, Oregon today to walk around the city and take in all the art galleries. Obviously I haven't been there lately. There are only a few, solitary galleries left, most have been replaced by those therepeutic matress stores or knick nacs. Kind of sad. I always forget how many people live in cities and how everything is pavement. Ugh... I dont know why anyone would want to live in a major or minor city. You couldn't have pets and be fair to them, especially dogs, and I'd find myself eating out of a take out box more often than I care to think about. Oh well... I guess some people are cut out for country life either. Tah tah from the rural boonies!  
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Isn't it silly how people insist on having totally meaningless conversations just for the sake of contact. If contact were that important, shouldn't conversation hold some sort of deeper meaning because that relationship is important? I mean, a relationship should not be dulled down by slew of empty headed transactions. I don't know if I'm making any sense. I think I've been reading too many Ayn Rand books. Well, sometimes it's more fun to make sense only in your own head.    P.s. The word of the day is:  mushroom!   
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So.... blogging is fun. fun fun fun fun fun. I like pie. Pie is sooo much better than cake. I went out and picked blueberries at a u-pick place... yeah, not as much fun as they'd have you believe. Plus, if you're picking them for money, the average wages are about 22 cents a pound. I only picked five pounds in an hour, so... that'd be about 1.00$ an hour. That would suck.       
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well... welcome to my Blog! Heehee... now I can rant on and on about absolutely nothing, have all kinds of spelling errors and just be my weird self with an audience. This is the beginning of a beautiful friendship. Or whatever you'd choose to call it.       The Random Wordie of the Day is:  Vaccuum!   
    
</post>


</Blog>