<Blog>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm, This was an interesting one I'll say. It started off pretty weird, I was actually in a game of Counter-Strike. I haven't played this game for almost a year, so for it to be in my dreams shows you it's effect since 1999 :). It was in cs_militia, a deserty type map. Now it was the back of the militia map but was mostly in Irvine, near Tustin Market Place. Between my old neighborhood and the TMP, was a barren deserty field. Now the house from the map was there, but everything else wasn't. What the house looks like in militia...    So there was a long street, coming from TMP to a little buissness center type place, where they were putting up buildings, and to the left was the house from militia. This is what it looked like...    Now I had a team, but they were fuck tards and they couldn't do shit, go figure. I was using the SIG552. This is what it looks like...    So I went around back and just killed all the T's, and my team didn't do shit, so I was kinda pissed off. Now after a little while of that they leave, and walk down the street. Now down the street there is Jessica Simpson... yes, Jessica Simpson... dead though. She looked like she was standing up and then just fell backwards onto one of those green electrical box things. She was wearing some white gown/dress thing. My team was just rushed to her and they were talking and some construction workers went over there also to see what was going on. I went back to my spawn (the other end of the street) and some two kids were walking the other way (towards Jessica). They looked at me funny so I walked up to them and they talked trash, and as I'm about to smack this kid upside the head with the butt of my rifle, an old pick-up truck comes along and stops infront of me. So I look in and there is some guy in there who is now defending these kids. He gets out and I walk backwards some and as I'm doing that my brother riding a bike, randomly comes and goes between us. Just then I pulled out a pocket knife and stabbed the guy in his chest, and said something along the line of "You piece of shit cock sucking faggot, don't try to pull that shit", we then pushed him to the ground and beat the shit out of him (was quite fun) and then Ellen Cleghorne (from SNL)    who I guess is a cop, in a red Chevy Blazer drives up and looks as we are killing this guy, and drives away. that was pretty much it. Very weird one, I must say. Also pretty short.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well the dream I had last night wasn't that bad at all really. It started off as me and my family doing something, thus we were at some sort of hotel or somewhere. I remember going from room to room with my brother, and in one room there was some porn video on a shelf in some wall unit. I waited for my brother to leave, but he was in the back of the room or something. Eventually I came back and watched the video alone, it was alright, but there was too much scene acting so I fast forwarded it to a random spot and it showed some girl getting fucked on her back, so I rubbed one out to it. Then I left and then I forget what happened. Later I remember that I was at IHS and it was sunny out, and I went into a room and it was all red, from a red light I assume. I walked over to one side of the room and there was a little tub/spa thing and abunch of people around eating and talking. I took off my shirt and pants (still in my boxers though) and got in, but the water didn't feel quite right, so I got out and picked up my clothes and went over past a divider in the room. There was no red light here, but it was pretty cool temperature wise and seemed alright. There was a lower level to the room, and down low there was a floor with about a foot or so of water, and two more of the spa things, but they were bigger. So I got in one, there was nobody else in it so I was kind of relaxing at this point. Then I looked over and saw the other one had two girls in it, and they were alone. So I got out and went into their spa thing and talked with one of them. The other girl was good looking with somewhat tan skin, light tan though, and brownish-blonde hair. She just looked to the side and was mellow. The other one was Chinese, and had hair like this,    but her hair was shorter and she was really cute.  Here is what that room looks like,    So I was talking with her and then she got up from sitting down and kinda got on her knees with her toes straight into the ground (kinda hard to explain I suppose) and she wanted to kiss me. She had almost perfect lips in my book. I moved in closer and she opened her mouth and then I started to French her, and suck on her tongue and she got a kick out of this. So I moved my hand around between her legs, and stuck a finger between her bikinii or whatever it was and she rocked back and forth on it while we were kissing. It was pretty nice. Then we stopped for some reason. Talked a little more, then kissed for a little bit longer. Then I guess a bell rang or something and we all got out and i walked with her to another room. This room was pretty bright and alot of people were there, I remember I was between a copy machine or something and a wall talking to her about Cantonese (I had no shirt on and I was holding my pants up, still had boxers though) and a teacher from IHS was with a teacher from my current school, and the one from IHS said that I had to go to some room tomorrow to make up something. This is what this room looked like,    She went out the door behind her and I went outside and everyone was going from one class to another, and I was walking to this room that the teacher had told me to go to tomorrow. Then some other teacher said that I don't even have to do it, so I went back to the first room with the spa things. As I was walking in there were a hell of a lot more people. One of them from behind was a lamer from my middle school and he was yapping about CS, saying how we used to play online together (we never did) and he kept refering to my old alias 'Whitey' as 'Whitt-ey', and I just walked away and I went down to the lower level and there were again alot of people, and that is pretty much it. I probably would have said more but this is pretty much all I remember, this is about 3 hours since I woke up so I probably forgot some things.  This is somewhat weird because I was just talking to someone about Asian girls and girls with tans online just hours before. Hmmm...
    
</post>


</Blog>