<Blog>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday, until about 4 PM, my husband and I did nothing.  Glorious, apathetic nothing.  We slept until ten, woke and ate breakfast, then slept on the couch for three hours while the drying cereal bits bonded implacably to the bowls on the coffee table and the History Channel droned pleasantly in the background. We woke up, shook the sleep from our bodies and went to the grocery store, having discovered a lack of appropriately simple lunch options. Coffers replenished and stomachs replete, we resumed our positions and slept for another two hours – the television obligingly performing muted white-noise counterpoint to the afternoon sounds of the neighborhood that floated in through the open windows with the breeze.  Do you know the feeling of intense desire and stupendous relief associated with giving in to the urge to nap? Of giving up the struggle to remain awake and coherent as your eyes close heavily and, with an unconsciously grateful sigh, you burrow more closely into the couch-pillow’s heady warmth? Saturday afternoon was all about that sensation and these:  The disorienting momentary surfacing as the worlds of dream and reality blur and intersect; the clean white light of the unseasonably cool summer morning throwing the linen weft of the swaying curtains into sharp, pale green relief for an instant before the clear sunlight becomes too much for sleep-accustomed eyes; hair pressed damply soft against your neck from the heat of sleep; finding the infinitesimally more comfortable arrangement of limbs, blanket and couch-mate that plummets you once more into REM oblivion.  We are blessed with the luxury of laziness; of being able to pause busy lives and let our bodies shut down against the will of our Protestant work ethic. Lassitude such as this is a precious gift – allowing the tired body to heal, the tired mind to clear.    Sleep, rest of nature, O sleep, most gentle of the divinities, peace of the soul, thou at whose presence care disappears, who soothest hearts wearied with daily employments, and makest them strong again for labour! --Ovid     Every now and then go away, have a little relaxation, for when you come back to your work your judgment will be surer. Go some distance away because then the work appears smaller and more of it can be taken in at a glance and a lack of harmony and proportion is more readily seen.  --Leonardo Da Vinci    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Those of you who know me know that I have nurtured a rich and thriving hatred for a certain big-box retailer who shall remain nameless (suffice it to say that the name rhymes with "Small Heart" or perhaps "Everything You Buy Here Falls aPart"). I would be happy to provide a short list of the reasons for this abhorrence, but the short list would still take several months to write.  Is it unnatural to feel antipathy towards a place where one can legally purchase a hunting rifle complete with ammunition, or perhaps a feathered and sequined thong, and one cannot purchase a CD with naughty words and 80% of the book/magazine section is devoted to "Inspirational" literature? Not that I crave naughty CDs and not that there’s anything wrong with Inspirational literature – it’s just a disconnect.  A typically American, confused, are-we-or-aren’t-we disconnect.  Is it unnatural to feel a sense of righteous outrage that said retailer wields its bloated, corpulent corporate clout like biggest playground bully ever, squashing Mom and Pop ruthlessly beneath its behemoth posterior while it slobbers gleefully over an ice cream cone it outsourced to China (after it quietly ceased squawking “Made in America” and hoped no one would notice)? Over a company that blitzes the public with warm fuzzy television ads depicting the warm fuzzy  people it hires and the warm and fuzzy way those people help orphans and homeless puppies as if that somehow makes the company itself warm and fuzzy as well?  In any case, I decided just over a year and a half ago, that I would no longer support said big-box retailer with my business.  ("That'll show 'em," I thought. "I bet they'll be out of business within the month.")  And, satisfyingly, I have been able to survive without its presence in my life.  I only acknowledge it in order to sneer haughtily as a I drive past one.  Therefore, it is with an enormous sense of irony and a realization that God does, in fact, have a sense of humor, that I announce that the one-stop shopping and the low, low prices will, one day soon, be three doors down from my house. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blogtastic!  This is now affilare's home on blogger.  I have a typepad home as well, but I have been meaning to try blogger for a while now.  We'll see how it goes!  Right now I'm killing time waiting to be picked up for dinner. Whee! I should be doing work. In fact, I feel guilty, so that is what I'll do. 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I can't think of a caption for my head. It's just my head. Now it's my head on the web. I'm so  au courant.       This is only here because I needed to host a picture to attach to my profile up there in the right corner, not because I enjoy posting big pictures of myself.  One of these days I'll edit this with a better one, but I've got to look for it.  I really should have cropped out that strange, misshapen growth like thing down in the left corner of the picture. I'm not sure what that is. It isn't my shoulder, I can tell you that much. 
    
</post>


</Blog>