<Blog>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey everyone what's up its been a couple days since I last posted anything and I figured now was as good as time as any since I won't be home for the next few days. Yeah thats right I won't be here cuz I will be stuck in some cottage in Geneva-On-The-Lake for a few days woohoo what a vacation**cough cough** Anyway Tomorrow I will be busy first off going to work and then when I get home I will probably spend the rest of the day getting things ready to go and I definately can not miss the finale of LAST COMIC STANDING. Then after that it will be Friday and again I will be at work but I will be leaving early so I can go get my physical from my Afganny doctor what a way to start the vacation Getting fondoled by some towellhead who could decide to screw things up for me completely if you know what I mean. Then when that is all over with I will be hitting the road off to GOTL where I will probably be bored for the next three days but then again who knows anyway Monday I should be back just in time to go back to work since I dont want to miss any cuz school starts and I will basiclly be screwed cuz the I will be unemployed. At least I have a temporary job waiting for me at Cheesman's Fright Farm so that should give me some time to find a more permanent solution. Tuesday back to work again and when I come home QUAKER STEAK AND LUBE  hecks yea!!! Boy do I love food. Anyway when I get home I wont feel like doing anything since I will be so stuffed. Wednesday the day I have been waiting for for quite a while it's my BIRTHDAY yep finally I will be 16 and be able to get my permit and maybe stop getting made fun of by a certain someone for only being 5 yrs. old..... AND I KNOW SHE KNOWS WHO SHE IS .....anyway to start off the day my dad and I are going to get ... or at least try to get my permit...Then after that we will probably be going to see Alien VS. Predator...Then off to the Lawence County fair for the rest of the day,maybe this year I wont have to face the near death experience of faulty seat belts on their right but then that would take all of the fun out of it ....So who wants to join me in a funfilled day of peril first you get to ride with me in my car that was NEVER supposed to run with my driving (I thought I should mention that) then off to the fair were we can risk our lives by being tossed around tens of feet in the air in rides that were probably used for terrorism during the NAZI days. Well thats about in I will let you all know how the vacation went that is if I dont die of boredom anyway until then GOOD BYE. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This post is for your comments, ideas, or questions you may have for me. I know one thing Brooke Ill probably be hearing from you once you read the comment I left on your new post   UPDATE: You may now leave comments even if you are not a member of Blog so feel free to leave them  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah thats me just another face in the crowd. Normally I wouldnt be sitting here typing some of my deepest thoughts into my computer's database, but when I noticed my friends were fellow bloggers I decided it might be fun so I gave it a try. I know what one certain person (cough..Christy.. cough) is thinking while reading this fine peice of work..."Well big suprise here Josh is copying me once again" well what can I say I have no creativity on my own so have to get it from somewhere...well anyway..It's Wednesday The 4th of August and its only 2 weeks before I can finally go and get my permit yeah thats right I will finally be older then 5 and on that note if my b-day is getting close that also means the fun has to end sometime and I know that most know what I am talking about ... School ... yeah thats right its almost time to drag ouselves back to Stinkin Lincoln In the heart of the crudhole we all know as Ellwood City...well at least I have a few more weeks to enjoy myself... well thats about it for now...I hope the next post is alot more exciting...but until then this will have to do. 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>