<Blog>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Baby is the other other white meat. Why not give that a try for dinner? I know I am sick!! 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i think animal crackers are amazing. i love animals so much that eating a cookie that looks like an animal is almost like petting the real thing. i bought a big bag to nosh on at work today.   personally i ejoy bitting the heads off first then devouring the body.  i know you must be thinking oh my god that is horrible. but the cookie is not the real animal so it is ok. also cookies have no blood. which is a plus!!! plus your stomach acid gets rid of all the evidence!!!  i enjoy comitting animal crackercide!!!   
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Do not eat at burrito express in manhattan. Nasty. Mexican food should be good and not make you feel like you want to toss your cookies. I am now boycotting it!!!
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So after losing my visa and my id for the y, i have become anal about all my cards. this morning i go to put my metro card in my pocket so i would have it on hand for the bus. well i detach it from the belt clip of my ipod and put it in my pocket.  10 minutes later i put my cell phone in my pocket and my metro card is not there.   I start freaking out. i ransack my bead and floor. well i decide to go to the store get breakfast and use their atm to get money for a cab. 3 hours after losing my card at 10:30 am i feel my bra poking me. well i go to fix it. turns out marla tucked her metro card into her bra stap!! 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      for those of you that don't know me... i don't like people i don't know being closer then 5 feet from me. i can usually be found saying that i have a 5 foot bubble around me! now that you know this... my question is the following:  Why in manhattan do people walk so close together that they bump into people on nearly empty sidewalks?  the sidewalk is empty except for me and random passerby still brush up against me. it is quite iritating. it is like being on a uncrowded train or subway car or bus. that random person has to sit down right next to you instead of having their own row. nope they want to sit next to you. it irks me. people...i will never understand them!!
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So the last few days has been hotter and more humid then hell in Manhattan. So tell me, why on earth would I wear black? Jesus.. it sucked! But I love how I look in black so it is ok!!! I don't recommend wearing black on a very hot day to the faint of heart!
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have now created a blog. Welcome to my world.
      
</post>


</Blog>