<Blog>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Well Sunday, even though I felt like just lying in bed and sleeping instead of getting up for church, I dragged my lazy butt out and I’m very glad I did too. Pete gave the sermon because Pastor Roy is out of town and it was awesome! He talked about being "A Servant Hearted Christian," which brought us to 1 Corinthians 13 that talks about love. It goes,  
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        To start off with, last night was awful! A bunch of us started off meeting at Morgan’s house and from there we were going to go to the airport to see Amy when her flight came in. But Amy and her brother missed their flight sending all our prior plans into a mass chaotic mess. To make a long story short a few people left and we knew where they were going and just didn’t want to go and then some other people played a little game called "Let’s ditch Rebecca and Morgan and see how upset they get." Well we were upset, very upset. So we watched "Tuck Everlasting."  
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          HAPPY   by Matthew West    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Okay so I'm sitting here and I have just decided to do this Blog thing...and when I first tried to make a new one I was going to make the screen-name thingy "Live4Him" but it wouldn't work, therefore, I made it "Glory2Him" as you can obviously see. So...about 2 minutes ago I went upstairs and got my Bible out just because I felt the urge to. But anyway, I just randomly opened it and I opened to 1 Peter. To be specific 1 Peter chapter 4 which above the passage in italics is the title "Living for God" So I read it. I wasn't fully understanding the first 6 verses, but then I got to 1 Peter 4:7-11, which reads:  
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey Everyone! I see you have been wandering around for awhile and just happened to venture into my newest addition to my blogging life. Recently I have been thinking about ways to really start to dig down deep in my faith, so I came up with this. Because I love being on the computer even if there is absolutly nothing to do, and I want to be able to share my thoughts on different things and talk about the awesome things God is doing with my life I thought I would do something to kinda combine my interests and hopefully maybe even touch a few people and help me to understand things a little better.    But before anything I thought I should mention a few things about how I became a Christain for those of you who don't know or would just like to know. I used to go to Christ the King which is a Catholic Church, my sister and I would go to "CCD" (Religious Education) on Wednesday nights and church on Sundays. I HATED IT! I would honestly fake sick every Wednesday and Sunday! So when I was a freshman. a girl I met in gym class named Mateja, who has become one of my best friends, invited me to come to a thing called Young Life with her I immediatly said "NO!" I expected it to be just like CCD where we sat and read books about God creating the world and Jesus' life and the things he did. But she didn't give up, she asked me almost every day if I would come with her. So after about a month and a half I gave in and she took me. I had a blast! However I still was going to CCD and not enjoying church. Then I was persuaded to go to camp that summer and it sounded like an awesome thing, so I went. Little did I know that when I signed up to go to this amazing camp, that my life was about to take a drastic turn. After hearing people speak and learning about some awesome stuff and finially understanding what Jesus did for us when he died on the cross I gave my life up to Him. It was one of the most amazing things I have ever experienced. But it didn't stop there, when we got back I started going to several Bible Studies and doing things with people I had just met at camp who have become my support and a true bunch of friends. I am just so amazed at how much my life has changed since that time and I have gone through a lot since that time and I would not be the person I am today at all had I not made that decision last summer.      However, I have also not been on Fire for God as much as I want to be So this is what I came up with, I would really love and appreciate any comments people have about this idea and along the way. I really have no idea what is going to happen, but today in Cell Group we talked about getting out of the boat and having faith that everything is going to work out, so I'm starting here and trying to take a chance and we'll see what happens.   
</post>


</Blog>