<Blog>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I spent the weekend at the cabin, on a lake. It's great to have a cabin, the problem with cabins is that manytimes they're packed with relatives. I love my relatives, don't get me wrong, but I love to be able to relax somewhere and smoke my joint, rather than going off to hide somewhere. I supposed it shouldn't matter, shouldn't my family love me for who I am. Well, yes, but I guess I just don't want to put them in the position that they have to say "hey, wanna go do that somewhere else?" That would make me want to say "no, I don't want to go do this somewhere else, right here on the beach is just as good a place as back in the woods." ....but that would never fly. So, I guess I'll just have to deal with woodsness. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I read somewhere that time as we think about it, is more or less a property of light (i.e. as you approach the speed of light, the way time itself progresses, changes), then doesn't measuring certain properties of light in units of time seem recursive? That is to say, if light moves at 186,000 miles/second, and you were something that could move at 186,000 miles/second, how long would a second actually be? There's an idea that the speed of light is the fastest speed there is, but is it? At the speed of light, because time becomes so distorted compared to how we think of it, couldn't there be a speed faster than what you're moving at? Because time might be so off kilter, might there not be a way to view things that just isn't possible at velocities much MUCH slower than light? Oh well, blog on!  I told you I might be back! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, another day, another thought.  Today was an average day, I guess.  I worked, I played, I'm going to bed (just not now).  I'm going to Boston in like a little more than a month, I'm really excited for that. Here's a middle size Midwestern city boy going to, by my standards, a HUGE east coast city. I don't want to admit that I'm slightly nervous, but I am. A city that size, that far away is pretty intimidating (for me). It'll be an experience I'll forever remember, especially since I'm going to see someone. Her name is Gwen. I met Gwen like 2 years ago now, but I've still been talking to her on the internet pretty often during the interim. Gwen and I hit it off when we met, the thing that bothers me is that, I don't understand why the interaction hasn't decayed. I can't say I know her that well, she was here for like a weekend 2 years ago, and even then, we didn't spend a whole lot of time together. Maybe I should just ignore my apprehension, maybe it won't matter and we'll still have a great time together and when I leave things will go back to being just like they are now, maybe there's more going on in that knockout of a chick's head than I'd like to admit. I don't know. What I do know, is I plan to have the time of my life in Boston.  Damn, I'm going to have to get another bowl before I go there, and like an oz. of pot. OR...I could just bring lots of papers. The biggest thing is, I don't want to ride on a bus for 36 fucking hours, that's going to suck. But it'll be worth it. I'll bring a big book.  Twin Ports Juggler signing off (only to probably sign on again after I smoke some more ;-) ) 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      JasMcD92080 (2:04:26 AM): Give me your PS2 or pay the consequences, bitch. JasMcD92080 (2:04:36 AM): I'll kill your cat. JasMcD92080 (2:04:49 AM): The PS2 or Neptune gets it. Marimba169 (2:05:12 AM): Neptune would kick your ass, have you seen the size of him Marimba169 (2:05:20 AM): lol JasMcD92080 (2:05:21 AM): I'm prepared to face him. JasMcD92080 (2:05:27 AM): I have long range weapons. JasMcD92080 (2:05:36 AM): Like grenades and mortars and stuff. Marimba169 (2:05:38 AM): I hope you have your black belt in cat kwon doe JasMcD92080 (2:05:46 AM): If I threw a grenade you know that dumb cat would play with it til it blew up. JasMcD92080 (2:06:03 AM): Especially if I just rolled it past him, he'd chase it even. Marimba169 (2:06:06 AM): oh sure, might lose a little hair, but he''d be pissed Marimba169 (2:06:16 AM): and then....watch out JasMcD92080 (2:06:56 AM): I have a sword. JasMcD92080 (2:06:58 AM): I have 4 actually. JasMcD92080 (2:07:09 AM): I'll wax him. JasMcD92080 (2:07:14 AM): JUST GIVE ME THE GOD DAMN PS2!!!! Marimba169 (2:07:18 AM): I'll hold you to that Marimba169 (2:07:38 AM): I'll set it up, you and Neptune, one on one, no holds barred JasMcD92080 (2:07:39 AM): He'll be bald, after I wax him.  lol Marimba169 (2:07:49 AM): ohhhhhh, that's bad dude JasMcD92080 (2:07:59 AM): If I win I get the PS2 Marimba169 (2:08:42 AM): but I still get the xbox Marimba169 (2:08:52 AM): if you win JasMcD92080 (2:09:07 AM): Fine. JasMcD92080 (2:09:16 AM): I'm takin that kitty down. JasMcD92080 (2:09:27 AM): I hope i remember to take my allergy meds so he can't use that on me. Marimba169 (2:09:49 AM): lol, well if you get blades, I'm giving my cat some catnip JasMcD92080 (2:10:37 AM): Right on. JasMcD92080 (2:10:43 AM): Can I bring my dog? Marimba169 (2:11:04 AM): no, it's blades, wax, or the dog Marimba169 (2:11:10 AM): and catnip for neptune JasMcD92080 (2:13:38 AM): What if I wax my blades Marimba169 (2:13:49 AM): that won't cut schtick Marimba169 (2:14:48 AM): especially not super Neptune JasMcD92080 (2:15:01 AM):  I know karate. JasMcD92080 (2:15:06 AM): I was in the desert, man. Marimba169 (2:15:10 AM): lol JasMcD92080 (2:15:13 AM): The FUCKING DESERT!! Marimba169 (2:15:31 AM): my cat sleeps in his own urine JasMcD92080 (2:16:10 AM): so do I. Marimba169 (2:16:24 AM): whoh, that's hardcore dude JasMcD92080 (2:16:25 AM): And my own poo, too. JasMcD92080 (2:16:33 AM): I'm a trained killer. JasMcD92080 (2:16:39 AM): If I puke, I nap in it. JasMcD92080 (2:17:10 AM): If I pee, I nap it it. JasMcD92080 (2:17:14 AM): And yes, if I poo, I nap in the poo. JasMcD92080 (2:17:54 AM): POO. Marimba169 (2:17:59 AM): wow, you must do alot of napping Marimba169 (2:18:04 AM): like a cat Marimba169 (2:18:06 AM): hmmm JasMcD92080 (2:18:06 AM): POO I TELL YOU!!! Yes. JasMcD92080 (2:18:34 AM): Fearing for your PS2 now, I bet. Marimba169 (2:19:17 AM): no, I still stand behind Neptune Marimba169 (2:19:29 AM): he's versatile JasMcD92080 (2:20:47 AM): Hmm JasMcD92080 (2:20:53 AM): I think I can take him. Marimba169 (2:21:35 AM): sometimes I'll be playing with Neptune and he'll get me in this crazy head lock and he says "give me something to eat or I'll tear your head off" and damn, I'm pretty scared JasMcD92080 (2:22:02 AM): lol!!! JasMcD92080 (2:22:13 AM): dude I'm crying I'm laughing so fucking hard at that. Marimba169 (2:22:18 AM): there's nothing more fearsome then a cat talking to you while he's got you in a headlock JasMcD92080 (2:23:31 AM): Especially when he's making death threats. JasMcD92080 (2:23:52 AM): I'll take him.  Then i get a ps2 and kitty can never hurt you again. Marimba169 (2:24:43 AM): Well, just watch out for the damned kitty headlock of death JasMcD92080 (2:25:05 AM): I'll put him in a headlock. JasMcD92080 (2:25:12 AM): And pull on his peepee. Marimba169 (2:25:42 AM): but his is retractable JasMcD92080 (2:26:05 AM): I'll cut off his paws. Marimba169 (2:26:18 AM): he's quick I tell ya JasMcD92080 (2:26:46 AM): I was in the WAR!! WAS YOUR FUCKING KITTY IN THE WAR!! CAUSE I WAS IN THE GOD DAMN WAR!!! JasMcD92080 (2:27:02 AM): I KILLED THOUSANDS!!!! Marimba169 (2:27:43 AM): my cat's got that zen attitude, like, I don't need to kill another, I know what it's like. JasMcD92080 (2:28:38 AM): Your cat is gay. Marimba169 (2:28:59 AM): hey now, give him a break, he's got no balls Marimba169 (2:29:09 AM): I took them, and juggled them JasMcD92080 (2:29:50 AM): I will drink his blood after I tear off his head. Marimba169 (2:30:18 AM): who will tear whom's head off? Marimba169 (2:30:33 AM): ...on the next 20/20 JasMcD92080 (2:30:47 AM): Celebrity catfight. Marimba169 (2:30:53 AM): err Marimba169 (2:30:55 AM): wait Marimba169 (2:31:01 AM): wanna rephrase that? JasMcD92080 (2:31:10 AM): Celebrity Cat vs Jason fight.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello, I'm Hans.  Neat name huh? I like it.  Anyway, here I go, oh wait, I've stopped, hang on a sec......ok, now that my joint's rolled and burning, I'm ready.  Well, first things first, I'm a juggler and have been juggling for about four and a half years now.  I think everyone should learn to juggle, and yes I AM just saying that because I'm a juggler.  Anyway, I taught myself after high school in '99 and have been juggling since.  I'm starting to perform at certain events now so I guess I might consider (or at least I'd like to) myselft to be moving into the professional realm, albeit at a pretty slow pace.  Nonetheless, it is first and foremost a hobby that I really enjoy, and that brings me to the conclusion of my juggling prattle.  So, reader, what brings you here?  Sorry, just a question that I wanted to pose, however, did I mean 'what brings you to this blog' or 'what brings you to this world'?  I'll let you decide.  Well, that's my first little spiel. I might get motivated to spiel again tonight with enough beer (pun intended LOL, hey, it's my blog, I'll say what's funny and what's not :-D ) 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>