<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today me and sushan wanna go choir concert together but we quarrelled so we ended going in separate ways... she was late [i was not] ... then i saw mr ng tian hui playing the paino... wow! pro manx... the music was nice.. not him .. =p ... lolxx.... i sho bad.... then got damn lot of singing. then i saw banana man[zong xing]... hmpft... then lynn nvr sit wif me!!! never mind... the songs rox... then alsho got the pasir ris pri sing ley... so cute ley... nice lor... i wanna join choir! so damn tempted! wahahas... but i cnnt sing... sho sad =( wow... then randy sing solo! brave! so cool! wow.. then got other pple sing lor... the song so touching lor...... but hear until dun want hear le lorx...... hehez...... sad manx.... nice nice.... luckily i got go... if nort miss out all e fun =) so happy seh... shiok shiok until i reach home.... mum and dad say they wanna confiscate my hp... sho damn bad ...... then i got kicked out from my room.... idiot! fucker! fook larx! they suck manx.... y i m sho ill-fated de?? no one cares 4 me in this world... i might as well jump down from the building ..... death will solve everything....... i shall die of death... die is the solution... my life sux! wanna let this from the last blog... but i got no courage to jump! i haven done wad i wanted to do... i wanted to say "sorry" to amanda... say "i love u" to *****... say to sushan "u r my friend for life"...  i want to say " great thanks" to zong xing lynn melissa sis jen juliana shirley huan qing amanda wee and all those hu cares 4 me....  i dun want to live.. i rather die.... i want everyone to regret.... i want them to remember that they cause my death... i want them to noe that they gave pressure to the pathetic gal that she died... i want everyone to know that i died becos of them... i wanna go look 4 JESUS.... he will free me.... he will give me love.... he will not pressure me....... i shall live again under the hands of him..... he ish waiting for me in heaven......i will go to him..... he will give me the life of no pressure and a life of happiness........tomorrow i shall not be seen...... =) i shall end this blog wif a smile...... =) 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       woohoo... choir concert.... shiok shiok! shuang dao! i will love it manx... then also can cheng ji skip tuition! wahahas... loving it! dio... i blog twice a day... hahax.. make up ma... feeling bloggy ley... drinking fruit juice.. nice nice....... thking abt whether to go church on sunday ornot.. so much problems.. then tomolo still got red cross... sianx manx   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       haix... wad happen? i really hate wilson now... wad an unsincere kor kor... he doesn't even remember my face now =( i thk he doesn't la! then me and huan qing keep quarreling 4 nothing... and and and CME need to compose song and sing in front of the whole class... sick manx... i decided to do solo... but very shy -.- lame manx... wat the toot! then today i bully euhao... hehex... walaox. today cheng cheng "tao xue" 4 4 periods la... =P just to skip DNT! juan manx! nxt tym i shall do it too =p... wahahas.... hmpft... bleah... wilson suck la. then today i go sushan house ... lolxx. we play wif the new pens ... =) nice nice. tomorrow can skip abit of tuition cos got concert. if 5566 de then good lor. but it ish the ACS de... booboobooo.... =P wahahas..... i sho de bad... then i veh de miss bryan... sobx sobx... when will we meet again?? i dun feel like going church le... i wanna cool down down down... all e problems... okok.... this entry should be long le la... wanna go dun wanna go. yiyibushe. =( ok...... shld leave =p ... muackz! muackx! muackz! still hating wilson chang from 4c amkss!  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i hate hanling... gimme the kindda look! she sux man! bitch la! so fake then the felicia still like her... haix... jian nu ren lorx... lanjiaobin! chee bye face! fooking manx... shitty fucker man! she ish a bad gal... i mean worse than a bad gal.... bitch more like it lor.... i dunno wat the hell she ish upp to.... now i also a bit of hate the huan qing... she like keep saying me lor......haizx...... haven peace out wif her...... okok...... tomolo will be a better day 4 me... wanna do dnt le... buaiz!~ muackx!~  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i come home late again! then now mum say wanna cut my allowance again! haix wat to do? y cant my parents be understanding towards me? but i think all this is worth it! cos i took alot of neoprints! haix... should be opstimistic! now go bathe and pack bag le! pastor say tomolo will be a better day... yeah yeah... all those naggings will be out from my ears... GOD LOVES ME! at least i hope he does  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dio! lolxx... through that feng jia hao i noe a new guy... nice looking la... he ish now my brother le... hehex... cool eh... good catch! anyone wants to noe him?? come look for me k! wa ha ha ha... promoting my brother... lolxx... so bad...haix... i wonder if mum and dad would let me go to church this sunday! i wanna go badly! sobx sobx seh! then i hate that alan manx... sickening seh... anyhow touch pple de... =S scary.... ok dun tok abt that sicko guy le... make my hair stand... lolxx... i so bad! but it is true... i must thank mrs anad... she change samuel with tan yong xiang...good good... not say i like yong xiang but at least he not as IRRATATING as samuel... and he ish good to bully... dio! i realised i so long nvr put entry... then today one so short... tomolo got rc training... scared... first time ley... dio! then i cnnt attend cell group! kns! fook manx... wo hao sheng qi! suan le... ren sheng ming duan duan...ew... when i becum so poetic? haiyo! dun wan write le.. go watch tv... buaiz! muackx! 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yesterdae actually can reach home early de lor... just that i veh extra la... i go and watch the fireworks with han xiang they all and lynn and dunno hu la! then after that hor..it is already 9++ then have to go home la...then i dun want ma.. so we go walk around lor.. then bryan dad go call han xiang say he missing! dio! we so worried ... cos he left us at 5 ma... so late still haven reach home so we all veh worried .. then we frantic! we go look around.. then see that shao jing and jia hao and gang! alan ask them go help find bryan ...they dun wanna help so alan ask them fuck off... then lynn wan find powen.. they drag drag so i also dio lor! i have to hide in my aunt house.. then 1130 then reach seh.. so damn late! i tot they will not scold lar.. but they sae sae sae until everything change lor! they banned me from going church! arg! i must overcome the devil!!! i will be able to go church de! i believe! then today .. aunt ask me go temple then the monk ask me drink this drink that! puiz! i am gonna be a christian and no one gonna stop me! mu hahahaha!  i believe in God and believe in myself!  weiting changed so much! she sae wat bible study and go church no use de... tok cock1 ask her go eat shit! =pP  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       lolxx... i dunn wann go church leyy... then i dunno la... so confused now... i m scared of church le! haiyo! suay dao! today so damn disgrace in ah leow class! fook manx! i dunno y.. now things like not so easy-going 4 me... i go around scolding pple then make pple angry! damn it! y izzit alwaes lidat?! now.. back to scolding weiting... still cnnt 4 give her! y must she be so jianx... haix.. dun sae le.. scold some more i throw blood ar... !!! ar!  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       haix... fook weiting la... bitchy kwan... how can she do that to me?! jianx manx...! wo hen ta! she noes i having cold war with amanda wee yet she purposely get close to amanda wee... ba po! then amanda wee also dun wanna hear my explanation! yesterdae so duilian... they like so close then i kept crying... haix... fuck larx... jian nu ren[weiting]... if amanda ... u came across this blog... u will noe how much i treasure our frendship... i tried giving up.. but i cnnt do it... y dun u 4give me... u r e only one that brighten up my day during the holidaes... remember the chicken wings, shrooms burger meal? library? marshmallows? curry puffs? macdonalds? abt the plan to sakae sushi and escape? have u 4gotten all abt it? pls dun! i will be waiting for a chance... i believe God will make u 4give me... dada... woaini!   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hahax.. must do so many homework... hate it manx... fook la.. haiyo! thking weather should go church or not ley... haiz... such a short entry... ok.. bye bye.. :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       wah seh... this ish my dunno wat account le... nvm... suan le ba... okok... tok about today... i went to see mrs anand with weiting about han xiang thingy... haix... so suay, today after maths... zong xing and his frend dennis outside my class... i close the door then cheng cheng go open the door and shout " suet theng is here! " fook lorx... cos i very guilty ma.... yesterday i go scold zong xing... duilian! haix... like so bad ley me... then hor... i also decide to stop going church le lor... dui bu qi melissa, sis jen and many more... when u have read this blog, i hope u understand! i also veh sorry to lynn =[ she help me so much yet i still lidat! should reflect on myself... hahax... got 2 merit points today for helping the teachers do the small handout tomorrow... then come back damn tired so i did this blog and went to rest... FOUND OUT MOM BOUGHT NEW FRUIT JUICE... yeah! woohoo! shiok! drink till siao!   
     

    
</post>


</Blog>