<Blog>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We welcome all the enthusiast of iifm who want to share their feelings and ventilate their thoughts to the people at large. The blogging, is the phenomenon which has captivated the web/literary enthusiasts(or shall I say addicts?), so those who feels that they have something to say and something to share this is a very very convenient method, and there is also no control absolutely. The fear of getting the rejection letter from the editor does not stop and discourage any one. So feel free and have your say!!!!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   Something about IIFM to prospective students     &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Many students while coming to iifm have many qualms and don't know whom to approach for the same.They don't have an idea what iifm is all about.IIFM is not a conventional B school.Its a institute which has been specially designed to cater to the environmental and developmental sector.That's why It has been heavily susidised and i believe its the only institute which provides stipend to its students.The campus is very serene and full of lush greenery.The no. of students are very less and the facilities unique e.g. library and computer centre.Our alumnis are working in top notch organisations like  World bank,PWC ,etc.At the moment multi clubs have been made like Cultural club,Movie club,literary club etc.And each club is working to its potential to make the campus vibrant.The hostel is very spacious and the food very salubrious.The faculties are very cooperative and hardworking.Regular field trips are being organised to facilitate students to juxtapose their theory with hands on practical experience.The students have to undergo a diurnal tight schedule which is very grilling and makes them disciplined,teamworker and competitive,but at the same time it's fun.At iifm you also get the feeling that you have actually contributed something back to society and mother earth.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; So for next year i wish to say good luck to all of students who want to make to iifm   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;    Ranjan Kumar        &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; PFM 2006 IIFM      
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
          A Message From God To You  &nbsp;       cc: The World.  &nbsp;   &nbsp;   I     convey this message to you whom I have stirred with the sound of my voice. These words are my signature. You may bring your doubt, your fear, your faith, or your courage; it matters not, for you will be touched by the rhythm of my voice. It moves through you like a beam of light that sweeps - if only for a moment - the darkness aside. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I dwell in a frequency of light in which finite beings cannot uncover me. If you search for me, you will fail. I am not found or discovered. I am only realized in oneness, unity, and wholeness. It is the very same oneness you feel when you are interconnected with all of life, for I am this and this alone. I am all of life. If you must search for me, then practice the feeling of wholeness and unity. In my deepest light I created you from my desire to understand my universe. You are my emissaries. You are free to journey the universe of universes as particles from my infinite womb with destinies that you alone will write. I do not prescribe your journey, or your journey's aim. I only accompany you. I do not pull you this way or that, nor do I punish you when you stray from my heart. This I do as an outcome of my belief in you.You are the heirs of my light, which gave you form. It is my voice that awakened you to individuality, but it will be your will that awakens you to our unity. It is your desire to know me as your self that brings you to my presence so perfectly hidden from your world. I am behind everything that you see, hear, touch, taste, smell, feel, and believe. I live for your discovery of me. It is my highest expression of my love for you, and while you search for my shadows in the stories of your world, I, the indelible, invisible light, grow increasingly visible. Imagine the furthest point in space - beneath a black portal, cast in some distant galaxy, and then multiply this distance by the highest numeric value you know.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Congratulations, you have measured an atom of my body.  &nbsp;Do you realize how I am unfathomable? I am not what you can know, or see, or understand. I am outside comprehension. My vastness makes me invisible and unavoidable. There is nowhere you can be without me. My absence does not exist. It is this very nature that makes me unique. I am First Cause and Last Effect connected in an undivided chain. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; There is no supplication that stirs me. No prayer that invites me further into your world unless it is attended with the feeling of unity and wholeness. There is no temple or sacred object that touches me. They do not, nor have they ever brought you closer to my outstretched hand. My presence in your world is unalterable for I am the sanctuary of both the cosmos and the one soul inside you. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I could awaken each of you in this very moment to our unity, but there is a larger design - a more comprehensive vision - that places you in the boundaries of time and the spatial dimensions of separateness. The design requires a progression into my wholeness that reacquaints you with our unity through the experience of separation. Your awakening, while slow and sometimes painful, is assured, and this you must trust above all else. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I am the ancestral father of all creation. I am a personality that lives inside each of you as a vibration that emanates from all parts of your existence. I reside in this dimension as your beacon. If you follow this vibration, if you place it at the core of your journey, you will contact my personality that lives beneath the particles of your existence. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; I am not to be feared or held in indifference. You are my blessed offspring with whom I am intricately connected in means that you cannot understand and therefore appreciate. You must suspend your belief and disbelief in what you cannot sense, in exchange for your knowledge that I am alive and real within you.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;      &nbsp; This is my central message to all my offspring. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Hear it well, for in it you may find the place in which I dwell.   
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        The longer I live, the more I realize the impact of attitude on life. Attitude to me is more important than facts. It is more important than the past, than education, than money, than circumstances, than failures, than success, than what other people think, say or do. It is more important than appearance, gift, or skill. It will make or break a company...a church...a home.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The remarkable thing is we have a choice every day regarding the attitude we will embrace for that day. We cannot change our past... The only thing we can do is play on the string we have, and that is our attitude. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I am convinced that life is 10% what happens to me and 90% how I react to it. And so it is with you... we are in charge of our attitude  s 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      One day, a girl, 16yrs old, heared from her mother that if she will do a regular prayer for 4 yrs, a divine "Devi" will come to her dreams &amp; give her 3 boons(Varadaan). So she decided to do it. She completed 4 yrs successfully, doing prayer regularly. Now it was a day for "Devi" to come. So she slept earlier with thoughts in her mind to ask. And, really a "Devi" comes in her dreams. Now this is the dialogue between them. Devi: O Girl, you prayed to me regularly within last 4 yrs, so I am very very happy with you. I will complete any of your 3 wishes. You can ask anything you like, but there is one condition. Girl: Condition!, what is that? Devi: You have a boy-friend? Girl: Yes. Devi: When you were doing a prayer, he was waiting for you, so he also sacrificed same as you. Moreover, he didnt know anything about boon and all, so he is also eligible for the boons. So whatever you will ask, he will get 10 times more than that of you. If you are agreed, then proceed for the 1st boon. Girl: (After thinking for some time ... ): Yes, I am ready. Girl: 1st, Make me 10 times richer than the richest person in the world. Devi: But your boy-friend will be 10 times richer than you. Girl: It's OK. Devi: Be as you wish! Girl: 2nd, Make me 10 times more beautiful than the most beautiful girl in the world. Devi: But your boy-friend will be 10 times handsome than the most handsome boy in the world. Girl: It's OK. Devi: Be as you wish. Devi: Now the last boon remains. Girl: O Devi, please give me a MILD HEART-ATTACK. Devi: What? Are you sure! Girl: Yes. Very sure! Devi: Be as you wish. Think friends, what happened to her boy-friend, he got a severe heart-attack &amp; died at once, while the girl remained alive. Thus, the girl became the world's most beautiful girl and the richest one, too.   Moral of the story: So intelligent the girls are! Girls are really more intelligent than we believe about them to be. So be careful boys!      Now, girls please stop reading.           &nbsp;  &nbsp;... boys continue till the end of the article&nbsp;.....  ****** Dear boys, dont worry, actually what done is something different than what you all think! Actually, the girl's boy-friend got a heart-attack, 10 TIMES MILDER than that of the girl. So the boy-friend lived longer than the girl, being world's richest and the most handsome boy. Moral of the story: Dear boys, the girls are not really that much intelligent than what we believe them to be. So dont worry if you think that you have girl-friend, intelligent than you.  &nbsp;   sourced from internet ( from blog of an IIM A, grad)     
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hi Friends,  All those ppl who are interested in posting at this site ( you can post any event, any thing you feel like sharing to others),can post to this site. There is no restriction on what one can post, but one must have the some considerations in mind as all the post will be open for general viewing.  I am trying to creat a chronoligcal list of blogs(about events and life at IIFM) so that our juniors,or any one can see that.  For more info and getting the user id mail me at    urlLink san1378@yahoo.com     
     
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
            After a week of competitive badminton on campus the Tournament Finals wereheld today.Thank you to all participants and volunteer officials (referees and linesmen)Congratulations to the winners and more so to the semifinalists andfinalists without whom we would have no winners:-)Mr.Rathore was kind enough to take time off to watch the Finals. He wasalso very helpful in arranging for the shutllecocks at the last moment.In addition to the tournament finals, we also had 4 exhibition matcheswith Mr. Biswas and Lokesh(PFM05) who got together and showed everyone howto combine presision placement(Mr Biswas) with powerful shots(Lokesh).Unfortunately, two enthusiasts among the faculty, Mr. A.K. Bhattacharyaand Mr. Amitabh Pandey could not join us today.A big surprise was the appearance of the Director Sir, &nbsp;who came to watch and also played an informal doubles match. It was refreshing to see thatthough he was not a good player he had no issues about playing and wasactually enjoying himself with the students without trying to maintainsome kind of professional distance.Unfortunately, the turnout from the PFM06 batch was not so good. The MRMbatch came out in almost full strength although they had only onebatchmate (Nandini) playing today. Hopefully, the batch will be moresupportive in other co-curricular events.However, Lokesh(last year's Sports Sec) said that he had problems lastarranging matches because of participants not coming for matches on timeetc. We thank all participants for being punctual and cooperative inspiteof the heavy work schedule (and slight changes in our planned matchschedule due to extra classes etc.) and also accepting walkovers withoutargument in case of absence.There was some negative talk earlier about the system used in the draw forthe Mens Singles but since we had no way to seed players we were forced touse a lucky draw system WITH unoffical seeding (grouping the chitsaccording to perceived skill) to try to keep the better players in thetournament till at least the semi final stage. In most tournaments asystem is used to keep the better (top seeded) players from playingagainst each other in the early stages. To explain more here is notnecessary. If anyone needs clarification on the system used in the lastweek please feel free to contact either me or Ashirbad.Thank you and congratulations again to all participants and volunteers.The results of the last two days are as follows:    SEMI-FINAL RESULTS     MENS SINGLES     Param Chattopadhyay def. Avijit Kishore15-4,15-11    Ashirbad Das def Ushnish Chattopadhyay15-11, 15-0     MENS DOUBLES     Priyank Pradeep+Akshai Abraham def. Ashirbad Das+Dipendar Sharma7-15, 15-9, 15-14    Rohit Toppo+Avijit Kishore def.    Alok Kashyap and Pushkar Parashar15-5, 15-13     FINAL RESULTS OF MRM and PFM06 BADMINTON       LADIES SINGLES      Nandini Deshpande def. Michelle Thomas15-9,15,1     MENS SINGLES     Param Chatopadhyay def. Ashirbad Das15-12, 15,5     MENS DOUBLES     Priyank Pradeep Akshai Abraham def. Rohit Toppo+Avijit Kishore15-8,15-7   __Thanking you,  Sports Committee    
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Thank you seniors for the amazing party arranged for the new pfm2006 batch. The efforts to bridge the gap between the seniors and the juniz are worth admiring. Hope to have more get-togethers in the year to come and many other occasions wherein we come in contact with the veteran lot.thanx a ton and lets get IIFM rockin!!!. &nbsp;   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Life isn't about keeping score,its not about how many people u call and its not about who u ve dated ,are dating or havent dated at all.    It isnt about who you've kissed, which sport u play, which guy or girl likes u.   It is not about your shoes or your hair or the colour of your skin,or where u live or go to school. In fact its not about grades, money, clothes or colleges that accept you or not.   Life isnt about if you have lots of friends or if you r alone and its not how accepted or unaccepted you are.     &nbsp;  Life just isn't about that     &nbsp;  Life is about who you love and who you hurt.   Its about how you feel bout yourself.    Its about trust ,happiness,compassion.   Its about sticking up for your friends and replacing inner hate with love .   Life is about avoiding jealousy, overcoming ignorance and building confidence.   Its about what you say and what you mean.   Its about seeing people for who they are and not what they have.   Most of all its about choosing to use your life to touch someone else's in a way that could have never been achieved otherwise.     &nbsp;  THAT'S WHAT LIFE'S ALL ABOUT!&nbsp;  
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I want you to make it a leisure read and not a mandatory one . Though i am focussing on some critical issues my intention is not to hurt anyone's sentiments or criticize anybody,but to improve on our faults and bridge the lacunas which we have built amongst us. Yesterday i was going through the number of posts which our batch is holding and i was shocked to see it was as high as half a century and exceeded even our class strength!! The shock was not because of number of posts but the sense of being "one amongst the iifm fraternity" was missing , and one reason what i see was this huge number of portfolios and personal quarrels . I see following things missing , which if u give a patient read you would realize that each and every bit of it is true.   Ownership  : The sense of ownership for responsibilities , may it be related to working within a club or on any other front . Going forward and asking for responsibilities is something that i have seldom seen. With the clubs saying that i will not take the responsibility of this event since i am taking the responsibility of other !! . Well i am really sorry to say that but in REC calicut from where i did my B.Tech , students used to fight to get the ownership of the event. And here it is exactly reverse. And still we want 30kper month jobs. Come on boss if you want something you have to show your worth. I see tremendous potential in terms of extra-curricular activites but personal differences is inhibiting us to show that.   Sense of unity  : Please see MRM batch. We can learn 5000 things about unity . Look at our own self and we will see every person is criticizing other on any and every mistakes committed. Let them do mistakes . IT s human to err. And always remember "United we stand" . Give chance for other to correct themselves.   Commitment to cause  : Our "raison-de-tre" is our uniqueness and infrastructure . Always remember we have come over here with a cause and ambitions. So make the best out of it. Utilize the available time in something important and constructive, may it be curricular or extra-curricular.   Ability to appreciate feedback  : Another important reason what i see not happening in right direction is to take feed back in +eve sense . When somebody is giving feedback "Keep your mouth shut and listen " no matter you discard it later on . You need to have a deep sense of gratitude to the person giving feedback , coz it is for your own good. What i see usually happening is that a feedback converting into fight and persons into enemies ! There cannot be anything worse than this.   I know that i have given a lot of suggestions, but i am no exception to all of these . I am also trying to improve on these .  I am also looking forward to become one amongst  44 strong members standing as one.   44 minds with one goal  -  "to be the best" .   44 brains with one "heart" .   What i believe is that day is not too far......  Cheers to iifm... Mandar 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       One fine day, a bus driver went to the bus garage, started his bus, and drove off along the route. No problems for the first few stops-a few people got on, a few got off, and things went generally well.    At the next stop, however, a big hulk of a guy got on. Six feet eight, built like a wrestler, arms hanging down to the ground.    He glared at the driverand said, "Big John doesn't pay!" and sat down at the back.Did I mention that the driver was five feet three, thin, and basically meek?Well, he was. Naturally, he didn't argue with Big John, but he wasn't happy about it.The next day the same thing happened-Big John got on again, made a show ofrefusing to pay, and sat down. And the next day, and the one after that, andso forth. This grated   on the bus driver, who started losing sleep over the way Big John was taking advantage of him.    Finally he could stand it no longer. He signed up for body building courses,karate, judo, and all that good stuff. By the end of the summer, he had become quite strong; what's more, he felt really good about himself.   So on the next Monday, when Big John once again got on the bus and said,"Big John doesn't pay!," the driver stood up, glared back at the passenger,and screamed, "And why not?"    With a surprised look on his face, Big John replied, "Big John has a bus pass."          Dear Friends , can anybody tell me the moral of this story?    
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       . 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Hi Friends       I found this speech on net.Just think if we can apply these thoughts regarding change , somewhere at IIFM.(2006 batch is different,& threr r already some new things happening here ;-)....)            SPEECH OF AZIM PREMJI AT THE IIM – AHMEDABAD CONFERENCE     “While change and uncertainty have always been a part of life, what has been shocking over the last year has been both the quantum and suddenness of change. For many people who were cruising along on placid waters, the wind was knocked out of their sails. The entire logic of doing business was turned on its head. Not only business, but also every aspect of human life has been impacted by the change. What lies ahead is even more dynamic and uncertain. I would like to use this opportunity to share with you some of our own guiding principles of staying afloat in a changing world. This is based on our experience in Wipro. I hope you find them useful.”     LESSON 1 “Be alert for the first signs of change.”     Change descends on every One equally; it is just that some realize it faster. Some changes are sudden but many others are gradual. While sudden changes get attention because they are dramatic, it is the gradual changes that are ignored till it is too late. You must have all heard of story of the frog in boiling water. If the temperature of the water is suddenly increased, the frog realizes it and jumps out of the water. But if the temperature is very slowly increased, one degree at a time, the frog does not realize it till it boils to death. You must develop your own early warning system, which warns you of changes and calls your attention to it. In the case of change, being forewarned is being forearmed.     LESSON 2 “Anticipate change even when things are going right."     Most people wait for something to go wrong before they think of change. It is like going to the doctor for a check up only when you are seriously sick or thinking of maintaining your vehicle only when it breaks down. The biggest enemy of future success is past success. When you succeed, you feel that you must be doing something right for it to happen. But when the parameters for success change, doing the same things may or may not continue to lead to success. Guard against complacency all the time. Complacency makes you blind to the early signals from the environment that something is going wrong.     LESSON 3 “Always look at the opportunities that change represents.”     Managing change has a lot to go with our own attitude towards it. It is proverbial half-full or half empty glass approach. For every problem that change represents, there is an opportunity lurking in disguise somewhere. It is up to you to spot it before someone else does.     LESSON 4 “Do not allow routines to become chains."     For many of us the routine. We have got accustomed to obstruct change. Routines represent our own zones of comfort. There is a sense of predictability about them. They have structured our time and even our thought in a certain way. While routines are useful, do not let them enslave you. Deliberately break out of them from time to time.     LESSON 5 “Realize that fear of the unknown is natural.”     With change comes a feeling of insecurity. Many people believe that brave people are not afflicted by this malady. The truth is different. Every one feels the fear of unknown. Courage is not the absence of fear but the ability to manage fear without getting paralyzed. Feel the fear, but move on regardless.     LESSON 6 “Keep renewing yourself.”     This prepares you to anticipate change and be ready for it when it comes. Constantly ask yourself what new skills and competencies will be needed. Begin working on them before it becomes necessary and you will have a natural advantage. The greatest benefit of your education lies not only in what you have learnt, but in working how to learn. Formal education is the beginning of the journey of learning. Yet I do meet youngsters who feel that they have already learnt all there is to learn. You have to constantly learn about people and how to interact effectively with them. In the world of tomorrow, only those individuals and organizations will succeed who have mastered the art of rapid and on-going learning.    LESSON 7 “Surround yourself with people who are open to change."     If you are always in the company of cynics, you will soon find yourself becoming like them. A cynic knows all the reasons why something cannot be done. Instead, spend time with people who have a "can-do" approach. Choose your advisors and mentors correctly. Pessimism is contagious, but then so is enthusiasm. In fact, reasonable optimism can be an amazing force multiplier.      LESSON 8 “Play to win...!"      I have said this many times in the past. Playing to win is not the same as cutting corners. When you play to win, you stretch yourself to your maximum and use all your potential. It also helps you to concentrate your energy on what you can influence instead of getting bogged down with the worry of what you cannot change. Do your best and leave the rest.     LESSON 9 “Respect yourself. The world will reward you on your successes."     Success requires no explanation and failure permits none. But you need to respect yourself enough so that your self-confidence remains intact whether you succeed or fail. If you succeed 90 per cent of the time, you are doing fine. If you are succeeding all the time, you should ask yourself. if you are taking enough risks. If you do not take enough risks, you may also be losing out on many opportunities. Think through but take the plunge. If some things do go wrong, learn from them.   I came across this interesting story some time ago: Story   “One day a farmer's donkey fell down into a well. The animal cried piteously for hours as the farmer tried to figure out what to do. Finally he decided the animal was old and the well needed to be covered up anyway it just wasn't worth it to retrieve the donkey. He invited all his neighbors to come over and help him. They all grabbed a shovel and begin to shovel dirt into the well. At first, the donkey realized what was happening and cried horribly. Then, to everyone's amazement he quieted down. A few shovel loads later, the farmer finally looked down the well and was astonished at what he saw. With every shovel of dirt that fell on his back, the donkey was doing some thing amazing. He would shake it off and take a step up. As the farmer's neighbors continued to shovel dirt on top of the animal, he would shake it off and take a step up. Pretty soon, everyone was amazed as the donkey stepped up over the edge of the well and totted off! Life is going to shovel dirt on you, all kinds of dirt.   The trick is too not to get bogged down by it. We can get out of the deepest wells by not stopping. And by never giving up! Shake it off and take a step up!”      LESSON 10 “Never change: your core values."     (Think it in context of IIFM &amp; try to preserve its core values)    In spite of all the change around you, decide upon what you will never change: your core values. Take your time to decide what they are but once you do, do not compromise on them for any reason. Integrity is one such value.     LESSON 11 “We must remember that succeeding in a changing world is beyond just surviving.”     It is our responsibility to create and contribute something to the world that has given us so much. We must remember that many have contributed to our success, including our parents and others from our society. All of us have a responsibility to utilize our potential for making our nation a better place for others, who may not be as well endowed as us, or as fortunate in having the opportunities that we have got. Let us do our bit, because doing one good deed can have multiple benefits not only for us but also for many others.   Let me end my talk with a small story I came across some time back, which illustrates this very well. Story   “This is a story of a poor Scottish farmer whose name was Fleming. One day, while trying to make a living for his family, he heard a cry for help coming from a nearby dog. He dropped his tools and ran to the dog. There, mired to his waist in black muck, was a terrified boy, screaming and struggling to free himself. Farmer Fleming saved the boy from what could have been a slow and terrifying death. The next day, a fancy carriage pulled up to the Scotsman's sparse surroundings. An elegantly dressed nobleman stepped out and introduced himself as the father of the boy Farmer Fleming had saved. "I want to repay you” said the nobleman. “Yes," the farmer replied proudly. "I'll make you a deal. Let me take your son and give him a good education. If he's anything like his father, he'll grow to a man you can be proud of you." And that he did. In time, Farmer Fleming's son graduated from St.Mary's Hospital Medical School in London, and went on to become known through-out the world as the noted Sir Alexander Fleming, the discoverer of Penicillin. Years afterward, the Nobleman's son was stricken with pneumonia. What saved him? Penicillin. This is not the end. The nobleman's son also made a great contribution to society. For the nobleman was non other than Lord Randolph Churchill. And his son's name was Winston Churchill. Let us use all our talent, competence and energy for creating peace and happiness for the nation.”     “Change is the only thing that will Never change. So better adapt to it."      “Change is Universal…      Change is Permanent….       Be ever willing to Change…..       For, change alone leads you to success and happiness!!!”       “If one desires a change, one must be that change before that change can take place”    
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      in a mba institute(not iifm) 4 students just before the exam night partied the whole night and sloshed out. as a result they were not able to reach the exam venue at time and got there after the exams. they cooked up a storythat yesterday night they visited a far off place and while returning  they had a flat tyre and they didnt had a spare tyre . they soiled their cloth greased their hand  and went to the examiner with this story. the examiner sympathised with them and agreed to take their exam the next day.when the 4 reached the place next day the examiner said that as it is a speacial case so they have to give the exams in seprate room. when they got the paper the first question was nor mal of 5 marks. the second question was of 95 marks and the question was" which tyre".  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        The road that led us to our destiny when we came here .....recognise it and preserve it!!!!     . 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        hello all,     today was a great day for humanity in general and us in particular as the gods unleashed showers with all fury on our beautiful campus to save us from the "sticky" heat ....in celebration i decided to join our blog... also the iifm 2006 batch got two periods free ....a celebration at post mid term....even though theyll be compensated...but such are the momentary pleasures that guide our lives...     "cheers to iifm"    
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hello all of you,                         I am a student of PFM batch 2006 at IIFM.I am from Gomoh,Dhanbad,Jharkhand.I have completed my graduation from indore.  I want to  share my experience of my first day at iifm.As i was in a management college already,getting into iifm was a conscious decision for me.When i had come for gd/pi to iifm,i was enchanted by the environment out here.I had subconsciously made my mind that i will join iifm.First day was full of excitement and thrill of not only seeing the campus,buildings but also here and there natural creatures like snakes,lizards etc.,infact it was the first time experience for many of us to actually see these so near.The faculty out here is very cooperative,and understanding.And iifm actually provides ample scope in its sector not only in india but also in whole world.Actually i have already started thinking that how will i live after getting out of iifm,leaving the pollution free environment,salubrious food and cooperative faculties.With our arrival also the Director Sir has come to iifm,and I am looking forward to the day when IIFM reaches its culminating heights.thanks all                                                                                                      Ranjan kumar 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
         Men:  
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
                                                                                         IN                                                            
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My this blog is dedicated to those bloggers who have mastered the art of   ctr+c   and   ctr+v .  Let me explain something about blogging. The phenomenon, which is known as blogging today, started in 1994 and it was more of a personal kind of writing people used to do on the web. But, right now it has become a major tool of expression and community building for the people world over. There are numerous website dedicated for blogging. Here, I would like to indicate that its nothing wrong with ctr+c (copy) and ctr+v (paste), if you want to put some information which is valuble to all, but have it in mind that the quality of blog indicates quality of a person's intellect,imagination, creativity and presentation skill,  so if you are producing through technology driven by ctr+v and powered by ctr+v, it shows your intellect level, and it does not show to us (c'mon, we know how talented we are!) but to everyone who is reading the blog, and they are not getting impression of me or you, but of an IIFM grad. I know, most of you would be thinking, I am giving a didactic lecture, but I am not. Actually what I am doing, I am trying to introduce you to "Blogging" in proper way, which I failed to do earlier. So I am sorry for that. I have given link to some b-school bloggers on the side bar, that will help you understand what blogging is all about. By the way, I would like to thank Mandar, Swapan, Akshai, Ranjan, Nitin, Akhand  and all other for their regular contributions.  If anyone wants to have more information about the blogging, or anykind of help, please send an email to  urlLink san1378@yahoo.com .      
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "If a man stood with one foot in an oven and the other foot in a freezer, statisticians would say that, on the average, he was comfortable." 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Friends this is an attempt to feel us relaxed from thought of such hectic week. u know we have to submitt two assignments(fre and stats) with 15 aug prepn.,and we have to play and chat and............................................................................   A man goes into a pet shop to buy a parrot. The shop owner points to three identical looking parrots on a perch and says, "the parrot on the left costs 500 dollars". "Why does the parrot cost so much," asks the man.The shop owner says, "well, the parrot knows how to use a computer". The man then asks about the next parrot to be told that this one costs 1,000 dollars because it can do everything the other parrot can do plus it knows how to use the UNIX operating system. Naturally, the increasingly startled man asks about the third parrot to be told that it costs 2,000 dollars. Needless to say this begs the question, "What can it do?" To which the shop owner replies, "to be honest I have never seen it do a thing, but the other two call him boss!"  ............................................................................   The manager of a large corporation got a heart attack, and the doctor told him to go for several weeks to a farm to relax. The guy went to a farm, and after a couple of days he was very bored, so he asked the farmer to give him some job to do. The farmer told him to clean the shit of the cows. The farmer thought that to somebody coming from the city, working the whole life sitting in an office, it will take over a week to finish the job, but for his surprise the manager finished the job in less than one day. The next day the farmer gave to the manager a more difficult job: to cut the heads of 500 chickens. The farmer was sure that the manager will not be able to do the job, but at the end of the day the job was done. The next morning, as most of the jobs in the farm were done, the farmer asked the manager to divide a bag of potatoes in two boxes: one box with small potatoes, and one box with big potatoes. At the end of the day the farmer saw that the manager was sitting in front of the potatoes bag, but the two boxes were empty. The farmer asked the manager: "How is that you made such difficult jobs during the first days, and now you cannot do this simple job?" The manager answered: "Listen, all my life I'm cutting heads and dealing with shit, but now you ask me to make decisions.". 
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In case you needed further proof that the human race is doomed through stupidity, here are some actual label instructions on consumer goods that can be found today being sold in stores nationwide: -------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 1. On Sears hairdryer:   "Do not use while sleeping."  (But..., that's the only time one have to work on one's hair)    2. On a bar of Dial soap:  "Directions: Use like regular soap."  (And that would be how. . . ?)    3. On some Swanson frozen dinners:  "Serving suggestions: Defrost."  (But it's "just" a suggestion)    4. On Tesco's Tiramisu dessert (printed on bottom of box):  "Do not turn upside down."  (Oops, too late!)    5. On Marks & Spencer Bread Pudding:  "Product will be hot after heating."  (Hmm . . . .)    6. On packaging for a Rowenta iron:  "Do not iron clothes on body."  (But wouldn't this save even more time?)    7. On Boot's Children's Cough Medicine:  "Do not drive a car or operate machinery after taking this medication."  (We could do a lot to reduce the rate of construction accidents if we could just get those 5-year-olds with head colds off those forklifts.)    8. On Nytol Sleep Aid:  "Warning: May cause drowsiness."  (One would hope)    9. On most brands of Christmas lights:  "For indoor or outdoor use only."  (As opposed to underwater?)    10. On a Japanese food processor:  "Not to be used for the other use."  (I gotta admit, I'm curious.)    11. On Sainsbury's peanuts:  "Warning: Contains nuts."  (NEWS FLASH)    12. On a child's Superman costume:  "Wearing of this garment does not enable you to fly."  (I don't blame the company, I blame parents for this one.)    13. On a Swedish chain saw:  "Do not attempt to stop chain with your hands."  (Was there a chance of this happening somewhere? . . .Good grief!)   14. On a bottle of Palmolive Dishwashing liquid:  "Do not use on food."  (Hey, Mom, we're out of syrup! It's OK, honey, just grab the Palmolive!) 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Put eight monkeys in a room. In the middle of the room is a ladder, leading to a bunch of bananas hanging from a hook on the ceiling.Each time a monkey tries to climb the ladder, all the monkeys are sprayed with ice water, which makes them miserable. Soon enough,whenever a monkey attempts to climb the ladder, all of the other monkeys,not wanting to be sprayed, set upon him and beat him up. Soon, none of the eight monkeys ever attempts to climb the ladder. 
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        When things in your life seem almost too much to handle,when 24 hours in a day are not enough, remember the mayonnaise jar......and the coffee .                                A professor stood before his philosophy class and had some items infront of him.  When the class began, wordlessly he picked up a very large and empty mayonnaise jar and proceeded to fill it with golfballs.He then asked the students if the jar was full.They agreed that it was.               So the professor then picked up a box of pebbles and poured them into the jar.  He shook the jar lightly.  The pebbles rolled into the open areas between the golf balls.  He then asked the students again if the jar was full.  They agreed it was.    The professor next picked up a box of sand and poured it into the jar.Of course, the sand filled up everything else.  He asked once more if the jar was full.  The students responded with a unanimous "Yes."    The professor then produced two cups of coffee from under the table and poured the entire contents into the jar, effectively filling the empty space between the sand.  The students laughed.   "Now," said the professor, as the laughter subsided, "I want you to recognize that this jar represents your life.The golf ball are the   important things--your family, your children,your health, your friends, your favorite passions--things that ifeverything else was lost and only they remained, your life would still be full .    The pebbles are the other things that matter like   your job, your house,your car . The sand is everything else--the small stuff."   "If you put the sand into the jar first," he continued, "there is no room for the pebbles or the golf balls.  The same goes for life.     If you spend all your time and energy on the small stuff, you will neverhave room for the things that are important to you .      Pay attention to the things that are critical to your happiness.    Play with your children. Take time to get medical checkups. Take your spouse out to dinner. Play another 18 holes.  There will always be time to clean the house and fix the disposal."Take care of the golf balls first, the things that really matter.   Set your priorities .  The rest is just sand."                  One of the students raised her hand and inquired what the coffee represented.The professor smiled.  "I'm glad you asked.  It just goes to show you that   no matter how full your life may seem, there's always room for a couple of cups of coffee with a friend."                       So...... , anybody ready to pay for my cup of coffee ;-).    
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Cracking an international market is a goal of most growing corporations. It shouldn't be that hard, yet even the big multi-nationals run into trouble because of language and cultural differences. For example... The name Coca-Cola in China was first rendered as Ke-kou-ke-la. Unfortunately, the Coke company did not discover until after thousands of signs had been printed that the phrase means "bite the wax tadpole" or "female horse stuffed with wax" depending on the dialect. Coke then researched 40,000 Chinese characters and found a close phonetic equivalent, "ko-kou-ko-le," which can be loosely translated as "happiness in the mouth." In Taiwan, the translation of the Pepsi slogan "Come alive with the Pepsi Generation" came out as "Pepsi will bring your ancestors back from the dead." Also in Chinese, the Kentucky Fried Chicken slogan "finger-lickin' good" came out as "eat your fingers off." When General Motors introduced the Chevy Nova in South America, it was apparently unaware that "no va" means "it won't go." After the company figured out why it wasn't selling any cars, it renamed the car in its Spanish markets to the Caribe. Ford had a similar problem in Brazil when the Pinto flopped. The company found out that Pinto was Brazilian slang for "tiny male genitals". Ford pried all the nameplates off and substituted Corcel, which means horse. When Parker Pen marketed a ballpoint pen in Mexico, its ads were supposed to say "It won't leak in your pocket and embarrass you." However, the company's mistakenly thought the spanish word "embarazar" meant embarrass. Instead the ads said that "It wont leak in your pocket and make you pregnant." An American t-shirt maker in Miami printed shirts for the Spanish market which promoted the Pope's visit. Instead of the desired "I Saw the Pope" in Spanish, the shirts proclaimed "I Saw the Potato." Chicken-man Frank Perdue's slogan, "It takes a tough man to make a tender chicken," got terribly mangled in another Spanish translation. A photo of Perdue with one of his birds appeared on billboards all over Mexico with a caption that explained "It takes a hard man to make a chicken aroused." Hunt-Wesson introduced its Big John products in French Canada as Gros Jos before finding out that the phrase, in slang, means "big breasts." In this case, however, the name problem did not have a noticeable effect on sales. In Italy, a campaign for Schweppes Tonic Water translated the name into Schweppes Toilet Water. Japan's second-largest tourist agency was mystified when it entered English-speaking markets and began receiving requests for unusual sex tours. Upon finding out why, the owners of Kinki Nippon Tourist Company changed its name. and finally... In an effort to boost orange juice sales in predominantly continental breakfast eating England, a campaign was devised to extoll the drink's eye-opening, pick-me-up qualities. Hence, the slogan, "Orange juice. It gets your pecker up." 
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        The Future of Customer Service   Operator : "Thank you for calling Pizza Hut . May I have your..." Customer: "Hello, can I order.." 
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
          A few weeks ago NIMH (National Institute of Mentally Handicapped ,Hyderabad,   INDIA)   had conducted a sports meet for all the Physically &amp; mentally handicapped   children at National Stadium Hyderabad.    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      First of all sorry to all those who watched the hockey match few hours before. The match was very well placed and we were realy doing well(remember we posted two goals within two minutes).Then  notion of being cheated always teases me?  yes! Its not my alone views evrybody of us will share that the refree was (not a bit) but more   biased.The australian player was just shown a green card  while he tried hockey stick wrongly while dhanraj was sent out even when he drew back his stick well in time. There were many occasions when he oversaw there faults and penalised us.  I donot know why this persists and again is not limited to hockey. There is same story in cricket,but in both game we play so well that no cheating and foul would let us down and I think this is the only spirit which can help us.   but frens can we do something ???    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A few days ago there was a very interesting question in Ecosystem class by Ushnish . He asked ma’m that how can Rajasthan have wetlands when there is desert and it does not get proper rainfall.  Let me clear some misconceptions people have about Rajasthan. Whenever one thinks of Rajasthan the general picture is of a big Moustache Man with Turban on his head, A  L athi   in his hand ,sitting on camel in a vast desert. I don’t know why various Governments of Rajasthan have promoted this beautiful land as such.  Also people think that Rajasthan means  REGISTAN  and there will be no water, people must be crazy about water,there must be no rains, which not absolutely true.  Though it is true that Rajasthan does contain desert that does not mean whole Rajasthan is a desert and there is no water at all there. The fact is that even I have not seen desert till now in my life though I have traveled many pars of Rajasthan.  Only western part of Rajasthan is covered under desert(which itself is very beautiful and a good tourist destination). And it is also true that it have water scarcity. This part includes Jaisalamer, Jodhpur, Barmer Jalor , Bikaner etc.Other than these u will not find much water scarsity in Rajasthan. But in these parts also people have adopted such good water harvesting systems from ancient times that if these methods be adopted in whole country there will be no water problem throughout India. The remaining parts of Rajasthan do not have much problem (except summer season when whole country sings to same tune) and they get adequate annual rainfall     Have a look at some of the facts    Farmers of Sri Ganganagar are at par with Panjab farmers in terms of productivity and richness. The whole area is irrigated by   Indira Gandhi Canal.    Kota is a city where people does not have water tanks in there homes. They get 24 hour direct water supply, thanks to   Chambal River.    Chambal is so big a river that three big dams are constructed on it (  Rana Pratap Sagar, Gandhi Sagar and Kota Barrage  ) Not far from each other to hold its water.  The electricity supply condition in Rajasthan in   much better   than the states of M.P. & Bihar(even in remotest villages).    Mount Abu   is one of the favorite hill station and has got very good climate, landscapic beauty and Jain Tamples.  Udaipur is called   City Of Lakes   and attracts tourists from all over the world.  Rajasthan has got various national parks, wild life sanctuaries, bird sanctuaries ,& wetlands. Some of them are   Ghana Bird Sanctuary, Ranthambhore National park, Kewladeo, Sariska Tiger Reserve,Kumbhalgarh Sanctuary,Darrah Sanctuary,Desert National Sanctuary,Jaisamand Sanctuary &amp; Lake,Mount Abu Sanctuary,Sambhar Lake   and many more.  Even desert place of Jaislmaer is a world famous tourist hotspot. .  This is only the tip of the iceberg and there are many more hidden adventures Rajasthan promises.  So next time you speak about Rajasthan don’t think only of desert but think some thing beyond that.     R  a  j  a  s  t  h  a  n  …… S   i  m  p  l   y   C  o  l  o  r  f  u  l .     
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
         thanks bagla I know u r a quick guy actually all men for jhalawar are quick I m right na . ( I wsa thinking who will be the first guy/gal to post after hectic week)  I have to share a joke sent to me by one o f my friends. I 'll just paste here for all of u    The Perfect Couple  Once: upon a time, a perfect man and a perfectwoman met.   After a  perfect friendship, they had a perfect wedding. Their life togetherwas,  of course, perfect.    One snowy, stormy Christmas Eve, this perfectcouple was drivingtheir  perfect car along a winding road, when theynoticed someone at theside  of the road in distress. Being the perfect couple,they stopped to  help.   There stood Santa Claus with a huge bundle oftoys. Not wanting to  disappoint any children on the eve of Christmas,the perfect couple  loaded Santa and his toys into their vehicle. Soonthey weredriving  along delivering the toys.  Unfortunately, thedriving conditions  deteriorated and the perfect couple; and SantaClaus had anaccident.    Only one of them survived the accident.  Question: Who was the survivor?       Answer: The perfect woman survived. She's the onlyone who really  existed in the first place.  (Everyone knows thereis no Santa Clausand  there is no such thing as a perfect man. )   Women stop reading here, this is the end ofthe joke.  **** Men keep scrolling.      So, if there is no perfect man and no Santa Claus ,the woman musthave  been driving.  This explains why there was a car accident. Men Keep scrolling   >
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hi guys.........& gals,      Seems maths assignment and extra classes r taking there toll. bcoz there is no new blog here since 12 August....not even a copy pest operation ;-).      by the way last week was full of happenings with thanxgiving party , i- day celebrations and than quiz on 17th .It was a miracle that Prof. CVRS postponed his assignment due date & i had some relief.but there r assigments lined up for the next week EM , BCDH, QT etc. to mention a few.But as usual, everything will be completed by last date.      Seniors had the best of last week with winning everything they participated in &amp; i think we must have a dope test fron next time onwards.      Also i danced on stage for the first time in my life.And the poem 'NEEND' was praised by many.       Also 'Indra Dev' were at their best during full week with not even a single day sparing with rains &amp; it was really enjoyable to watch n hoot for Football match in rain on I-day.      rain also showed its magic in my home state Rajasthan where till 15 days ago Govt. was planning for Drought Relief and now they have to plan for Flood relief(It happens only in India).      by now the postponed date of QT assigment is again approaching and i think i should leave n prepare for that.       BC Kaayam Rahe.         
     
    
</post>


</Blog>