<Blog>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Pics from today!!! Crib's done..it was fun! :-)       At THIS point.... Someone (who shall not be named) screws up :-) Here's the pic of the screw up, and the next is the punishment.      And so we keep going!      Phew.. that took all my strength.       And Finalllyyyy............     I Guess NOW everyone wants to take their pics with the crib LOL :-)         Daadi Daadi...where are you????     Write back folks...and have fun!! Ria's room is on the start.
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      this is paul there, and im making a promise, i will try to loose some weight in time for Ria to get here, paul mama has to look good u know lol..and i will be da most handsome guy by christmas lol.........dats a promise. 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am waiting for my little cuuuute grandbaby..... 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know for sure that it must be a girl. ....... 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         This is MAAAMMMUUU 
      
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Arjun Mamu has a nice ring to it, or should it bee Mama Singh as i call my mummy :-p 
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You spelled the name wrong, and in the words of Jiju Singh "LOL", you chose the name now let me choose the spelling.......go to microsoft word, put in Ria, and click spell check, you shall see that you are wrong big guy.   
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This weekend, we (Me, Angad, Arjun, Sami, Dolly) will be setting up Ria's crib, and STARTING on her room.  Future planning includes painting and decorating her room. The color is still not decided upon... but the current favorite seems to be lite bright green. Any color suggestions will be appreciated and considered.  Over and Out.... 
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Throughout the ages, this relationship has stood the test of time. Rituals, ceremonies, cultures, technology changed, but that special bond that a child has with it's mother remains unaltered.  What makes this bond so strong? so special?.  It cant be because the mother loves the child more than the father does, as love for the child is unconditional from both sides. The more logical reason would be the impact that the mother has on the first 9months of the child's unborn life. The child is a PART of the mother, they are one and the same. The needing relationship of the child/mother begins as soon as it is conceived and never stops, even after the umbilical cord is cut. This 9months forms a permanent bond between the child and mother. Quite honestly, I am jealous. Women often complain about the inconveniences of pregnancy and child birth.... and it's quite understandable. But I wouldn't mind going through with it, if it meant that I would know my child better than anyone in the world.  It might be taken as a cliche when your mother says "I know you 9months more than you know yourself", but .. IT'S TRUE.  More Later.....
      
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      alrighty then.....as everyone knows im going to be the best mama ever.  I dont know but i think babyies like me its just a curse i have to live with everyday.  Okay some babies might look on top of my head when they first meet me but they love it what can i say.  Ria is going to be soooo lucky to have a family like us.  I always say a family need diversity and thats how im going to be.  I cant wait 'til Ria can interact with me so i can make her laugh.  Even if i dont say anything funny she will laugh and make me feel good.  But i always say funny.  Well i will sign again.  PUNJABI FO' LIFE!!!!! 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I hope she doesnt get my ego, It can be good sometimes, But really bad sometimes. I have a huge ego.   Physical:  Hansome(lol :D), Honey-Golden eyes, Tall(5'10), Broad Shoulders(I think), Average length forehead, regular calves, muscular, dunno anything else.   Personality(Good):  Caring, Loving, I cant think of anymore.   Personality(Bad):  Huge Ego, Moody, Bad Tempered, some more I dunno. If I missed some please tell me.  Il add more here later,  -Peace, Ku 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hummm...where should I start from.  Well, food seems to be a very big issue during pregnancy.  What type of food is good for the baby, eating nutritional food, what will help the baby grow, blahblahblah !!!  From my personal experience during pregnancy, I dont have a choice on what types of food to eat.  Even before pregnancy I personally never liked vegetables or Indian food (because alot of veggies are involved) and now especially during this stage I dont feel like eating indian food as much.  Maybe my baby will end up eating alot of veggies or maybe she won't, who knows ! The point is, I don't like veggies, so dont make meeeeeeeeeeee eat it. ( I admit I am a little picky about food-just a tiny bit)  Since Dharmesh will eat anything, I dont mind if the baby takes after him for food preferences. (just don't go over board with food, otherwise she will regret later) :-)  Dharmesh should feel lucky because I did not get any type of cravings.  The baby should thank me later for not eating certain foods since it will be a problem later, such as WATERMELON AND BANANAS (these two are small examples).  I loooooove both of those fruits and couldn't wait till summer came so I can gulp down a whole watermelon, but me being so sweeeeeet, I gave them up for my little girl so she won't end up having a cold (old wives tale if during pregnancy eating too much watermelon or bananas or cantolope in the last 3 months, the baby comes out with a COLD) I guess my three months sacrifice will help the baby for her rest of her life.  (ain't I sweeeeeet).  Ok bahut ho gaya, ab mujhe bhook lag gayee khane ke baare mein sochteh sochteh !! :-)
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So what are some thoughts on eating habits of the mother-to-be while she carries the baby?  Would it be fair to the child that the mother eats food that the baby might not like when it grows up? More importantly, would it fair to the mother to change her eating habits to give the baby a choice.  What I am trying to say is...Let's say that you eat chicken while you're pregnant, now wouldnt that be forcing the baby to eat chicken?  What if the baby turns out to be vegetarian, can she REALLY make a claim that she is vegetarian, when the foundation of her life; her initial growing process was done on chicken and fish?  I am not pulling towards either side, but it's an interesting thought.  More to come........ 
      
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hmmmm...am not sure if I am signing the right blog...should it be Baby Ria or Baby Aryan...I know brother you are going to kill me for writing this but for some reason I am just not convinced. Hey whatever it is I can't tell you guys how excited I am even though I won't be the baby of the family anymore *sob* *sob* but I am happy to give away my spot to the little one..... Oh...! Bhabhi just the spot not the room yet (don't get too happy)....I hope its a very healthy and cute cute baby (Just like me :D). I am really excited October just can't get here soon enuff...I have asked more like begged the baby to kick for me many times but the baby just doesn't listen to me...Stubborn baby I wonder like whom...hmmm...*thinking*      Baby shower was really fun....I guess I will write more as October arrives and I guess I will be the first person to post after the baby arrives to clear up if its Baby Ria or Aryan...till then keep guessing.....      Oh something about my personality...      Physical: You guys don't wanna know...   Good qualities too many too little space...   Bad qualities...I just don't have any...:D    Daughter, Sister, Masi, Bhuwaaaa 2 be, wife never to be.....how ya like that brother?  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Forgot to update :/ Ria is now in full motion for the past couple of days.  According to Sami you can see the stomach move while Ria is moving around in there.  The movement is so much sometimes..that she cant even get a good nights sleep (poor Sami :( ).  She has also started getting a lot of heartburn, which they say  means that the baby is growing hair.  Our baby is growing, and in about 8 -9 weeks will be between us.  Cant Wait.  Dharmesh 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I enjoyed alllll the attention I was getting in my baby shower, especially the presentssssss.  Eventhough it was no use unwrapping them because first of all they weren't for me and I couldn't do anything with the gifts after opening them.  But over all I am so happy to see that our baby is so much loved even before coming into this world, can't imagine after she has arrives she will be spoiled completely.  I think I will be the bad guy in parenting because Dharmesh is going to do whatever she wants, she will have him dance on her fingers (not unless I can help it). :o)  The party was great but I did not like the baby shower ritual (i dont know how to spell "baby shower" in hindi - God-Bharai). Anyhow, I liked the idea of walking down the stairs on Saree which seemed like walking on Red Carpet, but I did not like the slapping seven times tradition (that kinda hurts and a little insulting).  Its like I am getting punished for getting pregnant..hehehe !!  I think I have to ask my Mother-in-Law about this but I am sure I wont like the explaination.    Oh well, besides that I caaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaan't wait till our baby is born.  Hopefully dharmesh will start setting up Ria's room this weekend, since I cant pick up anything myself (I am helpless).  I want my baby's room to be light purpleeeeee, Ok dharmesh !? Eventhough Ria will sleep in our room first couple of months then in Mom's room so no need to set up the baby's room but I want to do something for my baby before it arrives.  Will see !  Thats it for today will write more tomorrow.  
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ---------> What I would like My Ria to be   1) Personality - I don't want my baby to experience different family genes, unless Ria picks up only the beautiful genes from three different families. She should pick up definately MY SMILE :-) (no offence anyone).  The patience can go on her dad because girls should have LOTSSSSS of patience in order to deal with different types of people, especially after marriage.  Since I don't have much patience I can relate to it.  So hopefully my Ria will end up a cool, calm, and patient.  2)Physically - I don't want my baby to be very "Feminine".  I want a girl with attitude so people think twice before messing with her, but I dont want her to be a "Tom boyish" either.    Lunch time, Ria's hungry for some gulab jamun.... :-) more later ! 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The family is starting to gather around now :-)   I will change the description of the blog from "A loving couple" to "A loving Family" to reflect this change.  Discussions/Thoughts of the day:  1) The reason I choose the title as I, Ria (no it's not to copy the movie I, Robot), is to wonder what personality would Ria have? Would she go more on the Ahuja family....Topiwala family or the Bulsara family? As the generations keep growing, the arriving child gets a much bigger gene pool to swim in.  For eg., Ria will have the option to aquire from ALL the gene pools that I have been a part of + ALL the gene pools that Sami has been a part of.  However scary that may sound, it wont be that hard to figure out who she is imitating when she exhibits a certain behaviour. Keeping that in mind... I would like for each one of you to list the following:  	a) Physical Characteristics 	b) Personality (Good) 	c) Personality (Bad)  Maybe...just Maybe..we'll get an idea of what she CAN have.  We'll start with me, and It would be cool if you guys/gals can comment with yours.   **Dharmesh Topiwala (Dad-to-be)**  -Physical Characteristics-: Tall (5'10), Broad, Long Nose ( :---) ), Hairy, huge calves (naturally), long eye lashes, long and fast growing finger nails, uneven body (right side is higher and shorter then the left side), no upper lip, square face structure, vascular (lots of veins, even when I was big), huge hands, big feet.  -Personality (Good)-: Confident, Patient, Intelligent (I think), Loving, Caring.  -Personality (Bad)-: None .. hah J/k.  Moody, Bad temper, Jealous, Sometimes..TOO carefree.  I am sure there are more, as Sami and others will point out..and I will happily update :-) .   2) Ria will also do something that no doctor, or scientist can do. It will make blood relatives of two separate families.  For eg., Priyesh and Kunal will be blood related to Angad and Arjun through Ria. Such a little life..possesses so much power.  More later...  Dharmesh 
      
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I'm supposed to tell you about how I can't wait till Ria is born :) "I can't wait till Ria is born" :) ok bye!          ok I'm just kidding :D  Not about the part where I can't wait though.. it will be awesome!  I know one day I will be in the same position as Dharmesh-bhai and will be exponentially more excited!  Wow, I'm a geek.  Anyway, that will be really great, but until then I will make do with what I have ;)  We need to start planning the dance early.  I think this time we should do one that even the baby can enjoy.  After all, its HER party!  Well, bye for real now Bigger better post from Dharmesh bhai tomorrow :) -Me 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha! I get to be the first to post in the blog other then Dharmesh bhai. Well, The thought of Ria coming in to the family is ku. I cant wait to spoil her Muhahaha! Im gonna teach her to make Bhabi mad. Just say 2 words out of no where "huh?" and "what?" lol Thats getting old...I know Im not the one who is the mos psyched about her coming. I bet Sami Bhabi is the most. Anywho, I still dun get why the baby shower comes before the baby is born. lol. Well Itl be fun to have a party when its born, I knwo im doign a dance with Dharmesh bhai in it. Itl be great. Well thats all I can think of. -Peace, Ku    
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just a quick note:    Anyone who is a team member of the blog can write blog enteries.  Just make sure it has something to do with the baby :-)   Another update tomorrow.  Feel free to post a blog about Ria, and how you cant wait. 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So...I have returned. So much for all those nay sayers who thought I wouldn't keep up with it (Which would be nobody BTW). Couple of things I've been thinking lately, and thought I would share:  1) I don't know about any other parents-to-be, but Sami & I are already madly in love with the baby. Every little move, every little kick is special. So much care and love goes in, even BEFORE the baby is born. Now one would think that our parents went through the same things when we were in the womb. Now that we are all grown up, we sometimes get mad or say mean things to them, without realizing the amount of care and love that went into us as babies and teenagers. I guess it the circle of life...takes a parent to know a parent. I don't even know our baby personally , but I know if she got mad at me, it would hurt my feelings. Live &amp; Learn I guess....Live & Learn.  2) Gift Registries..... that concept apparently eludes the Indian community. The fact that someone would tell you exactly what they want to receive as gifts is apparently mind boggling. They still like to keep the element of surprise in giving gifts (not in a good way, I might add). Obviously, what do WE know about what WE want, they know us WAY better than that. I think they should put that power to good use, cause god knows the world can use some good mind readers right about now. It's not even about the money.... I mean we have gifts registered all the way from $9.99 to $199.99. A $9.99 bib set would do us a lot more good then ....let's say..A photo frame ??? Well ...A lot more to say on that subject.. but you get the drift.  Well...more later...  *edit*  Noticed something during lunch time. Walking with a pregnant woman changes the way people look at you. Everyone is nice to you all of a sudden. That's strange... but I'm taking Sami everywhere I go from now on :-)  *edit2*  3) Would having a kid  be more like playing god or guardian?  You give life, you shape life, and then you watch the results.  If you think about it....ever single one of us gets to play god in our lifetimes.  So I wonder, why do we worship something that we ourselves possess the power to do?  We can Give Life (Birth) We can Shape Life (Raise Kids) We can Take Life (Kill) We have the determination and skills to even perform miracles. (child birth, space travel, self healing)  So why dont we take the energy we put into praying and use it to better ourselves.  Make ourselves better parents, better educators, better protectors, better scientists.  I dont know why...maybe someone can enlighten me.  I am not saying that god doesnt exist...I dont want to touch that subject :-) 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, I decided to start a blog.  I was thinking of a way to jot down all the preparation and excitement that our family shares, waiting for the arrival of our baby.  Oh ... BTW...I should mention that my wife of almost 2 years (Sami) is 7 months pregnant with our DAUGHTER.   I cant wait for her to arrive.  I will spoil her rotten.  Had the baby shower this weekend, and it was a boat load of fun.  We hosted a party at India Palace II restaurant in Morrisville, and a lot of family members showed up.  Looking at all the family together, gets me to notice...how each generation seems to get further apart from each other, and the rest of the family.  It's really sad, because that's a great part of being Indian.... is the family ties.  I will try my best to make sure that the generation that FOLLOWS me, will be better kept in touch with their uncles, aunts and cousins.  Anyways...enough of the sappy stuff, and more about the party.  It was a blast... there were many individual performances.  One in particular surprised me.... My cousin Priyesh.  I have always thought of him as a more reserved kind of a person...caring...but reserved.  His dancing in the party will be one of the best memories of how much fun the party really was.  My sister Dolly also partook in a dance, which also surprised me..in a good way.  All in all , everyone did a excellent job in showing their happiness through their dancing.  Me & Sami would like to heartfully thank (In no particular order :) ) Dolly, Priyesh, Kunal, Tushar, Smruti,  Angad, Arjun, Paul, Mannu, Hannu, Deserie(sp?), Sukku, Pooja and Palak for their dances.  Hope you guys had as much fun as I did.  I will try to update this blog as I decide to share more information/ feelings about the coming baby, and events surrounding.  Dharmesh Topiwala Son, Brother, Husband, Father (to be) 
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So today we went by the doctor for the bi-weekly doctor's appointment.  She just asked us if we had any questions, and we got to listen to Ria's heartbeat.  It was around 130.  The doctor said, "oh, we must have caught her at nap time".  It was so cute :-)  Cant wait to SEE her take a nap.  Sooooon....sooooon  Pappa Pyare!! 
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I am starting my 8th month on Saturday and sooooooo happy that its finally ending.  We have been waiting for too long for this month since its the ending and can make some preparations for the babies arrival.  As you can see we have started on the babies room recently and eventhough the baby will sleep in our room for first couple of months.  Dharmesh and I go in that room everyday and feel our baby presence.  Its also sad in a way to see the crib empty. Just another month or so then we will have the most precious and adorable baby whom will love more than our selves.   Its too bad Dharmesh can not feel what I feel and I am not talking about getting sick or anything, I mean the babies movements.  In a way I should actually feel lucky that my first and second trimester went fine, I didnt have any health problems or particular sicknes.  The pregnancy is SO FAR going smoothly, I just hope labor goes smoothly too.  Will worry about that when the time comes!!  Right now I should enjoy the wonderful feeling I feel during pregnancy, for instance just sitting at work or at home, seeing my stomach goes pop from one side to another...or sometimes some air pops (like the baby farted) or a feeling weird stuff deep inside the stomach (that feeling I dont like, its very annoying because I cant make it stop)  It feels like she is scratching the womb to annoy me, and it WOrks everytime.   The recent experiment I experienced was baby getting startled.  I was cleaning up things going up and down stairs, I suddenly feel baby hardening from time to time from moving fast or from loud noices.  Well  as you know ME being a genious, I made some noices with the chair downstairs or got up quickly and every time the baby hardens, hehe...its kinda cute feeling.  I did that couple of times to see if she can hear that, and it turns out she can recognize loud noises (Dont worry I read loud noises will not harm the baby)   ANyways thats enough for today we shall update next time @@@  Mommy Dearest !!
      
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Heard there's a new little angel on the way who'll bring you a little bit of heaven on earth. wow it is a great feeling to be a masi.. to have someone new to love.. dear sam and dharmesh there is no joy greater than knowing you are bringing a beautiful new life....wishing you all the joys of parenthood.....  
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For those of you, who are looking at this website and would like to contribute; send me an email at dharmesh.topiwala+request@gmail.com (make sure to have the +request in there).  Here are the steps that needs to be followed to be able to post on here.  1) You will receive an email from "Blogger Invites" (hotmail users, make sure to check ur junk mail folders, since hotmail tends to put blogger emails in junk/spam folder)  2) You will have a link in that email.  Click on that link and accept the invitation.  3) Create a new account with blogger (button should be on the lower left corner)  4) Choose whatever username and password you desire. However, be aware, that the "Display Name" is what is going to show up when you post; so choose a nice simple name.  5) with the above created username and password, log in to your account (through www.blogger.com) and click on the "Special Delivery For Sami & Dharmesh" blog.  6) Be aware that there are people from BOTH sides of the family, and not everyone knows everyone. Your first post would best be kept to introduction.  7) DO NOT...I repeat DO NOT reply to the emails that you get whose reply to address is "riamadhu@googlegroups.com". This is setup so that everyone in the group can get an email when someone makes a new post. If you are not getting this email, or if you would like to STOP getting these emails; email me at the above address and let me know.  8) If you have allready registered and you DO NOT see your name under the contributors list on the right side...something is wrong :-) Update your profile with some information and then see if it shows up, if not.. contact me.  Any other questions, email me at the above address.  Take Care folks, and will update soon with more pictures. 
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so today was the first day of school. we didnt do anything but write down our information for the teachers, which really i was prefectly fine with it. i saw friends i havent seen in awhile and that was probably the best part of them all. well no...the best part was after school when i met a friend that ive never seen since 7th grade. but no details provided. im just waiting for Saturday to go to jiju's house and have another project to work on. well for right now thats all i have to say because i have to eat my subway sandwich.  toodaloo. 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so the summer has finally ended. sure im ready to go back to school and get out of the house. the only problem i have and will always have is waking up early and coming home after school. yesterday i was out most of the day at the mall getting some school clothes and then i had a gyro for lunch and it was great. i headed to jiju's house and we moved the mattress down stairs in the garage and then we made Ria's playpen. like last time there were some techniqal difficulties that followed. as smart as i am i just asked jiju to use the instructions BUT "NOOOOOOOOO, MEN DONT READ INSTRUCTIONS." oh yeah proved how manly you were. HAHAHA. so we ended up using them and then what was a 5 min. job ended up taking bout 30 min. eventually we got it done and then took pictures like we always do. it was a great day and i can do it everyday. 
      
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Another fun day... Another fun project. Fun Mama (Angad) & Mamu Singh (Arjun) came over again to help with the playpen. (Seems like they just cant get enough of me... or is it the baby that's making them come more now ..hmm cant figure it out)  Here are some more pics to feast your eyes on.  Enjoy!!    DO NOT FORGET TO VOTE FOR THE COLOR!!!            Take Care, 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hiya there folks! Painting on Ria's room should start anytime now, however, we cant seem to decide on a color. Help us out, and tell us what you think would be a cool, nice baby color. Help is much appreciated!!      Thanks,  PS: If you select the color+wallpaper option, then please leave a comment on what combination would be good. 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      haha that was one of the best days ive spent with  Aunty  ( daadi ),  Sami  ( mommy ),  Jiju  ( PAPA ),  Dolly didi  ( Foi ),  Arjun  ( mama ).  On  Saturday Aug. 7, 2004  we had a mission that needed to accomplished and that was making the CRIB!  Ofcourse somethings went wrong when trying to construct an object; im not going to say any names; but hey im just human, i make mistakes too!  Well after jiju got that out of his system we got right back to work.  We had no time to spare because the Mama's had to hurry back home.  HAHA.  So we waited for Dolly didi to arrive home so she can also help with the crib and then with the finishing touches we completed this unbelievable task.  Actually it was quite simple because there were only like 10 screws to put in.  Then the time finally came.....the crib was done and we got treated to Goodberrys.  Ive never seen a papa get so excited over ice cream. HAHA. Just kidding jiju.  Now the only thing missing in that crib was baby   RIA  !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  love, the fun  Mama  ( Angad ) 
      
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, does not matter if it is going to be a girl or a boy, but the baby is just going to look like me... So cuttttttteeeeeee........ well guys ne comments?? huh wait and see... and sami u better eat lots of chicken for me so the baby can get my taste.. I want her to be just like me.. and tell ur hubby darling to keep my pic next to ur bed, and see the pic day and night.. I cannot tell about the temper, because it runs in the family.. Wait and see, the baby is going to get my good personality, and charm and wow what looks.. n ofcourse this genius mind of mine.. whatelse can u ask for?? ;-)) And the baby is going to be mine and only mine first, because I m elder to all of u bachas.. ok  Dolly sweetheart, kunu darling and piyu darling.. and ofcourse Angad and Arjun mamu singh, and all other bachas I forgot to mention here.. The baby is going to be totally gujju and  Ofcourse "TOPIWALA".. So my baby welcome to this beautiful world, and  Topiwala family. Me ur big Foi, Nilesh Fua, and ur Big Brother Asht are waiting for your arrival.. Love Smmmmooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooch!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
      
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One week passed after starting my 8th month.  You know when you are waiting for something, it takes its precious time.  I wish this month goes quickly and smoothly (thats what I have been saying for the last seven months) :-)  The ninth month is going to be a little tough and also scary.  Its Scary because I will be leaving my outside life behind for my baby for at least a year if everything works out, which I dont really mind staying home but still I dont want to miss out on anything. Right now staying home is like sooooooo quiet, looking for work to do around the house, or just watch TV.  Later it will be baby this baby that, baby crying, cleaning baby all the time, feeding, cleaning again...hehe.  I hope my baby is NOT picky in eating.  I dont want to run around the room later to feed her, she should just wait for me to bring her food and finish everything (I guess this is too much to ask from a baby) :)  I hope our baby is chubby baby, I have a little competition going on at work from all the people I know who already had their baby.  I want mine to be the fattest and of course CUTEST, which shouldn't be a problem because her mom is soooooo cute herself..hehe !!!  I know some people will AGREE to that....rite dharmesh???!!! (good)  Well thats about it..will rite more when I have more to share.  Mommy Dearest!
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok......I had enough #*%^%(*&!  I want my baby now, and want to go back to my regular clothes size. She is moving so much inside which makes me WANT to see her.  I want to see her Yawn, suck her thumb, and strech after waking up.  Thats going to be soooooooooo cute!!! Now when she moves my whole stomach goes side ways, left to rite.  Its like my baby is teasing me..."ha ha you cant see me..suffer mom suffer!!!"  One more reason I want her out is so I can get sleeeep..not easy sleeping at night because I move around alot during sleep.  Now when I turn I have to shift MY WHOLE stomach and wait for the baby to drop the other side...hehehe.  I guess these last two months is going to be the hardest, but once the baby is born its not like I am going to get sleep anyways.  So I should or everyone in our house should enjoy the quietness around the house.    I think Dharmesh is getting eager now as well to see the baby....pappa gotta suffer as well as mom.  Mommy Dearest !!
      
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       We all know that if its a girl the name is going to be Ria....But what if? What if? What if you know its a boy....What will be the name be....Couple of suggestions...Vikram,Samay,Aryan....does anybody else have any other suggestions for name for a boy? Please post....  
      
</post>


</Blog>