<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So, I went to Rondeau Provincial Park on the weekend for a bike ride with friends. What a gorgeous day. A friend was having their family reunion there so we dropped in. Her family is fantastically crazy, so we had some good laughs. We chilled at the beach too. Sometimes you just have to get back to nature and give your soul a good scrubbing.  The next day we had a welcoming party for a new friend from out of town. I sang, but not very well. I need some singing lessons.   The L Word  made its premiere in Canada. Finally I don't have to spend an eternity downloading the series off of the internet. So I made a wonderful dinner, and watched it in my pajamas. following this I had a "late-night-all-by-myself-dance-party". I really am good company. This should provide at least a bit of bootylicious (bi)sexual content for what seems to be an absence of longing for a mate.  I'm still looking for a job. Are you looking for someone with experience in Non-Profit &amp; or Hospitality Management experience? Would you be in the Southwestern Ontario Area? I think i'll post my resume on here at some point...just for fun....  ta!  

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hmm.  Some words i've re-learned today...  enabler dependent **peace** responsibility forgiveness  The olympics were beautiful today. I had a big fight with someone I love this morning. It was the best thing that happened to us. I suspect things will be much better now, even though they have never looked so messy. The darkest point is before dawn.  I often think that peace in the world can't be attained until we have peace in our own souls. One by one we have to make peace with ourselves. Is there even a point? After watching thousands of athletes prepare to make their big races, I have to think of how "insignificant" those athletes in the original olympics were. Do we know their names? Nope. But yet, they contributed to the greatest peacemaking venture we humans have. Did they even know what they were doing for the world? How cool is that...all by living their measly lives. I guess I should try to do the same.  If I had a song for this moment it would be:  "Offer" by Alanis Morissette.  I'll say a prayer for peace today. Thank God for my messy, confusing, blessed, romantic, shitty, fun, exhausing, challenging, beautiful, pointless, invaluable, perfectly imperfect life.  

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So Today, I try sign into my msn and this dickweed decides to highjack my msn messenger and send all these (really nasty) messages to all my friends. So I participate in a sign-in war where each time i sign in I get a message that says...you have signed in at another location.  So eventually i sign in very quickly change my nickname to..."I know who you are and i'm going to kick your ass bitch". So after that...there isn't much signing in going on. Punk kids.  Moral: When I pick my password, it's good to have a REALLY secret, secret question.  ---  As for the good news, according to  urlLink Tickle ...  Cinnamon Bun**, the right design for you shows off your Eye for  Trends      Hey, trendsetter. You're quite the hip and happenin' one. With your tastes for telling what's hot and what's not, you're on the cutting edge. And what better way to keep showing off your fashionable ways than by making sure your room says as much about you as the style that precedes you? To make your room the casa of cool, go for accessories and touches that are edgy and stylish like you. Look to a multi shag rug, pretty bohemian striped pillows, a sari bedding set, a color block rug, or a willow hamper to complete your look. A room that reveals the true you is as cool as it gets. So get decorating!  Look at me! I'm a Trendsetter!  Psst. Honey.                Put those hoop earnings away.                      So   Out.   

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hmm. So...I guess I should explain myself.  I'm 23 I'm a student, who hopes eventually to graduate....sometime this decade I'm currently in the library... and this young kid is reading over my shoulder. but that's cool.  I need a  urlLink job , but i'm overwhelmed by a mixture of my own stupidity and my ambition. And so, i'm totally wasting time here, by writing this blog instead of getting a life. And it's o.k. to say that here because no one is going to read this except for me. I think.  And what's worse..as i'm writing this my (far too long for my own good) intermittent crush has just sent me a message on msn.  urlLink Just when you think you're ready  to let go of them, they decide to pop right back in there.  Sheeit...but this time i'm ready to let go. Seriously. I'm pretty sure about it this time.  I successfully ignore him. Eventually, it gets old.  I'm poor, I'm overweight, but since i'm one of those people who don't care about that (but secretly kind of do) I fight myself in attempts to do anything about it.  And now I think I may have vented enough to feel a wee bit better, and so I just may get something done.  bye.   

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Hooray, look at me I have a blog now. I'm so cool.  So this last week has basically been about cleaning out the closets of my life. They resemble the closets of packrats with OCD. Bad friends, lost ambitions. So I decided to cut some people lose and start fresh. A la Bridget Jones I have decided to watch what I eat, get some exercise, get a new job and start a 'diary' YAY!  Last week I went to a poetry reading. Guess what? It was fun!  I also checked out a modern dance class, the music was really great (Ani DiFranco and other folksy worldsy stuff)  Then I went to Detroit for a   urlLink  Dignity    Mass, and afterwards found myself instead having dinner with about 20 caucasian gay men (and one asian). They were so fascinated by me. The Nuns think it might be because i'm all afro-looking yet canadian sounding.  That's what I think too.  Oh and I got a new bike.    

						
</post>


</Blog>