<Blog>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ...but at least I know it.   This weekend I visited my parents to celebrate my mothers birthday and her new job. I arrived together with the message that my grandfather had died. Wednesday will be the funeral, so I'll have to travel again.  My Grandfather was 86 Years old. I met him last time early this year. Two weeks after that he went to hospital, where cancer was diagnosed. Shortly after he was operated, but he never really recovered.  Our last conversation was about the past. He told me about the time, when he left our family and fled to west Germany. My father was still a little kid then and had never forgiven him. My grandfather never told me why he left or how he felt about. He only ask for forgiving him. I think that I will never be able to answer the question whether it was his fault or just the condition of living in a dictatorship.  The other thing he told often about was the war. He spent his entire youth fighting the second world war in whole Europe. He felt never really guilty about what he did then too. Or maybe he did, but he wasn't able to tell me. Clearly I can remember the stories he told me. How he seen Moscow from their position in the winter of 1941. How he lost his unit and had to find his way back to Austria by himself. All the way on foot, suffering from hunger and afraid of being captured by Russians. He came back in late 1943 more dead than alive and after a few weeks in a hospital they sent him out again to fight at the western front, where he got captured.  When he told me about the war he never mentioned any suffering or fear than his own and I guess from this experience he had deduced the idea that he had suffered enough. That is the only way how I can explain how he lived his life further on. He was never pleased with what he had. Always jealous of what other people achieved and he didn't, although he had a good life after he left east Germany. He romanticised his own past so much that he considered his life in the third Reich better then the one in west Germany after the war.  I see my grandfathers life completely different and draw completely different conclusions. He spent his whole youth in the war fighting and killing for some crazy mans ideas. It is unimaginable for me what personality is necessary to repress all feel of guilt and even to glorify this time in any way. I learned from that the mans mind is a dangerous thing and that seld-deception is the most dangerous thing that it can do.  I liked my grandfather when I was a child, but when I grew older I tried to understand him but I couldn't: confronting him with my thoughts and opinion about his past he told me that without experiencing it I have possibility to judge correctly, but leaving out the topic was not possible, because he liked it too much. Other people from my family could listen to his talks without having anything to ask or comment. They considered it as the harmless thing that old people had to tell. I could never.  So during the last ten years, when I was finally able to visit him, he became more and more a stanger to me, which disgusted me with his ignorance about his own past - his past in the war and after. I can not blame him for anything, he never did anything to me. Also I can not judge over the thing he did, because I don't now enough. But for sure that's the reason why I'm not actually sad or mourning today. But I will keep in mind the story he told me about the past and I will tell them to other people, because I learned a lot from those stories not only by hearing them, but by putting them in my own context of newest history.  Wednesday is the funeral. I will go there, even though I feel not dedicated to him. But my parents will be there and my sister might need her cold-hearted little brother to smoke a secret cigarette.  good night. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I refuse to work like the military and to age like the cockroaches       Time passes quickly. Another day is gone and nothing is finished. It seems to be some sort of phenomenon that appears here stronger than anywhere else: the time is passing faster than normal. The people in the country with the name 'Cockroaches' react in an appropriate way. They act as if they were older. Some start to collect money for their own funeral when they enter school. Except foreigners nobody is going out on Saturday night. The people here feel already too old when they are allow to go to club or bars. So they sit with their parents and their grandparents at home watching TV. They talk about the old times and about the whether. Sometimes these native people get up and get a fresh beer from the fridge. When they come back from the kitchen they have a slight smile on their faces. This is the best moment of the day.      Today I hate Sergei more than anything else. He ruined the whole day. He came two days ago to help me with my work. But he is only surfing the internet and reading magazines. When I ask him something he tells me about anything else. His favorite sentence is: 'that's all simple stuff'. Everything seems simple if you don't do anything. So what can I do? Send him home again? Tell him that he is a lazy sucker? Would that change anything? I refuse to organize my work with orders like in the military.       Yesterday Sergei played football. He didn't come to our barbecue party. Soeren drunk so much that he had to throw up. He returned from the bathroom with nosebleed, so we brought him home, before we went dancing, which is maybe the only way to avoid the early aging. The hangover in the morning was not so bad. I simply stayed in bed until twelve. This is the best place to deal with a hangover. Saying goodbye to Soeren was not so bad either. He seemed to be recovered from the night before and spoke less loud than normally. But Sergei really spoiled the day.       As I told before, the name of the county here is 'Cockroaches'. It's just a translation, but it fits. The people seem to be bugs. For me they all look the same, even though they are bigger and smaller. They are all around me with their ugly old faces and feel disgusted. But they can't harm me in any way. The only thing that could happen is that I start aging as fast as them and I'm afraid of that.         TODAY   up_12am   breakfast_cereals with fruits    lunch_none   dinner_crispbread   cigarettes_4   music_nirvana   sleep_2am        
    
</post>


</Blog>