<Blog>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Skin Deep        what is love when barely there and I can stare straight through do you know what to do when so shatters your heart you dart and dash around any Truth to set you loose rend your heart of all the dark and let ignite the living spark how hard is it to guard against all you know are lies cries out from the pit, Lord of the Flies, his trickery dies in One done to Him all we do because He is the One life is through knew it inherently but blew it away like feathers from His wing oh to sing when saved from the eternal grave of spirits hear it, loud and clear, but fear it not for He is love dove wings flap and then you leave behind all that is divine find Him where He was all along and sing for Him a song!         (c)Crystal Joseph      
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         Triduum      a haunt of jackals break free from shackals blood for life no more strife wake up your heart make a new start random thoughts of chaos nothing can slay us redemtion is paid life is made pain and suffering spent your back is bent no more broken neck don't bother to check soft flutter of wings make like new things His body lays took three days He rose untarnished "It is finished"          (c)Crystal Joseph     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Cracked Cup of Water        day ends and time bends to fit it all in... trickle down into the little cup that is my hands hold it in by and by until its dry thought I caught up with it all by now glass falls only to bend and break I wanted to not be like the glass knowing I was showing the tiniest cracks enough to shatter through the toughest stuff thought I belonged but I was so very wrong I am not enough to hold tough agaisnst it He is the strength I find to hold me up it was not home until I knew He was there. day ends and time bends to fit it all in...         (c)Crystal Joseph     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
           Primordial Fear          Where is away when away was here Thinking and hoping there's nothing to fear I look and search for the One to come Then I find I am all alone.      Find a way to get myself through the day Don't know what else I can do Need a way to be free of the pain I'm told its found all in You.  Where is away when away was here Thinking and hoping there's nothing to fear I look and search for the One to come Then I find I am all alone.  Like those times we could play all day The world was full of things to do Younger times we didn't know any pain Before I forgot about You.  Where was I when I was lost Blinded by demons and almost paid the cost I've looked and found the One who came He's never gone because He rose again.            (c)Crystal Joseph     
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
          Forevermore          Mirror reflects prospects of life on a fairy's wing To learn to sing a song not of remorseful meaning If you look with meaning in HIS eyes you'll find light Escape the original plight befallen to mankind from deceit Walk on sure feet. Forevermore. Clean air carries songs to be sung, for ears to hear Know it, dear one, for the song is sung for you Even two notes lost are worth the whole song to the Composer Nothing is leftover here that HE cannot beat Walk on sure feet. Forevermore.            (c)Crystal Joseph      
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        We are SO saved      eDge oF eTernity lOoks sO dIrty I aM sO uNworthy LeDge oF tHe uNiverse lOoks sO pErverse I cAn sEe tHe hUman rAce sLedge hAmmer oF saLvaTion bRoke tHe dAmnatIon oH hOw wE aRe sAved!       cRying oN tHe iNside fOr tHe LandsLide nO mOrtal sEems tO cAre LyiNg iN tHe vaLLey iS rIght uP oUr aLLey tHe eNemy fOund uS tHere rOck soLid foUndaTion buiLt oN cRucifiXion oH hOw wE aRe sAved!           (c)Crystal  Joseph     
     

    
</post>


</Blog>