<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like to think of myself as a pretty mature guy. But sometimes, I turn into a 13-year-old girl (b-cup and everything). Like this... Sometimes I gossip like nobody's business. And sometimes I get all riled up about stuff that really doesn't matter at all and that I ultimately can't do anything about. The worst is when I realize that I've done both things at once. I don't have any strict moral code against gossiping or anything; I just hate that it usually hurts someone and more-frequently-than-not it comes back and bites me in the ass. My ass hurts from all the biting.  I heard some bad things about the Mansion through the grapevine and I told my new boss about them. Looooooord, that came back. The person I heard the bad things from had heard them from someone else whose friend had worked at the Mansion. Then I told my boss, who called her previous employee who asked his friend if he'd told anybody. Then the friend called the person I heard it from and soon enough I hear all about it! I'm not mad at all, because it's not like anybody did anything wrong except the guy who used to work at the Mansion who told his friends a bunch of lies that eventually got back to the owner. But I kind of screwed my friend by passing on information that he had been told in confidence. If I'd just kept my big mouth shut, nothing would have happened. But whatever, bygones.  Today I got to work and Abbadon had emailed me asking why I didn't hire someone at the store they had applied at and why I sent the applicant to another one of our locations to interview... She was all mad and aggressive. So I - of course - got all angry because she is just a bitch. It's innate.  It's like her hair is brown, her eyes are brown, her personality is bitch. Some things just ARE. Anyways, in her email she wasn't just nicely asking me a question. She was accusing me of making a bad decision. And she's one of those super-bitch-power-bitch's who will never back down or admit that she's wrong. Funny, she's single. Whoda thunk it? So I faught back against her with a "Here's my reasoning, so suck it" email and another "Well, tell me if one of your stores is in such dire straits and I will be better suited to make decisions" email. Then I talked to Michael and he told me I should just drop it because I'll never change her. She's always going to be a bitch. Except Michael doesn't really think she's a bitch. Just I do.  See what I mean? I get all riled up about nothing and then I gossip about it and do petty shit to make myself feel better. Really? How much better does it make me feel to send off aggressive emails to Abbadon? No better at all. Just making the situation more dramatic. It's because I hate her and I never want her to feel like she can step all over me without me realizing it and telling her to get the fuck off me. But ultimately she just ignores me. So what good does it do? I'm all about supporting the underdog, but when there is no chance of winning? AND WHAT DO I WIN REALLY? Does a house land on her or something? Jesus Christ I'd love to see those shoes shrivle up.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Will someone who knows about these things please help me put pictures on my blog??? I feel like there is limited media.  Thank you!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've had a week full of change! Here are the highlights:  Mansion I accepted a job as a manager at a mansion in town that has been restored and converted into a bed and breakfast. It's still up-and-coming, so there is a lot of work to be done. But I'm excited to be able to dig into a project and really get involved. The owner is a great businesswoman and I'm excited to work for her. She has two kids who are great. The staff is very small, so there are no benefits at the mansion and the salary range for someone in my position is fairly low. But it all works out in the end. We worked together to set up a reasonable compensation package. I'm excited that it's grassroots!  Fake Cow Job I gave my notice to the fake cow yesterday. She was like "Guh-huh, I knew it was coming. Dude, I just sent an email saying we should start recruiting someone to fill that position." She didn't want to know anything about why I'm leaving or where I'm going really. Just the necessary questions. If she didn't ask them she'd look like a bitch and the "fake" thing would be over. She has to at least maintain an image! Anyways, I told my friends at work that I'm leaving and all went well. I'm not going to miss this place. My back hurts from all the knife wounds!!! I didn't join a frat in college. I hate the culture. Working for this company, though, is like being in a frat... More like a sorority. Alpha Kappa Screwurself.  Benefits One of the things I've been stressing about so bad is health benefits. So I finally got it taken care of! I'm looking at two different plans and the Benefits Manager at Fake Cow offered to help me figure out which one would be best for me. That's totally awesome of her, since that stuff scares me a little bit! It's really not as expensive as you'd think it is... I'm not paying anymore here than I did at Fake Cow. Anyways, I'm excited that's almost taken care of. I can get all the herpes and ear infections I want!!!!! :)  Car Insurance I pay an ungodly amount each month for car insurance because I have a loan for it and because my dad is on the title. Well, we got that taken care of this week!!! My parents gave me some money and I paid off the car. The title is in the mail to me as we speak - type, speak, whatever - and I'm going to get it transferred next week. I got my car insurance changed up and it dropped by $400 every six months. HOLY JESUS, eh? That'll buy a communion dinner or two! And my massive car payments are over now too... I'm gonna be rolling in money!!! Well, no, that's not true. I'm going to have a ton more money to put towards my college debt!!!  Michael He's been good... I freaked out and tried to dump him (that's what he told his friend in an email I saw "I haven't talked to him for like four days since he tried to dump me" HILARIOUS) while I was in freak-out mode and he was like "BIATCH, I invested too much emotion in this. Suck up your shit and get through it. We'll be fine." So whatever, we're fine. He's still kinda on the sidelines a little bit... Everybody is. But all of my relationships will be fine as soon as my life settles and I am not so crazy.  Life is all about function right now... Just get through. Then in a while when all this craziness is over, I'll be able to divert my focus more and do things for fun and actually be FUN while I do them! I feel bad for people who have to hang out with me right now. Hanging out with me is like chewing chalk. Not worth the effort AT ALL! People are so used to me being goofy and crazy, and I'm so focused on function right now that they think I'm mad at them or that they offended me or something. That's totally not the case - and I'm sorry to any of you who I've made feel that way. I've just been stripped of personality recently. It'll come back, just give it some time. And I won't be offended if you want to leave me alone for a few days. It'd probably be good for both of us.   That last paragraph is hilarious. I really am not writing to anyone specific, just writing. SO TO ALL MY SELF-ABSORBED FRIENDS, Don't think I'm writing about you!!! :)  K, back to Fake Cow Enterprises... One more week!!!!  PS - I just got an email from my boss that killed me... I had emailed her to say that I have court on Wednesday of next week and to ask what she wanted me to do about my schedule. She forwarded it to Abbadon and said "Please go to Schaumburg after court"... So Abbadon totally knows I am going to court, but the email didn't say traffic court. She probably thinks I am a mass murderer or something!!! God almighty.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To top it all off... I have a zit like Hellboy on my forehead... It looks like one of these...  http://www.imdb.com/gallery/ss/0167190/Ss/0167190/046-R35-28Ao.jpg?path=gallery&path_key=0167190
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm not sure when it happened that I became crazy. Last I remember I was in college, having a blast, getting decent grades, and had a great job. Now I'm not doing anything worth writing down on paper without an end goal and I'm not even doing well at it. I used to be level-headed and too logical for most people... I lost friends because of how logical I was. Now I'm an emotional basket-case who has anxiety attacks that last days or weeks. Logic? What logic? Just don't hurt me.  I wrote my offer letter for this job at the mansion today. I'm signing it tomorrow and giving my notice at my current company. If I stay there any longer, Abbadon will have her way and will find some way to have me terminated. I'm sure I'll screw up somehow and she will do her best to bring it to everyones attention and put a fuckin' spotlight on it like I'm a gaudy Christmas wreath on her cold-hearted grinch-house. Heartless bitch. Whew... "Crazy, party of one? Your table is ready in the Hold-A-Grudge room."  I broke up with Michael last night...  But I'm not sure we're really broken up. I'm too fucked up to think about it really. I'll figure that out later. If I think too much about it right now, I'll probably pass out. I need to let that sit out there untouched for a while. Oh man, when Abbadon found out about that... JEBUS, she went nuts. Some fuel for the fire of her hate for me.   I think I just need to start doing some of the healthy things I did in college. I think that's probably a huge part of what's making things so different. I haven't worked out in months. My sleep patterns are fusked up really bad. I think I just need a more consistent and healthy lifestyle. I've given up on trying to be the sexy twink that I was a couple years ago. I don't really care about that anymore... I just want to be healthy and not crazy. I can't even think straight. And the not being able to breath thing is too much for me.   I think all this change is freaking me out... I just need to do it, get it over with, and start my healthier lifestyle. I need to join the gym. Some boy at the Baton offered to hook me up with a free Crunch membership because he manages the place, but I think he would require that I go out on a date with him for that to happen. I'm not gonna do that. I would rather just join the Y, where I can be my true brokeass.  Also, it will make me feel better about myself because I am at least physically above par there. Can you imagine how depressing it would be to work out at Crunch? Jebus. I'd be so depressed.   Alright, I'm gonna sleep off a few hours of this funk. Things will be better soon. They always are.  OH ONE MORE THING... I have a friend who I think is trying to tell me he has a crush on me. This is not what I need right now. I am in no condition to try to balance someone else's emotions on top of my own. What do you do in that situation? Ideas anyone? I've just been avoiding it like the plague.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It would be a blur. Seriously. I start work on Friday at 8am (although I tend to actually get to my first store of the day around 8:30). Then I work until 3 or 4pm, go home to change clothes for the Baton, then work again until 3am... I sleep for a while, wake up on Saturday to do all my chores, then go back to the Baton. I sleep some more, wake up on Sunday to have some downtime until I have to go to bed again and get up on Monday and my cycle starts all over. What's crazy is that I like my weekends a lot! I kinda like that it's crazy and jam packed. Right now it's 4:28am and I'm just finishing up my Friday night.  Every time I work at the Baton, I pour myself a cup of coffee during the last show of the night. So tonight my ritual came due and I poured the coffee, walked over to the Godiva bottle, dumped a shot in, then realized that my boss was standing RIGHT next to me. Well, actually I realized it after I took the first sip. Man did I feel like a jackass. That's how things work when you're me. You do stupid shit like drink on the job in front of your boss. Granted, I had about 2/3 of a shot of Godiva and every other employee had about a quarter of a bottle of vodka each, I feel bad about it. What ya gonna do!? What ya gonna do when they come for you...  Tomorrow is my sister's girlie-day. So I'm gonna take the dog all day and do errands and stuff. I have to pick up her heartworm pills and bleh bleh bleh... I want to go tanning (I really think that tanning last weekend helped me feel better about myself, be more outgoing, and ultimately make more friends and more money). If there is time after that we'll probably spend some of it at the dog park. Ella can play with her friends and I can pretend like the strangers that I see all the time at the dog park are my true friends that I look forward to seeing as I clean poop off the asphalt ground. Saturdays are supposed to be my cleaning day, too, so I've got to get some things done. Pretty much what I do is sweep the floor and swiffer it. Then I take out all the garbage. Those are good chores, right?  Alright, I need to shower and get to bed so I can get eight hours and still have enough time to do a couple of errands. I'll probably write more on Sunday, so log back in to check out my adventures! They're SO not "adventures". They're like "meanderings". That's a better word. Just random things I walk into. Or that walk into me.  Good night. Jebus I'm tired.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bailey's and coffee has become my resolution for all sorts of things. When money gets tight, I brew up a pot of coffee and dump a little sweet Bailey's into it. When I have a bad day at work, you can find me at the nearest FRiDAYS getting a big fatty Bailey's and coffee with whipped cream on top. When the girl I am making drinks for at the bar gets bitchy with me... I have myself a Bailey's and coffee and the world is better. I think it's like warm milk for a baby. It just makes me feel so comfortable. I reccommend it.  Things are cra-cra-craaaazy in my head right now. I hate commuting to the freeking suburbs every day and I have an awesome chance to get out of it, but I'm not sure what the best decision is. It's a big risk because it would be a huge change in lifestyle. But it would mean that I get to spend more time with my sister and my dog. I'd probably be able to squeeze in a workout or two each week. But I'd lose some very valuable things - like my health insurance. I guess I could always buy that for myself. Or maybe I can get it from the Baton. Me and the drag queens can go to the same doctor. FABULOUS. I'll wear my sequins.  This store I'm working on opening is going well. Abbadon is being alright. I think she realizes that I'm not going to put up with being treated like a hog bottom by some glorified quick-service restaurant manager, so she's at least smiling every once in a while and I can tell she's trying really hard to not be a cold-hearted bitch as much as she usually is. Honestly, it makes me feel really good when she tries to be nice to me. But it makes me really mad that even though she is trying so hard, she just never is truly nice. Whatever Trevor. I am certianly not the crux of that situation, I'm just a little electron who happened upon her neucleus and is there for a short ride. I'll find a new atom to join up with soon.  I had some rockstar sex yesterday. WHEW. Maybe it's because it's been a while, or maybe it's because things just work out really well with the two of us. But Jesus "Tap-dat-ass" Christ it was good lovin'. Sometimes I can't help but laugh really hard when the climax is over. It's just such a funny thing!!! Two gross bodies grunting and sweating and all that??? That's HILARIOUS!!!  Last night after we finished at the new store, me and Michael and a bunch of trainers went out to dinner at Cheesecake Factory. Man, what a horrible dining experience. But the company was good. I got a little out of hand, as always, since most of the trainers were really young and I thrive off goofy kids. I ordered the Ono special, but our server forgot to order it (when Michael asked him what happened, he said "They forgot to order it". As if he's not responsible at all). When it came out, everybody else was finished with their meals. Then the manager offered to comp me a dessert. NO WAY BUDDY, I want you to comp the meal. But I couldn't get too confrontational, because I have a tendancy to throw chairs. So I backed down and eventually Michael handled it. I couldn't help but give the guy a stare that probably melted the hair off his chest though. It just came out!!! Sometimes I'm a big poonanner, but sometimes I have to be really careful to not go crazy... I think I did alright last night.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My life changes too quickly... There are big changes in the works. BIG changes. But I can't write about them on here because they're still in the Top Secret folder. But they're scary plans... Just know that these are things that consume my thoughts and my energies. Today I went about my business at work and recruited people to work in the impossible-to-recruit-for store, but all I could think about is what the next chapter in my life will look like. I'll tell you this: it includes a mansion...  I was at a soon-to-open store today in the north suburbs that I just got assigned to last week. They're supposed to open on Friday with about 35 people, but only 23 have been hired as of today. So now I get thrown into the mix. T girl who had been staffing the store before last week went on vacation. So we're screwed. No, no I AM screwed. It's my face attached to it all. The district manager up there, Abaddon, already hates me. She chews me out sometimes just because it gets her lavarocks off. The Regional VP for that store was very nice today though. We had a conversation about what needs to be done to bring people into the store, etc. At least she was constructive. That's all I need really. Someone who is constructive and not mean. Or fake. Fake is even worse.  I went to meet my ex-boyfriend-turned-friend, Jason, for dinner tonight. We had a good relationship - excepting some shit that young stupid fags do - and I am kind of sorry that it ended. But it did... And it's nothing we could really ever go back to. So we do the whole "friends" thing. Pretty much we just text message each other back and forth. We were going to meet for dinner tonight, then when I called him after work there was no answer. Stupid. Sucks to get ditched by a guy who you already have a screwed up past with. A little bit demeaning.  Now I'm at home with Brady (Michael's dog) and Ella. Michael's supposed to come over tonight because he's horny and we haven't had sex in a while. One day I'm going to start a blog where I can write about him and not worry about him reading it... I talk through every aspect of my life on here, except that... I never should have given him the address!  My parents called me tonight and they want to meet for dinner tomorrow night. They are going to meet me at my apartment and they told me to choose a place where we could talk. I wonder what that's all about!?? I just found out last week that they are going to a support group for parents with gay kids. So maybe it's about that. I hope it's good. I hope they don't want to convert me or something like that. Ugh. We'll see! It's only 24 hours away! I've recently started going to a support group for children of George Bush's fan club. Maybe we can discuss that as well. Suckers............
     

    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend has been fun, but I've been constantly on the move so far! Last night after work I took a shower and changed clothes and headed to the Baton (my second job) to bartend. It was busy as hell in there. I guess it wasn't just busy at the Baton, it was busy everywhere in River North last night. There were all sorts of people in all sorts of places around town. So I got out of work and came home. I didn't eat anything after work though. I'm a little bit proud of myself for that. Oh man, I was on my way home last night at like 3am and I was working my way through a traffic jam on the enterance to the Kennedy and I realized that I was having a really stupid emotion. I felt really proud of myself because it was 3am and I was one of the elite few sobor drivers on the road. Then I realized how rediculous it was that I felt PRIDE of all things and how I should probably feel FEAR or something. FEAR THIS.  So I got home, chilled for a big, and went to bed at 5am. I had to get up at 10:30, though, so I could make it to my first event of the day. A COLONIC. That's right. I had a man named Ricardo shoot streams of water into my large intestine and then drain it out. It was amazing. It felt really weird, but I feel so much better after having it done. Ricardo was saying how you should do it every day for like a week or so to get started and I realized how great you must feel after doing it that often, but how broke you must be. I wish I had that kind of money! $$$$$ 8)  When I got done being internally cleaned I went to Salon Blonde to get my hair colored... Brown ironicaly. I sat there for a long time with hair color burning a hole into my scalp and then, when it was all said and done, my stylist charged me... ? I know that doesn't sound weird, and I'm not one of those elitists who thinks they deserve everything for free. But my hair was always one good hookup I had. Jodi always lets me off by paying like $30 or something. I had to pay $60 just to get colored today. Ugh... Whatever, it looks great so it's worth it.  I might round off my day and make it entirely too shallow by going to the tanning beds because now that my hair is dark I look like Powder - very white skin. But then I might feel just a little bit too shallow, ya know? Eh, whatever. It'll make me look good. It'll make me more money in tips. It will make me a little bit happier. I'll do it.  Alright folks, have a great night. I'll be slinging the drinks at the Baton for some transistors. I'm sure you'll hear from me tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One of my coworkers is totally in love with himself. Seriously. He's sitting in the cube next to me right now singing Sister Christian or something like that as if everybody in the office wants to hear his low-quality karoke remakes. One of those guys who wants to be the life of the party, but there really isn't a party going on. He calls people and says things like "DUDE, you won't believe it..." and he calls people by their last names. He uses all the keywords that make people's ears perk up. He's just full of it, ya know what I mean? I don't really mind him most of the time since we work in different districts and each do our own thing. But when he's shoved into the hotel cube right next to mine, I want to die. Also, he thinks he is my boss. I love that. He tries to make really awkward conversation with me. Today we had been sitting next to each other for an hour or so and he reached around the cube and said "Hey, how are you?" Um, fine. I have been for the past hour.  I'll tell you the nice thing about Fridays. My company caters in lunch. Granted, it's our concept's food and I eat it all week long, but this time I don't have to order it for myself! It just comes right up to the office and all I have to do is go grab it. And since I eat lunch at my desk I get to leave at 3:00! It kind of makes us for an hour or so of driving that I do throughout the week, so it helps me leave work for the weekend without such a strong sour taste in my mouth. That's healthy for me, right?  When I leave work today I'm gonna go play with Ella for a while and take her for a short walk. I'm gonna try to take a nap, but I have to be at my second job (I bartend at a drag show) by 6. I love that job; it's kind of a nice retreat from reality. And people are totally real there. I mean, as real as a girl who is actually a boy can be. I mean, they tell you what they think and they let you know how things are. If they hate you, they hate you. If they love you, they love you. If they don't give a shit about you, they don't pretend like they do. And they don't expect you to be anything but the same way. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My days:  Wake up - I'm a snooze button kind of guy. I always set my alarm for the exact time I need to be up to get to work on time, then I snooze button it in the morning. Then I rush to get ready. I think it makes mornings exciting for me or something.  Shower/Walk the dog - I combine these things because one happens so quickly after the other, that they're practically the same thing. I take a very thorough shower... Shampoo, condition, Ivory body wash, some prescription body wash thing, mouthwash, brush teeth, shave, rinse out the conditioner, wash face with normal soap, wash face with prescription soap. Dry off, get dressed, etc. Then I walk the dog to one end of my block and back. When we get home I feed her and fill up her water bowl. Then we play for about three seconds before I leave.  Drive to work - Bitter. I'm very bitter about this. I just got a new district and I have to work in the north suburbs. So my drive takes around an hour each way. That's a big change from my 25 minute el ride each way. I hate my boss for this. But I do it. I take my 1996 Exploder and we trek 90/94 or 294 or 53 or some other road in an overpopulated area.  Work - This changes all the time. Sometimes I go to stores and people pretend that I am important to the company because of my profound Human Resources contributions to their stores. Then, if the store is short on employees, I do something very professional like printing out 100 "Now Hiring" flyers and putting them on people's windshields. It's a guarantee that someone will yell at me for something in each work day. Then it's probably likely that in any given week my boss will hear about it and instead of backing me up, she will tell me that I'm horrible at what I do. Except, she'll try to make it sound positive by doing something like this... "You've done an awesome job for the past two or three months. I mean, people comment about how well-pressed your polo shirts have been. But really people hate you because you printed out 'Now Hiring' flyers on yellow paper instead of pink papers. It's really important that they be on yellow paper next time so people don't yell at you.  But keep on pressing those shirts, bucko" Stick it, you fake cow. So I get through one of those days and end up feeling like a useless cog on an antique bicycle and go home.  Drive home from work - See "Drive to work".  Walk the dog - As soon as I get home - as long as I'm not going to have an assplosion or pee myself or something from my 8 hour drive home - I walk the dog right away. My sister (I'm SO thankful for her) has usually walked the dog once or twice already and fed her dinner so that's all taken care of. So we walk for a while and then we celebrate when she poops. I bag it up, we throw it away, then carry on with our evening.  Personal time - This is the 3 hours of time when I get to do something for myself, but all I can really do is think about the person who yelled at me that day at work or how I don't want to press my polo shirt the next day just for sweet revenge against the fake cow or something. But to avoid being entirely TOO overcome by resentment, I go to the dog park with Ella (my previously referenced dog), get dinner with Steph (my previously referenced sister), hang out with Michael (a new introduction: my boyfriend), or do something by myself. Recently I've just wanted to be by myself. I think I'm having my man-period. It doesn't happen too frequenly, but when it does, watch out. Somebody should just drug me up and let me sleep through this bitch. She's fierce. And it's not one of those 4-day things where I can just go to Planned Parenthood (sidenote: I was in the suburbs today and saw a Planned Parenthood EXPRESS. Are they that big of whores out there that they need an EXPRESS Planned Parenthood?) and things will be better. No, I need things like wine and beer and Vicodin and season 1 and 2 DVD's of Queer as Folk to get through these puppies.   Go to sleep - I LOVE THIS PART OF THE DAY. I really like my bedroom because it's kind of like a cave - and kind of like a bowling alley too because it's about 4 feet wide and 15 feet long, but I just call it a "cave" instead of a bowling alley - but it's really cool, so I feel pretty comfortable in it. And I can make it really really dark when I sleep and my dog has been sleeping in my bed recently so that's kind of cool. I love being asleep because nothing maters and you can have great dreams! And even if things suck in your dreams, they're just dreams! But, ultimately, the sleeping ends when my alarm goes off...   So I hit snooze and it starts again...
     

    
</post>


</Blog>