<Blog>

<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink       Maybe she does have some sense in her... No, no what was I thinking. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wish I had this in my front yard... urlLink      
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                 ...running for President of the United States or for the mayor of New Hope, Pennsylvania?   urlLink      urlLink    
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      John Kerry says that 4 months of serving in Vietnam, which he left 8 months early, and also two decades in the Senate, with nothing to show for it, qualifies him to be President of the United States... Are you joking?  Pictured below is Kerry with his fellow soldiers in Veitnam, who all but one do not support him.  urlLink       urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink        urlLink Heinz Kerry: Four More Years of 'Hell' if Bush Wins     MILWAUKEE (Reuters) - Teresa Heinz Kerry, the outspoken wife of Democratic presidential nominee John Kerry, pulled no punches on Monday in telling a rally what she thought of the Bush administration -- hell.  And later, discussing the war in Iraq, Heinz Kerry subtly questioned Republican President Bush's intellect, saying: "It's vital for anyone with intelligence to acknowledge mistakes and change positions -- hello."  When a Bush supporter with a bullhorn shouted "four more years" from the back of a large crowd packed into a downtown Milwaukee park, Heinz Kerry, who was introducing her husband, responded: "They want four more years of hell."  "Three more months!," she declared, referring to the Nov. 2 presidential election .  ___________________________________________________________________    On the eve of the Democratic National Convention, the wife of Sen. John Kerry told a journalist to "Shove it."   Teresa Heinz Kerry accused the editorial page editor for the Pittsburgh Tribune-Review of misquoting her -- though she had in fact used a word that she denied using.   The Kerry campaign and other Democrats have said the paper is biased against the Kerry campaign and the Democratic Party.   It is owned by Richard Mellon Scaife, who has donated millions to conservative causes.   Kerry told reporters Monday that his wife "speaks her mind appropriately."   Senior Kerry adviser Tad Devine said Monday that Heinz Kerry "tells it like it is."   "She is such an enormous asset to our campaign," he said.   Republican National Committee Chairman Ed Gillespie said only, "She is obviously a spirited campaigner."    Heinz Kerry's comment came Sunday after she told a group of voters, "We need to turn back some of the creeping, un-Pennsylvanian and sometimes un-American traits that are coming into some of our politics."   As she was leaving, Colin McNickle, the Tribune-Review's editorial page editor, asked her what she had meant by, in his words, "un-American activity."   According to an exchange posted on the paper's Web site, she denied having said "activity" and also denied saying "un-American."   After stepping away and speaking briefly with Democratic organizers of the event, she returned and asked the reporter whether he worked for the Tribune-Review. He said he did.   "Understandable. You said something I didn't say, now shove it," she told him.   McNickle said Monday that he was "taken aback" by Heinz Kerry's comment.   "The purpose of my question was to get a little clarification on what she meant, to try to elicit an example," he told CNN from the floor of the Democratic convention.   When asked if there should be some kind of apology in the incident, McNickle said, "She's a public figure. I asked a question; she has the right to respond in any way she so desires."   The paper released a statement saying the journalist had done "what any good reporter does -- he asked questions. And the question he posed in this instance was legitimate."   The statement accused Heinz Kerry of "resorting to exactly the type of tactics she was criticizing."   After the incident Sunday, a spokesperson for Heinz Kerry told CNN affiliate WTAE, "This was sheer frustration, aimed at a right-wing rag that has consistently and purposely misrepresented the facts in reporting on Mrs. Kerry and her family."    Asked about the comment Monday, Sen. Hillary Rodham Clinton said she believes that "a lot of Americans will say, 'Good for you -- you go, girl.' And certainly that's how I feel about it."   Devine said Heinz Kerry has been a great campaigner for her husband. "She's someone who connects with voters, who cares deeply about issues. And the fact that she speaks what's on her mind, I think it's enormously refreshing. It's something the American people want to hear more of."   Heinz Kerry will deliver an address at the convention Tuesday night, he said.   "I'm sure the nation wants to hear from her because she can lend so much valuable insight as to who John Kerry is, where he comes from and what he believes," Devine said. ___________________________________________________________________   If she gives insight to who John Kerry is, where he comes from and what he believes, then I am very very scared. "Shove it" "Four more years of hell" What a nice first lady she would make, too bad that won't happen...     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       If you haven't heard a large portion of the people that served with John Kerry in Vietnam do not think that he is fit to be President. They have formed a group called   Swift Boat Veterans For Truth  . They are doing their best to get out what they knew and saw of John Kerry during his service in Vietnam including running   a television ad   and writing a forthcoming book titled "  Unfit For Command  ".      But rather than   answering the shocking alegations of killings and the torching of villiages by their candidate   the Kerry camp is attacking the funding of the group. They have been screaming that the Swift Boat Veterans For Truth is funded by   a wealthy Republican supporter from Texas  .  Oh the humanity!  Of course they forget that their attack dogs, Moveon.org and others who   like to portray President Bush as Hitler   are   supported by a wealthy Democrat supporter, George Soros  .        It's obvious that the Democrats can't take their own medicine so my advice to them since they hitched their cart to someone who wants to use his four months in Vietnam as his campaign cornerstone is to sit down and shut up. If you're going to dish it out you better be prepared to take it. 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink       Democrats and Liberals definition of a war hero: Someone who admits to burning down innocent peoples villages, someone who leaves the battlefield early, someone who is awarded medals, and then disrespects America by throwing the medals away, participates in anti-war protests... That's a great guy your nominating for president.  Also people say President Bush was wrong about going to war with Iraq and also lied to the American people about weapons of MD, yet John Kerry and John Edwards both have been quoted for saying that Saddam needed to be taken out of reign because he was a murderous leader, and the he should be disarmed immediately of all weapons of MD, so why don't liberals say that John Kerry and John Edwards are wrong and are liars? 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's some stupid quotes from John Kerry:  "I'm not proud of these medals.  I'm not proud of what I did to receive them." -John Kerry, who now claims the experience he gained from four months of combat duty in Vietnam qualifies him to be President of the United States.  "I'm a Christian. I've read the Bible and I know you can find the clauses that go both ways (on gay marriage)." He's wrong about two things here, 1. He's not a Christian 2. The Bible is 100% against gay marriage.  Kerry says that we shouldn't depend on gas in the Middle East, yet he is opposed to drilling in Alaska.  "We need to disarm Saddam Hussein." Only smart thing he has ever said in his life. But he now goes against his earlier belief.  Vote Senator Flip-Flop Even Democrats know that John Kerry is a world-class two-faced, flip-flopping dope.
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      www.kerryoniraq.com  Great Site
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                Who do you like in this election?          President George W. Bush         Senator John Kerry         Other          &nbsp;&nbsp;            urlLink  http://www.georgewbush04.blogspot.com/           Comment on your reasons why you think one or the other is better.
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    July 31, 2004 -- SCRANTON, Pa.  John Kerry's heavily hyped cross-country bus tour stumbled out of the blocks yesterday, as a group of Marines publicly dissed the Vietnam War hero in the middle of a crowded restaurant. Kerry was treating running mate Sen. John Edwards and his wife, Elizabeth, to a Wendy's lunch in Newburgh, N.Y., for their 27th wedding anniversary  an Edwards family tradition  when the candidate approached four Marines and asked them questions.  The Marines  two in uniform and two off-duty  were polite but curt while chatting with Kerry, answering most of his questions with a "yes, sir" or "no, sir."  But they turned downright nasty after the Massachusetts senator thanked them "for their service" and left.  "He imposed on us and I disagree with him coming over here shaking our hands," one Marine said, adding, "I'm 100 percent against [him]."  A sergeant with 10 years of service under his belt said, "I speak for all of us. We think that we are doing the right thing in Iraq," before saying he is to be deployed there in a few weeks and is "eager" to go and serve.  The Marines  all of whom serve at nearby Stewart Air Force Base  wouldn't give their names.
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      http://www.swiftvets.com/  John Edwards: "If you have any question about what John Kerry is made of, just spend 3 minutes with the men who served with him."  Al French: "I served with John Kerry."  Bob Elder: "I served with John Kerry."  George Elliott: "John Kerry has not been honest about what happened in Vietnam."  Al French: "He is lying about his record."  Louis Letson: "I know John Kerry is lying about his first Purple Heart because I treated him for that injury."  Van O'Dell: "John Kerry lied to get his bronze star ... I know, I was there, I saw what happened."  Jack Chenoweth: "His account of what happened and what actually happened are the difference between night and day."  Admiral Hoffman: "John Kerry has not been honest."  Adrian Lonsdale: "And he lacks the capacity to lead."  Larry Thurlow: "When the chips were down, you could not count on John Kerry."  Bob Elder: "John Kerry is no war hero."  Grant Hibbard: "He betrayed all his shipmates ... he lied before the Senate."  Shelton White: "John Kerry betrayed the men and women he served with in Vietnam."  Joe Ponder: "He dishonored his country ... he most certainly did."  Bob Hildreth: "I served with John Kerry ...  Bob Hildreth (off-camera): John Kerry cannot be trusted." 
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a picture of Flipper holding a funny sign... urlLink     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     How many people wouldn't want to do that?
    
</post>


</Blog>