<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "Lulu on the bridge" arrived into my hands, finally! I couldn't wait getting it for a few days. I kept asking to a super of my apartment building  if something had arrived for me when I was out. He kept saying nothing has arrived. And he passed me a parcel this afternoon like it occurred to him suddenly. He never appologized and he told me nonchalantly how funny  he forgot to give the parcel to me, which arrived a few days ago. I just thanked to him. What else could I say?  "Lulu on the bridge" was a screenply of a movie with the same title, which was written and directed by Paul Auster. It was starred by Harvey Keitel & Mira Sorvino. Sophie Auster, Paul Auster's daughter seemes to  have starred in this movie too.  I haven't started reading it yet. I should finish "New York Trilogy" first. I like this feeling of the moment when a book wating is for me  to be read, that expectation. I know I won't be disapponted. Whatever was written by Paul Auster never disappoints me.   

						
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   After writing the title I realized that I have only 4 things.  1. Watching "Phantom of the Opera" at Her Majesty's theater London  2. Going on a long journey around America (I want to add "on my own" but it would be terribly dangerous)  3. Traveling Hokkaido, Japan with my "Mr. Right Guy" (It's two times tougher to achieve than to do any other things^^)  4. Going to GLAY's concert (It came to my mind after seeing the video piece yesterday from GLAY's concert when they playing a song named "I'm in love". I wished I were they with other audiences singing along "I'm in love")  Is it just that I'm not greedy? Or Haven't I thought about my life seriously? Why can't I think of any decent, splendid wishes but only those things? Besides I can't even think of 10 things I want to do before I die. What life am I living?!  

						
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   When reading "Locked room" written by Paul Auster yesterday, I met his referring to Marco Polo. It's a trivial mention that was nothing to do with the entire story. What caught me was that he mentioned Marco Polo in his another book. (Believe me, when Paul Auster talks about something in his one book, you can find another mention the same thing in his another book)  Anyway, it was "Moon Palace" that he talked about Marco Polo. I took "Moon Palace" out of the shelf and looked for the part where this name was reffered to.  The name of the protagonist is Marco Stanley Fogg. He used to be teased by his friends due to his unusual name. So his uncle who raised him interpreted his name as good meaning. It was that Marco means Marco Polo, the first European who had traveled China and Stanely stands for Henry Stanley who is a famous explorer of Africa and Fogg is Phileas Fogg in "Around the world in 80 days". Marco Stanley Fogg's uncle finished talking about the name with this remark, "The travel is in your blood" (It's a new good expression I picked up yesterday.)  After reading this part from "Moon palace" I thought about my name. My name means "High cloud". My mom used to told me jokingly that she named after me like that cause she thought this name might bring more chances to fly. You should think that riding on the plane stood for being wealthy in 1970s when I was a baby.  I'm not sure my name brought me any good or any luck. I have flown just 3 times until now. But it's true that I've always wanted to get out of my home country and to go and live somewhere new. Maybe the travel is in my blood too, like Marco Stanley Fogg.  

						
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have a canker sore now. It hurts so much whenever I talk and I eat something. It almost kills me. It was intolerable so I sneaked out from the office and went to a drug store to buy some medicine. This pharmacist seemed to be preoccupied and she started talking on the phone in the middle of the conversation with me. After listening to me, she almost threw a poorly looked ointment onto the desk. I always can't stand a negligent worker at the store. Now I'm under the weather everything drives me crazy.   

						
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     This picture was downloaded from  urlLink http://cafe.daum.net/tonyjjang    Tomorrow is my best friend's birthday. She is far away now so I can't spend her birthday with her this year. So I sent an e-mail wishing her spending a great birthday wherever she is. Since I wanted to give her a very special birthday message, I looked for Leslie Cheung's picture through the internet to attach to this e-mail. (She's such a huge fan of him)  And... Bang! I discovered this picture! Someone from Korean Tony Leung fan club posted this picture, which was from the postcards in DVD of "Buenos Aires Zero Degree". "Buenos Aires Zero Degree" is like a making film of "Happy together". And I suppose that Leslie had his birthday when he was taking this film. So all of staffs might have thrown a birthday party for him. The cake he's holding might have been bought for him.  Anyway... What a luck! It was the best discovery I've ever had when surfing the internet. It's like that Gorgor had his picture taken for me. Wish luck to those who posted this picture!  

						
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     This picture was downloaded from  urlLink www.members.optusnet.com.au/    Erhu is a Chinese musical instrument. I haven't known what this musical instrument is until yesterday. I listened a very oriental music piece named "Silent moon" played by "Jia Peng Fang" last night by chance and it was very mysterious and unique music. So I searched about Erhu through the Internet. "Jia Peng Fang" seems to be a very prominent Erhu player in China. I highly recommend this music, if possible I want to post that music. It's a shame that I don't know how to do it...  

						
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     This picture was downloaded from    urlLink http://www.eastbayvoice.org/movieimages/   One cold day of last November I went to a Chinese shop to buy DVD of this movie even though I was barely familiar with the actors or the director of the movie.  It's not the kind of movie you can get anywhere besides it was too expensive for me, still something in this movie captivated my whole heart, I thought, I couldn't be freed from that feeling until I give a watch to the movie. Since I'd heard about this movie, how this movie is addictive so much, I just wanted to check what in this movie makes people get so absorbed with. And I've had a glimpse of the leading actor, Liu Ye through the internet before seeing the movie, I was totally overwhelmed by his not-that-handsome-face.  After watching this movie I couldn't think of anything but this movie for a while. I wanted to go off early to watch "LAN YU" during that time. This "LAN YU addiction" lasted for a while... Even now, just by listening the theme song of this movie makes me BE in this movie, reminding of the cold street in Beijing. I need some LAN YU from time to time.  Those who you see in this poster now are Handong and Lanyu. And it's the love story of them...  

						
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     This picture was downloaded from  urlLink http://www.moderntimes.com/palace/    This movie was referred to in Paul Auster's "Ghost" of "New York Trilogy" I thought, at first, it is a non-existing movie which Paul Auster had made up. But it was a real movie starred by Robert Mitchum. Paul Auster's detailed description makes me want to see this movie so much. It looks like an old, stylish detective movie.   

						
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     This picture was downloaded from  urlLink www.glay.co.jp    I purchased GLAY's album for the second time on Saturday.. "The Frustrated!" It's the last album they had released and in contains sophisticated and cutting-edge pieces for it's their recent album. This album includes lots of so-called hardcore rock music, which I'm not that familiar with. Even in these hardcore numbers, you can meet the beautiful melodies, which I think the magnificence of their music. Teru's voice is, of course, good and their playing is excellent. But the most distinguished thing about their music is heartbreakingly beautiful melody made by Takuro.  

						
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I've heard that a Korean writer reminisce about her early days when she began to write a story. She used to copy down a prominent senior writer's story on her notebook, and she said that it became a quite good exercise to writing her own stories. And I took the idea from this story, I, myself, began to copy down Paul Auster's story on my notebook. I bought a new, clean notebook and a too much expensive pen for me and started making a handwriting copy of his sentences thoroughly. It is a very fantastic act, it makes me feel like I'm participating in writing these excellent sentences for myself.  By writing down his sentences from page to page onto my notebook I learn how to make a sentence in English. Paul Auster is the best role model when it comes to "Writing English". I started with "New York Trilogy", I'm doing now "Ghost". It takes quite much time to do it, but I believe that I could obtain something when I finish doing it.  

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Of Paul Auster's many books, most protagonists disappear. They desert their family and friends and go somewhere where nobody knows them and start a new life sometimes with a new name.  In "Leviathan" , Sachs disappeared one day and and nobody count reach to him until Peter, who leads the story ran into him accidentally. In "Moon palace",  the old Thomas Effing disappeared when he was young and it was the start of all tragedy. An unknown actor called Hector Mann disappeared into the air, and led a totally different life in "The book of illusions"  Besides them, there are more leading characters who disappear in Paul aster's stories. Some disappeared willingly, others disappeared cause it was the best they could do at that time.  No matter what their reasons of disappearing were, the thing is, THEY LED A QUITE PEACEFUL LIFE AFTER DISAPPEARING, despite of the misery those who were left behind had to suffer from. They might haven't been that happy, but at least they could lead a calm life.  What is necessary to me now is... This "disappearing". I want to go somewhere very far away and spend a new life with a fancy new name. I could disappear without any note and send a postcard to my friends whenever I want to. I could think of nobody but myself. I could get out of this hell...  But I know I wouldn't do that. I couldn't do that. Only those who can't disappear writes this kind of thing.  

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's kind of odd that his offical site has British server instead of American one...   

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written work! I should write a written work of about 6,500 words. The problem is that I have no idea what to do, I haven't even got any topic to write down. It's so stressful, I can't concentrate on anything these days. Almost everything around me annoys me. I want to shout at everybody that "Leave me alone!". But even when everybody really left me alone, nothing comes to my head.  I' m totally lost. I have no idea what the heck to write down. What should I write about?  Reading novels, it might be the only thing that I can't be too satisfied. When I read Paul Auster's "LEVIATHAN", I decided to study English literature, I promised with myself to understand his every word in his stories. I've decided to study English literature...  But I don't have any idea what to do after graduating, even if I'm so lucky that I could pass the graduate school. And I don't have any specific thought of what to or how to study at graduate school. I-just-like-it-so-much-feeling doesn't help at all anyhow.  I think these days are the first time I've ever lost my appetite...   

						
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    The most recent Paul Auster's book that I read. I was quite happy for these days thanks to this book.  In short, it is a too-Paul-Auster. I mean, positively... If you're a fan of Paul Auster you might notice that there are many common things with other his works.   Such as 1. Someone has disappeared AGAIN! (My favorite feature) 2. A story within a story 3. A tiny chance totally changes one's life 4. There is a definite mention of Columbia Univ.'s student (Oh, come on! Can't he just refer to another university? I know, it's from my envy) 5. The protagonist is so much in love with his wife 6. And... Not- happy ending  Despite of these so many common features with his other stories, it was still so unexpected and a page-turner.  I thought seriously why I'm falling in love with his books. Most of his books, the protagonist bumps into the most unexpected thing in the world. Almost that unexpected things are bad things, I mean, really bad things. Every protagonist isn't that rich, they don't have any decent family, job or money. Things are going pretty tough with them. Still they try their utmost to be upright and decent no matter what happens, not because they are strong but because they are bold. In Auster world, fail is the commonest thing. And the protagonists get over that fail with their boldness. That might be the reason why I'm so fascinated by his stories.  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink      

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     urlLink    Before going to Japan, I had much free time to fill in, so did a lot of reading, walking and hanging around alone. One day I went to a public library and lent a book named "Mr. Vertigo". It was the first time that I'd ever met Paul Auster's book. Before that time I didn't even know what kinds of his books are like. My first impression about him was just that
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    There is a GLAY's song named "Winter, again". It is one of my favorite GLAY's song. Takuro, who writes almost every song and also is a leader of this band, told a story about this song in his autobiography.   "She is cursed with asthma. She always takes the very severe medicine due to the asthma attack. No matter how she is careful, she had to spend several months in a year at the hospital. When season changes, the asthma gets worse. Since she was very weak at the cold wind, taking her to Hokkaido to show the snow was absolutely impossible. If did so, it would mean her going to the hospital.  "I want to show you the whiteness of the town where I was born"  that line of this song,"Winter again" was made for this reason. I really wanted to show her the white scenery that I have seen when I was a boy, at any price. Since I knew the dream never comes true, my longing got so intense. She has no idea how I feel about.... "   "Winter again" has this romantic story. He, at last, could show his girlfriend the white scenery of his hometown through the beautiful lyrics. When I read this story, it made me keen to go to Hakodate in Hokkaido. I still dream of going to Hokkaido, someday. When I ever get there, I will be listening this song.  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I discovered this great site where I can hear his real voice. His voice is so warm and intelligent like his book, and so young!  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     This picture was downloaded from  urlLink http://cafe.daum.net/LoveGLAY    I'm so absorbed with their music these days From left, Hisashi(guitar), Takuro(guitar, he writes songs) Teru(vocal), Jiro(bass)  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Hi! I'm so excited to have my blog, finally! I name it after Haruki Murakami's the first novel "Hear the wind sing", paying my homage to him. Well, there are several reasons to make my blog~ First of all, I've always wanted my cyber space to share the trivial things with my friends. Second, I think maybe I can increase my English by writing something everyday. Third, well I' m terribly bored!...  Anyway, I want to meet many friends on this blog. Even though nobody knows about it yet. I think I will be the only one who knows about this blog for a while. It's too early to tell it somebody, I should post something more.  Now I declare that my "Hear The Wind Sing" was born today ! May it last long~  

						
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Welcome to "Hear The Wind Sing"! Your any comment on any topic is much appreciated. There might be lots of mistakes and awkward expression on English, your advice and correction is always welcomed!  

						
</post>


</Blog>