<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Wash - Pearl Jam  Oh please, let it rain today This city is so filthy, like my mind in ways Oh, was a time, like a clean, new taste Smiling eyes before me, inches from my face Wash my love Wash my love, yeah... Sin the sale, buying just a need Just who planted, all the devils seeds And what the truth, and the truth that lies at home It's on the inside, and I can't get it off, yeah... Wash my love Wash my love, yeah... What's clean is pure, but hey, I'm white on the outside, though I stray What she don't know today, might kill us both tomorrow, bring it back someway Bring it back, bring it back, back to the clean form, to the pure form Wash my love  

						
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Excuse me but can I be you for a while My DOG won't bite if you sit real still I got the anti-Christ in the kitchen yellin' at me again Yeah I can hear that Been saved again by the garbage truck I got something to say you know but NOTHING comes Yes I know what you think of me you never shut up Yeah I can hear that But what if I'm a mermaid In these jeans of his with her name still on it Hey but I don't care Cause sometimes I said sometimes I hear my voice and it's been HERE silent all these years So you found a girl who thinks really Deep Thoughts What's so amazing about really Deep Thoughts Boy you best pray that I bleed real soon How's that thought for you My scream got lost in a paper cup You think there's a heaven where some screams have gone I got 25 bucks and a cracker do you think it's enough To get us there But what if I'm a mermaid In these jeans of his with her name still on it Hey but I don't care Cause sometimes I said sometimes I hear my voice and it's been HERE silent all these Years go by will I still be waiting For somebody else to understand Years go by if I'm stripped of my beauty And the orange clouds raining in my head Years go by will I choke on my tears Till finally there is nothing left One more casualty You know we're to EASY easy easy Well I love the way we communicate Your eyes focus on my funny lip shape Let's hear what you think of me now but baby don't look up The sky is falling Your MOTHER shows up in a nasty dress It's your turn now to stand where I stand Everybody lookin' at you here take hold of my hand Yeah I can hear them But what if I'm a mermaid In these jeans of his with her name still on it Hey but I don't care Cause sometimes I said sometimes I hear my voice I hear my voiceI hear my voice And it's been HERE silent all these years I've been here silent all these years Silent all these Silent all these years  

						
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I Hate Capitalism. It turns grown men into children, and lovers into fighters. Capitalism covers us all in a canopy of greed, and turns the land of milk and honey into the pit of greed and money. If capitalism were a giant hippo, it would eat us all, sleep in our beds and make slave labourers of our children. Capitalism hates you, your friends, your families and everything that you believe to be truthful and sincere, and would wear your peeled skin as a fashion accessory. Fuck capitalism, I hate it.  

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    What is Frankie doing todau I wonder?&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    You are the cigarette's prey, THEY ARE THE HUNTER.&nbsp; urlLink    

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I can do this. This is not impossible, and it is not earth-shattering. This is not bad, it is instead, good. I will  feel better  in everyway. I can do this.  Nebulous' Reasons to quit smoking;   g)YOU ARE RESTRICTING THE FLOW OF THE PRANA, YOUR LIFE FORCE.   

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have sat upon the throne, the ruler of my body in the kingdom of my mind. Listening to the orders, fulfilling the decrees, my time goes on and on. There are no citizens, no golden statues, no pomp and circimstance; and the mind gets restless. The orders are not always followed, the decrees become cast aside. While the mind knows that orders are noble, a part feels like doing the opposite; out of resentment, or despiration, or satire, the mind fights itself for change. An overthrough of ideas, an enemy onto itself, a stall in the process, the usurper of the mind.  

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Look at all those fancy clothes, But these could keep us warm just like those. And what about your soul? Is it cold? Is it straight from the mold, and ready to be sold?  And cars and phones and diamond rings,  Bling, bling , because those are only removable things. And what about your mind? Does it shine? Are there things that concern you, more than your time?  Gone, Going, Gone, everything. Gone, don’t give a damn. Gone, be the birds, when they don’t wanna sing. Gone, people, all awkward with their things, Gone.  Look at you, out to make a deal. You try to be appealing, but you lose your appeal. And what about those shoes you’re in today? They’ll do no good, on the bridges you burnt along the way. Are you willing to sell, anything? Gone, with your head. Leave your footprints, And we’ll shame them with our words. Gone, people, all careful and consumed. Gone, gone, gone, everything. Gone, don’t give a damn. Gone, be the birds, when they don’t wanna sing. Gone, people, all awkward with their things, Gone  

						
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    What is it that is being referred to? What is this "it" that I should feel, when I feel like it? To do it well, to get it going, to be in it; to SEE it. Have I seen it? Has it happened already, did I miss it? It may sound strange, but sometimes I think I feel it; like it's all around me. It can be so heavy one day, but it can be so easy the next. Maybe I've become obsessed with it; I do think about it all the time. I wonder if it is my problem or my solution, picking it apart, piece by piece, hoping it will all be OK. Truly, I long to know what "it" is, what it is that is being referred to?   

						
</post>


</Blog>