<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gosh, it's been so fun the past few days shopping for new school clothes and buying books. I feel like the princess that I am. I went out to dinner last night with my honey. I had a blast. I wore my black lace top with my tighter than boa squeeze jeans and heels. The place we went to was fab, in fact, everything was fabby-fab. Today I slept in until noon.  Of course, it is just the calm before the storm because classes begin on Monday. I wish someone else could just sit in for me, take my tests and do all my homework. Sigh. Such is my stuggle. 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I am working out in the gym on campus today. Two totally old, totally not rich-to-make-up for-their-oldness, men want to get their game on with me. Liver spots are okay if you accesorize them with a fat, fat wallet. Like I am going to hook up with some prof on a 45,000 to 70,000 dollar a year job, in Kentucky no less.  In my opinion, the best these old boys can hope for is a blow for a good grade... eeeyuck!   
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I am getting started on my reviews of the LSAT.  It's an inspirational/loathing thought to me that someone like the  urlLink "Kentucky Hammer,"  or the woman who turns into a tiger, were able take the LSAT, get into law school, graduate, and pass the bar, truly.  Ah yes, the good ole U.S. of A., where one can be an ass of a human being and still wang out a living. Anywhere else, the KY Hammer or the  urlLink grrrrl tigerlawyer  would have either died at birth or been prepared as mystery meat... but not so here in the States.  See why I am so frustrated with the interception of my royal life?   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So do you think you may have been switched at birth? Think you may be a princess, but somehow were denied your birthright? Well, you don't have to be a  urlLink little girl  to have your suspicions. This  urlLink kinda stuff  happens A lot. 
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.aardman.com/chickenrun   Ginger is probably royalty as well, although her accent is a bit rough. In any other form, Mel just sucks, but as a claymation chicken, he's do-able... Mel is not royalty, no matter how hard he thumps on Jews. 
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As you know, I come from royalty, but I am living out what began as a huge mix-up from the very moment I slipped out of the birth canal.  If you saw me with the rest of my family you would say, "There is no-way those people who claim to be her family and Meryl are swimming in the same gene pool." The thing is we don't even speak the same genetic code.  This is how it happened; Some overworked, crackhead nurse fucked up and put me in the wrong baby holding tank, then took me to the very wrong mother.  Let me tell you, it isn't easy having royal blood flow through you veins while you are living on a used shoe string. Sigh... champagne on a 40 budget. Paris Hilton/ Simple Life  my ass!   
    
</post>


</Blog>