<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm so tired already lohz... now writingt at 11.56. jux finished my stupid bio revision. I wanna start earlier but  due to unforseen circumstances like STOMACHACHE ! i cannot do it earlier. hmm... many things happen in sch, dun wanna tok about it. oh yes, i've watched singapore idol... so... kinda wierd to see that (wad'z his name)? er..   david sth to go to top 30. yucks man...     in the auditions for singapore idol, he shouted that mediacorp has no $ to pay wadsoeva.. but now, he is in top 30! can't u believe it? after scolding mediacorp. they let him be the top 30. hmm.. this is so crazy. i think he will not last long in the competition.. he looks so... crazy ah nvm about tat,  i did the long and lengthy geography work.. hate that.. if there is no homework for geo, i can do my bio revision peacefully.. yea? okok... nth much.. today i skank myself in the morning.. sitting there waiting for jane then all of a sudden i remembered that i 4gt to bring my file.  ( THE FILE IS my LIFE... ALL THE WS IS INSIDE)  then i rushed up like dog to get it, panting so hard, she called me then i said give me 2 mins.. then i run down like panting dogs and cats.. wadeva.. got into the car, said sorry and she laughed.. saying so funny.. haha, then i said maybe the hungry ghost came to hynotise me.. haha! but really, these days, there is an increase of accidents and wad so eva.  Drive safely, play safely. . ok.. Ciao. Getting late now!  
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
          Holly yea..  Today is a very tiring day… when I woke up, I felt a burden on me, so tired! After that, I watched LOTR , the return of the king dvd. So cool man! Chatted with diyana for awhile, oh yea, my new friend (known frm cassendra’s bdae party yesterday) then…i slept all the way in the afternoon. I’m beginning to feel that I’m a pig. There I go, lazing all around again. I think there is the weird sickness in me, the overload homework nausea. I think my body dun work and react to all this homework anymore! I  can’t believe it, where is my motivation and strength? Y I become so weak?  Ah nvm… when I fail any sub, maybe my motivation may… may only come back? Oops! Writing a blog is  my motivation to do well in English, I guess… to go mass com mahz.. =P after sleeping, me and my family went to Thomson plaza to return all the dvds. Oh yea folks!  Video Ezy is much better than laser flair to borrow dvds or vcds! It is much cheaper and affordable! $5 for a dvd and for a week! Can’t u believe it? In laser flair, a dvd rental cost $4 but for 2 days…  it sucks man.. oh yea, I’m beginning to like fantasia new single, Chain of fools. This is the meaningful song I’ve eva heard! Cool man.. Influenced by Singapore idol.. haha! It’s awesome yar! Go pple! Go and d/l  chain of fools by fantasia barrino!  Not the other singers… all sulky.. haha Ok, me gtg… go and do physics hw liao… Zai Jian.. ciao  
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         whao, today i can't write much because tml there is a ss test. i haven got to study yet.. silly of me. i'm kinda tired and lazy these days.. i dunnoe why. oh yea, today reading period was very fun! izwan, maslyn, pei shan and me chatted a lot.        today was mr mak's birthday, i didn't noe about it until when they sang the birthday song, i tagged along and realised that it was his birthday! but i guess.. hmm, today is rather a weird day to have a birthday on.         shan't say much today. all the best for tml folks.  
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Well! Today is my first day that I’m writing a blog! Whao! After tedious work on the website, I finally got the time to write a blog. This week is rather a tiring day. Doing the greeny paper thingy and loads of homework piling up, making me so stressed up. Actually, I think that with more work, I tend to get lazier. I dunnoe, this is like human instinct I guess. Oh yes, today was a rather nerve-wrecking day! Today is the announcement of the Chinese o level results! I can’t believe it, as I did the paper 2 months ago. Oh no, I had the weird feeling that I would fail my chi paper. Alamak! Cold sweat ran down my spine and I felt very uneasy..  Oh gosh, this was rather bad. But fortunately, I manage to pass and scrape through the exams. So, in conclusion, I can at least go to a JC. But I thought of it for a every long time, I guess I may go into a poly. I don’t want to stress myself into a JC. Look guys or gals, u see, if I studied so hard, everyday crawling out from home to school to study like a freak, would I be happy? Oh yes, my marks will be pretty well off but think long- term, I wouldn’t be happy in the long run because I have another obstacle for me! The JC fever… what a hellish place to be, I think. After hearing people in JC saying that they are stressed up, not sexed up... haha, I think JC is not suitable for me. Instead, I aim to do well off in English to go to Mass Communications. I love it, I hope to me some people in the entertainment industry, esp. being a DJ. Isn’t it fun? Chatting with avid listeners and listen to ur fav songs... aw…. A paradise for me  Ok, shan’t talk more about that. Oh yes, today, the second batch of the oral exams were rather… hmm, tongue tied. The topic is so difficult lohz! Jane told me about it, something like that: What skills should a person acquire to be a leader? Something like that. This is too difficult lohz… except for izwan, I think he’ll do rather well in it because he has many leadership roles. So, in my opinion, I might have some experience in a position of a leader. That’s all for today and thanks for reading. My intention to write a blog is to improve in my writing skills and I dearly hope that I’ll improve one day… Ciao! 
</post>


</Blog>