<Blog>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      will she know ?  beyond her enigmagnetic eyes lies the dark mystic tunnel as deep as the deepest gorge, i feel like a wounded hound sniffing for a trace of myself in the maze called her heart.  searching for the finish line she's running an aching-marathon  spanning the zig-zag curves of my brain those looks i know dont feign I dare not halt this girl for i'll drive myself bonkers !  yearning to feel soul to soul plunging into the vague madness  will die for her, life after life but not look into her, eye to eye to recite my myriad love, until atleast my vault is buried. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'll never do it again  Never in life was I haunted knew no bounds nor any fear so tasty was the sleep until I was driven to pain  the brows kissed each other was that a bow or what ? the eyes so piercing, were the arrows into my heart.  the bliss was short-lived paving way for the eternal. And the worst I confronted was, sitting beside my dream knowing that she's not mine knowing that she'll never be mine !  Graves are for words unsaid and for deeds undone, they say, for i knew not under her sway that I’ll lie in the warm mud Grass roofed on my vault, with those unsaid words and undone deeds.  Never in life was I haunted knew no bounds nor any fear can't taste my sleep now for it knew nothing but pain and I know not, if I'll do it again !!   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Down & Out today                                        Jul 31,14:31  feel like a crumpled paper thoughts blank as the outer space drowning towards an abyss my eyes closed, ears plugged "what is wrong with me?", kurt screams cant take it anymore - she said, yet to recover from the dosage I'm desolated, her eyes staring at me... the mind, ahead of the heart words flew like arrowheads buckled under remorse, in grief who else will I turn to now ? thoughts about sunshine in the hills swimming in the darkness, to the shore my eyes open, ears still plugged "and this is how, you remind me", sings Nickelback. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Enough is Enough.  More than a year in Bhubaneshwar...aaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh !! Thats how it feels...Would like to shout at the top of my voice and run away from here ! The first 7 months just galloped away. Heavily loaded with work and the enthusiasm of being in a new project clubbed with the will to perform, I never knew how time went by. It was just work and nothing but work all those days. Now the last 4 months have been terrible, least did anyone here knew that this was coming, I mean No work was coming ! Its not bench, its floor... Ok..work apart, the discussion here is about the place. This place sucks ! I positively hate the extreme climates here in the summer and the winter (47 c and 8 c). The only solace is the rainy season but it too gets on to the nerves when it doesnt stop raining for almost 3 or 4 consecutive days ! Now its the rainy season, and guess what ? It has been raining cats and dogs for the past 3 days. The biggest problem in this season is the fungus which leaves no things to chance ! Leave the washed clothes alone, they even catch hold on to the chappals ! As for the climate, thats it. Lastly it would be injustice if I dont say anything positive abt the climate...The months of December - February are great here.,If you dont need anything else but the climate !  And now lets shift our focus to the most important issue since the day I landed in this deep shit !! FOOD !! Being a S.Indian, I first thought it was going to be difficult to chew up rotis everyday. I had been in Jalandhar for 3 months before, and I knew I can adjust. But the worse was yet to happen ! And my taste buds have disappeared and my appetite for food is down in the dumps ! And know what ? You cant get good food even at nominal rates, forget cheap rates ! All my friends here belong to different places. Jamshedpur, Aurangabad, Patna, Calcutta, Hyderabad, Chennai, You name it...But there isn't one who is happy over the food they eat ! The canteen in our office...Oh..please..dont ask. One word - Pathetic !! And all the restaurants have this common pattern of preparing food carelessly ! Complain, and you get a wry smile, the very thought of it makes me wild. I have lost count of the number of times I shouted at the waiters, chefs, managers ... the list is on. Once I decided to stop complaining...but that was betrayal. I was betraying my tongue and my patience levels were actually decreasing ! And the service? Actually guys...am losing patience now. You give an order, he brings something else, not on time. Wait...,you think am going too much on this. You know how a chopsey is served ? The noodle and the mix is brought separately and its for you to mix yourself ! Well, its very simple. Am not happy with the food I get for what I pay ! Hmm..There's no stopping them and there's no stopping me. There was only one solution which I dont see in the near future. We'll come to solutions later !  Now the people ! Have you ever been to Goa ? People are lazy there for a reason. They drink and live happily ever after...Lazing around throughout the year. But I dont find a reason for the slow life people lead here. Early to bed and late to rise. All shops close by 9pm. They open at 10am. And there's a break for lunch from 1-4pm. I really wonder when they make business ! And most of the thurdays and all sundays, they remain closed. Whaaaaaaaaat ?? I know for sure that this city (forgive me for calling this village, a city) has a lot of unemployed. It can be seen from the number of petty shops all over the place. But when will the situation change ? One reason I would like to attribute to this unemployment is the number of people migrating from villages to this big village, not knowing whats in store for them.,that this place is already struggling for creating opportunities. Another reason could be the climate !! Whatever it is, the people are slow and that is ridiculous. The upper class is not the face of Bhubaneshwar. This place needs a lot of investment to grow. But who is investing ? Whats so special about this place which is not about others ? Call this a "Temple City", So ? I dont see a reason ! And Even if it evolves into a city, the Slowness will always be there. Because it is an inherent characteristic of all the people here !  What else man? What else do u need to know about this place ? Aah..yes, I was talking about solutions. There is only one solution - I go away ! SIMPLE isn't it ?  The time is not far away, when I'll be out of here, out of my frustration which comes with bearing with this place.   Enough is Enough.    
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This was a reply to Amir, my colleague. Heard about "an eye for an eye" ! This one is a "Poem for a Poem". Enjoy !!   Sliver  nowhere to run, nowhere to hide i want to be alone, stay out of sight losing every battle, i tried can't take it anymore,i just can't fight forgive me all,i apologize i'm not good, i'm not ur type tears is all i have, i can't smile pain is all i feel, i don't lie kill me, i just want to die  - Amir.   Mirror Image  the whole world to run, why should you hide  you are never alone, and always in sight battlefields change, battles don't, how much ever u try, will have to fight till the end, (u can't take it anymore only after ur end) apologies accepted for ur innocence, good and bad, its all hype what r friends for, to put a smile where tears are share ur pain with us, i too don't lie, what do we do without u, if u die ?  - redi. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Its been more than a year since I have started to write poems...or rather some songs ! Its only after coming to bhubaneshwar that i was prompted by my friend Amir to write ! It all started when he mailed us all a poem and it was great. It really prompted me write one too...And off the journey started with my first one - "Raman Effect". There was nothing in it at all.,I didnt know what to write..,but I was happy to have discovered another facet of my skills ! From thereon there were poems on my code, bugs, Love, the daily routine, a Bitch and so on...  All the poems reflect my different moods, on different things and persons. Some poems came rightaway with a lot of anger or pain, some took a longer time to complete ! Only a few of my friends have read my poems, some appreciated, some were annoyed ! But one thing that I know for sure is, I am not going to stop writing...because I have to express myself and I find this as a way to do that !!  This one below is one of first and one of my favourite !  I hope you enjoy it. While I'll be back with some more after sometime !!   The Wink     i hear colours and see her voice for my heart blindfolded the mind i felt the staccato movement in me everytime those eyes made a wink...  pretense.,it certainly wasn't. those 10-metre-apart looks incited the already-hyper cells everytime those eyes made a wink...  interpret.,i did. so did everyone. she knew that i knew that she knew. paranoia, as i said, prevails... as i never wanted to hear her say what her eyes did not convey. but the eyes...had the same wink.  ofcourse.,i knew it was all over but my sorrow waited to take form and persisted to keep me awake until i told her what i read everytime those eyes made a wink...  the days are still haunting for i deceived my own self but, did i ? as my beat doubles and so does my distrust on those eyes which made a wink...  vkredi. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A few lines on my memories of stage performances in my college years. Its been more than 3 years since I passed out of CIT, but the music played in the background of our adapt themes are still fresh...  Bits of music - A page from the past  didnt crave for that applause for the first time on stage dont feel like going back and give the opposition an upstage. never knew its addiction for the music still haunts me with expressions unlimited... we held a thousand-crowd in awe laurels poured in, flawless they said overjoyed, team effort we said.  compiling our bits of euphony sessions of rehearsals overnight fun, frolic, imaginations thrusted, our themes, destined for success we were monkeys, we were buildings, the villians and the riots, the God and a sage was fruad, laughter, agony, anger &amp; sorrow, spirited and caught the unawares the acts never will repeat neither in our minds nor our hearts for memories would die with us ! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>