<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    she/he?? won gold for russia&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Germanys effort could only get a silver&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    its it a man or woman who knows?&nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      sorry guys i havn't written in ages, Cory thanks for your comments, i welcome any feed back, (i'll email you persnally mate!!) we have had a break from college this week, we will be starting a new term on monday which is exciting but scary to think that 7 months has gone past so quick. I have grown so much and need to evaluate where God has been taking me and set new targets for the final term and onto second year!! me and the boys had a bit of fun watching the womans shot put last night, we just couldn't figue out though some of these girls just looked to masculine, it was almost enough to give us night mares what do you think??    german pic  18/08/2004 © GETTY IMAGES/Scott Barbour hands up pic 18/08/2004 © GETTY IMAGES\Michael Steele russian 18/08/2004 © GETTY IMAGES/Scott Barbour
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ok so here goes with my first diary post... it is now Tuesday the 10th of August, for me, my weekends rollover onto Monday, becasue Monday is the church and college day off which is cool. On Saturday, I helped out as I do every Saturday with kids church, I am working with the 5 year olds right up to the 10 year olds and for safe guarding laws I can't and shall never go into much detail about what goes on. But to say that saturday for kids is like a kids service, we have worship, and games and a drama and a message. With kids you have to know that there attenion span is very short so you have to be quick and to the point. After kids church I watched the rugby with some of the guys from church, they had a big screen set up at the church.  Sunday was also cool, we had Impact 68 which see's our young people come out of the service and chill out and play pool and table tennis and x box, Ben our pastor gave a youth talk which was awesome. Phil Baker spoke in the service (I served at one and attended the other) about finding Nemo and lessons we learn from the film it was amazing, because he likened movies to parables, which is true. In the evening  church was cool but I was really tired, I went home and set up for the party, we had a party for two college students who are moving out to the hills campus which was sad but happy too.  Yestoday (Monday) was cool I just chiilled, then went into town (CBD) I got a couple of books on Churchill, I love his leadership style and as I'm training to be a leader I wanted to look at different leadership styles, on I really love was called: 'Hitler, Churchill, Leadership lessons' it's fascinating because it goes on the bbc series about the two leaders, it does not comment on whether or not these were good or bad men (for we all know the answer to that). But simply looks at their leadership styles.What books are you reading right now? I would love to know. I went on to my homework supervision class, with my good friends Tony and Nas, they are like second parents and close friends whose kids I help with homework, this was fun. I enjoyed helping the kids and enjoy seeing them discover the revelation of how to answer a simple maths question or how to write a letter (which can be quite trying for a 6 year old) any way I hope I haven't been too long winded but I hope you guys continue to pray for me a God (and others trains me in leadership ready to serve His almighty purpose) much love and blessings Nat 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink     &nbsp; urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sunday 8th August Hi everyone my name is Nathaniel Fisher an englishman in Sydney. i am currently studying the youth and pastoral leadership programme at Hillsong collge until 2006. i was at church this morning and heard Phil Baker talk about his blog so i thought what a good idea for all my mates back in the UK (and everywhere else!!) to read about the mazing things God is doing in my life.  the story so far..... I followed my call to study at college here in Sydney Auz, I am now two terms through my first year with one remaining. I am activly involved with both the childrens ministry and 68 the junior high school programme. we are seeing tremendous blessing, and I seen God strech me and shape me so much that if i went home now I don`t think people wuld see the same person!!  anyway this is meant to be a short introduction, hopefully I can encourage you to keep on going in the faith and believing Jesus. if you don´t know Jesus why not ask him into your life, all you have to do is follow this link  urlLink http://www.ccci.org/wij/index.html   anyway my aim is to be able to add a diary of how God is changing my life on a daily basis. please come back for more......  bye and God bless  
     
    
</post>


</Blog>