<Blog>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                                            C  o  l  o  u  r   Me   GoO  d...          Are u feeling  blue ?Or maybe you're seeing  red ?Or are you just  green  with envy?Understand colours and take control of your life.Teenage August 2004 issue(5566& K-one),Health Bits paints you a clearer picture.         We are always surrounded by colours.From the clothes we wear to the walls we paint.But what most of us don't know is how easily we are affected by these colours.Our emotions and physical state are strongly influenced by the colours that surround us.   It's already been scientifically proven that our physicological functions are related to specific colours.Why do you think hospitals are painted in calming earth tones,or fast food restuarants are bathed in red and oranges hues?   They each have different effects on the human body...      How does colour therapy work?   So,how exactly can colour help in our everyday lives?   Here's a list of the common colours we encounter and how we can apply it to our own well-being   - Red    - Orange    - Yellow    - Green    - Violet    - Black    - White    - Blue              Red     ------     When we think of red,the words that come to mind are love,passion and even anger.Physically,red is energising and revitalising,helping to stimulate the brainwaves,heart rates and blood pressure..It is also the colour of love.          If you're feeling tired and lethargic,red is the perfect colour to concentrate on.However,too much of this colour may make you irritable and impatient.      
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Haha..Heya!Common test has finally ended which means i get to use the Com everyday frm on now till my end-of-year exams!so hapi!!!yeah!!(Ps:me sort of "crazy" lately..)*sigh* i just hope i will do well for my common test.Me now using the skool Com.Now having IT lesson.Just hope tt Mr Shi(IT teacher lah!)wun turn the internet connetcion plug off...*keep my fingers cross* This few days,i dun hv much to blog abt.Evitime i will see 'Him' lei..His lyk everywhere lor.Mic sae tt it is "Fate".When i go to KFC,i'll also see 'Him' der..Life's been so sianz for me lately...Corn doesn wana help wif the Bread Stall.Me startin to lose interest in the Stall too.Wad to do?Help me!!!   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I know i didn blog for days.Cuz i couldn't get into my blogspot account then...Anw,i dun think i can blog daily during this whole week,as i will be havin my Common Test.*sigh*Today,school ended early.Instead of 2.45pm it changed to 1.35pm..Missed 2 periods.(Weekly assembly)Nel,Gie,07,Hui Shan and me went to KFC today...I saw 'Him' there too..07 commented that his ear-hole is too big!!!haha...Ltr we went home..Now shop.Luckily,we didn see any mad/strange/werid lookin man around!!!(Mad-Man!!!)I guess,that's all for today!Cyaz!=)    
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hi,today i blog late cuz i was so tired tt i dozed off.Anw,today i saw 'Him' again.During reccess,Me,kailin,Mic,Gie & siowting went to staff room to find Mdm Ngo to pass her the list of bread we are making(31st Aug Event).While we walking down the spiral staircase,Mic asked me to look down..I looked down and saw him..surprisinly,as if he knew I was watchin him,he looked up too..*smiles*Mic sae he got suspended cuz he brought his bag along wif him and recess was almost over..[He is the pai kia sort..but v quiet]=)Haiz..I didn get to see 'Him' nowadays.Recess...Lunch...After School...=( This makes me think of another quote...Look below ltr.;)  Today went to CP(compass point),saw a mad man.Mag so scared,nearly cried.The man is sick!Go and rub his...on the glass panel!I was so scared and shocked..Then he acted as if he wanted to chase us,luckily we ran!!!=) I dun think i hv anymore to write lor..haha..=) Now listenin to Jay and JJ's songs..Qi Li Xiang,Jie Kou,Dou Jiang You Tiao,Ju Li..So nice!!!=) My bro so gd,he got alot of of songs from his frens then store in one folder so i everytime can listen.=)   Quote Of The Day: "Cherish Yr loved Ones"    
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hi,actually,i dun feel lyk blogging.Cuz today,nth much to say lah..Sg idol ytd was so-so only.Not so funny then monday's.But,it was touching and inspiring.The deaf gerl and the speech problem guy were brave to even audition for Sg idol.When they wanna do something,nothing can stop them.Even if they fail,its alrite...Can still try again at least,u get a chance.Better then some who wanna audition but dun dare(scared lose face mahz)...Hmm...it makes me think of a Quote...Look at the bottom of this blog ltr.   Today,Nel,07,Gie,Mic,Shan,YJ& me went to OP @ CP(compass point).Nel bought a shirt for her "Kor"(i'm her Jie,until nw still haven rcv any present frm her,except b'day..=( haha...jk,jk...).Her budget was only $19.00 but we selceted a $26.00 shirt.When we were told of the price by the cashier it was so pai-seh!!!Haha..so many ppl looking.Then Nel blamed me and YJ(cuz we were the ones who select tt piece)!Ltr went to Mc's and Comics Connection..At 4.00pm we went home..=) Continue bloggin tml!Buaix...=)   Quote Of The Day: Dun let anything stand in the way of yr dreams.;)    
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hi again...I'm bored,so i decided to blog again.=)*sigh*I can't bear to see my blogspot in such a state(plain,no tagboard..etc..etc..)!!!u noe..I feel so "small"cuz evione hu has blogspot has done it up so nicely.While my is....forget it!!I just dun feel proud of my own web..It sucks,totally.But anw,Danni has agreed to help me insert the templates,tagboard..etc..etc.. must realli tk her!She's gr8!lolx..today,didn't hang out wif my frens afta skool.Instead,Gie accompanied me home.nw me tokin to Nel on MSN.below my hse,Holy' boys playing bball.Haiz..Holy' bball damn sucky lei.Tt time my skool(NCHS)thrashed Holy' C gerls 40-13.See?haha...today no HomeWork..Done the Journal already...only left wif 2 articles..Tml den do lah,no hurry..(Me Eng pro wad..Haha.jkjk.One muz not be too full of themselves)Now earnin neopoints.If anyone of u hu play neopets,here's my user:Blue_Chill_5.  Can't wait till 31st Aug,1C will be settin up a bread stall!Our stall name will be name"Bread CraZe".But some of 1C bois & gerls lyk sianz,sianz..Dunwan help out.Only a few are so excited abt tt upcomin event.On 30th Aug, Nel,Mic,Gie,07&amp; Corn will be cumin to me hse to prepare the bread..U noe,i hope 30th Aug will arrive soon!Time pass so slow..*sigh*Can hardly contain my excitement!!!Today saw "Him",eating Chicken Rice..=)During Lunch period,Mr Fabian Lim shouted at a boi.Usually,Mr Lim not so fierce always joke wif us.wad i had seen today,has realli startled me..=S    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        If there is something tt I feel strongly abt,I like to tell people wad I think.Every so often when I'm bored I will post my opinions on things up here for u to read.I understand tt since these are opinions,not everybody shares the same belief that I do and tt's perfectly fine.I'm not tryin to convince anybody of anything;I'm telling u how I feel and mayb giving u a different perspective on an issue.If I convince somebody in the process then that's great,but tt's not my ultimate goal here.Another thing is tt I love writing!=)I usually can't focus on writing long stories since I get bored of those very easily,but these little articles are perfect and I enjoy putting my thoughts on paper...well...rather,on this web. =P  Even tho two people can have different opinions on a subject does not mean tt these people hv to be enemies or start insulting each other or bashing their sites.I'm not going to think badly of u if u happen to think that playing neopets is childish.There are still 50year-olds playin and i won't hide the fact tt i do too.We can agree to disagree and it doesn't have to go any farther than tt.I'm not going to mention u,make any reference to yr site(if u have one),tell people how wrong u are,or things like tt becuz tt just makes people look immature.I mean seriously people,dun u hv enough drama in yr own life?Do u really hv to bring it into the internet?"Lyk omg u guys!Sum1 wrote a article about how they think ppl who plays neopets are childish."Well,they are so wrong and tt is so DUMB!!!!I get really tired of reading tt kind of thing on forums.Can't we all just get along?I'm not e-mailing u with my opinions or doing something else tt would make u feel compelled to read what I think,so u should do the same for me.  So let's all respect other peoples' opinions and just get along.I know that's not going to happen,but at least I tried...    
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink    
     
    
</post>


</Blog>