<Blog>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Today hasn't been too bad.  Overslept and took James to school; got Mickey D's for breakfast on the way back.  Got at least one of my songs DLed last night.  (St. Theresa by Joan Osbourne)  Still waiting on "Allison Hell" by Annihilator, "Is This Love" by Survivor, and "Torture" by the Jacksons (80s Jacksons, not the 50s-60s incarnation).          Need to answer some replies in my LiveJournal.     
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        While I love thunderstorms, I prefer the thunder and lightning over the rain.  Today is no exception.  This morning, I woke up to elephants in the room above us doing the macarena.  Don't know if it was James rocking back and forth in his bed and making it hit the wall or if Nadia was jumping off the furniture again, but it was loud and they were awake.            So, I get up. I get them up. I get breakfast and their milk and chase a boy armed with a lid and a pop tart down to get him dressed for school.  After spending nearly five minutes just trying to find his shoes, he's finally dressed and ready.  I stick 4 diapers in his bag and we go outside to wait for the bus.          Now, I swear that when we got out there, it wasn't raining much; just a slight drizzle.  Well, we're waiting...and waiting...and waiting. Still no bus.  So, I carry a kicking and screaming (and slightly soggy) boy to the porch.  Nadia is standing on the steps in nothing but her pull-up, playing in the rain.  (Another cold in the works, I think to myself.)  James proceeds to bang his head on the porch and then on the door. When told to stop, he screeches.  I think I hear the bus, so I carry him to the end of the driveway. No bus. Again.  He squirms out of my arms, so I put him on the ground. When I try to get his hand to go back to the porch, he fights for all he's worth. By this point, we're both soaking wet to the bone, so I say "screw it" and we stand in the damn rain until the bus gets there: 5 minutes later.          EQ still won't load on my comp.  I was pissed last night; looking at porn didn't even help.  Hell, my HD could use a good wipe. So, whenever we can afford it, I'm going to get another copy of XP Home and re-install Windows altogether.   
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Ever had one of those days where you were bored out of your skull and, despite the fact that there was alot you *could* do, nothing appealed to you?  Today is one of those days for me.  I want to write, but when I sit down, nothing comes out. (Nevermind the fact that I have ideas and rewrites that need to be done.)  I need to work on the guild's website, but I don't feel like it.  I don't want to go take a nap.  The internet bores the hell out of me unless I'm checking message boards (which I've done several times already today) or porn-hunting (which I did this morning).  I guess I'm just going to have to accept the fact that this is one of those lazy days, no matter how much I hate it or how restless I am.   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I hate website updating.  Actually, it's more like a total revamp.  It needed to be done, but DAMN, it's a major pain in the ass.  Dark Writer is going through a major overhaul right now.  So far, I've redone the index page, the bio page, the stories page, and added a music links page.  Still haven't done the actual links page, and I plan on redoing the pics page(s).  I'm going to add pics other than just mine.  (I need to take new pics anyway.)          Well, back to work. :P   
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I hate technology. Yet, as Lace said, I make such good use of it. *sighs*  Watching Women's Olympic Volleyball now. It's Germany vs. Cuba. No clue who's leading; commercial is on at the moment. Last night's Opening Ceremonies were incredible! They did a great job on the costumes and makeup. UPDATE: Germany leading - 16 to 8.  I may not actually transfer my LJ stuff here. I may keep it for my writing (which is where I usually turn to purge my brain when I'm fresh out of story ideas or when I've hit a dry spot in a story). I'll save this blog for everything else (including my rants).  Well, I have some work to do, so I will probably post more later.    
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Our roommate uses blogspot, and after looking at her blogs, I figured I'd check it out for myself.  So far, I'm liking it.  I usually rely on livejournal, but I like blogspot better...so I might be transferring posts to here...at some point.          Will write more later when time (and babies) permit.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>