<Blog>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      轨迹　 周杰伦  怎么隐藏　我的悲伤　失去妳的地方 妳的发香　散的匆忙　我已经跟不上  闭上眼睛　还能看见　你离去的痕跡 在月光下　一直找寻　那想念的身影  如果说分手　是苦痛　的起点 那在终点之前　我愿意再爱一遍 想要对妳说的　不敢说的爱 会不会有人可以明白  我会发着呆　然后忘记你　接着紧紧闭上眼 想着那一天　会有人代替　让我不再想念你 我会发着呆　然后微微笑　接着紧紧闭上眼 又想那一年　妳温柔的脸　在我忘记之前  心理的眼泪　模糊了视线　你会看不见   
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1. what are you doing now?---> doin this shit n listenin 2 songgies 2. what were you doing before this?---> watchin the Athens ! 3. what are you thinking now? ---> whether wanna out later 4. what time is it?---> 1pm 5. what time did you sleep last night? ---> 1am 6. what did you do last night? ---> watched the Athens .. 7. what did you last say to a friend last night? ---> bye 8. what attracts you to the opposite sex?---> sense of humour and overall character 9. what makes you happy? ---> when i see both of you.. playin games.. when i've lotsa money 2 spend.. 10. what are you wearing right now? ---> black tee n short 11. what will you do after answering this? ---> watched Athens la.. or gamin or out 12. who was the last person you talked to?---> bro 13. what do you want to tell someone but you didn't get to tell?---> i like you. 14. when is your birthday?---> 04 feB 88 15. when is your bf/gf's birthday? ---> im single 16. when did you last cry?---> i dont rem such thing 17. when did you last smile?---> just now 18. why did you answer this?---> boliaoness 19. when will you marry? ---> ??? 20. when did you last receive a gift?---> cant rem 21. when did you last drink alcoholic beverages?---> 4gotten 22. Who give u this survey?---> hmm.. 23. who was the last person you talked w/ yesterday?---> js 24. who makes you happy?---> jokers lor 25. who is your enemy?---> the Diablos.. Yakuzas.. Yardies.. lol 26. who has the qualities you like in a guy/girl? ---> .... 27. who do you hate most among your friends? ---> no1 28. who's your closest among the females? ----> lawyer 29. who has the cutest smile you've ever seen?---> jingle bell and chaota 30. who do you talk on d phone with often?---> xy lor.. she always call me.. and oso js 31. do you belong to a team in your school?---> nope 32. how's school?---> okie la.. 33. any regrets?---> yes. 34. do you smoke? drink?---> no and seldom 35. are you a workaholic?---> used to.. now no.. slackin.. 36. do you have someone in mind that you want to marry?---> no 37. do you like swimming?---> used 2.. nw nv swim 38. do you wear eye contacts?---> ya 40. do you kiss your parents good night? ---> nv b4 and nv will 41. does your crush often send you messages in friendster?---> ple mei you friendster.. and mei you online.. mei you use computer.. 42. how about in e-mail?---> no 43. how often do you use the internet? ---> almost every day 44. how is your hair styled right now?---> veri messy .. but i think look nt bad .. 45. how is your feeling right now?---> nt bad =D 46. how is the weather?---> dont know 47. how will you treat your loved one?---> the way i treat my teddy 
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thursdae .  Nth much happenin 2dae . .  Er, today was xtremely damn tirin . .  Slept durin the tp lesson . .  Hmm, den today i reached home at ard 2.30 pm . .  Coz there was no maths remedial lesson . . Moreover I've tuition at 6 plus and hence i gotta be back hm early and prepare 4 Maths qns so as 2 ask the teach to prevent wastin time . .  Alrite so i took a nap at 4 plus . . Woke up at 6.25pm . . ! While i was waitin 4 his arrival, he called me and said that he thought he could nt make it on time and therefore the lesson was called off and i was screamin happily 2 my mum telling her bout the 'gd news' . . Lol . . Nt dat i was lazy . . It war juz dat i was v tired juz now and i did nt feel like havin any lesson and i was nt prepared and i wanna slp . . 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thursdae .  Nth much happenin 2dae . .  Er, today was xtremely damn tirin . .  Slept durin the tp lesson . .  Hmm, den today i reached home at ard 2.30 pm . .  Coz there was no maths remedial lesson . . Moreover I've tuition at 6 plus and hence i gotta be back hm early and prepare 4 Maths qns so as 2 ask the teach to prevent wastin time . .  Alrite so i took a nap at 4 plus . . Woke up at 6.25pm . . ! While i was waitin 4 his arrival, he called me and said that he thought he could nt make it on time and therefore the lesson was called off and i was screamin happily 2 my mum telling her bout the 'gd news' . . Lol . . Nt dat i was lazy . . It war juz dat i was v tired juz now and i did nt feel like havin any lesson and i was nt prepared and i wanna slp . . 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wednesday.  2day, lessons damn sians. had fourrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr 44444444444444444444444444444 period of Engerlish. 4. coz no more chn lessons and da 2 period of chn lessons ch to ENG.   v frustrating .  Anyway, after sch, went 2 teach Maths . LOLs . Js wanted me 2 teach her Sci, but I sucks in that. So change to Maths. Nv know she brought another 2 frends.. which were Lindy and xiaomei.. So I taught them Maths.. chap on Trigo.. Pythagoras.. and stuffs..  Lindy was damn funni larz.. the trigo.. she asked wads dat.. bla bla.. lol.. i talked a sentence she asked one qn.. 'she mer lai de.. ?!'  haha.. then ....... she was there copying hw and stuffs.. then still dare 2 say she cheated during geo test.. hah.. oh ya she said i can be a tutor.. LOLs.. hai ple fail den have.. then oso helped js do some wk.. lau eh, she know liao still ask me how 2 do.. then still dare 2 tell me she pian wo.. ! haha..  then duno wad time, then we went..     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today. Monday. Tired.  Woke up at ard 6.05am. Then fell 2 slp again. Then woke at 6.25am. Lied on bed till 6.30am. Msg chaota. Talked abt the HT paper. Hmm.. till 6.40am. Veri tiring.  Today.. stayed back for xtended lessons. While waiting for the time to arrive, I juz stayed in cls and do nth.. sms.. and then went 2 find Js n talk.. Played a little bball with her.. hmm, oh ya, my foot injury, duno what hapened.. I can't jump lor, maybe juz a little only.. if nt the wound below the foot gettin worst. Duno why the hack become like this.. It was liked 'split' lorz. And i mean it Splits. the pain is.... ahem.. u know.. Okie then sumtimes when I'm walkin.. yup.. juz do some normal walkin.. then the wound will oso hurt like duno wad. So sumtimes when I walk Im a little bai kar.  Okie, so played until ard 6.15am or wad.. go cls tk bag.. den proceeded 2 canteen.. lessons started.  Then Van bought the Mac 4 me.. okie i was there eating like nobody's biz.. sat there ate n ate.. doin nth.. then crap.. lame ard.. with van.. tkk.. kkk.. xy.. they all.. lols.. v idiotic..  then i do some binomial.. coz i nv brought my bk down.. hmm.. then ard 8.30pm i left..   Okie therefore when i was home i was here.. Hmm, actually 2 day plannin 2 buy Tamagotchi .. but nv went out .. 30 bucks .. hmm .. maybe tml.. or the day after.. and gonna get a GBA SP .. shiok .. it'll accompany me.. so dat i wont feel so lonely in sch.. LOLs.. relieve stress too.. the GBA of mine.. the cover.. broken .. but still nt as bad la.. however.. the cartridges.. !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! dont know wad da heck.. all canot be played.. xcept the mario.. which i did nt like 2 play.. the castlevania canot be played.. hmm.. then other GBC cartridges oso..  okie la, i'll stop here.. juz felt v .... coz.. my mum scolded me .. scolded me 4 being so late 2 come home.. she said i went out 2 play.. then she called me juz now when i was having the xtended lesson.. she called me and asked me why i kept goin out.. i xplained 2 her.. then she said 'fine' . THEN when i reached home, she asked me again.. asked me why so late den home.. I XPLAINED AGAIN.. then i asked her 'waddya wan..' .. dont trust me or wad.. then she asked me 'the sch gt opened until so late 1 meh.. really study?? ..' So i ignored her words den walked out the rm. Go sch study oso kana scolded. What's this. Okie, i can sense dat readers are gettin bored with my words.. (",)*  oh ya anyway 2 day was da 1st day of the hungry ghost festival.. hmm.. hope nth happen.. oh ya.. i saw 2 figures when i was alone walkin past the classrooms juz now ard 8pm........................... They seemed 2 be walkin abt.... 
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you look better and better each day...and tonight, you look like tomorrow!  Why don't you surprise your room-mate/parents and not go home tonight?  Damn, if being sexy was a crime, you'd be guilty as charged!  Is your name Summer? 'Cause you are as hot as hell. Screw me if I'm wrong, but I could swear you were Julia Roberts.  How was Heaven when you left it? You are so beautiful that you give the sun a reason to shine.  I think I can die happy now, coz I've just seen a piece of heaven.  You must be going to hell, because it is a sin to look that good.  You've made me so nervous that I've totally forgotten forgotten my standard pick-up line.  If I had a rose for every time I thought of you, I would be walking through my garden forever. It's not my fault I fell in love. You are the one that tripped me.  Do you believe in love at first sight, or should I walk by again?  I'm betting that you cannot wait until tomorrow, because I bet that you get more and more beautiful every day.  Do you have a Bandaid? Cos I just scraped my knee falling for you. Do you have a map? Cos Honey, I just keep gettin lost in your eyes.  Hey baby, you must be a light switch, coz every time I see you, you turn me on!  You're like a dictionary - you add meaning to my life!  I'm sick. My medicine is to talk to you.  You're eyes are bluer than the atlantic ocean and baby, I'm all lost at sea.  I'm good at math, U+I=69  Please help the homeless. Take me home with you...  If you were a car, I'd wax and ride you all over town.  Since sex is a killer, would ya like to die happy?  There's this movie I wanted to see and my mom said I couldn't go by myself. Was your Father a mechanic? Then how did you get such a finely tuned body?  You must be Jamaican, because Jamaican me crazy. 
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      2day, nth 2 do.. as usual.. play com.. listen songs.. rot.. anyway later gonna watch the Athens.. gt table tennis.. and i think i missed the bball match out.. dat was this morning.. i think is 1.30am - 2am .. darn.. later gt swimmin too..  hmm, anyway, for the past week, i had spent lotsa $$$.. now my wallet is vacant.. gotta save more $$$ liao.. gonna buy lotsa things.. oh ya, today maybe later gonna go out buy tamagotchi.. lols.. heard dat there's a new type of dat gadget.. cost srd 29.90 .. can be bought at 7-11.. lols.. 7-11 ?? then it has new function.. can mate with other tamagotchi.. hmm.. nt so ex la.. but i gotta see 1st.. but i think in the end i will still make it mine.. haha.. oh ya 4got 2 add on.. i'm gd at spendin and wastin $$$.. hmm.. dont follow my path ya.. ?  hmm, im gonna concentrate more on Additional Mathematics.. gettin rusty.. SINCE JAN.. !! okok, im helpless.. im gonna start the 'Differntiation' ALL OVER AGAIN.. oh my.. However I believe I can do it.. hmm.. as for E-Maths, i can manage.. ENG? read more bahz.. havent been readin for quite a long time.. some weeks.. hmm.. SCI? Whats that? lols. Err.. i dont know.. really dont know what 2 deal with it.. im really aint interested in dat.. FULL of Technical words lor.. and i hate 2 memorise all.. Lame.. im nt gd at it la.. xpecially CHEM.. !!!! PHY? Still 'fineeeeeeeee' . calculation.. hmm.. SS. okie, it's the SEQ section which makes my result 2 drop. reason is, i nv study. =D. same for HISTORY. SEQ. i juz read through. ONCE. okie la, next time i memorise.  hmm.. CHN? im retakin.. dont know im lame or what. juz wanna get a '1' . but however, im nt gonna study for it. waste of moi time. maybe juz read through.. flip flip.. and this time rd im gonna do well in paper 1 .. ! I BELIEVE its the paper 1 which made me 2 get an 'A2' .. coz the compo i've written in the june paper was sucky.. thats what i think. if nt A1 is mine liao.. so for the nov paper im gonna do a planning 1st b4 i write any Craps. *grins* . the sch was 'forcin' the students 2 retake their chn. whats this? Ivan gt a 'U grade' for oral and a '6' for the written paper [okie sorry my dear Master im writin these here im sorry hope ya dont mind when ya see this okie] and he did nt wanna retake the paper HOWEVER the sch was forcin students 2 do so.. IMO.. i think that the sch wasnt doin anything right coz i think its the students' own individual 2 decide whether they wanna 2 retake or not. anyway, his mum will be goin 2 sch 2 meet da headmaster to talk abt this issue. whatsmore, Master had written a 'letter' regardin on the retakin of the chn paper. LMAO. but it was well-written. it WAS convincin. haha. nice try~  Okie, nth much 2 write.. sian life.. short of cash.. = / ~~ ..  okie im off. gonna do some A-maths. *grins* . No, shld be doin and watchin the Athens at da samE timE.        
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday. Afternoon. Nth 2 do.  Okie let's talk abt ydae's stuffs. Ytd, Saturday, I overslept, woke up at ard 12-1pm plus.. And so I missed my History test !! I've 4gotten 2 remind my mum 2 wake me up that morning.. Haiz .. Okie, so ydae.. was the opening of the Athens 2004 .. hehe .. I love it .. Watched swimmin .. table tennis .. bball .. !! and duno liao .. Hmm, so spent the whole afternoon watchin the Athens ..  Then during the nite, nth much 2 do .. coz the prog kinda sucky .. simi boxin .. and there was soccer matches .. korea - mexico .. which did not interest me @ all ..  Hmm, called pizza delivery .. bath .. ate 2 pizzas .. the new curry rice [kinda sucky and ex] .. beef balls .. [nt bad..] then taught JS .. history !! over the fone .. LOLs .. History!! .. me teachin .. joke of the day eh .. ? Used my didi's bk and taught her .. It was abt the SG's election la.. i stil rem .. 1948 .. 1955 .. and 1959 .. plus 2 merdeka talks .. MR Lee Kuan Yew .. David Marshall .. Lim Yew Hock .. hehe .. taught awhile .. [abt 5 pages] lols .. then we started 2 crap .. lols .. SO we talked on the fone for abt 3 hrs.. from 12 till 3 in the morning .. and at the same time we were waiting for the bball match 2 start la.. then dont know why the match still did nt start .. i rem the magazine said 1 mah .. 1.45 am .. bluff me.. then JS was waiting for the diving event 2 start .. diving nice meh ? haiya.. then we were veri lame la .. did not put the fone down .. or shld i use 'refuse' .. ? 'unwilling' ? lol .. i felt xtremely bored .. so i told her 2 talk on the fone longer .. but she wanna zzzz liao .. hmm .. then i dont know what she doin .. we bye liao she still hold the fone .. +_-" okie, so ard 3.15am finally put the fone down .. then my bro n didi n daddy still watchin the soccer match .. hmm.. so i went 2 zzzz ..   
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is the releasin of the Chn Os Results . I wasn't anxious or what, coz I was prepared .. For the worst . I think I'll get either a B3 or B4 . Coz I've nt prepared for the exam . Paper 1, I screwed almost evrything . The letter writin still okie. However the compo, I feel that it was the suckiest compo I've ever written in the past 16 years. LOLs. Coz I had chosen a descriptive compo . And I'm sucked at it. I always do argumentative compo. Hehe . My descriptive compo, I really did not know what the hell am I writing .. Full of craps . And aint complete. No plan. No intro. No everything. Okie. Therefore, I rem dat day after paper 1, I knew, and I told myself I wont get an A for sure. As for paper 2, it was still alrite.. Okie, so I've no confidence. However, 2day I was really shocked. I got an A2 . And distinction for Oral. Okie, nth surprising. I wasn't satisfied abt it. I wan an A1. However, I knew I could not ask for much. An A2 was already quite good.  
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is the releasin of the Chn Os Results . I wasn't anxious or what, coz I was prepared .. For the worst . I think I'll get either a B3 or B4 . Coz I've nt prepared for the exam . Paper 1, I screwed almost evrything . The letter writin still okie. However the compo, I feel that it was the suckiest compo I've ever written in the past 16 years. LOLs. Coz I had chosen a descriptive compo . And I'm sucked at it. I always do argumentative compo. Hehe . My descriptive compo, I really did not know what the hell am I writing .. Full of craps . And aint complete. No plan. No intro. No everything. Okie. Therefore, I rem dat day after paper 1, I knew, and I told myself I wont get an A for sure. As for paper 2, it was still alrite.. Okie, so I've no confidence. However, 2day I was really shocked. I got an A2 . And distinction for Oral. Okie, nth surprising. I'm nt here to boast . I wasn't satisfied abt it. I wan an A1. However, I knew I could not ask for much. An A2 was already quite good. Okie, I aint sure whether I wanna tk the exam again .. Maybe not.. Coz muz concentrate in my ENG. Spend more time in ENG .  Anyway they trashed Nan Chiau with the score of 86 - 36 i think. Wow. Okie, *claps* . Nuff said.   
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday. Day after the National Day. Hol.  Today woke up at 1pm. Hehe. But still v tired.  Oh ya. Had a bad hair day siaz. Coz I cut my hair ydae nite. !!!! I juz wanna trimmed only mah.. Then dont know why.. The fringe getting shorter n shorter.. Until touched my eye-brow.. Damnnnn. Did not the outcome would be like this. Then looked kinda .. LOLs .. stupid .. Haiz. Dont know what I'm doing. Hands juz felt the itch. Oh ya, 4got to add on, I love 2 help ple cut hair since young. LOLs. Crazy.. OkOk.  Anyway this kinda new maid of mine, damn freaky.. LOLs. Will smile 2 me whenever I accidentally looked at her.. Looked at me whenever I walked pass her.. [kept staring with a smile until I walked 2 my rm frm the living rm.. she was still doing that..] Talked to me whenever I was doing sth such as watchin tv.. playin com.. doing hw.. slackin.. Damn freaky .. ! Whats more, her smile was v .. No word to describe . Nt those normal type. Damn afraid of her. *scareded* And juz now she tok to me when I was using com, I ignored her words. Then she talked to herself. ??????????????????????? What's happening to this world?? LOLs. This type 1 I sure sacked 1 if I'm my dad. Okie, I know I'm cruel. But cant help it. LOLs.    Anyway, I havent buy Js's bdae present. I.. dont know what 2 buy .. I dont wan sth too simple.. But I juz dont know what 2 get 4 her. Lack of idea. And tomorrow is her bdae liao. I am still sitting in front the com.. typing.. playing.. happily.. What's more, I dont feel like gg out today.. Tired.. Ermm, was planning 2 buy a shirt + a box of chocolate OR some sports accesorries OR the sch shoe but she nv tell me what kind 1 OR soft toys but she seem have no interest in these kinda stuffs OR dont know liao.  ************************************************************************************   
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okie, this blog sucks, I know.  Monday. National Day. Happy Bdae Singapore.  *sing songs* ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Lame.                            __  Oh so today, I went to Bugis. Met Js and her frends.  Reached there at 12pm. Zhun bo ?  Hmm, then abt 5 min later saw Zexuan. Okie, he was a frendly guy. Cute. Haha. Did not know what he said.. I juz kept 'orh orh' .. Erm, 10 min later Js showed up with her frends..  There were 2 guys and a gal. That gal was 1 of Js's frend's sis. Her bro was probably a sec 2 guy.. and he liked Js.. Named Benn huh? Another guy was Benn's frend..  So we decided 2 catcha movie. However, the movie list was sucky..  Therefore, they decided 2 go 2 Suntec. Okie so off we went.  I was .. expecting 2 meet .. somebody. OkOk.  So at Suntec, they wanna took their lunch at Delifrance. I was sitting there .. doing nth .. Dont feel like taking anything.  Then after that, we strolled ard.. ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Then, we went to the arcade .. Play for dont know how many hours. Saw 2 gals playing Beat Mania.. Eh? No. Did not know what was that game called. 4gotten. They were damn PRO ~ Okie, it was juz something like Beat Mania.. Just that the name was different. I only know 2 play with.. Controller ! LOLs. OkOk. So spent the time at the arcade.. Spent abt 10 bucks in total there.  So when they had used up their tokens, we decided 2 leave the place.  Hmm, gonna go home.  Took bus at the bus stop.  I accompanied Js to her place.  We all juz took the same bus.  Then at the bus stop, I met someone.. Kinda replaced L .. Dont know. I juz felt that way. I juz.. kept lookin at dat person.. Yup.. Dat person made me have the same feeling as L.. I mean whenever I met L in sch. It was.. juz a feeling.. I.. Dont know..  Okie, so reached Boon Keng. Acc Js 2 buy dinner for her family. On the way the fireworks started. Did not get 2 watch clearly la. got those trees.. buildings.. blocked.. The fireworks sucked though. Veri sucky. And last for 1-2 min only. 1 word to describe. SUCKS Okie. So I took a bus home after that. Bus 21. The bus was damned packed after the bus stopped at somewhere at Kallang. Those bus stops ard that area was damn congested with I think those ple who juz back from the National Stadium. Then there were some kids beside ME. Damn noisy. Kept toking non-stop lor.. and uttering nonsense.. LOLs.. Felt like scolding them.. although their parents was juz standing in front of ME. I hate noisy kids. And those naughty ones. =) *grinned* Okie, then I alighted at the Geylang area. Then again, I gotta squeezeeeeeeed through the passengers. Then that damn bus driver closed that damn door, LOLs. I was stucked. LOLs. Then the door opened again. Some passengers and I quickly alighted. LOLs.  Okie. That's ALL abt it.        
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okie, this is the latest blog. LOL.  have been changing and changing ..  letme tok abt the events dat happened 2-3 days ago.  Sunday. Reach City Hall at 6pm. Met Ivan and the band members at Aljunied MRT. Met PeiYin too. We were gg to watch fireworks at Esplanade that day.  Okie I thought I was late. But luckily.. hehe.. Gotta wait for other ple 2 come..  Hmm, reached the bridge at ard 8pm. The place was congested siaz. Fireworks session started at 8.30pm if I'm nt wrong.. That nite the fireworks were.. beautiful.. Lasted for abt 4min.. I took the video with my fone.. Nt so clear though.. But still nt bad..  XY's parent came too. And in the end, her bro tag along with us. Hmm, so we were discussing abt where 2 go next, what and where 2 eat.. The whole process took abt half an hour. Damn.  So we went to take train and at the MRT station, again, the place was packed with ple. I was squeezeeeeeeeeeed.  Then we alighted at Somerset.  Went to Cineleisure. Ate pasta. That was ard 10 sth..  After that, it was getting boring.. Coz every one started 2 go home..  I dont wanna 2 be home soooooooooo early. Coz there was nth 4 me to do at home.  Met zilin. shanna. weini. zhixiu. at the roadside . We got stucked there. Did not know where 2 go and what 2 do. Den suddenly, weini's mum suddenly appeared. Scare me. LOL. Okie, so she went hm with her mum. And the rest of us just.. walked ard..  Then at the traffic light, zilin, xy and her bro went home .  Left the 3 of us.  We were like nerds or what, walked  here and there.. And we met Quan Song and gang.  Ard 11.45pm then we decided 2 go home. We took a cab.  Was getting damn bored coz I did ont plan 2 go home that day.. I juz.. got veri active at night la.. During the day I juz slept like a pig. OkOk. And there was no one to accompany me.. So I reached my place at ard 12.15am. Bath. Slept. Yup.     
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      She knew how worried her husband was, and as he lay sleeping next to her, she gave him a soft kiss and whispered soft and low,  "Everything's gonna be all right. I love you, Bryan Anderson." 
    
</post>


</Blog>