<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yo dudes! Youth camp was the best!!! I met this guy but I'll say no more... I stayed in a tent with Claire, Katherine and Sarah (tent leader) and Kezia joined us all on Tuesday night. I'm sooo tired. Sleeping on a li-lo in a chilly tent in an open field wasn't my first idea of fun but it turned out ok. We went to the leisure centre twice (indoor toilets and showers- Woohoo!), we also went to Charmouth to go on a quest but I managed to make my group fail by making them go right instead of left (oops). We also did messy games, they were fantastic. We sat in a circle and passed aroung an egg timer. If it went off in our hands then we had an egg smashed on our heads!!! Gross! I managed to get three smashed on me... The game after that involved sticking our faces in flour to find hidden sweets. I opted out of that due to my eggy state. We then had a water fight using coloured water (water mixed with different colour food colourings). We then all washed the egg off of us and decided to have a water fight, I got drenched. This was all fun but a waste of time as we went to the leisure centre (swimming) in the afternoon. The weather has been ok I suppose. There's been gales and storms at night causing the tent to flap around make me and my tent mates a little scared. The worst night was Friday night. It was about midnight! We heard 3 taps on the back of the tent (tap, tap, tap). This scared us but we convinced ourselves it was the wind. We heard it again (tap, tap, tap). This time we knew it wasn't the wind but a person. It came again (tap, tap, tap). By this time we were going to get up and see who it was when we heard 2 small taps and a loud one (tap, tap, TAP!!!) We all screamed our heads off. It was awful. A leader came over and asked what the screaming was about and we told her there was someone round the back of our tent. She climbed throught the tent pegs and there was no one there. She climbed back and told us this. Then she sees Tom Kunda (a guy in my year at school) walking across the field giggling. She asks him where he's been and he hold up a handful of socks and claims he went to get them off the washing line (which was behind our tent but not directly, about 50 yards away). Alex believes him, sends him to his tent and us to sleep. It's when I get up in the morning and find Tom Kunda's Sock out the back of my tent that it's guaranteed that it was him. As an act of revenge we took his swimming trunks and put them on the flag pole and raised them up high. It took him all morning to notice! The journey home was fine... I sat next to Sean and we fall asleep on eachother! He's so sweet. That's about all I have to say about youth camp. If anyone wants to know anything more or anything in detail just let me know.I've almost finished unpacking which is pretty impressive for me. I usually takes me about a week.  I have my third baptismal class on Thursday. I hope it's not as bad as my last one, no mess-ups this time I hope.  Well I must go because it's getting late and I need sleep.  Love you all and God bless, Lizzie xxx   
      
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yo dudes!   I had my second lesson today. Brian came at 4:30 again and we sat and talked. I made a huge mistake by saying genetiles instead of gentiles. TOTALLY EMBARRASING!!! I had to try my hardest not to laugh as I was still reading. He gave me a few more pages to read and take in by at least Wednesday. My next official session is on Thursday.      So... I've been packing nearly all day today and I'm so tired. I'm excited to be going away to camp but I don't like the 'getting ready' bit. I've managed to cram everything I'll need for a weeks camping into a small suitcase and a holdall. I don't know why they call them holdalls, if I named them I'd probably call them hold-halfs. Anyway... I've made sure i've got spare batteries for my torch and an extra energy cell for my hair curlers/straighteners. I'm possotive theres something I haven't packed but I'm sure that I'll work out what it is when I get there. I have to suffer a four hour journey in a stuffy mini bus tomorrow at about 10am. I'll be first off the minibus when we get to the services station (I'm not a good traveller). I've got a top and two pairs of jeans still to pack but they are still wet.       I just want to say I hope Jess had a happy Birthday.       I'll miss you Remi but I'm only gone for a week and I'll make sure I come and see you when I get back. You're a really cool guy and I'm so glad you're there for me. I'm always there for you aswell and I hope you know that.      Love you all and God bless   Lizzie xxx  
      
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yo dudes!   Just writing to give you the latest. I'm almost definately getting baptised. I had my first session yesterday with Brian (my church youth minister). We'll be working through a booklet over the next five sessions. My next session is on Friday and i have to have a total of five maybe six sessions. I've got youth camp next week so we might be able to meet then. I'm so excited!!!      Anyway...   So, I went to Miso's last night with my sister. I had never been there before. She advised me to have the duck with noodles whilst she had the Char sui (Pork that's been dipped in something with an ample amount of noodles). She also had the side order of deep fried squid which was grossly chewy and made me feel physically sick. I didnt really like the duck or the noodles but I forced myself to eat some of it because my sister bought it for me and to leave it all would be too rude. If anyone has ever been there, they'll know how big the meal is that they give you (if you haven't been there, they give you quite a deep, big bowl that they over fill). I just about flattened my plate (got the food level with the sides of the bowl). I had to give up. It was just not very nice at all. My sister however, she finished her food and would have been willing to make a start on mine except the waitor came over and asked if we were finished. My sister said we were and he took our plates away. We walked out of the resteraunt and she was up for going to get pudding from Sainsbury's. We ended up in there and I was a little peckish because I hardly ate anything. She bought a tub of Ben and Jerry's chocolate fudge brownie ice cream. I decided to get a can of pringles. I got almost halfway through the can when i look at my sister. Thinking she'd be stuffed I didn't bother offering her one but she took some anyway. I gave up on them after a while. She told me she'd saved me some ice cream. I can bearly eat another thing by now but i knew the ice cream would be completely melted but the time we got home so i forced it down. I felt so bloated all evening. I'd eaten way too much. My sister was fine! Trust me I'll never go Miso's with my sister again! I'll probably never go to Miso's again because it's just a waste of money.   Anyway... I'm going to the cinema tonight with one of my best friends. I'm going to see 13 going on 30! It looks really cool.   Ho-hum. Must go...   More later...   Love you all and God bless...   Lizzie xxx  
      
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Yo dudes!   Lizzie here!   SOUL  IN THE     CITY    was fantastic last week! I did hardly any work, made some wicked new friends and decided that I want to be a Christian! The team was painting the creche, painting some games and a new netball court on the playground and making a garden area behind the cage... I painted one of the netball court lines, two butterflies in the creche and that's about it. The evening worships were cool. I learned loads of new songs and had a laugh. I really enjoyed the Gig on Wednesday but the funday on Thursday sucked. I really liked meeting new people and making new friends like Jess, Rachel and Vicky. I also met Abby and Emma but I wouldn't really call them friends, I only spoke to them once. I met up with Chris and Jon Cousins which was cool (they are in my sisters year and they went to my primary school, I haven't seen them in 5 years). On Friday we went to Dansan Park in Bexley, Mike Pilavachi is sooo cool! I loved singing along to all the songs and i really enjoyed the Mexican wave, especially in slow motion... This week at home has been good so far. I went to Gavin and Becky's really romantic wedding, which included a horse drawn carrige and a honeymoon in Italy. The wedding dress was gorgeous (something like I want mine to look like)! I went to church on Sunday which was cool. I went shopping with mum today and that's it! I've got youth camp starting next Saturday (14th August to the 21st) One whole week in a field, DEEP JOY! No, I'm joking, it should be wicked. There probably wont be anymore news from me until after Camp so from now until then, stay safe, have fun and God Bless! Lizzie xxx    p.s. Jess I'll let you know when it is, trust me I'll need you there!  
      
</post>


</Blog>