<Blog>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So... last night, I freaked out 'cos my computer kinda crashed. I couldn't login to the administrator account. I mean, I'd almost finished the damn multicam script and then this happens... not good you know? I could login to the guest acount though, so I did and backedup those files...  then this morning, I tried it again, and still the same thing: it said that they could not find the user data and that I would be logged into the default user. Click OK... then I get this blue screen stating that there was a fatal error and that the system has been shut down!!!  !!!  okay, so I get my mum to give me a lift to the toshiba centre to go figure out whats wrong, and see whether I can get my files on my admin account back.  I get there, open the laptop, and it WORKS....  ...  okay, so the lady is really nice and tells me that its probably a software problem, then says that I should backup my files into the C drive...  okay, so after I do that, I thank her, and Go Home....  Thank You GOD! I didn't lose ANY info!   so... now that everything's just peachy, (i re-installed the norton antivirus) I can finally relax and finish that script, and the rest of my projects...      

						
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Here's something that Rose Mary, my sister wrote...  Its called: THE WAR OF THE PRAWNS.... *grins* Characters: RM = Rose Mary, MA= Mary Anne, Ryoma, Evang=Evangeline, Eliz=Elizabeth.  RM: Hey, Why are you eating so many Prawns MA?  MA: So I can do THIS! *bangs the edge of her plate so that all the prawn shells fly at the others sitting around the table*  Ryoma: Run for Shelter!  *RM dives under the table, Eliz as well, while Evang and Ryoma hide behind the couch*  RM: Take COVER! We are under attack! I repeat, WE ARE ---  Eliz: Being bombarded by prawn shells? *pulls a glove out of her bag and pretends to shelter herself with it, even though she's still under the table - she puts it on her her head*  *RM suddenly turns around and sees a GLOVE*  RM: EEee! Wha-? Uh, Liz, have you been cooking?  Eliz: Huh? Oh! You know this is my new hat!  RM: Liz, You have an--oven-mitt-- on your head....!  *MA flings the prawn she's holding at Evangeline. It hits her right smack on the nose*  MA: GOAL! Haha! Gotcha!  *Evangeline squeals and pretends to be terrified*  Evang: AHH No! Get it offa me! Yuck!  Ryoma: Fear not Fair Maiden! I will save You!  *Ryoma Jumps up and grabs a prawn from the table. He lunges at the prawn on the floor, using the one in his hand for a sword*  Ryoma: Hah! Take THAT! and THAT!  RM: Oooch!  Eliz: Quick away and ring the SPCA! There're two prawns and an idiot fighting!  --------------------------------------  Haha! We had a good laugh over it... *grins*  

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    well.... Yesterday, I went to school for a multicm meeting. we were supposed to discuss and take FM cue pictures...      Which we did. after some argument and a LOT of protesting on my part, I was FM, Zar was the camerawoman, and Nessa took the photos..........      I hate being photographed.      ONLY the girls turned up, with Josh coming down later... (I woke him up witha phone call-poor thing) *laughs*    Nick was too tired, and Keith had Floorball.   oh well.      yeah.      And so, today?      I'm going to school later, to borrow books for BMR, and then I'm going to Church in katong for some meeting about the youth website.      *yawn* still feel like sleeping though. I din't have a very good night's sleep.   I was bunking in Mary Anne's Room 'cos my air-con's leaking and I've been banned from using it. Plus, unfortunately, I can't sleep without it. I don't like S'pore's humid, warm air.      Was tired and got woken up by my mum this morning (much to my disgust... Hey! I am Supposed to be on Holiday! I get to sleep in!).      Shucks... I gtg for lunch now... laters...     

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Haha... I finally screwed up my courage and tried starting a Blog... Well, I hope that I'll be updating this more often. Casey's been bugging me... kinda, to update more often.  Oh well... I don't even know what posessed me to start a blog at this time of the morning, especially when I have to meet Case in School tomorrow, or rather, Today at 11am. Oh shucks... yeah, we're going to use school ink to print the icky BMR surveys...  Till Then...  

						
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Just trying things out...   

						
</post>


</Blog>