<Blog>

<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       As you may know, Lou Reed's satellite of love has been re-released. As someone who has never heard it before, I listened to it on the radio and heard what I thought to be the following lyrics:   Satellite’s gone Way up to mars Soon it will be filled With Haagen Dazs   I mean what on earth would it be doing filled up with posh ice cream? I looked up the lyrics and it was as follows:   Satellite’s gone Way up to mars Soon it will be filled With parking cars   Which is still bloody stupid if you ask me     I was looking at  urlLink Tom Watson's site  (Labour MP for West Bromwich) and happened to look at his  urlLink 'teens'  page where he tries to appeal to young people by sounding something like Ali G whilst being incredibly patronising in the process. By using what he assumes to be a teenagers way of speaking/typing (thankfully with out going into the realms of txt spk) he attempts to get them involved in politics, at the same time as sounding like a complete prick.  He does however have the words 'l33t Hax0r' on the page (OMG!!!11111) and I'm not sure weather to be impressed or not (sarcasm alert) but I'll err on the side of caution and not be impressed  . It actually surprises me that a politician has heard of l33t, as most of them havent got a clue about what goes on outside their own fat arse. (He'll never get people emailing him questions about l33t like I do!  ) All in all, I think its good that as a politician, he has a blog but please, please, please Tom, stop being so patronising.   This site was the victim of the ultimate form of flattery a while back - some thieving little bar steward ripped off my leet page and classed it as his own. I got his site shut down though lol   Black Coffee pwnz j00 l4m3r!.    BTW isnt  urlLink Rachel Stevens  a babe?    
     

        
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      As anyone who has read the blog on Black Coffee in the past will notice that things have changed slightly. The blog is now using Blogger as it makes it much easier to update than messing around with HTML in Notepad. It also gives me chance to concentrate on the writing rather than whether I mess the layout up whan adding pictures etc. And hopefully it will allow me to update more   The site is also not as direction orientated as it once was. I wanted it to be an information site; to have lists of free stuff and tutorials etc, which are on the site, but probably not that relavent any more. Now the site is going to be more humourous, in the direction of the web lookalike thing I have on the main site. In future, this blog will be linked to the front page. Black Coffee has been going since about 2001 in its free webspace days and most of the content has been around since then. Its way out of date, but my l33t page has got a lot of hits and has been linked from forums etc. I still get good comments and emails asking for linkage. I *still* havent got around to writing that PHP guestbook  The couple of years have seen changes to my attitude towards the web. There are more free web providers now, but so many of them add popups and dodgy downloads; Tripod and angelfire both have ad-frames that severely bollocks up the layout of any sites on their servers. Coupled with that, there are banners and popups. Using a free host aint fun anymore   I dont use the web as much as I used to any more; I dont use chat or IM any more. I dont visit as many forums as I used to. I've lost count of the amount of times a driveby download has almost happened to me, but I've stopped it because I have all  but turned of ActiveX controls on IE. Spyware is more prevelant now. All the websites I used to visit are either dead or dying on their arse. All this may seem negative, but its not. I dont feel negative; This is a positive time for me and for Black Coffee. I dont care what people think of the site. Its whatever I want it to be; and it that means it changes every so often, then so be it. Progression is all about change, either in real life or on the web    
     

        
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Doesnt this make you bloody sick?!?   This little chav scrote gets £1,150 a month off the state to house him, his wife and 5(!) kids. He doesnt work but says he would if he found a job that paid him enough to look after his 5 kids (yeah..right). Firstly, if I was in charge of this country, I would have the bollocks of these little tossers chopped off so they would not be able to father any more kids. Secondly, I would take their benefits away and make them get work. No work = no money! If they didnt want to get work, they would be confined to a life of poverty. That would be their problem. Britain (I dont call it Great any more for obvious reasons) is far too soft on spongers whether they be immigrants or home grown, yet the people who really do need help off the state dont get it, or have to fight very hard to get it. It makes me wonder why I bother working to be honest. The way I feel about this country at the moment, if I had my time again, I wouldnt have bothered making the effort when I left school. Having been unemployed for very small periods when I was younger (due to redundancies) I hated it however, and couldnt bring myself to live like that. Its Tony B-liar's fault. It was a bad omen when he came into power. The first thing he did was have a celebrity wank-fest at number 10. Stuff the working people of this country, he was more interested in being seen with celebrities. But I wouldnt want the opposition either. They have proved themselves to be incompetent in the past. The whole government situation reminds me of the lyrics of a Steelers Wheel song: "Clowns to the left of me, jokers to the right....." Ever get the feeling you've been cheated....? 
     

        
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Whats all this then? White powder and milky fluids all over my kitchen work surface? It this some sort of sordid debauchery involving Abi "Tits out" Titmuss and John "I used to be famous" Leslie? Thankfully, No!   Its just me making a complete mess of opening a tin of soya based protein, then making even more mess by adding soya milk to it, in an attempt to accelerate my progress at the gym.  Directions: (Shake the can before each use) For adults, blend one (1) scoop of the protien powder with low fat milk, fruit or vegetable juice.  What they didnt bargain on was me being a complete spaz and not taking the scoop out before shaking. Thus the scoop ended up at the bottom of the tin and I created the afore-mentioned mess trying to get it out. 
     

        
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Picture the scene; a dark, dingy, smoke-filled pub, somewhere in deepest Worcestershire. Groups of lads gather, high on a cocktail of booze and testosterone. All macho posturing, laughing, joking, drinking.. The girls meanwhile are crowded round, chatting girly chat, each one wanting to be the sexiest, the most glamourous; hoping that their skirt's the highest or their hipsters the lowest..... The DJ playing the same tunes as he played the week previous, and the week previous to that.... A room cram packed with needy souls, fractured egos, and sad wannabees all drowning in a sea of booze... Come 1.00, the bouncers herd them all round to the front of the pub, ask them to finish up, then herd them out onto the streets. Thrust out from the safety of their poison womb, they stagger home in different directions, stopping at the chippy or the kebab house for some food to soak up the booze... I'm so glad I didnt go out tonight. I could have got in the pub for 11.00, after work if I had wanted to. Instead I'm here, sober. And I prefer it that way. I get so pissed off with drinking these days. I dont enjoy it any more. Its the same old scene; I played it out hundreds of times, the video tape becoming thinner and thinner till it snapped and could be played no more.... 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      According to Sky News (above link for more details):    Britons are amongst the most promiscuous people in the world, according to a new survey.  Well theres a bloody surprise! That sort of goes hand in hand with our 'binge drinking culture': In fact, I will go as far as to say the two are inextricably linked. We (the Brits) get hammered in the pub before the 11.00 'last orders', go back for a shag, either with a current partner or someone we've pulled on the night, and possibly stop for a donner kebab on the way back. What is it about the British obsession with sex though? Its almost as though we feel if we dont have sex, or at least look sexy (in the female's case anyway) then we are a nobody. You only have to look at 'celebrities' like Jordan and Jodie Marsh (I'll use the word celebrity loosely.. slappers being more appropriate) who wear just enough to stop them getting arrested, and they're seen grinning in the gossip sections of the tabloids as if looking like that is something to be proud of! I may be an old prude, but I dont find women like that attractive. In fact, its completely off putting. I wouldnt want to be seen out with a girl who would wear that little, for the simple reason that blokes would be ogling her all night. I just wouldn't want that. IMHO someone who stoops to that level, is a very needy and egotistical person. And on the subject of clothes and sexuality, has anyone noticed how 90% of the girls these days are wearing 'hipster' jeans. Thats right, the low slung ones that look quite sexy on about 5% of girls. Sadly, a lot of girls dont realise that hipsters dont flatter their figure; Theres nothing worse than a larger lady wearing hipsters which reveal about 3 inches of arse cleavage. Couple this with a cropped top, out of which bulges their blubbersome belly, top it off with the customary Celtic tatoo on the lower back and your quite rapidly descending into chav culture. The trend amongst blokes is also pretty worrying; they to like to wear their kecks low slung too, but this time exposing about 3 inches of underpants. I think its a skater thing, but I'm not sure. But I cant see how girls could find this attractive. 
     

        
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
         An occasional award for a particularly good looking female in the public eye:  Anyone who lives in the Midlands and watches BBC Midlands evening news cant have failed to have noticed the lovely  urlLink Suzanne Virdee  who is one of the presenters. She's a very professional presenter, always dressing well and she's a bit of a babe too   Whilst searching the web for some pictures of her I found  urlLink this  site. A veritable Virdee-fest if ever there was one. Also contained on that site is a set of pictures of the equally lovely Shefali Oza, another Midlands Beeb-babe.  It seems I was a bit harsh on Tom Watson about his  urlLink teens  page in a previous entry. It turns out it was a spoof about how politicians try to 'get down' with 'the kids'. If you scroll down far enough on the page you will get his explaination and some of the emails he has recieved, several being from Americans; two of which proved irrefutably that they  do  understand irony and British humour across the pond. Whilst we British are notorious for whinging about the weather (and lets face it, over the last few days we've had bloody good reason to), perhaps we ought to be grateful that we dont get it as bad as they have had in America with hurricane Charley. I watched some footage on the telly on Friday, I think, and it was so shocking that the weather could do so much damage. Roofs were being peeled off like the lid off a sardine tin. So next time theres a few spots of rain and you feel a whinge coming on, just think, it could be a lot lot worse. 
     

        
</post>



</Blog>