<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Corner of world   How do I feel about that, the corner of world
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I finally fish my MA courst....should I happy about that?   People easy to used something, but when the environment going to chang...they will feel nervous.      15 of Aug, I got one music box...the music can play 'Autumn Leaves'   For now, the Autumn is coming.      I still wear my shorts, and feel cool.      Sad a litter bit...therefore I make myself more busy..      Hope I wont think too much.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ye ye ye      Finish my dissertation lo...   But the content not really good I think..   Later, I wanna go to Windsor...have a nice lunch and shopping..      Back to real life finally.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night, I went to bed at 10:30... No idea why I was so so so sleepy... Then wake up at 8:30..god..yes..I'm late for work.. so. Lose one day salary..just stay in my room then wait to 9am, went to Ray's office to pick up the new Taiwanese PHD student..  She looks quite old..and really like a teacher..traditional type.. I cannt or even try to talk with her too much..then escape...to supermarket!  I bought one scented product and hope I can write my work in the nice environment(which is my aim)  Yeh Yeh....spent 12 pound..  Whole afternoon..I was rethinking my discussion part.. Really...complex..I cannt expect got B anymore...I have to face the reality!  I didnt do my research well... And I am fucking Fail la!!  After dinner, I working hard..and made a lot chart..then feel better...ho~~  Ho~~Ho!!  I wanna successful la!  Dammit.   Good Luck to me~    
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I can laugh loundly, as you can hear.      I can rend the air with cries, as you can see.      The  sweat runs down like raindrops, you can smell it.      I  brim over with enthusiasm, as you can touch.      I am a emotional person, but hope you know it.      Deeply, we connect with each other in this complex world.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       For you my friends,   take a cigar with you then,   seize a happy memory      Waiting for you expel my unaccompanied heart      Merry time in here      Mist over my 26 memories  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Far away, can not say I have no feeling about it...      Far from the earth, we come from different place.     Have different thought.     Have different mind.     Wait for the time, one day..., we gonna be different...    In the final, we are stranger still.    I listen with silence.    Stranger, we come from the different world  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lone &amp; lonely  Lone=  Lonely=  Answer me, tell me the meaning of the word. I tried to ask myself.  Same? lone is more lonely...because lonely have ly with it...   understand?   ha ha ha ah ahah  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was washing my oily hair in the middle of the night.  Things came into my head like puzzle pieces  Puzzled  How come I never use this word?  How come it has already been a year..  How come I've written 13000 words...  How? what is next now?  Midnight, puzzled with my wet hair 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      toturial toturial  ha ha ha ha ha   Dear Dr. Ray...   Change my project..again  However he do a good thing, he help me find a reading-prof just cost 40 pound...uum  Fine...at least..I dont need to worry who can help me check my crap english  Go on  Need to finish as soon as possible.     
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ha ha ha ha,  From my dear Cola finally I got this page to explain all my feeling..  I would like to learn more how to build this web page..  However..too many things need to do.  Fisrt day hope it can be my new day.    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes..A lot of shit in my day..  I cannt understand why I cannt finish my goddam dissertation... even it only get discussion and recommentation part...  My eyes r painful...cannt see window clearly..  Bitch! 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>