<Blog>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Why do most fantasy publications give you a synopsis of each NFL team containing their projections on the teams final record, where they are likely to finish in their division and, oh joy, whether or not they will make the playoffs.  Frankly, I don’t care about this information (and you shouldn’t either). It’s useless. Yes, it’s important to know how a team’s D stacks up, or who will be getting the most snaps under Center, but as long as Peyton gets his 300 yards and Edge scores his TDs, I could care less if the Colts finish 0-16.  As for who will be in the playoffs, just about every Fantasy Season is over by then. So why are you other prognosticators out there wasting our time and money giving us your postseason predictions. Predictions, by the way, that are usually about as accurate as a Seth Marler field goal attempt from outside the 50.  With this said, my next installment will begin the StatLeader 2004 season analysis starting with the NFC West. We will only worry about the information that is important to you, the Fantasy Football owner. One more thing, as a die-hard Buckeye, I have a natural revulsion to anyone (or anything) from the University of MeatChicken. That does not end simply because they are now pros. If my evaluation of these players seems overly harsh, it isn’t…, just accurate. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Due to your large number of requests, StatLeader.com is pleased to announce that we will be adding AOL Fantasy Football to our list of leagues for which we will provide individualized statistics and rankings. Watch for this exceeding cool information to arrive next week.  RM  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      August 13:  The NY Giants beat the Chiefs in pre-season action 34-24 with Ron Dayne, RB showing signs of days-gone-by with touchdown runs of 29 and 67 yards.  Dayne overshadowed the debut of Eli Manning, who went 7 of 13 for 49 yards.  The Chiefs offense ravaged the Giants re-building "defense" for 311  first half yards .  The fantasy football story, however, is the performance of Ron Dayne.  Personally, I think Ron Dayne is about as good a fantasy player as Taylor Dayne!  She's better looking - and has a greatest hits CD, while Ron's greatest hits are well behind him! 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Virtually all Fantasy Football leagues require you to have at least one tight end on your roster. In some leagues the option exists to fill an additional roster spot with either a TE or a WR. In these situations, the question often arises as to whether to draft a starting TE or a #2 or #3 WR. Well, consider the following:  Lets assume you are in a 10 team league and that each team has already drafted one of the top ten TEs. Based on last years stats:   Receptions  - The #11 ranked TEs, Boo Williams and Erron Kinney, each had 41 catches, 5 less than #50 WR Curtis Conway.   Receiving Yards  – Boo Williams was also #11 in this category. His 436 yards is 152 yards less than #50 WR Josh Reed (588).   TDs  – In this all-important category there was an 8 way tie (Heap, F. Jones, Crumpler, Pollard, Kinney, Miller, T. Jones, Dunn) for the #9 position. With 3 TDs each none of these fellows rate a top fifty ranking relative to the WRs.  You don’t have to be Rocket Man to see that if your Fantasy Football league offers the option to pick between a WR and a TE, go for the WR. You may want to add an 2nd TE to your Fantasy Football roster during the bye weeks but generally this isn’t a great point producing position.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Earlier this week I told you that Rams RB Steven Jackson would back up Marshall Faulk, playing ahead of Lamar Gordon. With Gordon’s surgery and the Rams already resting Faulk’s knee Jackson looks better than ever. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Pittsburgh Steelers backup QB Charlie Batch underwent season-ending knee surgery and was placed on injured reserve Friday.  Batch had soreness in his knee this week and doctors found damage when Batch underwent an MRI on Thursday.  The Steelers signed quarterback Kurt Kittner to replace Batch on the roster.  Kittner is a third-year veteran from Illinois.  Last season he started four games and played in seven.  He didn't play in any games in 2002.  Fantasy football owners are watching players drop like flies even as draft days loom ever closer.  Fortunately Batch wasn't on your list of fantasy QB's (was he?). 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Up to now you have been subject to the mad Fantasy Football ramblings of our resident analyst Doc Bitters. Now I have a lot of respect for Doc’s opinions. He is a pretty insightful fellow. But starting next week, StatLeader.com will begin posting the first of our ever-expanding and unique core services, our computerized Fantasy Football rankings.  What makes our product so different? Well, a number of things. First of all, we individually rank all players relative to each of the major Fantasy Football league default settings. This includes:   ESPN  – LM Traditional, LM Standard, LM Yardage, FF Traditional and FF Performance   Yahoo  - Default   CBS Sportsline  - Default   NFL  – Default   Fox / Sporting News  – Basic and Ultimate  Since each of these leagues use different scoring systems, traditional rating services can generally not cover more than one or two of them. We give you all 10. Why? Well, just because Peyton Manning may be #1 in one league doesn’t mean he will be #1 in any of the others.  Additionally, we won’t waste your time projecting pass attempts, receiving TDs or rushing yards like other sites. We give you what you need and what you’re interested in, projected points based on your leagues scoring system.  How do we do it? Simple. OK, not so simple. Our analysis routines were developed by two honest to goodness “rocket scientists” (including yours truly). We have developed our own protected Fantasy Football methods that seek to be as mathematically accurate as possible while taking in to account the unpredictable nature of football.  As an example, we input over 40 different statistical pieces of information for each offensive player. These are used to calculate more than 300 intermediate values that are then applied to the individual setting for each of the 10 leagues listed. This allows us to provide what we believe to be the best league-by-league ranking and projections available in Fantasy Football.  We’ll let you know more shortly. In the meantime, enjoy The Bitter One’s ravings (Yes we actually do incorporate his opinions into the system) and get ready to launch into a new universe of Fantasy Football information. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      StatLeader.com is high on Arizona's Larry Fitzgerald.  An excerpt from Doc Bitter's Arizona thumbnail commentary states " Hasn’t played his first game yet and already is listed as the #2 receiver. Is he that good? Yes, the birds might just have their second straight ROTY ."  With the injury to Anquan pushing his return back to as late as October, Larry is going to get a lot of balls thrown in his direction.  With AB out, defenses will be able to key on the rookie.  Will he be able to handle it as well as Boldin did in his rookie year?  If  a running back emerges from the crowd ( Sleeper Alert  Josh Scobey?) it is very possible.  As fast as Boldin is falling in draft day position - Fitzgerald should be rising.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The bluest skies you’ve ever seen are in Seattle… (Theme from the ‘60s series “Here come the Brides”)…I agree, and that goes for both clear days this year.   Matt Hasselbeck , QB – One of the top producers in Fantasy Football leagues last year. Matt’s a little inconsistent at times, but still a solid starter for your fantasy team.   Trent Dilfer , QB – Having a surprisingly a good camp. If Hasselbeck goes down, take another look at Dilfer off your bench.   Shaun Alexander , RB – A solid Fantasy Football starter at the RB position. No need to say any more.   Maurice Morris , RB – Faster than Alexander, but all that gets him is a quicker trip to the bench.   Darrell Jackson , WR – Great numbers last year despite 15 drops. Jackson could be better this year if only he can remember to catch the ball. Yet another fantasy football starter from the Seahawks!   Koren Robinson , WR – Another fantasy football starter! This year, has the possibility to do better than Jackson.   Bobby Engram , WR – A good solid receiver with the ability to get open. On this team however, that only makes you number 3. Not worth using a draft slot.   Itula Mili , TE – Expect him to share catches with Stevens making neither one of them worth drafting.   Jerramy Stevens , TE – Expect him to share catches with Mili making neither one of them worth drafting.   Josh Brown , K – Scores lots of fantasy football points because of the Seahawk’s offense. Brown misses too many opportunities with his ugly 73% FG accuracy. Seattle’s weather could lower that number further. He’s a gamble even as a back-up Kicker.   Seahawks Defense  – A good Fantasy Football D last year. They tried to fill some holes in the off season. Expect a better pass rush but there are possible problems against the rush. Did they fill the holes or simply move them around? 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I left my heart…oh give me a break! Here are the 49ers!   Tim Rattay , QB – Most Fantasy Football sites don’t expect much from Rattay this year. A below average (and sore) arm, groin surgery, with unknowns at receiver certainly seem to justify that. But, since I don’t give a rat’s posterior for what they say, I’m going to rank Rattay as a good Fantasy Football back-up QB. He’ll have to throw to open things up for Barlow, and the receiving talent, while young, is there.   Ken Dorsey , QB – Gone but not forgotten: Garcia, Owens, Streets, Hearst. Forgotten but not gone: Dorsey.   Kevan Barlow , RB – Don’t expect him to perform like he did in the 49ers last four games (almost 600 yards and 5 touchdowns), but he should easily go over the 1,000 yd. mark. A solid fantasy football starter at the RB position.   Jamal Robertson , RB – Who?   Cedrick Wilson , WR – Hey Cedrick, get to the sidelines and stop the clock! Better yet, just get to the sidelines.   Brandon Lloyd , WR – Last year’s spectacular grabs were only a preview. Brandon is my favorite choice in SF receivers. Despite Rattay’s so-so arm and Dorsey as back-up, I still see him as a solid #2 WR.   Curtis Conway , WR – Conway brings the 49ers his experience at WR. So what???   Rashaun Woods , WR – Could end up ahead of Wilson or behind Hamilton. To risky to use a fantasy football draft pick for now.   Derrick Hamilton , WR – Expect Hamilton to challenge Conway and possibly Woods before too long. Returning kicks only adds to his value. Will probably be a decent mid-season addition.   Eric Johnson , TE – Might be a great sneak pick. With a bunch of young receivers (and one ancient one), Johnson could end up seeing an above average number of tosses heading his way.   Todd Peterson , K – 80% may not seem spectacular, unless your home field is 3Com. Had he played the full season, would probably have finished in the top half of Fantasy Football kickers. Peterson makes a decent #2 at the kicker position.   49ers Defense  – A good solid #2 Defense. In spite of all the changes and missing their star, we still think they can fill in as your “D” in certain match-ups. Their big concern will be the field position the 49ers’ offense leaves them with.   Edit :  Corrected misspelling 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       ESPN reports that Arizona Cardinal's wide receiver Anquan Bolding injured his right knee before practice Tuesday morning. The 2003 Rookie of the Year hurt the knee while loosening up before practice.  Anquan set a rookie reception record with 101. The team has yet to describe the seriousness of the injury.  Fantasy football owners beware - this is a great year to hold those drafts as late as possible!  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rick Stroud of the  urlLink The St. Petersburg Times   is reporting that Tim Brown has agreed to terms with the Tampa Bay Buccaneers and a reunion with former coach Jon Gruden.  Tim Brown's hunt for a Superbowl ring (and possible enshrinement into the NFL's Hall of Fame) may resume with the team that ended that dream in Super Bowl XXXVII.  Tim Brown should be #3 (at best) on Tampa's depth chart, so fantasy football owners shouldn't expect too much from Brown in 2004. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Washington Redskins win Joe Gibb's first game back with a late fourth quarter field goal. After a late score-tying drive by the Broncos, the Redskins marched back, and with 3 tics on the clock, booted a game winning 39 yard field goal.  Tim Hasselbeck had good numbers going 7 of 10 for 118 yards and a 33 yard TD toss. The outing will continue to solidify his fantasy football believers.  Man - it's good to have football back! 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Next up, we take a look at the Saint Louis Rams   Marc Bulger , QB – With last year’s experience - and without Kurt Warner looking over his shoulder, Bulger should produce even more (as long as he can remember which color jersey he’s throwing to.) Given the Rams receiving corps, he should score more points than the last American Idol winner.   Chris Chandler , QB – Sitting behind Bulger will keep him sitting. About his only hope would be a phone call to Tanya Harding.   Marshall Faulk , RB – Rickety-Rack-Rack-Rack, Marshall’s knee is back. But, for how long? The artificial turf at home only makes it worse. Not the fantasy football “sure thing” he once was.   Steven Jackson , RB – Will back-up Faulk. Should see a fair amount of work even when Faulk is healthy.   Lamar Gordon  – Lamar did an adequate job filing in for Faulk last year. Rams will use him sparingly in case they need him late in the season.   Arlen Harris , RB – A move to Fullback will limit his value.   Dane Looker , WR – Good   Isaac Bruce , WR – Better   Torry Holt , WR – Best. Virtually any Rams receiver is a safe choice (unless, of course Bulger does get inured – then you are screwed!)   Jeff Wilkins , K – One of the best. First in points, third in accuracy.   Rams Defense  – A strong secondary could be hurt by a poor pass rush, especially if Leonard Little is busy sitting in an alcohol education course instead of playing. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As promised, here is my take on the NFC West. First up, we address the Arizona Cardinals.   Josh McCown , QB – I like the look of the 3rd year Arizona QB. In the last four games of ’03 he was a consistent and impressive performer. Taking over the starting role this year he will have a strong receiving corps featuring last year’s ROTY (rookie of the year) Anquan Boldin and newcomer Larry Fitzgerald. Couple this with a weak running game and new coach Dennis Green’s fondness for QBs, McCown could easily pass the 3000 yard mark. I make him a solid pick as a #2 fantasy football QB.   Shaun King , QB – If McCown stays healthy you’ll probably get more fantasy football points playing Stephen King.   John Navarre , QB – Had a reputation for not being able to win the big ones at Michigan. He won’t even win the small ones this year.   Emmitt Smith , RB – Was one of the greatest. Was. Despite being recently named as the starter, don’t expect much when the hitting starts for real. I expect he will share a significant number of carries with Scobey or Anderson. Think Emmitt is inspired to produce? Think he wants to show he still has it? Think he is motivated to go out on top? He was motivated against Dallas last year, the result, 6 carries, -1 yard and a broken bone. Not suitable for your fantasy football line-up!   Marcel Shipp , RB – Out for 8-12 weeks with a broken left leg. Out most of the rest of the season with other talent moving ahead.   Damien Anderson  – With 35 year old Smith ahead of him, he’s an injury away from a starting position. With Scobey behind him, he’s a stumble away from moving back to #3.   Josh Scobey , RB –  Sleeper Alert . He’s inexperienced, but fast and hard to bring down. Watch for Scobey to sneak ahead of Damien Anderson for the number 2 slot.   Anquan Boldin , WR – Last year’s ROTY (Rookie of the Year) will avoid the sophomore jinx. Still, his numbers may drop some this year. Why?, a move to Split End and more good targets this year.   Larry Fitzgerald , WR – Hasn’t played his first game yet and already is listed as the #2 receiver. Is he that good? Yes, the birds might just have their second straight ROTY.   Bryant Johnson , WR – Another good one. May get some openings with opposing D’s scrambling to cover Boldin and Fitzgerald.   Neil Rackers , K – 67% accuracy might be acceptable if this were basketball. Unfortunately, it isn’t.   Cardinals Defense  – Defensively speaking, Sadam’s Air Force was stronger. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Associated Press is reporting that the Chicago Bears and Miami Dolphins have agreed to a trade involving the Bears'  WR Marty Booker  and Miami's  DE Adewale Ogunleye.   The report is from an anonymous source, and the deal is said to hinge on the Bears being able to come to terms with Ogunleye.  Dolphin's General Manager Rick Spielman would not confirm that any deal was pending.  The Dolphins would add a quality veteran receiver to a depleted receiver corps, and the Bears would add some teeth to their pass rush.   Fantasy Spin :   Bears  - just what  Rex Grossman  needs...less talent to throw to!  This trade would affect Grossman's fantasy football value negatively.   Dolphins  - Marty Booker has never really gotten any respect from fantasy football.  My opinion:  90-100 catch season!   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      #2 Philadelphia RB  Correll Buckhalter  suffered what is believed to be a season ending injury to his right knee during the 1st quarter of the Eagles’ game against the Ravens Friday night.  Buckhalter was expected to carry a significant part of the load along with #1 RB  Brian Westbrook . With Rookie RB  Bruce Perry  already having suffered a season ending injury, the Eagles have only 2nd year RB  Reno Mahe  to back up Westbrook. Mahe’s 2003 stats…2 games played, 0 rushing attempts, 1 reception for 5 yards.  Watch for the Eagles to start a desperate search for another RB. (How about making an effort for  Ricky Williams , or  Whining Willis M .) Meanwhile, Westbrook’s value just shot up.   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It’s the time of the preseason where depth charts are starting to firm up and egos melt down. First it was  Browns RB James Jackson  who looked to be carrying the  “Play Me or Trade Me”  banner. Jackson has backed down a bit on that bit, however, it appears that the banner has been picked up by  Bills RB Willis McGahee . Well Willis, if these “Play Me or Trade Me stories” are true, ole Doc Bitters has a message for you….  Who the hell do you think you are? Most rookies don’t get the chance to play let alone to start. What’s that? You’re not a rookie? Oh, that’s right you were a member of the Bills last year. What were your stats again? 0 TDs, 0 yards, 0 carries. Yes I know you were injured by those Big Bad  Buckeyes  when your team lost the National Championship. Yes I know you've worked hard to get yourself back to where you are able to play, but let’s face it, that’s what you are being paid for.  What gives you the right to think you deserve to start ahead of  Travis Henry , an excellent running back who tried to carry the Bills last season despite playing with a broken leg the latter part of the year? Rookies generally earn their starting positions, and until you have completed you first season with some real game action you are still a rookie.  While I appreciate and respect the competitive spirit, there is also a thing called teamwork. Someone saw fit to pay you a yearly salary that is several times more that what most of us will ever make in all of our working years combined. That doesn’t make you better than anyone though, just more wealthy. Money may give you lots of things, but the one thing it can’t give you is class. You want to see class, look at the guy you are playing behind, that’s class.  It’s a shame that a snot-nosed little kid who has proven nothing so far thinks that he has the right to dictate terms to his employer. If most of us tried that we would find ourselves on the outside looking in. Maybe with a little luck so will you.  
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Pittsburgh Steelers right guard  Kendall Simmons  has sustained a tear of the ACL in his right knee during team drills on Wednesday. The season ending injury is especially painful for Simmons who also battles adult onset diabetes. This is a major blow to the Steelers who have been hoping that an improved offensive line, anchored by Simmons, would help bolster their running game. Expect this to impact the value of Steeler RBs  Duce Staley  and  Jerome Bettis . 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Rex Grossman , QB – Rex has only started 3 games and is going to need help. He has some good talent around him and if the Bear’s O-line can learn coach Lovie (Lovie??) Smith’s system, Grossman could surprise a lot of Fantasy Football owners. If not, Rex will spend more time on his back than a Windy City hooker. (Gross…man)   Thomas Jones , RB – Showed some flash last year and I think he will do a lot better than many think. I don’t know how well the Bear’s line will protect Grossie, but they can block for the run. Don’t be surprised to see Mr. Jones put up some impressive numbers.   Anthony Thomas , RB – (Anthony) Thomas doesn’t have much value unless Thomas (Jones) fails to produce. He’ll be used primarily in short yardage and pass option situations. Face it, this MeatChicken “A-Train” is stuck at the station.   Marty Booker , WR – Booker could have a great year depending on how familiar “Rex the Wonder QB’s” posterior becomes with the turf. A risky #1 Fantasy Football WR, a safe #2.   David Terrell , WR – David! Didn’t they teach you at “scUM” (MeatChicken) to actually hold on to the ball? Didn’t think so. If you do, with your talent you could have a tremendous year. If not, the only thing you’ll have to worry about holding on to will be your suitcase.   Justin Gage , WR – Keep an eye on this gage.   Bobby Wade , WR – #4 on the Bears for now… for now .   Desmond Clark , TE – Could get off to a slow start since he has missed a lot of training camp. Smith’s style of play enhances his value and he could become a favorite target if Grossman (YES the “if Grossman” caveat again) spends a fair amount of time running for his life. A #2 Fantasy TE, but then you know how Doc feels about TEs.   Remy Hamilton , K - and  Alain Kashama , DE – Worthless MeatChicken players of the day.   Paul Edinger , K – Paul has never missed a PAT. He was 8th in FGs but only 13th in overall points. What does this mean? Simply the Chicago doesn’t score many TDs. If Smith’s (YES, the "if Smith’s" caveat) system clicks, that could change. A low #1 or high #2 Fantasy Football K.   Bears Defense  – I expect the Bears to show significant improvement on D, but it will take time. Rate them as a low #2 at the start of the season moving to a high #2 by week 9. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Kyle Boller , QB – Kyle can throw the ball into the next county with pinpoint accuracy…as long as the other team isn’t on the field. The presence of those irritating defensive players appears to confuse him. His mechanics are about as impressive as the guys down at "Billy Bob’s Car Repair and Doughnut Shop". Compounding the situation is the miserable receiving corps he has to work with. A #3 Fantasy Football QB at best.   Kordell Stewart , QB – How much value does a guy released by the Bears and backing up Boller have? Not much…for now. But, when Boller goes down later this year keep an eye on Stewart.   Anthony Wright , QB - Wrong   Jamal Lewis , RB – Neither opposing Defenses nor Federal Drug Charges shall keep Jamal from his appointed TDs. With a Super Bowl lurking and a dismal passing game, the Ravens will spare no expense to assure Jamal’s trial is delayed until after the season. A #1 Fantasy Football RB and a top five draft pick.   Kevin Johnson , WR – The good news for Kevin, he is the Ravens’ #1 WR. The bad news for the Fantasy Football world, he is the Raven’s #1 WR. Proof? He finished 31st in receptions, 42nd in receiving yards, and out of the top 50 in TDs last year. A Fantasy Football #3 at best.   Travis Taylor , WR – Worse than Johnson.   Randy Hymes , WR – With the bench time he’ll see, Hymes could qualify as a judge…oops, sorry Jamal.   Devard Darling , WR –  Sleeper Alert . Has the tools, but he probably won’t do much this year. With injuries though, who knows?   Todd Heap , TE – One of the best. Proves that there are exceptions to every rule (Doc’s rule #1). Given the pathetic nature of the Ravens WRs, Heap will likely be Bollers’ primary target. A solid #1 Fantasy Football TE.   Matt Stover , K – Should score lots of points as long as Jamal is on the field and out of the courtroom. A definite #1 Fantasy Football K.   Ravens Defense  – Ray Lewis’ crew is a #1 Fantasy Football D. Why? 1st in defensive TDs scored, 1st in sacks, 2nd in takeaways, 2nd in fumbles forced, 3rd in INTs for TDs, 3rd in total yds/game allowed, and 4th in INTs last year,  that’s  why. 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Arizona Cardinal DT Kenny King  is reportedly out for the season with an injury to his right wrist. This is the same wrist King had surgery on over the off-season. Referring to King’s four months rehab Card’s coach Dennis Green said, “…it didn't work.” King is the third Card to fall out of the sky with  WR Anquan Boldin  out 8 – 12 weeks and #2  RB Marcel Shipp  also likely out for the season.      
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For what they’re worth, here are the Dolts…er…Bolts.   LaDainian Tomlinson , RB - A definite #1 Fantasy Football RB. Should be considered one of the top three RB's in the draft.   David Brandt , G - Only mentioned here because he is another useless University of MeatChicken product.   The rest of the Chargers Offense  - Forget about them on draft day.  Reche Caldwell  (WR) and  Antonio Gates  (TE) could be mid-season pickups but with Drew Brees and 41-year-old Doug “A-wop-bop-a-loo-lop a-lop bam boo, tutti” Flutie at QB there probably won’t be much to catch.  Expect  Philip Rivers  (QB) to hold out until he reaches retirement age (not that he would be worth anything if he did sign).  If the Bolts were smart they would drop  Drew Brees  and sign Drew Barrymore. At least she could keep the fans entertained.   Nate Kaeding, K  – Deadly accurate at Iowa, just dead here.   Bolts Defense  – The Patriots success with the 3-4 last year has inspired the Chargers to switch to a 3-4 themselves. A good idea, unfortunately they don’t have New England’s talent. Avoid their D unless you have the last draft in a 32 team league. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ...for one game at least.  Eli Manning gets the start this week in what Coach Tom Coughlin calls his "planned rotation."  "The decision coming in was that they were going to compete for the job, therefore we are going to give both of them the opportunity to start, and this weeks is Eli's opportunity."  Coughlin told the Associated Press.  Fantasy football team owners will be watching closely to see how the young man does. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Rich Gannon , QB – Don’t let his age fool you. Gannon reported to camp in top shape and with a chip on his shoulder.  He’ll play from a wheel chair if he has to.  With some new young lions on the O line, watch for him to put up strong numbers this year.  A good Fantasy Football #2 QB choice.   Kerry Collins , QB – Was either decent or very bad last year.  What do you expect from a former Knitting Lion?  Could actually be a decent Fantasy Football #3 QB choice since he is playing behind a 40-year-old starter.   Marques Tuiasosopo , QB – The leader of the Raiders’ “difficult to spell my name” team (along with Zereoue, Janikowski, and Gbaja-Biamila).  That’s about the only reason to care if he is on this team.   Tyrone Wheatley , RB – Another stellar University of MeatChicken grad.  He could run for 2,000 yards and score 30 TDs this year…but only if the opposing teams forget to show up for all 16 games.  Expect his value to fall faster than Joan Rivers’ face.   Justin Fargas , RB – Would you be worried about playing time if you were playing behind Wheatley?  Neither would I.  Watch for him to move up to #1 by the fourth or fifth game.    Amos Zereoue , RB – Will primarily be used for third down passing situations.  I doubt if he will get past Fargas in the lineup.   Troy Hambrick , RB – Yawn…   Jerry Rice , WR – Jerry could be 60 (maybe he really is) and still outclass most receivers.  While other Fantasy Football publications are writing him off, I think Mr. Rice is going to put up impressive numbers this season.  Base this on the extra protection Gannon will get, the fact that there is finally a decent backup QB if needed, and the presence of a healthier Jerry Porter.  Also, if this truly is the Rice Man’s last year it will only provide him with extra motivation.   Jerry Porter , WR – A healthy Jerry Porter should earn some decent Fantasy Football points, as long as he can stay a healthy Jerry Porter.   Doug Gabriel , WR – Should be the Silver and Black’s #3 receiver.  Keep and eye on him as he could easily find himself as the #2 receiver.   Alvis Whitted , WR – I don’t expect anything from him this year.  I just listed him because I like his name.   Doug Jolley , TE – You know how Doc feels about TEs, notably those in the lower half of the rankings.  His 1 TD last year was especially impressive.   Teyo Johnson , TE – I would say that he has a chance to move up but its more likely that Jolly will move down.  If he ends up starting, he could make a decent #2 Fantasy Football TE (if there is such a thing).   Sebastian Janikowski , K – When (Sebastian) The Crab isn’t kicking field goals, he’s usually kicking someone’s butt in a bar fight.  I expect a revamped Raiders offense to give him more opportunities to score this year, assuming he’s at the game and not in the pokey.   Raiders Defense  – OK we all know that the Raiders D got a lot more Sappy during the off season.  Oakland added the King of Rude along with Ted Washington (from NE) to strengthen their run defense.  Too bad Warren can’t tackle with his mouth.  If he ends up playing half as good as says he can, the Raiders should improve significantly on defense. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The "fish" have been hit with the worst luck this year!  They lose Williams, one of the best running backs in the NFL, to early "retirement", they are being decimated with season-ending injuries, and their training room continues to look like a MASH unit!  They got a double dose of bad news Sunday when they learned both Kendall Newson, who had emerged as the No. 3 receiver, and backup cornerback Alphonso Roundtree needed surgery and most likely are lost for the season.  In an attempt to shore-up their sinking ship, the Dolphins have reached an agreement with free-agent WR Antonio Freeman.  Will you have  any  Dolphins on your fantasy football team?  Not at this rate! 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Would you like StatLeader.com delivered to you fresh daily?  If you have ever registered at Yahoo, you can have StatLeader delivered to your MyYahoo page.    Log-in to your Yahoo account  Visit StatLeader.com  Click the "add to MyYahoo" graphic in our right sidebar menu  Click the "Add it" button on Yahoo   It's that simple!  We sincerely hope you enjoy StatLeader.com 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Trent Green , QB – Got his game together last year to earn top ten status. The question is can he do it again? On the plus side he has an offensive line that protects him better than Donald Trump protects his money. On the minus side, he is on the same team as TD machine Priest Holmes, and he has a receiving corps that rivals the quality of the Ford Pinto. Despite his numbers last year, I’m going to rank him no better than a high #2 Fantasy Football QB.   Todd Collins , QB – The good news – has connected on 77.3% of his passes over the last three years (vs. Green’s 60.2%). The bad news, that includes all 22 total passes attempted during that period (vs. Green’s 1516). If Green stays healthy, Collins will be lucky to reach double-digit attempts.   Priest Holmes , RB – Worship with the Priest.  Should be everyone’s first Fantasy Football draft pick.   Larry Johnson , RB – Fighting with Derrick Blaylock for the opportunity to backup Holmes. As long as Priest is healthy neither one will be worth anything.   Derrick Blaylock , RB – Fighting with Larry Johnson for the opportunity to backup Holmes. As long as Priest is healthy neither one will be worth anything.   Eddie Kennison , WR – Eddie has been pretty consistent the last two years. Unfortunately, that is consistently average. His 56 receptions ranked only 34th among all WRs last year. Add this to his current wrist injury and Eddie is a #3 Fantasy Football WR at best.   Johnnie Morton , WR – 34 is an important number for the KC WRs. Why? Not only did Kennison earn a 34th ranking, Morten garnered two more (34th in Receiving yards and 34th in TDs). My recommendation is to draft him to fill the 34th slot on your team.   Dante Hall , WR – Burned a lot of Fantasy Football owners last year who equated kick return abilities with receiving potential. Depending on how the current Kennison/Morton injury situation progresses he might get more touches, but don’t count on it.   Marc Boerigter , WR – Had an 8 TD 2002 and was listed as the “Super Sleeper” for 2003 by many Fantasy Football publications. We give him our “Titanic” award for the fastest sinking career.   Samie Parker , WR –  Sleeper Alert . Fast, unlike most of the rest of the KC receiving corps. Samie could work his way into the top 3 (or 2) as the season progresses. Watch him.   Tony Gonzalez , TE – This Tony award winner should be everyone’s first choice for your Fantasy Football TE slot.   Morten Andersen , K – If Morten Anderson married Johnny Morton would he be Morten Morton? (Disclaimer: No T. Owens-type inferences being made) A great kicker with not so great range anymore. He’s still good enough to be ranked as a solid backup Fantasy Football Kicker.   KC Defense  – Another example of Doc’s rule #1. Real Season value and Fantasy Football value frequently have no relevance to each other. Last Year KC’s D was below average, ranking 29th out of 32, yet they put up great Fantasy Football numbers. A good part of this was due to Dante Hall’s kick returns. With teams kicking away from Dante more and more, the Chief’s D might not put up similar numbers this year. I would rank them a medium #2 defense. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We now move on to the AFC West and the Denver Broncos   Jake Plummer , QB – Jake had probably his best year ever this past season. Ho-Hum. While Plummer will probably put up decent numbers, I don’t expect anything spectacular. Last year his passing was used primarily to keep the opposing D’s honest for Clinton Portis. But Portis is gone, as are Shannon Sharpe and Ed McCaffrey. What’s left isn’t much for an average QB.   Danny Kanell , QB – You would be better off drafting the late Danny Thomas on your Fantasy Football roster.   Quentin Griffin , RB – I expect Griffin to win the starting job over newcomer Tatum Bell. (San) Quentin will likely do a good job, but lacks the power to reach the end zone on those goal line sets. Expect Mike Anderson to carry most of that load. As such, Griffin will probably be worth more in yardage leagues. Don’t be surprised if Bell sneaks ahead of him by mid season.   Tatum Bell , RB – Tons of raw talent and most likely the Bronco’s RB of the future. Given Denver’s Defense, their Offense probably won’t have to do a lot to win games. Expect Denver to bring him along at a moderate pace. Bell could be an excellent mid-season acquisition by the astute Fantasy Football owner.   Garrison Hearst , RB – About the only thing required for Hearst’s career this year is a hearse. Don’t even think about drafting him.   Rod Smith , WR – Smith will soon be old enough to star in the next “Cocoon” movie. He probably is a decent Fantasy Football # 3 WR.   Ashley Lelie , WR – What is it with all these “Girly” names? Tatum?? Ashley?? Lelie has a lot of talent, and he might have a great year - if only it was not Plummer throwing the ball to him. Get him as a low #2 or high #3 Fantasy Football WR.   Adrian Madise , WR – Yo Adrian…Talented but not domesticated. Don’t think about Adrian until mid-season.   Darius Watts , WR – Has all the tools. Keep an eye on him as a possible mid-season Fantasy Football addition.   Byron Chamberlain , TE – Shanahan likes to go to the TE position. Last year Shannon Sharpe was second only to Tony Gonzalez in number of catches, receiving yards and TDs. Unfortunately, Chamberlain is not Shannon Sharpe.   Jed Weaver  TE – “Come and listen to my story ‘bout a man named…” Well Doggies, those of you who think you are going to strike oil with ole Jed better take a dip in the Cement Pond. I think Ellie Mae will catch more passes.   Jason Elam , K – Top 5 on just about every list. In the rarefied air at mile high, he can probably keep his range up until he’s as old as say…Rod Smith. Oh wait a minute, he is. Still, he will consistently get you points and is a solid Fantasy Football #1 Kicker pick.   Denver Defense  - Already one of the best, the addition of John Lynch and Champ Bailey only increase the Fantasy Football value of this D 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>