<Blog>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haiizz.....first time writiing a real blog perhaps, today, august 16, 12.05,just played my ps winnin 11....lost to classic neth usin brazil 2 to 1...haaiizzz fought so hard, just like in life!!enough said of that, well i was jus waitin for my hair to dry and haf a gd sleep and recallin of what a great day i have today....great great one, then recalling bout tellin joey she got a great way of expressing her feeling thru tis blog thingy and was thinkin of writin it 2moro ,welll,, perhaps i wun , caz i 4gotten everythin...so y not , and why not write it rite now. So begginin with earli in da mornin, haf a bad bad hair day, cant get my hair straight, was like a slacker, so keep on combbin and was nervous ,scared tat i might b late as i was meetin liz at tanah merah.So after meddlin with it in n out de toliet, help mum put up clothes to dry, then finally settle down haf quick breakfast.then "rush out",kept lookin at watch. Soo....reach tanah merah at 11 sharp but she ain there, think too much , then call her, scared wrong place or sumthin like tat...(supid me).soo on and on i wait till she came bout 15 or so late,but it was pretty great lookin at the scenery. So "first time" realli with her, so look damn awkard...kind of hard to speak up, so start askin her sudden supid qns....hope she wun mind...den aft a while, saw her look rather sleepy...then ask her go slp. And there i was "alone", kept lookin around, then at her(she look funny and rather....ok,...i will say a small barbie doll sort of gal)nahh,....dun tink wrong.! So reachin boon lay still rather earli, and went walk in the shoppin mall juron point with her, and tok bout things(still akward but she damn a.aa...hh...cool(haha....)so aft a while, onli a while arron came, and aft a while all came ..so nx destination......TO CITY HARVEST CHURCH...yeah!!yearnin to that place as i heard it was rather grant... so we reach there and WOW!!! dammnnn stylo...so big n SO MANI PPLE ARRHHH....so squeeze in..and to the service and WOW again like a studio sort of thingy...so mani great faciltieS" as in de cameras n lightin. and on to the service ,i will give it TOP TUMBS UP to it ...fun and great de feelin i will say. and....then aft tat.....went squezzin for food(foolish us onli got jelly) then sat at a garden...eat then tis gal garadin or sumthin (opps) say i look like sum actor in hong kong(cherilyn aso say b4)hahaha...WAHAHA damn cool , how cum i dun knoe....k la, aft tat, we went to the wad brigde to see fireworks.errr....rewind....at orchard in goin to the bridge tok to JOEY,a gal i always wanted..to tok to,she unique i will say....so i ask her bout she likin gal thingy and we tok , and she got real great personality...(100%)but tooo...bad she sort of not like guys tooo...bad haiizzz....(i not sure wad im thinkin at tat moment thinkin bout me and her, joulbert and me, she and gals and her ex!???)nahh....jus a stupiid feelin of mine....feelin comfort,,,,love?...aft gettin to understan sumthin bout her...but i will say it still FAr far.....she too "mysterious and a great great unique person ..........onli tink i regret is she luvin galss....i was hopinnn....haizzz....STOP STOP i SAY STOP To u ,LEWIS dun ever think bout luv.....u dun deserve and u sux!!!ok?.......haizzz was completyy damnnn shattered a broken hole nv to b heall....nv nv ever....y is the whyss comin out and up  urlLink again1! !!!???????????nono!!!plss ........ k i got to get myself down..down okkkk......now , caryy on so we went on tokin ,as in me and joey towards the bridgy n watchin the fireworks.....one thing linger in my mind,,,as in me not touchin gals.......but tat is sumthin i dun understan.......guyS,,are flirts r jerks, statisfie on touchin on flirtin(ok...4get bout tat, but here;s a senario....if there;s is no law....most i will say most guys will surely go rapin .pple go on killin , bombin and such.......,,and i mean GUYS BOYS  MAN ,they got the genes the hormone , of sex ,of watchin nude ,porn watchin dirty stuff watchin gals flirtin touchin.....why wun they if there;s no law.(guys r guys,violence,sex and everythin hurtin) As of y there is "little" or i wil say limited rapes of molest is caz of law..!so wad if LAWS not there.)As for gals, nowadays havin 20+ bf is so normal i SAY NORMAL and havin lostt virginity is i will say 40% and who knoes, will my future wife b faithful or will i b, and willlll she still b a virgin ....hiya,,,,,jus thinkin too...much !!JUS TOO MUCHHH TTOOOO much......so me being "traditional" im not sure....me jus respectin jus keepin a clear consious jus hopin tat i wun touch other guys gf jus becaz i wan it or caz it is veri squezzy in here......and so who cares ,or i dun touch other pple aso touch ,or dun touch i will lose out......ARRHHH .......im jus tooo much in my stupiidd thinkins, or so joey is rite.....but joey i will say i will touch gals or i will say lay a hand on them , or gif a hug if they need a comfort or anithin;.....i willl do it.....i swear ....so joey , sori.....so sori.. for me havin tat thinkin...(if u still dun understan hang on to the last few lines) so aft fireworks ,,,,went to makan saw my  relative.......so misss them , thoought of my mum's dad and missin them (my realatives) too....jus too buzy.....wad if sumday sumthin happen wad IF?? i realli dun know ......havin to face reality is so hard.......*hope sum1 will lend me a shoulder now to cry it out loud*IM JUST LONELY........PLSss,............but i dun wan to get into commitments , scared to disspoint , to fail, to regret, to hurt for my selfishness for me wantin to study ,to b free...and aso i will totally haf no time ,.....all day lg at sch,,,,,,not even a time to spend wif mmy family....slackin on my studies..!!!!(i realli dun understan too.......am i too wantin to b perfect , am i a perfectionist as my horoscope tells me????im tryin to chg, hopin tat sum1 will cum into my life....to answer all my qns but not for me to gif her a comfirm commitment.....(hope u undestan)..!!so enough said, we wentt to carefour for drinks n went up to a garden......tok bout flloorball...took pics...aso at the church aso took pics......haizz kept thinkin of why joey is .......sum1 likin gals.....why why why??how can i or whoever chg she or ,,,,,my friend ..cherilyn aso.....!!???why ?so aft drinkin, it's bout 10+ b4 we start to leave ,went to wait for taxi....keep...worryin bout the wanderin joey.....dun knoe why ....scared sumtin bad happen to her....(im realli not sure to let her see tis.....things might turn out like she n joulbert.....no perhaps nv nv ever....goin to keep it to myself ..tis blog is secret!!)so finaly got a taxi....kept thinkin and thinkin......(*why am i a worrier, im thinkin now*)then got to the taxi........got my arms on joey and on liz ....me look like a flirt or sumthin haha(like junwei but not so overboard)jus gettin comfort, *dun knoe why* a sumthin tat overruns my loneliness.....haf i fall in luv mood tonite(though i was goin to haf a bad day earli iin da mornin ....as i did sumthin (Bad....?) the nite b4.......but it turns up a great great day at nite n in the whole....it jus so great)so i was in the taxi......wif liz onli when joey went off.....and my arm stilll kind of lyin on her arm....still dun mind.....still dun mind so perhaps this is FEELing ....a feelin man needs, a feelin of comfort , a feelin of sumthin ,sumthin tat is totally indescribable?......so>was in the taxi ......then the taxi uncle ask 2 of us sumthin ....a quiz....(btw he is an engineer and lives at orchard or so call live b4)ask us wad is the river that is behind the coffeeshop opppsite centrepoint, then in the end said bout leadin along orachard and sumthin like tat...cant recall dun knoe why....was lookin and thinkin while lookin at liz......(does she has a bf .........?? nah...but i swear no feelins to her...jus feel tat she seems so lonely too.....so ke lian.......?haiiz who knoess wad she needs? )and then the uncle ask sumthin again .......what is prevously in the pst at the exact location of ngee ang city..........and we started guesin ......hospital.? school?raping centre(wahhahaa)laammmmee me.....base then i carryy on til i say grave yard and hit the target....and wow ...correct and uncle say rumour say 1 storey pple say haunted.....so carryin on til liz house,,,,wow she lives and bungalow.....and aft she left .....i ask uncle if he witness accidents aft yrs of taxi drivin .........he told me a few and we started tokin........til he ask me a math qns....which is haiizzz.......a hotel stay cost 30 dollars...and 3 pple went to book it ..so which is to say .....1 pple pay 10 .but on tat day there was an discount off $5 which left $25 ....so havin 5 dollars...they gave the person tips of $2 which leaves them $27 for thm to book the rooms......and tat each one got $1 back....rite?.....so here goes.....each one pays $9 to book de room......and tat (tis is wad i dun understan)9*3=27 and+the $2 tat was given as tips which is total $29 , so where did the $1 goes to??????helpp!!no ans was given and wad was more funny is tat ........the uncle say go back solve it with ur gf which he means liz.....Haizzz......but i jus kept quiet .....left taxi back home and here i am......1.20 alreadi.......music on,,,,,,,lights off......got traiinin 2moro got to wake up earli.......but sumthin still lingers.....who was it today ?joey or liz....................?who knoes...neither ....im not the one neither.......so sayonara..........gd nite...*muacks*like ta pastor says dun worrry about anithing"!!!! worryin time til then ....WAHAHAAa......jus luv LOVE COMFORT but Dun understan feelings ???and why why why ??? 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A man came out of his home to admire his new truck. To his puzzlement, his three-year-old son was happily hammering dents into the shiny paint of the truck. The man ran to his son, knocked him away, hammered the little boy's hands into pulp as punishment. When the father calmed down, he rushed his son to the hospital. Although the doctor tried desperately to save the crushed bones, he finally had to amputate the fingers from both the boy's hands. When the boy woke up from the surgery & saw his bandaged stubs, he innocently said, " Daddy, I'm sorry about your truck." Then he asked, "but when are my fingers going to grow back?" The father went home &amp; committed suicide.       Think about this story the next time someone steps on your feet or u wish to take revenge. Think first before u lose your patience with someone u love. Trucks can be repaired. Broken bones & hurt feelings often can't. Too often we fail to recognise the difference between the person and the performance. We forget that forgiveness is greater than revenge. People make mistakes. We are allowed to make mistakes. But the actions we take while in a rage will haunt us forever. Pause and ponder. Think before you act. Be patient. Forgive &amp; forget. Love one and all. If you judge people, you have no time to love them. -- Mother Teresa 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm...........jus create tis.....looks rather wad i always wanted .......frm young....but no time to write on bk and aso at home no privcy 1...tat's wad i hate.....but now havin tis..tryin tis.... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>