<Blog>

<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I spent my entire weekend (well, the waking hours part at least) at the Northampton Balloon Festival. The amount of free stuff I got was ridiculous. Particularly from the RAF/ATC stand I was working on. I have compiled a complete list of everything free I got from the weekend-  RAF Careers Wallet (in a rather gay powder blue) Stickers of various RAF planes x about 20 An RAF Roundel Badge 6x little fluffy things with the sticky feet One poster of a plane I can't quite identify One RAF pen One Northampton College pen RAF "Way of Life" CD Bendy rubber thing RAF Bottle Opener RAF roundel Keyring Northants Police keyring RAC "Drive Alive" keyring Multiple Del Monte fruit drinks Multiple Banana Milkshakes (from the Nintendo Konga Beach Tour) One free slice of goodfellas pizza various free bits of cheese Several RAC sweets and last but certainly not least nearly a dislocated neck.  The story behind the last one is quite simple. At the (excellent, may I add) Nintendo Konga Beach tour, there was an attraction called "Mario's Surf Run". It was basically a large inflatable alleyway with an elastic rope at the end. you were strapped to the rope, given a few bananas, and told to place them as far down the alleyway as you could. Excellent fun. And then you had all the fun of being twanged backwards at high speed. However due to my own daftness, I flipped right upside-down, bounced around my head as one would on a pogo stick, and then fell over. It didn't hurt a bit when I did it yesterday, but now it hurts when I look too far in either direction and when I yawn. Oh well, it was still excellent fun (and may I add that I totally destroyed Mark Longland's banana-placing record).  I also bought a mirror on a stick (for nitexs and for being a pervert) and a magnet on the end of a stick (for picking things up and irritating people). And a chair. For sitting on (duh!).  And I gave away umpteed million stickers to small children. The greedy little cunts. And I may have recruited someone to our squadron. We'll have to see if he turns up to our next intake.  Balloonist friends of my father didn't turn up, curse them. So I didn't get a single chance to blag a free flight. Or to run across the arena, pursued by security guards. Oh well. 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's amazing how much good a party can do you. Yesterday I was quite willing to slit my throat, along with the throats of several other people. But following a night out with a bunch of mates, I quite honestly could not be much happier. Maybe I'm just temperamental.  Anyway, tonight I went bowling along with about a third of the squadron. And I didn't lose at all. I won both games (five strikes in one night, a personal record), and I then proceeded to thrash Ollie Slough at air hockey (or whatever the game with the paddles and the puck and the floaty table is called). Overall I really am quite proud of myself.  And of course tomorrow looks quite bright as well. I'm wandering down the Northampton Balloon Festival (probably with a few friends) and I plan to loiter around the Nintendo booth because I am a sad geek. But hey, that's my role in life and I plan to enjoy it.  Anyway, if there is anyone reading this (which I am now seriously beginning to doubt), may you have many enjoyable things happen to you, as I really am feeling quite fluffy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Why am I blaming it on everyone but her? 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Interesting things have happened since last time I blogged. This morning I ran all the way round my block, and I haven't quite recovered since. It was nearly two and a half hours ago, but I'm still trembling slightly. Perhaps I should go back to bed. Hmm.  My mate Andy came online on MSN last night after having disappeared for several weeks to Cornwall, and he was quite severely drunk. He'd drunk either a pint or a litre of malibu (can't remember which). And there are few things funnier than the results of a drunk person typing. His attempt at spelling "thought" "thouyyoug" nearly sent me off my chair. I'm kicking myself for not saving the convo so I could post it here.  Another interesting thing- I'm taking a pretty girl to the cinema on wednesday. This sort of thing doesn't normally happen to me, so I'm reasonably overjoyed about this. I won't name her here right now, as people who actually know me might get a bit surprised. If anything comes of it I might name her on wednesday (or thursday, or whenever I blog after going).  Oh, and a catchphrase for today- "shit doesn't happen, it's a fucking noun!". 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      First things first, last night I went on a Nitex. Basically wandering around in greens and camo paint in a wood, trying to avoid the Hunter Force and get to certain locations. I got stuck in an all-girl team (bar me, of course). And one of them was my sister. And I was supposed to be leader. Can I please ask someone what chance I stood of getting them to do anything I wanted? We did end up going roughly the direction I wanted to travel, but that was just about how far they listened to me. But I was amazed, greens actually are very good camouflage. My team kept disappearing and reappearing as they moved in the dark. Very cool. Wasn't half glad of the shower I had afterwards though.  I got a letter from Pizza Hut this morning saying that I didn't get a job there. This is fair enough. It may even have something to do with it being Friday the 13th. But I'm enraged about the fact they sent it a full two weeks after the interview, nearly a month after I applied! I needed a summer job, and thanks to the cunts there, I now have under a month of holiday left to find another job! Looks like I'll be pushing trolleys around B&amp;Q from the looks of things. Cheers Pizza Hut, you've made my summer. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It may or may not interest you to know that I nearly wrote a book once. In the end it didn't happen for the same reason most things I plan to do don't happen- sheer abject laziness. But hey. Anyway, I will now proceed to tell you the basic outline of the greatest story never told. Don't mind if it contradicts itself or just sounds rubbish, this is basically only a plot outline. If you feel that you can write this book, please feel free. Just remember to send me a percentage of the royalties.  Story starts, we have one bloke who's captured by angels after doing a good deed, one bloke kidnapped by devils after doing a bad deed. Both are given godlike powers and are told that they are the weapons in a war between heaven and hell, which will be staged on Earth. Winner takes all, losers are wiped off the face of the universe.  Devils and Angels then begin slaying living people left and right, and the people become spirit warriors for the side that killed them. This is because spirit warriors are quite difficult to hit compared to soft fleshy humans.  Stuff happens, and then we get to the anticlimax of the book. The armies of heaven and hell race against each other, all set for a stunningly cool battle. Two godlike blokes begin having a matrix-style kung fu war with lots of magic effects thrown in as well*. However they soon discover that neither of them can win as they are both equally matched. They begin talking and discover** that the angels/devils that recruited them were actually not angels/devils at all, just vastly powerful beings playing a kind of chess with the human world as we know it. They then gather the armies of Earth (as well as all the spirit warriors) and march against the beings fiddling with human affairs. In one cool final battle they destroy those that created them and then they both die, due to them not being needed any more.  I then proceed to rake in money from hardback editions of the book, film rights, and merchandise (specifically spirit warrior cuddly toys).     *Alright, so maybe I also planned a film version as well. Is that so wrong?  ** Via some cool plot elements  I failed to mention.  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've got myself a blog. Colour me proud. Now I have to face the moral dillemma I have with blogs that stopped me getting one before.  This is the dillemma. I want a blog to post all my personal stuff and have people I don't know comment on it, as they're impartial observers. However this then runs into the thing that most of the people who read my blog will be people I send the link to (i.e. my friends). This defeats the point of looking for impartial observers as the observers will be friends in a situation to remove the michael, the piss, and quite possibly my dignity. Such as it remains. Anyway. So the problem I have is that I cannot actually post anything I want to post in my blog. Unless all my friends look the other way. I know. I'll post whatever I want, and if you happen to know me, close the page now (but not before commenting, because that way I know not to post anything else).  Let's see how that works out. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>