<Blog>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have always written articles for an email list that I run but the thought of creating a blog never caught my attention. This seems to be a nice place to express one's views, but how many people do really read these pages? I would have to experiement with this and see what I can make of the traffic! Tell me what do you think of this article I wrote recently.     Simplicity   Some of us are complex thinkers albeit simple talkers while others are simple thinkers but complex talkers. The complex thinkers try to simplify concepts and use minimal words to drive their point home. The complex talkers on the other hand, pride in inundating us with a plethora of verbiage that is beyond a normal man's linguistic artillery. If you read the previous line twice you exactly know what I mean. If you have ever read Dilbert's comic strip on manager's colloquial-ness then you have a fair enough idea as to how abstract and pointless some conversations can be. I would like to share a story that I read some time back on the pointlessness of complex language and why more often than not, it is a mechanism to camouflage the underlying lack of knowledge of the orator.  Once upon a time there was a small village nearby a small town, where there was a small school with its share of inquisitive students. On a bright sunny day, one bright student was puzzled by the nature of the glass that covered their windows. He was very curious about how light seemed to pass through glass and not through the stony walls. Unable to control his inquisitiveness, he asked the teacher "Teacher, why does light pass through glass?" The teacher blurted out "Because it is transparent, you fool! How can you not know that?!" The student having never heard of the word "transparent”, felt very ashamed about his lack of knowledge and quietly sat down. He was astounded by the answer and wondered why he never understood it, while every one in the class seemed to have grasped it. He thought to himself "It will take me ages of study to be as smart as my teacher!"  The word transparent actually means "capable of transmitting light so that objects or images can be seen as if there were no intervening material". The student's question was exactly curious about this very nature of glass, "why does glass behave so?!" I am sure Newton must have asked himself the same question years ago, only he was fortunate enough not be among the bright teachers or thinkers of his time!  What we learn from the parable is quite simple. We should not be disappointed by those who do not appreciate your questions, for they do not know the answers themselves. Those who really know the answers will provide you with what you need. There will always be strong opinioned people with a very shallow knowledge base who will ridicule you for questioning their authority or their beliefs or their assumptions or some times their understanding of how the world works. But that should not discourage us from having the courage to ask a question and also have the patience to find out the answers. If you don’t know an answer to a question, have the courage to admit it, instead of wrapping your answers in dialects that no one can really perceive. It is quite surprising how the answers to some of our questions have the capacity to change the understanding we have about ourselves. Some simple questions like “Why does the apple fall from the tree while the moon stays where it is?” have even ushered in a new era of science and technology! As Einstein rightly put it “universe loves simplicity and beauty”. Simplicity is divinity. Now that's a complex thought! 
</post>


</Blog>