<Blog>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HAHA! TAKE THAT FIENDS! I AM NOW THE ALMIGHTY MASTER OF THE HOUSE!  Y'ALL = OWNED!!!! PWNZ00RED!!!!!  MWAAAAHAHAHAHAHAHA!!!!!!!!!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok, everybody's admin!  I just had tea with my professor and Linda for THREE AND A HALF HOURS.  He's so awesome.  And British.  I'm experiencing a plateau of euphoria.  Tonight I'm going to see "Princess Diaries 2."  It's Linda's idea.  Just to clarify.  How are you all doing?  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i want admin toooooooo.....o_O weeeeee!!!!!   i want admin toooooooo.....o_O weeeeee!!!!!  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Right   here. Yeah, should I be Moony (as with us) or Captain Jesus (as with Halo, RadicalD, etc.)? i think i'll stay Moony.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, well...nobody can say I didn't join.  So, yeah!  Where's Moony? 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Charlie made the first post! Whoo! Actually, the other members have yet to join. I re-sent their invitations though. I don't think they got them the first time. But Charlie, I made you an administrator, which gives you special powers or something. You should take advantage of those. It will be a glorious blog!  
     

    
</post>

<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is Charlie, Just saying hi. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, that's right.  I have no teeth.  And I look like a chipmunk.  Well, not so much anymore, but I did.  You can ask Lilly.  I have so much frickin' AP summer work to do that I simply have not started.  I mean, I've got... ten days.  FUCK, I am screwed.  Ok, I have to read  The Catcher in the Rye  now.  See y'all later!  Actually just Moony, since the rest of you DON'T READ THIS. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So what are all of your schedules?  We have to have classes together.  Here's mine:   Physics  VHS  Chem  Lunch  Español  Español  English  English  Euro  Human Geo   Add "AP"/"Honors" where necessary. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah Prongs!  I saw Alex at Redner's today!  That just made my day.  I was thinking "YEA-AH!"  (That's supposed to be 'yeah,' but sort of with two syllables... yeah.)  Sheer clarity.  (Clarity = totally awesome/complete awesomeness, etc.)  And then I drove next to him at that intersection between Collegeville Crossing and Redner's.  IT WAS AWESOME.  That just goes to show, The House is meant to be.  Fate draws us all together.  It's true. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so i'm guess the two other losers don't read this.... 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I have found THE PERFECT SAND for Charlie's room.  I bottled it.  You all have to check it out.  It's so SOFT!  Like COTTON!  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>