<Blog>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I once did this thing with my friend Jesse where she stood somewhere in New York and I stood somewhere in Vermont.  One of the things I loved about it was that I felt that in some way it was like we were sensors or spies for each other and for the earth.  Like I had some obligation to really sense and experience my immediate environment in Vermont, so that I could  send her , or so that we could both  send the Earth  the sensations we were receiving.  It is related to a creation myth I have in my head where God creates the Animals and Man, not because he is lonely, but because God lacks eyes and ears and wants a more visceral experience of his own creation.  On Wednesday, when I mentioned this to Tom R., he told me about a buddhist meditation retreat he went to where at meal time he was told to taste and experience his food, not merely for himself, but for all the spirits and ghosts of the earth who can no longer have the visceral experience of taste.  As a proxy.  He said that all of the people at the meal were lending their taste buds and noses to the dead.  Tom and I were eating sushi.  It is a powerful idea.  Putting it into practice has a profound effect on me, and also it feels really right.  Hoping to do something similar with some people in  urlLink iraq  sometime soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes someone else's way of being and moving in the world makes such an impression on me that it starts to work through my system and something in me gets healed or completed by it.  So as I was going to say on Wednesday, this is going on with Otto Ramstad's way of being and moving.  The crux of it seems to be about feeling my power coming from throughout my body, from every cell and my whole being (and especially including my eyes), rather than from specific locations I am used to feeling power from (my arms and forehead, mostly).  I find that when I think about this, it changes the whole alignment and positioning of my spine.  My eyes and head move back in alignment with everything else and my shoulders drop and my motion becomes stronger feeling, and I can move my legs faster, too.  The first time I really paid much attention to Otto was when he was leading the closing circle at the western mass moving arts festival.  We were supposed to clap 29 times in a pattern and then say "HO!" and I saw that when he made that powerful sound it was like his whole body became engaged and sure of itself and powerful, and he loved it.  The following day, in the workshop, he led an exercise where we went back & forth, moving parts of our body and then thinking about moving the whole, or moving from every cell.  It was a breakthrough for me.  Two days later he led another exercise where we pushed and pulled and yielded and reached with our eyes alone.  I found that just thinking of my eyes as powerful and engaged changed my posture.  This is not even to mention everything he and Olive presented about human anatomy, and all the warmups and exercises he led which involved considering our bones, tendons, ligaments, organs, muscles, vasculature, lungs, etc, in all their glory and power.  Nor to mention the way that they both feel they are part and parcel with the natural world, which is powerful and nothing to be ashamed of.  Good stuff.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When I have emotions that I haven't given myself time to fully feel, parts of my body freeze up, my movements are constricted, and I can no longer make the progress that I want to make in dance.  At least I think that is what is happening.  The thing I need to do in these circumstances is take time to feel the things that I need to feel.  It's not easy though -- I find that I need all of the following ingredients before I can feel something that I'm scared to feel:  * a suitable time and place, away from most people * permission not to be doing anything else * self-love * courage & relaxation * hope * faith * explicit invitation:  asking myself what I'm feeling * patience * permission not to focus on the pain, but to mix in rejoicing, reveling, and being one with the world.  If I do all these things, I find that something sweeps through my body and afterwards there is a loosening and relaxation and a greater sensitive to joy and the possibilities of the movement and to the state of my own body.  Sometimes I also become aware of other emotions, or of physical sensations (like back pain) that I wasn't aware of in my previous, less-sensitive state.  This can be trouble if these new perceptions scare me, because if I am unwilling to feel them -- or if I focus on them too narrowly -- then I am back in square one 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Had a tremendous dance w. Jeff Bliss at the noho jam tonight.  He said he was in a company with Ray Chung, Chris Aiken, and Nancy.  He said I reminded him of John Marinelli in the way that I move into and out of character while remaining grounded in physicality, and that he hadn't had many dances like that since John died.  He said something about Kirstie Simpson.  He said he was sad that he didn't have money to do workshops when I told him about BodyCartography.  During the dance I was doing Otto's exercise, where I was relating my inner spaces to those around me and inside Jeff.  I believe I have something deep to learn from this exercise.  It seems simple but it is a different kind of consciousness.  It also serves to keep me grounded as I dance at the edge of my ability.  There are other things I am trying to grok right now:  * Something about the way Otto holds his head and uses his eyes, and the way those things affect his entire posture and stature and power, has been working its way through me.  I'll write more later.  I was just told that I'm going to have to move out of my wonderful dance space/apartment.
     

    
</post>


<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just sent the following letter to a Norwegian dude who's been helping out this school in Baghdad:      Hi.  I'm a modern dancer near Boston in the USA.  So as to raise   awareness and a feeling of connection with the people of Baghdad here   in the USA, I was thinking of having a dance performance that is   performed simultaneously in cities here and in Baghdad.  All I would   need is a single willing dancer in Iraq who could learn the steps.  Or   we could work out the steps together.    I was wondering if you had an email address for anyone at the Baghdad   school.  Or postal mail if there's no email.    Thanks a lot,     Joe Edelman    Northampton, MA.  USA.  
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I thought I'd start with some links to the kinds of things I'm interested in exploring in this blog.  See also my  urlLink links page .  Movements   urlLink urban exploration  and  urlLink industrial archaeology  are about exploring &amp; documenting the hidden, off-limits places in cities, like underground tunnels and abandoned buildings.   urlLink site-specific dance ,  urlLink parkour ,  urlLink skateboarding ,  urlLink breakdancing  and  urlLink graffiti art  are all activities which can act to recapture public or off-limits urban spaces.   urlLink flashmobs  are internet-organized, very-brief gatherings of large crowds.   urlLink geocaching  is a sport where people hide gift packages for each other, often in the wilderness or on derelict urban land.   urlLink land mail art objects  include art gifts sent in the mail between strangers, notebooks that make it around the world several times and return to their origin, etc.  they are part of an even larger internet-coordinated  urlLink random acts of kindness  movement.   urlLink locative media ,  urlLink tactical cartography , and  urlLink psychogeography  are all terms used by artists and hackers to describe a nebulous bundle of location-aware art, technology, and political action.  Individual Projects   urlLink the degree confluence project  is attempting to have ordinary individuals photograph all those location where latitude and longitude lines meet on the globe.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>