<Blog>


<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      there is this new mt dew  called pitch black. its pretty good to. it taste like grape dr.pepper. yumm. and i learned how to play insomniac by greenday on guitar. kick ass. i got my school clothes in junk today. yay! so much fun going to the mall and all the other stroes with my brother and mom. atleast i got new clothes out of it. it is hott in here. i am turning on the air.  my gramdma wants me to go to chutch cuz i kno how to make a dog with a balloon! HAHA that is so easy but they got free food so maybe i will go. lol! i m gunna put a picture in here cuz i found a button u can do that with.   co0l! never mind u got to down load sumthing. my computer doesn't need anymore stuff on it.  i am finally figureing it out. wish i would have before this summer but i got lots more. you see i had problems when people i cared about had problems. even rite now with pj scoty and richard. the whole katie thing was i cared about her. but now i see that i can have no problems if i want. it my choice to do wut i want. i can care about u or i can not give a rats ass about u. one or the other. and if i care about u then u r either a good friend or a gurl friend. and those people like wut i like and hate wut i hate. not mix and match. so if u like bush i anit ur friend and if u dont like weed then u can go some were while i choke on the chief. wut i m saying is that if we dont match dont come to me compling. and if u got problems and i dont really kno u anit gunna care. if u kno me u would kno that i wouldn't care and u wouldn't of came to me!  so has ur mom told u cant be a asternaut? cuz retarded people can't become asternauts loser 
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this hole summer was fun and sucked some ass. i could of not did some things but i could of did something twice. but i anit making a bet ove a gurl ever again in my life, cuz thats wut really ruined my summer. and some how i dint move on. i should of. i should of said theres more gurls out there that would fuck me but i had to have her. and she was mad cuz i mad a bet on her with a buddy of mine that now me and him hate each other now. i dono i agree'd with the bet so its my fault but some anit. like richard's gay ass narced on me scotty and pj. i ont understand why he even hung out with us.  but sleepin on katies porch and seeing richard get hit with a throwing card and cry like a lil baby. dressin up like chicks and smoking the with the carnies. those were fun days. but now jerry is moved in and he brother is hella cool. so i am gunna start school and stare at the wall when bad shit happens and pretend it dont happen cuz i dont need a reason damn it!  and another thing is that i with never have a gurl frined that don't think politicly, legaly, and music wise like me. that means kerry, weed aand rock! yupp now i got carple tunnle from typing so much so good day lady look alike!  
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i rememered this time hahahahaha grey!!! i got 4 grams cuming and i wanna do it so bad but i am gunna stash it. cuz i need to lay low for a lil bit. cuz i dont need a reason damn it! i need a new guitar bad. damn it! pj got on and i am bord n hungry and this is gettin gay so bubi!!!!!!!!  
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      pj got caught. cuz of richards dum ass. he had to rat on us. i am beating his ass. and pj likes wanna kill himself. he is gunna ask out masy and like tiffany i dono. she likes me but i dont know. pj is running away tomorrow i mite go with him. i need to get drunk high and laid. lol 
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damn was was hung over so bad today. i passout in katies yard. it was crazy. i can only remember i had to go get chris then i drunk some more and then andy and katies brother were trying to get katie to go to bed cuz she was drunk and wanted to do chris. then chris lefted and i was siting on the couch and katie started yelling at me fer sumthing. then she got really mad at me and told me to sleep outside and i did. it was freezing but fun!! i was drunk off my ass. and then today i woke up and went home and tore the bathroom apart trying to find some chaser but there was none. then tiffany and shelbie and some dude named kavin came over. i was watching blade 2 and kevin was liking the vampires killing each other!! lol tiff wasn't. she told me to call her but i dono if i am gunna go fer her cuz she does wanna go ouyt with anyone so whats the use. my grampa came and said he walked in on sumthing. lol my mom says she is gunna get a letchure from my grandma lmao!  i didnt do a color its pink! my favorite color!!!!!!!!!!!!!!   
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i just ate some nasty ass pudding. it tasted like play dough. it was so nasty. plus it had nuts in it. my mom says  it like pastashio pudding but i say it crapio pudding cuz its crap. good news i got 5 dollars. yupp $5.00! i got regesterd too. my mom was all up in my biznus for not getting a hair cut. my hair looks fine. i m not getting a hair cutt. katie has lunch with me and nikki has 2 class with me and grant has advisory with me. his birthday is tomorrow. i wanna go but pj n them and my house is gunna be empty so...... i fegot to pick a color to day and it is this peachy color. dont u feel peachy!!!!!!!   i m gunna go get some cool ass icons n stuff and maybe later go to see tiff. i m gunna ask her out!!!! i m gunna get laid again finally!!  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its day time  green is the color for today. ya green hip hip hore ay!! i want a new guitar but they cost a lil more money than i got so maybe christmas time i will get one. thats new my new goal after a car. if gramps gives me that honda that would be so sweet cuz that car rocks. it got s the auto matic seat beats but a tape player. yea!!!  
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i m at my aunts house rite now. it blows like usual cuz i got to watch the heath andrew again but i am gunna get paid so its ok. money for me. i got no music here.it really sucks ass. katie anit mad at me no more. i guess she was just playing around or something. i dono but we are cool now so.. but pj said josh dont like me but i talk to him sometimes. damn DUDE I NEEDSOME MUSIC!!! red is cool..and tiffany got some kind of lip desises but i am gunna ask her out when it heals. i dont wanna catch a desisease. dans green is so good. i took one hit and i could stand up straight. it was crazy. ummmmm i got nuthin else to say......... mega deth rules!!!!! fuck metallica!!!!     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its late but not really late  it is time. i am talking to this chick and she is so cool. i got her screen name from this blog thing. sheplay guitar and has a boyfrined named adam. thats crazy!!  
    
</post>


</Blog>