<Blog>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      [/neutral mood] [bad mood]  There are very few things in this world that irritate me.  Verbal and physical abuse generally bounce off of me with all the love of those little fabric softener sheets that are shamelessly plugged by a fluffy brown bear.  I rarely show any extremes of emotion.  Today I was on the verge of a certified outbreak.  It was just one of those days when things just irritated me a little more than normal.  I live in the Florida panhandle, a place that has become known to me as 'Little Georgia'.  I was out driving in town on my way to purchase a particular brand of entertainment which the masses refer to as 'Madden 2005'.  On my mini-journey, I was required to pass by an icon of southern culture, a shopping center of vast dimensions known as a 'Walmart Supercenter'.  This place is the southern equivalent of a circus or some strange traveling carnival.  As I maneuvered my car of death through the traffic leading towards the bargain-shopper's temple, I was staggered by the plethora of ignorant drivers which this bastion of southern hope attracted.  Navigating the three lanes of traffic isn't supposed to be this damn exciting.  A great proponent of obesity with a mass of gray, disheveled hair gave his best effort to run me off of the road when he thought it was convenient for him to switch lanes.  I should have let him hit me and trash his fucking 1942 POS truck with the nauseous clouds emanating from his rusted tail pipe.  I sped past him barely able to contain the urge to shout profanities and run his busted-ass truck off the road.  As if this pillar of the redneck community wasn't enough for me on this short venture, I next passed a rusted brown minivan.  Behind the wheel of this instrument of mass transportation was a middle-aged woman with fewer teeth than my god damn grandma.  Now, this in itself is nothing out of the ordinary for Little Georgia, but what really disturbed me and has so far successfully robbed me of sleep was her personalized license plate that read 'LUVPUMP'.  I did a double take and almost rear ended the car in front of me...  Now, finally at my wit's end, I arrived at the parking lot of the local mall.  The first aisle I come to has an SUV just backing out of a prime parking spot and preparing to leave the premises - or so I thought.  After he successfully backed out of his spot, I turned in behind him.  Though he didn't drive away like I had thought.  Instead, this fucking dipshit sits on his cell phone yakking away while the ass end of my car is still stuck out in the road waiting for him to pull forward.  I remain there for thirty seconds or so before I become fed up and back my vehicle back onto the street.  I drive ahead looking for the next open parking spot.  Up ahead I see two women looking to cross the street.  At this point I'm ready to just run somebody the fuck over, but I resist the urge once again to inflict grievous harm on a member of the southern community.  I fall back into my docile mold and cheerfully wave for them to cross the street ahead of me.  They wave their thanks and proceed across.  However, for some unknown reason, they stop right in the middle of the fucking road and begin pointing around the parking lot, perhaps looking for their vehicle.  Now, when I am granted a pass to cross the street ahead of any motorist, I do so expediently so as not to make the aforementioned motorist wait any longer than absolutely necessary.  However, for some reason, these two women, for whom I had now fostered a deep hatred for, thought that they were indeed the only beings of importance in the entire world.  There they sat in the middle of the road trying to find their car and backing up traffic on the road.  I seriously doubt that the ten yards it would take for them to cross the damn road would have disoriented them any more than they obviously already were.  gah!  I'm done with this for now.  I must say a couple things in closing however.  The very select few people I actually know personally from the south are normal people who are fairly considerate of those around them.  Its the south in general that tends to disgust me - or at least the local inhabitants of Little Georgia.  If you the reader are from the south - do not take offense to this little rant.  However, if you do take offense, then you most likely fit one of the descriptions of the assholes above and you should keep your fucking ass off the road and stay home.  If that is the case, then I hope you are offended.  [/bad mood] [neutral mood]  Have a nice day. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Let me take you through an ordinary day for me - at least ordinary until I start up school again in a couple weeks. I woke up bright and early....I think it was around 12:30pm. I would have slept longer had it not been for the sun and his evil rays invading my bedroom and pillaging the darkness I had hidden myself in. So, I gathered myself for a moment and rolled over onto the floor. With my face pressed into the carpet and my ass pointed straight up posed to do battle with the sun's evil rays, I slowly came to my senses. I wiped the crusties from my eyes and blindly stumbled for the bathroom. Very rarely does a day go by where I do not inflict some sort of physical damage on myself. Sometimes these feats of daring are intentional, other times they are not. This day would be no different.  It began simply enough. My roommate was already up. We will call him Kiwi since he hails from New Zealand and apparently that is what they go by. I don't think I've ever called him by his rightful name, nor do I really have any desire to do so. He sat motionless watching TV as I banged my shoulder in my first attempt at getting through the bathroom door. My other eye opened at that point and things became much easier.  I only had minimal time to do my daily rituals of shit/shave/shower before I had to hasten to work. Work was about 40 minutes away and began promptly at 3pm. So I had about an hour and change to do the necessities. Plenty of time.  Work was something I really didn't enjoy all that much - not that everyone loves their job, but I'm working for my sworn enemy - not many people can say that I don't think.  I really don't care for structure all that much.  I don't like stupid people, though I myself can sometimes fall into that category.  I don't like arrogant people who are put in charge based solely off of their time in their job and how they scored on some fucking test.  People shouldn't just be given responsibilities based solely on these merits.  Shit, some of the people that have been appointed over me wouldn't know their ass from a hole in the ground....as cliche as that sounds, its the damn truth.  Ignorance if fucking bliss.  But alas, I am forced to deal with these things day in and day out.  I can't really quit....not without going to jail anyway.  Yeah, if you haven't guessed by now, I'm in the military.  The branch of service is not important - they're all pretty much run just the same.  Me being of the ilk I described above working for the military seems kind of a paradox, much like braille on a drive up ATM machine.  However, it is just a means to an end and I play their game.  After all, the schooling is free and they offer to take a chunk out of my school loans which I had accumulated in my first attempt at a responsible lifestyle.  So into work I go.  Today wasn't anything special - a lot of people gone on leave today and only a small handful of us left over.  I think the one hilight of my night came when I threw small plastic caps (dust caps for electronic equipment) at the blonde I work with.  This was your typical junior-high flirtation at its worst.  It did not go without reward though - although not as I planned.  One of the caps landed on a table between us.  I got up out of my rolly chair to grab it before she could use it against me.  In the process of lunging forward, my chair rolled out from under me.  When I failed to acquire the dust cap, I jumped back to where I thought the chair was.  However, my luck being what it is, the chair wasn't there.  It had moved slightly back and off to the side and I think I could even hear it snicker as my arms flailed madly for that brief second before impact.  There I lay on the floor staring up at the ceiling tiles, the echoes of laughter filling my ears.  Well, it could have been worse I guess.  At least someone was entertained.  So....that was about it.  I won't bore you with the details of my work.  I'll just say it consists of butting heads with some of the more ignorant people placed above me.  I can't wait for school to start up again.  I'm between semesters now and I need something to take my mind off of this mindless crap. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I just opened this.....more to come.... 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>