<Blog>

<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       good morning... i'm in all blue this morning :-) my fav color! hhmmm...where shall i start...my weekend..kind of long boring weekend...except yesterday eve.i went out with Azwan, one of my close classmate back in form 2. its been like months we didnt see each other..everybody is busy with works, life..and so on... best gak sekali sekala lepak...byk citer..and non-stop laugh!thats for sure!hehehehe...Azwan i would consider one of my bestfren till now...even though we dont really communicate that often(just like Doe) but we manage to update each other once in a while. that whats friendship is all about.and she never forget my birthday!so sweet :-)    the rest of my weekend...the whole saturday was really an unproductive day for me...slept the whole eve. at nite watch tv.sunday morning went jogging with Anne.balik2 pastu penat slept till 2pm!hahahaha...then eve, went out with Azwan.at nite, watch vcd Stephen King's "IT" really scares me to death!!!then slept at about 12 something i guess...today, i'll have my netball training and tonite my futsal, kindaa miss my frens there coz its been like 2 weeks i didnt kick the ball!!hahaha...once u join it u got addicted to it.believe me!hahaha...i gtg now...some works to do...  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink          urlLink butterfly      Originally uploaded by  urlLink ::Butterfly:: .  
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       its gonna be a long boring weekend i guess...well..nothing much happened yesterday..after a long working day, i join my colleague play ping pong in front of our office!hehehe..and guess what??i'm palying with my baju kurung!believe it or not?hahahaha...it was fun game actually...eventhough i don't really know how to play..but they're very helpful...during the lunch time i played dart!hahaha.. this is the easiest one!i don't know...i just love to do all this activities...can help me reduce lots of tensioness actually, and can make me forget bout my problems for a while...well..now i'm into futsal and badminton. i joined sports club in my comp, and i played volleyball.but unfortunately we lose!hehe.. but nevermind, at least we tryed our best. i just feel like doing all this sports really help me alot...well..ppl always ask me, you already thin but why do u have to exercize?its just one of my hobby i would say...and just love doing it.i love jogging, specially early in the morning..and alone.feels so good...actually im kindda hungry rite now...can't wait to go back and have lunch...and i'm kindda sleepy a bit...hehehehe..gonna sleep the whole eve today...happy weekend...  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I miss my sayang, as usual..didn't see him for 3 days already...god i really dont know how to describe this feelings when i'm missing someone that i really love so much...its really hurting me inside.. dont know when he's free..i understand his situation rite now, i really do understand, but just can't stop thinking of him day and nite...miss u so much sayang..and luv u even more..each and every day... gonna love you forever sayang...      
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       finally...the 2 days audit day has ended...alhamdulillah...feels so relief!!!!and feels like i can breathe like a normal person again...hehehehe..and i can show back my smiles...not the fake one!tmrw there will be an exit meeting, and will summarize everything. thank god its over...for the time being laa....i really cant believe that this is really a tough job!well...at least i've experienced it once in a lifetime.hahahaha...  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       good morning...it was a really tiring day yesterday...after the tension audit session, i went to play badminton till 7.30pm i guess. then i went back, had my dinner with ellia and then go to sleep at about 11pm.quite early actually ... coz im so tired..my brain exhausted!!!hahahha...this morning another audit session..which will crack my head once again!!!hahahahahaha...i miss my sayang so much...really do...better move now, going to technical in a short while..all d best dear...i know u can do better.. :-)  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i just finished my first audit session which really CRACKED my head!!!!feels like i wanna throw out now!!this moment!!!aaaarrggghhhhhh!!!!!i hate this...but i have to do this....its feels like after hearing a long letures!!!! tomorrow will be the second day of this whole entire thing...well...i'm really 'looking forward' for it!hahahahha...wish me luckk...now im going to play badminton...to release bit of my tensionness...best of luck....  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      good morning!what a beautiful wednesday morning :-) i slept kinda early lastnite...after eating too much of cake!yesterday was actually my sis and my bro's birthday, so my mum bought a cake for my bro and we celebrate, just our family...but sadly my sis already went back to Perak...but we called her when we're singing the birthday song...hehehhe..so sweet..and she's kindaa blur!hahahaha... kelakar la plak.. finally manage to talk to my sayang...he's kind of busy lately since his mum is not around.so he have to take over everything that used to be done by the mom.dont worry sayang...of course i understand ur situation now...i'm always here if u need me. today...there's lots of thing to be done, my auditing thing will start today!!!and the golf is postponed to next month!!!yahooo!!!!i gtg now...got to do some work! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       morning....guess what...my sayang merajuk...god i really dont know what to do...it was my fault anyway...lastnite i went out for a drink somewhere in subang with ellia, and i told him.and he merajuk  coz i tak ajak him...sayang...i didnt mean to ignore u...earlier u said u was really tired so i was expecting u to rest at home and i dont wanna disturb u. but u take it as i forget bout u...sayang...of course i want u to come last nite but...i tak sampai hati nak suruh u dtg jauh2...i'm really sorry sayang.i luv u so much...i'm really sorry if i disappoint u...forgive me please sayang...i'm truly sorry.   
     
    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       God i can't believe this!!!!i passed the AUDITORS EXAM!!!the super duper damn hard exam which crack my head for bout 5 days!!!well...even though its not really good result, but at least i passed.hehehhee...Well...time to celebrate.cheers!  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       finally i got the place for the next golf event..in Palm Garden Resort, Putrajaya...i was so worried, afraid i didnt get any place...so one of my biggest task for today is done,now have to call back all the customers and tell them bout the new venue..lagi satu plak keje!!!aaaahhhh boringnyee!!!actually i'm really2 tired of all this so called GOLF thing!!!i hate it so much!!!but i have to do it somehow...till next year plak tu...this thing really make me sick sometimes, specially when dealing with all the bosses yg byk kerenah!what to do...im juz a small little creature who work here...nak tak nak kena tahan jer laa...      ya...now let me tell bout my weekend, it was kind of fun, on saturday evening, went to ucu's house, there's like a family gathering with AF!hahaha...and also celebrating ayah cu's bday. it was fun though i was really2 sleepy...i have to wait till the AF over baru nak potong cake!!!but the cake was really nice...blueberry chesse cake...yummy!! but just a bit dissapointed coz Linda and Adam won!!!so unfair!!i was really expecting Farah to win..but what to do..it was based on sms, so anybody can win, depends on how many ppl like and vote for them...but it was a sad ending. well...i dont really watch this reality show...but since my sister was at home and she keep the tv on that particular channel,somehow i have to watch it!!!so bored sumtimes.but she went to perak already, yesterday.so im gonna conquer the remote again!!!hehehhehe...(like i watch the tv???)hahahaha...actually i dont really watch tv, only once in a while like once a week, even my fav tv CSI pun dah lama tak tgk...kind of miss that series...alot of weeks actually i missed it!but what to do...lately got lots of works to do...      on sunday...got up quite early actually, do my laundry and wash my BEM :-) so damn dirty...hehehehe... then i waited for my sayang's call the whole eve...he didnt call :-(    i called him , and he told me that he can't come coz he have to stay at home.then he ask me to come over.i straight away wash my face (i just got up from sleep!hehehe)and went there, pick him up at his house and we had drink.then i send him back, coz he was really2 sleepy...ciann sayang i nie... but eventhough i just see him for bout 2 hours, its more than enough coz i really miss him!!!miss his hug so much!!then i went back, and prepare for tonite football match between blue and red house!!!   suria pick me up at bout 7.45pm and we went to uitm stadium.kindda boring game...i dont really enjoyed it since i dont like to watch, i only love to play (futsal). then my sayang called and he's coming :-) bestnyer...!!!! then he came and pick me up, we went for a drink somewhere there.and then we watch the match, and blue lost !!!;-( nevermind...then i got the medal for the volleyball match, 4th place!!!malunyaa!!!hehehhe...after that suria sent me back.       what a long weekend....hehhehhee..      tonite i got my futsal as usual, but dont know yet whether i wanna go or not...cam malas2 jer...heheheheh...tgk laa...  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i've been very busy since morning...kindda miss my blog! well...i'm still worried coz the golf place not confirm yet!!!!u gotta do sumthin!!!!!go to work!!!NOW!!!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Its almost 1pm...time to go back...God i really miss my Sayang..really thought that i can see him today but..he's busy..nevermind...he got something more important to do. of course i understand.but tomorrow i really have to see him. god i miss u sayang!really miss u so much!!!maybe i would go and have lunch with Dora. Called her just now..its been like..3 or 4 years didnt see her!the last time we met was in UUM, she came and sleep over at my room with her frens, lots of them actually...talking about Dora, she's one of my close buddy back then in Sri Aman when i was in form 3. She's very soft spoken person. very polite. sweet. actually we just love to lepak and chatting and gossiping bout the latest news!heheheh...then after form 3, she left to teknik school but that doesn't stop us from keeping in touch. we write each other regurlarly, every week infact we will write so called "diary" to tell about our activities for the whole week...and we exchange our SPM trial paper and past years paper, preparation for SPM.She helped me alot on that actually. then after SPM, she went to Uitm arau in perlis, and i went to UUM. but at that time we almost lost contact, then i manage to get her email and we communicate thru email. but as usual campus life is a bit different compared to school and everybody will be very2 busy at one time.we dont really communicate as often as before but we still KEEP IN TOUCH. then after graduation, and started working, manage to get her number and we call each other. but still have no time to see each other....heheheh (how busy we are!) well..i really hope she can make it today...kinda miss her!!...anyway...many thanks to the technology that never failed to keep us in touch with each other. its also actually depend on urself whether u wanna keep in touch with ur fren or not...coz if u really appreciate ur fren u'll never ever gonna forget them.like for me...i treasure every friendship that i have..and for me..   FRIENDS ARE FOREVER...  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I just hadmy breakfast ...fried mee with chicken...yummy! Its raining since i got up at about 7.00am i guess... kindda late actually. But manage to get here in the office by 8.25am...today i got to settle few things bout the Golf Tournament. and confirm with all the managers the place. but nothing much to do actually since boss is not here!heheheh...    Yesterday, i went back at 6.30pm and pick Ellia at komuter as usual.But it was really-really jam and i reach there round 7.30pm.Kesian Ellia kena tunggu lama...Sorry dear. I didn't see My Sayang yesterday, coz he's kind of busy at the workshop. But nevermind, i understand that..but i just can't stop myself from missing him..And i slept at 9.30pm i guess...the earliest since..2,3 months kot...dah lama tak tido awal...Then at 1.25am, tiba-tiba jer terjaga, and i thought its already morning!hahahah...Lucky i didnt take my shower...well..i almost did.hehehe..Then I called my sayang..talked for few mins and then i go back to sleep.   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        She will be similar to Leo woman in appearance. A slim woman who walks with confident and proud. She has an egg shape facial structure, high and round forehead. She likes to look straight as if she is searching. She is not a pretentious type and will always say what she thinks. You will see Virgo woman walks fast. She will try her best to be perfect, to look perfect and to feel perfect even though there is no such perfection. She is very delicate of what and how she dress. She is bright and easily despair with obstacles. She likes smart guy who will be compatible with her, so if you are a rich dumb guy, you can forget about her right now. She is not a very possessive or jealous person for she expect respect from her love one. She does not like a part time lover, or a temporary mate. If she finds her dream man, she will not go away. If she does not like you, she will always keep a certain distant. Act proper and appropriate is her discipline. She does not like and can not stand bad languages, cursing words or phrase. She likes a gentleman who open the doors for her. She wants to feel protected and when a man taking care of her, she will feel like a complete woman. She memorizes everything about other people and about herself very well. She can really keep secret, you can trust her on this. She likes a refreshing and a mild scent. She is very delicate in maintaining her beauty, so you could see she is seriously picking soap which match and most suit her skin. Do not comments her on this very picky habits, it is her happiness in working full times as a self beautifier. She is not an innocent angle for sometimes she can be as tough as steel. Even she easily despair, she is not the type to cry over it. She is a shy type, so making speech in front of the room can make her nervous even she walks and talks confidently. She only search for true love , not just any love. Her love is an ideal one. She likes to think no one is neater and as effective as her, which can irritate you sometimes for there is no such thing. She likes sweet talk, but she can slip and say something unpredictable and unbearable to you too. When she stops getting mad, she will totally forget what she just said and be an angle again. If you have a date with her , you'd better be there on time. Flowers and sweet word can calm her down. If you want to say sorry , make it brief and straight forward. Do not drag your apologetic words into a long making it up events, it could lead you to another world war. She likes her man to dress nice and clean. She is good in details especially with money. Do not make she thinks that she is a clown or funny. In the beginning of knowing her, please try not to glance at other pretty woman so much. Early period of dating her, try not to hold her so much in public, it would not be a proper thing to do. She loves books, stage play and music and likes to criticize about them too. Criticism woman is her icon including big and small things in life starting from your hair, your dress , and the way you talk. If you are in love with her, be as almost perfect as your can.  
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When the first time I know you There is something in my heart That I can’t hardly tell out Since we've been together I found out that how much I love you Everyday misses you so much At night hope to dream of you There is a sickness that can’t cure Even a doctor only you can help Everyday hope you are at my side Talk to me share some happy talks And also to lend your shoulder to me Never though that miss you was so painful There is only a few words to describe My feeling now I love you so much and miss you! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What if   One question   With a thousand answers.      Whaf if I never see you   Would I regret it?   What if you were the one   But I let you go.      What if we never met   Would it be lost love?   What if the world ends tomorrow   Only for me to know I love you today.      But for the first time   I see clearly   That none of it matters   Because the only thing that matters   Is you.      For the first time   I can throw all the what if away   I can sleep at night   Without ever wondering what if.      Because for the first time   I realise   That no matter what happens   You will always remain special to me   And I will always hold you   Dear and close to my heart.        * This poem is specially dedicated to my one and only Sayang that really mean alot to me.     Sayang, I love you so much...Just couldn't live without you!   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This is my first article of all...nothing much to say..I'm about to go out for lunch.   Kinda bored today coz nobody's around, bosses also not around (yahoo!) hehehe...   But still have tons of works to do anyway.. better get going now..  
     
    
</post>


<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       rapper:   yo man you know what(what?)   here me and sarah go again   she saw me talking to Shorty yhe other day   Shorty from the block   Yeah you remember Shorty   That wasn't nothing man   we were just having a conversation   about the studio   No Sarah had to take it somewhere else   I mean she now I'm down for her forever   I don't know why she even go there   I guess I'm staying with you tonight dog      Sarah:   (Heeey)(Hoooooooow)   I ain't gonna take this no more no!( no babyyy)   chorus:   Bounce baby out the door   I ain't gonna take this no more   Bounce baby out the door   get up and move,don't make me act a fool(2x)      Says you're going with your boys today   and don't worry cause I'll be home late   but I know you're cheating out that creeping   you been freaking babe   so let me tell you how it is gonna be yeah   you can run your game but not on me boy   so who the hell r you trying to get   you know this is what I get I   I called your pager and your 2way boy but no response   start looking and I found you in some other womans arms   Don't try to front boy cause I saw you there with my own eyes   just get your stuff boy cause    I'm tyred of hearing all your lies      chorus (2x)      Baby boy I know you'll never find,   no stuff as good as mine   she can't work you like I did   you can look but you kow I got the good shit   I know that you hating it   that you better stayed with the one you were with   You made your bed and now you have to sleep in it baby   I called your pager and your 2way boy but no response   start looking and I found you in some other womans arms   Don't try to front boy cause I saw you there with my own eyes   just get your stuff boy cause    I'm tyred of hearing all your lies      chorus (2x)   rapper:   so waith a minute sarah give me a chance to explain   I was just talking to Shorty don't even know her name   Ain't nothing from the one who's trying to take your place   aint one damn baby that can fill your space   no need to find a nikkel got a diamond home   cause i love in every night the freaky way we role   I ain't trying to get gone,aint trying to play the role   I rather stay and party and dream thats all      chorus(2x)   so bounce (what? you know I aint try to front you girl)   just bounce baby bounce(why we got to go there)   don't make ma act a fool   just bounce (you know I aint trying to front you girl)   just bounce baby bounce ( sarah take it)   JUST BOUNCE  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I'm not a perfect person   As many things I wish I didn't do   But I continue learning   I never meant to do those things to you   And so I have to say before I go   That I just want you to know      I've found a reason for me   To change who I used to be   A reason to start over new   and the reason is you      I'm sorry that I hurt you   It's something I must live with everyday   And all the pain I put you through   I wish that I could take it all away   And be the one who catches all your tears   Thats why i need you to hear       I've found a reason for me   To change who I used to be   A reason to start over new   and the reason is You [x4]      I'm not a perfect person   I never meant to do those things to you   And so I have to say before I go   That I just want you to know   I've found a reason for me   To change who I used to be   A reason to start over new   and the reason is you      I've found a reason to show   A side of me you didn't know   A reason for all that I do   And the reason is you     * Just love this song so much!!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       People always talk about (ey oh ey oh ey oh)   All the things their all about (ey oh ey oh ey oh)   Write it on a piece of paper,   Got a feeling i'll see you later.      There's something bout this,   Lets keep it moving,   And if its good lets just get something cooking.   Coz i really wanna rock with you,   I'm feeling some connection to the things you do.(you do, you do).      [Chorus:]   I dont know what it is,   That makes me feel like this,   I dont know who you are,   But you must be some kind of superstar,   Coz you got all eyes on you no matter where you are,(you just make me wanna play)      Baby take a look around (ey oh ey oh ey oh)   Everybody's getting down (ey oh ey oh ey oh)   Deal with all the problems later,   Bad boys on their best behaviour.      There's something bout you,   Lets keep it moving,   And if it's good lets just get something cooking,   Coz i really wanna rock with you,   I'm feeling some connection to the things you do,(you do, you do).      I don't know what it is,   That makes me feel like this,   I don't know who you are,   But you must be some kind of superstar,   Coz you got all eyes on you no matter where you are,(you just make me wanna play).      I like the way your movin' (ey oh ey oh ey oh)   I just get into the groove and then (you just make me wanna play),   If you just put pen to paper (ey oh ey oh ey oh)   Got that feeling i'll see you later.      Make your move,    can we get a little closer,   You rock it just like you're supposed to,   Hey boy i ain't got nothing more to say,   Coz you just make me wanna play,   i don't know what it is,   That makes me feel like this,    i don't know,   Gotta be, gotta be a superstar,   All eyes on you.      [Chorus x2]  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       [Verse 1:]   What ya hear this time   Go on and speak ya mind   I know somebody's lying   It's always somethin   Her auntie told your cousin   Then all your homies jumped in   And now the whole hoods buzzin   He said, she said   Don't let it get in ya head   Baby don't say   Something that you will regret   I'm on your team   It's us against them you'll see   Hey, we ain't gon stop   They just want what we got      [Chorus:]   The more they talk about our love   The more they make it obvious   The more they seem so envious   How can they talk about our love   When they don't know one thing about   Instead they just runnin they mouth   So all we do is tune them out      [Verse 2:]   I swear they got some nerve   Spreadin what they heard   I cant give them no run   I can't be concerned with all that talk   I won't be involved   That's my word   See I'm not the one   They got me confused   They got me messed up   Don't you think    I've had enough   When it comes to what we do   All that matters is us two   Don't pay them no mind   We just gon show and prove      [Chorus]   The more they talk about our love   The more they make it obvious   The more they seem so envious   How can they talk about our love   When they don't know one thing about   Instead they just runnin they mouth   So all we do is tune them out      [Kanye West:]   Heres a couple of things I can't honor man   How you listen to a girl who still wanna man   Tell me the truth is that a man or Juwanna Man   I'm wonderin why she red to go like Wanda Van   When we met you was a V like Madonna man   Now you went field runnin plays like Donovan   McNabb before you get in a cab   I trade in my cab   Just to take you back to last summer man   You don't remember when you was my sweetest   You don't remember I called you Reeces Pieces   Cause it's no wrong way to do you know what   She turned around giggle said you so nuts   But nowadays we actin way too grown up   But how ya ex girl get that new numba   The rumors was so numerous   For sticking by me I had to give you two thumbs up   And that's why      [Chorus:]   The more they talk about our love   The more they make it obvious   The more they seem so envious   How can they talk about our love   When they don't know one thing about   Instead they just runnin they mouth   So all we do is tune them out      The more they talk about our love   The more they make it obvious   The more they seem so envious   How can they talk about our love   When they don't know one thing about   Instead they just runnin they mouth   So all we do is tune them out  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       no sleep    no sleep untill I am done with finding the answer    wont stop    wont stop before I find a cure for this cancer    sometimes    I feel I going down and so disconnected    somehow    I know that I am haunted to be wanted       I been watching    I been waiting    in the shadows    all my time    I been searching    I been living    for tomorrows    all my life       in the shadows    in the shadows       they say    that i must learn to kill    before i can feel safe    but I    I rather kill myself    then turn into there slave    sometimes    I feel that I should go and play with the thunder    somehow    I just don't wanne stay and wait for a wonder    I been watching    I been waiting    in the shadows    all my time    I been searching    I been living    for tomorrows    all my life       lately    I been walking walking in circels, watching waiting for something    feel me touch me feel me, come take me higher       I been watching    I been waiting    in the shadows all my time    I been searching    I been living    for tomorrows    all my life       I been watching    I been waiting    I been searching    I been living    for tomorrows       in the shadows    in the shadows    I been waiting       * Love this song!!!its my sayang's fav song too!:-)   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I've been waiting all day for ya babe    So wont cha come and sit and talk to me   Tell me how we are gonna be together always   Hope you know when it's late at night   I Hold on to my pillow tight   And think of how you promised me forever   (I never thought that any one)   Could make me feel this way   Now that your here all I want    Is just a chance to say   [Chorus]   Get Out, (Leave) Right Now,    It's the end of you and me   It's too late (now) and I can't wait   For you to be gone    Cuz I know about her and    I wonder how I brought all the lies   You said that you would treat me right    but you were just a waste of time   Tell why your looking so confused   When im the one who didn't know that truth   How could you ever be so cold   To go behind my back and call my friend   Boy you must have gone and bumped your head   Because you left her number on your phone   (So now that through all that is said and done)   Maybe I'm the one to blame   (to think that you could be the one)   Well it didn't work out that way I wanted you right here with me but    I have no choice you've got to leave   Because my heart is breakin   With every word im say   I gave up on everything I had    On something that just wouldnt last    But I refuse to cry   No tears will fall from these   Eyeeee eyeee eyeeesss    [Chorus X2]       *my favourite song currently...   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       hello there,    the angel from my nightmares    the shadow at the backround of the mourge.   the unsuspecting victim    of darkness in the valley,    we can live like Jack and sally    if we want to.    where you can always find me.    we'll have halloween on christmas.    and in the night we'll wish this never ends,    wish this never ends...       (miss u, miss u)       where r u?    and im so sorry    i can not sleep   i can not dream tonight    i need somebody and always    this sick strange darkness    comes creeping on    so haunting everytime.       and as i stared i counted    the webs from all the spiders,    catching thongs and eating their insides.   like indicession to call u    and here your voice of treason    will u come home and stop this pain tonight,    stop this pain tonight...       (miss u, miss u)       dont waste ur time on me    ur already the voice inside my head (miss u, miss u) repeat x4      (miss u, miss u)    repeat x7         * This song specially dedicated to My Beloved Sayang...I miss u all the time sayang..miss all the moments that we shared together, miss you so much, miss you day and night, miss you always...   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       You're with me   Til the bitter end   What we had transcends    This experience    Too painful to    Talk about    So I'll hold it in    Til my heart can mend    And be brave enough to love again       A place in time    Still belongs to us    Stays preserved in my mind    In the memories there is solace       Never too far away I won't let time erase    One bit of yesterday    Cause I have learned that    Nobody can take your place    Though we can never be    I'll keep you close to me    When I remember       Glittering lights    Incandescent eyes    Still preserved    In my mind In the memories    I'll find solace       Never too far away    I won't let time erase    One bit of yesterday    And I have learned that    Nobody can take your place    Though we can never be   I'll keep you close to me    And I'll remember       A place in time    Still belongs to us    Stays preserved in my mind    In the memories there is solace       Never too far away    I won't let time erase    One bit of yesterday    Cause I have learned that    Nobody can take your place    And though we can never be    I'll always think of you and me    Always remember       Love       You're never too far     
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Sorry, I never told you,   all I wanted to say.    Now it'stoo late to hold you.    'Cause you'veflown away, so far away.      Never, Had I imagined,    yeah,living without your smile.    Feelin' and knowing you hear me.       It keeps me alive.Alive!   And I know you're shining down on me from Heaven,   like so many friends    we've lost along the way,    and I know eventually we'll be together,    Together babe,    One sweet day.    One sweet day.      Picture a little scene from Heaven.   Darling, I never showed you,    Assumed you'dalways be there,    Always be there,    I, I tookyour presence for granted,    but I always cared,I always cared,    And I miss the love we shared.      And I know you're shining down on me from Heaven,   like so many friends we've lost along the way,   and I know eventually we'll be together,    Together,   One Sweet day.      Although, the sun will never shine the same,    I'll always look to a brighter day.   Yeah, yeah, Lord, I know,    when I lay me down to sleep,   you'll always listen, as I pray!      And I know you're shining down on me from Heaven,    like so many friends we've lost along the way,    And I know eventually we will be together,    together,   One Sweet Day,    One Sweet Day,    One Sweet Day,    One Sweet Day!      And I know you're shining down on me from Heaven,    like so many friends we've lost along the way,    and I, I know, I know we'll be together.   One Sweet Day,    Ooh, Sorry,    I Never told you,    all I wanted to say.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       They can say anything they want to say    Try to bring me down   But I will not allow    Anyone to succeed    Hanging clouds over me       And they can try hard to make me feel    That I don't matter at all    But I refuse to falter    In what I believe    Or lose faith in my dreams       CHORUS:    'Cause there's a light in me    That shines brightly    They can try    But they can't take that away from me    From me       They can do anything they want to you    lf you let them in    But they won't ever win    If you cling to your pride    And just push them aside    See I have learned there's an inner peace I own    Something in my soul    That they cannot possess    So I won't be afraid    And darkness will fade       'Cause there's a light in me    That shines brightly    They can try    But they can't take that away from me       No    They can't take this    Precious love l'll always have inside me    Certainly the Lord will guide me    Where I need to go       They can say anything they want to say    Try to break me down    But 1 won't face the ground    I will rise steadily    Sailing out of their reach       Oh Lord    They do try hard to make me feel    That I don't matter at all    But I refuse to falter    In what I believe    Or lose faith in my dreams    'Cause there's a light in me that shines brightly    They can try    But they can't take that away from me    From me       * This song is one of my Favourite which really motivates me alot.   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       (Mariah)   I would give up everything    Before I'd separate myself from you    After so much suffering    I've finally found a LOVE that's true    I was all by myself for the longest time    So cold inside    And the hurt from the heart it would not subside    I felt like dying    Until you saved my life       (Chorus - Mariah, 98 Degrees and Joe)    Thank God I found you    I was lost without you    My every wish and every dream    Somehow became reality    When you brought the sunlight    Completed my whole life    I'm overwhelmed with gratitude    Cause baby I'm so thankful I found you       (Joe)    I would give you everything    There's nothing in this world I wouldn't do    To ensure your happiness    I'll cherish every part of you    Because without you beside me    I can't survive    I don't wanna try    If you're keeping me warm each and every night    I'll be all right    Cause I need you in my life       (Chorus - Mariah, 98 Degrees and Joe)    Thank God I found you    I was lost without you    My every wish and every dream    Somehow became reality    When you brought the sunlight    Completed my whole life    I'm overwhelmed with gratitude    Cause baby    I'm so thankful I found you       -Bridge- (Mariah & Joe)    See I was so desolate    Before you came to me    Looking back I guess it shows   that we were destined to shine    After the rain to appreciate    THE GIFT OF what we have    And I'd go through it all over again   To be able to feel this way       (Chorus - Mariah, 98 Degrees and Joe)    Thank God I found you   I was lost without you    My every wish and every dream    Somehow became reality    When you brought the sunlight    Completed my whole life    I'm overwhelmed with gratitude    Cause baby I'm so thankful I found you   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       No I can't forget this evening    Or your face as you were leaving    But I guess that's just the way    The story goes       You always smile but in your eyes    Your sorrow shows    Yes it shows       No I can't forget tomorrow    When I think of all my sorrow   When I had you there    But then I let you go       And now it's only fair   That I should let you know    What you should know    I can't live    If living is without you    I can't live    I can't give anymore    I can't live    If living is without you    I can't give    I can't give anymore       Well I can't forget this evening    Or your face as you were leaving    But I guess that's just the way    The story goes    You always smile but in your eyes    Your sorrow shows    Yes it shows       I can't live    If living is without you    I can't live    I can't give any more    I can't live    If living is without you    I can't give    I can't give anymore  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       There's a hero   If look inside your heart   You Don't have to be afraid   Of what you are      There's an answer   If you reach into your soul   And the sorrow that you know   Will melt away      And then a hero comes along   With the strength to carry on   And you cast your fears aside   And you know you can survive   So When you feel like hope is gone   Look inside you and be strong   And you'll finally see the truth   That a hero lies in you      It's a long road   When you face the world alone   No one reaches out a hand    For you to hold   You can find love   If you search within yourself   And the emptiness you felt   Will disappear      And then a hero comes along   With the strength to carry on   And you cast your fears aside   And you know you can survive   So When you feel like hope is gone   Look inside you and be strong   And you'll finally see the truth   That a hero lies in you      Lord knows   Dreams are hard to follow   But Don't let anyone   Tear them away   Hold on   There will be tomorrow   In time You'll find the way      And the hero comes along    With the strength to carry on   And you cast your fears aside   And you know you can survive   So When You feel like hope is gone   Look inside you and be strong   And you'll finally see the truth   That a hero lies in you   That a hero lies in you.   Mmm That a hero lies in you  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Soft heavenly eyes gazed into me   Transcending space and time   And I was rendered still   There were no words for me to find at all   As I stood there beside myself   I could see you and no-one else      When I saw you   When I saw you   I could not breathe   I fell so deep   When I saw you   When I saw you   I'd never be   I'd never be the same      Only once in a lifetime love rushes in   Changing you with the tide   And dawn's ribbon of light   Bursts through the dark   Wakening you inside   And I thought it was all untrue   Until there, all at once, I knew      When I saw you   When I saw you   I could not breathe   I fell so deep   When I saw you   When I saw you   I'd never be   I'd never be the same      With no beginning   And without an end   You are the one for me   And it's evident   And your eyes told me so   Your eyes let me know      When I saw you   When I saw you   I could not breathe   I fell so deep   When I saw you   When I saw you   I'd never be   I'd never be the same  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Those days of love are gone   Our time is through   Still I burn on and on   All of my life   Only for you      From now   Until forever   And ever, my darling   Forever   You will always be the only one   You will always be the only one      As long as I shall live   I'll hold you dear   And I will reminisce   Of our love all through the years      From now   Until forever   And ever, my darling   Forever   You will always be the only one   You will always be the only one      If you should ever need me   Unfailingly, I will return to your arms   And unburden your heart   And if you should remember   That we belong together   Never be ashamed   Call my name   Tell me I'm the one you treasure      Forever   And ever, my darling   Forever   You will always be the only one   You will always be the only one   You will always be the only one   Forever   You will always be the only one   Forever   You will always be the only one   Forever   You will always be the only one   Forever   You will always be the only one   Forever   You will always be the only one  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Gypsy, sittin lookin pretty   A broken rose and laughin' eyes   You're a mystery   Always runnin' wild   Like a child without a home   You're always searchin'   Searchin for a feelin'   But it's easy come and easy go      OhI'm sorry but it's true   You're bringin' on the heartache   Takin all the best of me   Oh can't you see   You got the best of me   Whoah can't you see      You're bringin' on the heartbreak   Bringin' on the heartache   You're bringin' on the heartache   Bringin' on the heartache   Can't you see      OhYou're such a secret   Misty eyed and shady   Baby, how you hold the key   Oh, you're like a candl   eYour flame slowly fadin   'Burnin' out and burnin' m   eCan't you see   Just tryin' to say to you      You're bringin' on the heartache   Takin all the best of me   Oh can't you see   You got the best of me   Oh can't you see      You're bringin' on the heartbreak   Bringin' on the heartache   You're bringin' on the heartache   Bringin' on the heartache   Can't you see   Can't you see      NoNoNo      You got the best of me   Oh can't you see   You got the best of me   Oh can't you see      You're bringin on the heartbreak   Bringin' on the heartache   You're bringin on the heartbreak   You're bringin on the heartache  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Look into my eyes You will see, what you mean to me Search your heart, search your soul When you find me then, you'll search no more  Dont tell me its not worth trying for You cant tell me its not worth dying for You know its true, everything I do, I do it for you  Look into your heart, you will find There is nothing there to hide Take me as I am, take my life I would give it all, I would sacrifice  Dont tell me its not worth fighting for I cant help it, theres nothing i want more You know its true, everything I do, I do it for you  There is no love, like your love And no other, could give me more love Theres nowhere, unless you're there All the time, all the way  You cant tell me its not worth trying for Just cant help it, theres nothing in the world i want more I would fight for you, yeah I'd lie for you Walk the wire for you, yeah I'd die for you  You know its true Everything I do, I do it for you 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Have you ever loved somebody so much   It makes you cry   Have you ever needed something so bad   You can't sleep at night   Have you ever tried to find the words   But they don't come out right   Have you ever, have you ever      Have you ever been in love   Been in love so bad   You'd do anything to make them understand   Have you ever had someone steal your heart away    You'd give anything up to make them feel the same   Have you ever searched for words to get you in their heart   But you don't know what to say   And you don't know where to start       Have you ever loved somebody so much   It makes you cry    Have you ever needed something so bad   You can't sleep at night    Have you ever tried to find the words   But they don't come out right       Have you ever, have you ever   Have you ever found the one    You've dreamed of all your life    You'd do just about anything to look into their eyes    Have you finally found the one you've given your heart to   Only to find that one won't give their heart to you    Have you ever closed your eyes and   Dreamed that they were there   And all you can do is wait for that day when they will care      Have you ever loved somebody so much   It makes you cry   Have you ever loved somebody so much   It makes you cry Have you ever needed something so bad   You can't sleep at night   Have you ever tried to find the words   But they don't come out right   Have you ever, have you ever      What do I gotta do to get you in my arms baby   What do I gotta say to get to your heart   To make you understand how I need you next to me    Gotta get you in my world    'Cuz baby I can't sleep   ( repeat chorus twice )    Have you ever?  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>