<Blog>

<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The day had finally arrived, August 19th when the St. Mary's babes would be back on campus.  I was so happy and excited when I wokeup this morning, saying "We recruited them and they came.  They said "Sure why not?  We'll come to Notre Dame, IN!"  And so it came to be St. Mary's babes, recruiting at its finest!   I got to see them on my way to Ivy Tech to get my books at the bookstore.  Two of them were standing on the pillar.  I didn't think they would be standing.  They ususally sit on them and wave to the incoming cars.   There was two brunettes and I think the other was a blonde.  I liked one of the brunettes on the left side, I didn't look too much since she probably wasn't interested.   I got my account for Financial Aide setup at Ivy Tech.  I found my Algebra book after looking for like 10 minutes, to my disarray.  I bought a legal pad so I can practice the Math problems on there and during tutoring.  I also bought a Graphing Calculator which kicks major ass over the regular scientific calculator, I can't wait to start using it.  It will take awhile to master but it should be fun in the end.  I was worried I wouldn't have enough Financial Aide money in the end but it went through.  Then I was still worrying about afterwards when in the Cybercafe and I went back to the Financial Aide to ask them about it.  They said I had $400 and I had only used $248 so I'm glad because I didn't want to owe a bunch of money for the calculator.   I realized when I was waiting for the bus that I would have to use two dimes and a nickel to pay the fare since they are being stupid during this Customer Appreciation week which is a slap in the face for people like me who use a Handicard since you have to pay more each way than you would with the 35 cents fare, it adds up to 50 cents and no transfer so its screwed up, doesn't help me at all.  Only helps the people who pay the regular fare.   Finally the ride on the #5 bus and the moment of great anticipation has arrived.  Would the girls wave when we went by in the bus or would it turn into a bad memory like it did in 2001?  Sure enough, the worst did come true.  None of them waved, they were too busy talking with each other, this brunette just stares at us and I think I frowned at her, she frowns back.  It was to show her that they should have waved and I was not happy.  Waited for this moment for months, only to be let down in the end, its really depressing.  I'm still glad I got my book though and my Graphing Calculator, its always fun going there, I enjoy it since I get the stuff for free with Financial Aide.   The weather is so pleasant today too, in the 70's and somewhat sunny, absolutetly great outside and I like it a lot.   The other good thing that happened today was the Machine Shop at Ivy Tech called me and this guy wants me to come in for Work Study so I think I will get a job, finally!  I'm so excited, even if its not a computer or clerical job like I wanted to do for experience, I will finally have some money that the bastard can't take away from me.  And also I hope then I get a Tax Refund next year, if I do, I'll be even more happy, maybe 2004 will turn out to be good, we'll have to wait and see, only time will tell.   4 is the number of Aquarius so maybe it will help me in the end, I hope it won't just be good luck for David and not me.  He has enough good luck and I'm the one who needs it more than he does.  He should have to suffer with bad luck for awhile and then he'll see what I am going through, he never has to though or not for long except for that surgery.  Which is all done and he has not any pain.  
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I went to apply at St. Joseph's High School for a Maintenance position.  I stopped at the Grotto at Notre Dame first to light a candle and say a prayer.  I rode my bike there and the sidewalk was so bumpy, I forgot since I hadn't gone on that part for awhile.  I saw some cute girls by the Cross Country team, in shorts and cute as can be :)  I went inside and went to the Main Office to apply.  It was fun being back inside, missed my old high school and saw a few more cute girls along the way :)  I filled out the application and turned it in to the lady at the desk, asked her if they would be calling people, she said they would go through them and then decide who to call, didn't sound too hopeful but at least I gave it a shot unlike last year where I didn't.  I then took a walk around the school, saw the 2nd floor and went into the Arts wing too.  It was fun and I saw my old English teacher, Mrs. MacWorter who I liked having.  We talked some, she is real friendly and I enjoyed catching up on what was going on with each other since we saw each other last, years ago.   I left after that and headed back through Notre Dame and decided at the spur of the moment to stop at the library to use the Internet there, just to spend time away from home, despite having it in my bedroom, I get so tired of being home so much during this break between school.  I typed so fast that people seem to be annoyed by it when writing back to my e-pals in the e-mail but too bad, that's their problem, I'm not stopping nor am I ever.  I headed back home after being there for like 20 minutes or so.  I see then that the girl I wrote on Saturday too, gets all bitchy about me following her and saying I stalked her but I did not, its not what I did, it was to talk to her but she didn't wait, decides to get in her car instead so she's screwed up, stupid snob!  I get tired of them being like that to me.  So I was so depressed about that and cried later on about it.  It was not good and it messed up most of my day after that.  I was upset again in the evening and it was rather disturbing to think about her.  But I later recovered after chatting with Kasey and surfing the web to read different things so I was feeling better in the end. 
    
</post>


</Blog>