<Blog>

<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Currently working on a Xanga.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I’m finally getting a new Xbox today. My old Xbox was working for awhile, but after I moved it upstairs to my room is started acting up. The Xbox would say there was an error and it couldn’t read the disk, and to make sure it was an Xbox disk, DVD, or audio CD, and to check to see if the disk was damaged. It was doing that to brand new games never played before. My dad took it back to the power zone and the people said they didn’t have any consoles in stock. I waited for 2 weeks with no games then yesterday I got a call saying that the consoles were in. Today around 5 I should have a new Xbox with Star Wars, Tetris worlds, Mechwarrior, and the GTA Double pack. I’m looking forward to fragging communist on Freedom Fighters and sneaking around on Splinter Cell.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've thought about it and come to the final conclusion that many of you reading this might not believe my last post. The reason for this is simple; you are all jealous and uncool. Meg talked to me and you can't stand it. If you’re still unsure about my claims read this and then go and cry, because you still don't seem to understand the fact that Meg talked to me and not you. Ha ha ha   DJHmxracer: I must say Meg DJHmxracer: You are even more my hero now than before   Meg s a y s this: ha-ha, why is that?   DJHmxracer: You take rad pictures and DJHmxracer: ....DJHmxracer: you play tennis.   Meg s a y s this: ha-ha you think so?   DJHmxracer:-D   Meg s a y s this: hahaha Meg s a y s this: thanks man Meg s a y s this: you're so cool   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      She actually talked to me!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Wow!! Meg's my hero 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      New screename for aim and new pictures. HHSmxracer 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Sometimes In a business venture you might not succeed. If you don't succeed you have to keep trying. Either that or go and become and entrepreneur and make millions. As Bender would say:   Yeah, well, I'm going to go build my own theme park with blackjack and hookers.  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Do people start a diary online to put down they're thoughts or so other people can read them, and they can feel cool? I don't know anymore. Anyway I got home late Sunday and In the back of my head I told myself to write in here, but at the same time I didn't want to go downstairs. Sunday I ended up going to Giebelstat and Wurzburg with my parents and brother. After checking out the PX’s (I bought season one of Futurama) we went to dinner with a friend of my dads from Italy. He and his wife are from South Carolina so we had baked beans, cooked out, and had Ice tea. I'm surprised to say but I actually liked the tea. I usually hate tea living in Alabama for 4 years I think Iced tea is disgusting but I guess I drink it because it reminds me a little of Alabama. Later on back at St. Leon I feel asleep watching Futurama. I woke up and sat around the house till about 3 then I went downstairs and ate some Oreos and milk. I was pretty happy I still have 2 disks of Futurama, a packet of Oreo's, and a carton of milk. Things were looking good. I finished out the day watching the DVD's and cleaning my room of boxes. Tuesday went pretty much the same. Wednesday, which I think is today, I ate some Ramen, watched some Futurama with my brother, and emptied my room of more boxes. Tomorrow looks like the same thing. Hopefully I can get frozen and become someone close to Fry or maybe even become a robot like Bender. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       All right now lets just find…Where is everybody?   Woa… Where are we? What is this place?   Freeze!! Drop your weapons!!   Uh oh   I said Freeze!! Dirt bag!!   Bleep bloo beep crash   Oww! Aww come on!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I went with my dad today to the Bank, airfield, and the commissary.  The bank finally got in the covers for checkbooks so my dad had to have one.  (I decided to get a blue one). At the commissary I saw Monique and her friend Sarah; I talked to them a little, picked up some Ramen and Code Red not much else. We left went back home and then went over to our neighbors for a cookout. At the cookout Pedro's wife reminded me to come by to help Pedro with his English.( When we first moved to St. Leon Pedro’s wife told me that if I helped Pedro with his English they'd both be willing to help me with my Spanish) I think that’s a pretty neat deal. I’m hoping before I leave Germany to be fluent in Spanish and be close to fluent in German. I don’t really know what else to put in here for now so I’m going to post this and go watch Red vs. Blue. Codeword: Dirt bag!! 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Currently In progress.   
     
    
</post>


</Blog>